<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:bnmedia="https://news.bitcoin.com/">

<channel>
	<title>Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/</link>
	<description>Daily Bitcoin News</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 02:02:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>BRICS Bank Official Discusses Common Currency as Reports of Gold-Backed BRICS Currency Gain Attention</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/brics-bank-official-discusses-common-currency-as-reports-of-gold-backed-brics-currency-gain-attention/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Kevin Helms]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 02:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BRICS Bank]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BRICS common currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BRICS currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BRICS shared currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[China]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chinese Yuan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[de-dollarization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dollar dominance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Leslie Maasdorp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[local currencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[national currencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[New Development Bank]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=596880&#038;preview=true&#038;preview_id=596880</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/brics-currency-gold-backed-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="BRICS Bank Official Discusses Common Currency as Reports of Gold-Backed BRICS Currency Gain Attention" decoding="async" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/brics-currency-gold-backed-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/brics-currency-gold-backed-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/brics-currency-gold-backed-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/brics-currency-gold-backed-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/brics-currency-gold-backed-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/brics-currency-gold-backed-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/brics-currency-gold-backed.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />The BRICS Bank’s vice president and chief financial officer has shed light on the economic bloc&#8217;s aspiration to develop a common BRICS currency. His remarks followed recent reports suggesting that Russia has confirmed the BRICS’ plan to introduce a gold-backed common currency, with an official announcement expected to be made during the forthcoming BRICS leaders&#8217; [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/brics-currency-gold-backed-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="BRICS Bank Official Discusses Common Currency as Reports of Gold-Backed BRICS Currency Gain Attention" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/brics-currency-gold-backed-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/brics-currency-gold-backed-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/brics-currency-gold-backed-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/brics-currency-gold-backed-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/brics-currency-gold-backed-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/brics-currency-gold-backed-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/brics-currency-gold-backed.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>The BRICS Bank’s vice president and chief financial officer has shed light on the economic bloc&#8217;s aspiration to develop a common BRICS currency. His remarks followed recent reports suggesting that Russia has confirmed the BRICS’ plan to introduce a gold-backed common currency, with an official announcement expected to be made during the forthcoming BRICS leaders&#8217; summit.</strong></p>
<h2>&#8216;Gold-Backed BRICS Currency&#8217; Gains Attention</h2>
<p>The subject of a common BRICS currency has gained significant attention as the BRICS leaders&#8217; summit approaches and an increasing number of countries pursue de-dollarization. The BRICS comprises Brazil, Russia, India, China, and South Africa. Their leaders&#8217; summit will take place in South Africa from Aug. 22 to 24.</p>
<p>On Tuesday, RT <a href="https://twitter.com/RT_com/status/1676720110353137664">reported</a> that the BRICS is set to introduce a new trading currency backed by gold which will be discussed at the August leaders&#8217; summit. The news outlet cited a tweet by the Russian Embassy in Kenya made on Monday, stating: &#8220;The BRICS countries are planning to introduce a new trading currency, which will be backed by gold. More and more counties recently express desire to join BRICS.&#8221;</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">The BRICS countries are planning to introduce a new trading currency, which will be backed by gold.<br />More and more counties recently express desire to join BRICS.<a href="https://t.co/lMKTd4FlnT">https://t.co/lMKTd4FlnT</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Russian Embassy in Kenya/Посольство России в Кении (@russembkenya) <a href="https://twitter.com/russembkenya/status/1675727818888716288?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 3, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>RT&#8217;s coverage has sparked a wave of headlines suggesting that Russia has made an announcement regarding the establishment of a gold-backed common currency for the BRICS nations. However, the tweet by the Russian Embassy in Kenya links to an article published on April 24 discussing the BRICS potentially backing its common currency with gold. There is no indication of any new information about a common BRICS currency.</p>
<h2>BRICS Bank’s Official Says Common Currency Is a Medium to Long-Term Ambition</h2>
<p>Leslie Maasdorp, vice president and chief financial officer of the New Development Bank, also known as the BRICS Bank, shared some information about the economic bloc’s common currency plan in an interview with Bloomberg on Wednesday. The New Development Bank was established by the BRICS nations to mobilize resources for infrastructure and sustainable development projects in emerging markets and developing countries.</p>
<p>He explained that while BRICS members are pushing for the use of national currencies, shifting away from the U.S. dollar, the BRICS does not have an immediate plan to create a common currency to challenge the dominance of the USD. Noting that the BRICS Bank has the U.S. dollar as its anchor currency, he described:</p>
<blockquote><p>The development of anything alternative is indeed a medium to long-term ambition.</p></blockquote>

<p>Some have suggested that the <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/chinese-yuan-to-replace-us-dollar-as-worlds-reserve-currency-says-russian-banker/">Chinese yuan</a> could replace the U.S. dollar as the world’s dominant currency. While acknowledging that the yuan has been gaining traction as a trading currency, Maasdorp said that it is &#8220;a very long way from becoming a reserve currency.”</p>
<p>The BRICS Bank&#8217;s vice president concluded: “It&#8217;s going to take a very long time for currency movements to take shape so any discussion of alternate currencies is indeed a much more medium and longer-term aspiration.”</p>
<p>Maasdorp insisted, “No one is suggesting right now that BRICS will form an alternate currency,” emphasizing:</p>
<blockquote><p>All we are suggesting is that we need to deepen the use of local currencies of our member countries and over time that is going to strengthen our ability to immunize or insulate our economies from the devaluation of our currencies if we borrow in dollars, for example. But, there is no suggestion right now to create a BRICS currency in that sense.</p></blockquote>
<p>The remarks made by the BRICS Bank&#8217;s chief financial officer align with the statements made by India&#8217;s External Affairs Minister S. Jaishankar, who reportedly said earlier this week that <a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/world-news/jaishankar-makes-big-comment-on-brics-currency-plans-amid-de-dollarisation-push-watch-101688387595429.html">there are no plans</a> for a new BRICS currency. Instead, the focus remains on enhancing the respective national currencies within the BRICS framework.</p>
<p><em><strong>Do you think the BRICS will introduce a common currency soon? Let us know in the comments section below.</strong></em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/brics-currency-gold-backed-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[The #BRICS Bank’s vice president and chief financial officer has shed light on the bloc's aspirations to develop a common BRICS #currency. #dedollarization]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA["The #BRICS countries are planning to introduce a new trading currency, which will be backed by gold," said the Russian embassy. #dedollarization]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Renowned Investor Jim Rogers Warns &#8216;US Is Going to Suffer&#8217; as Dollar&#8217;s Value Erodes Further</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/renowned-investor-jim-rogers-warns-us-is-going-to-suffer-as-dollars-value-erodes-further/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Kevin Helms]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 00:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jim rogers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jim Rogers crisis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jim Rogers Fed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jim Rogers inflation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=596849&#038;preview=true&#038;preview_id=596849</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/jim-rogers-inflation-debt-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Renowned Investor Jim Rogers Says Inflation, Debt Problems Will Get Worse — &#039;US Is Going to Suffer&#039; as Dollar Declines Further" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/jim-rogers-inflation-debt-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/jim-rogers-inflation-debt-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/jim-rogers-inflation-debt-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/jim-rogers-inflation-debt-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/jim-rogers-inflation-debt-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/jim-rogers-inflation-debt-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/jim-rogers-inflation-debt.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />Veteran investor Jim Rogers, who co-founded the Quantum Fund with billionaire investor George Soros, has warned that &#8220;the worst is yet to come” for the U.S. economy. &#8220;The U.S. is going to suffer&#8221; as the value of the dollar erodes further, he predicted, emphasizing that inflation and the debt problems are going to get worse. [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/jim-rogers-inflation-debt-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Renowned Investor Jim Rogers Says Inflation, Debt Problems Will Get Worse — &#039;US Is Going to Suffer&#039; as Dollar Declines Further" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/jim-rogers-inflation-debt-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/jim-rogers-inflation-debt-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/jim-rogers-inflation-debt-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/jim-rogers-inflation-debt-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/jim-rogers-inflation-debt-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/jim-rogers-inflation-debt-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/jim-rogers-inflation-debt.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>Veteran investor Jim Rogers, who co-founded the Quantum Fund with billionaire investor George Soros, has warned that &#8220;the worst is yet to come” for the U.S. economy. &#8220;The U.S. is going to suffer&#8221; as the value of the dollar erodes further, he predicted, emphasizing that inflation and the debt problems are going to get worse. </strong></p>
<h2>Jim Rogers Says &#8216;the Worst Is yet to Come&#8217;</h2>
<p>Veteran investor Jim Rogers issued several warnings about the U.S. economy on Sputnik&#8217;s New Rules podcast, published last week. Rogers is George Soros’ former business partner who co-founded the Quantum Fund and Soros Fund Management.</p>
<p>&#8220;The worst is yet to come,” the renowned investor warned. “It always comes later after normal fluctuations and corrections.” Rogers explained: &#8220;We have printed a lot of money, we have borrowed and spent a lot of money, which is wonderful for the short term, but eventually we have to pay the price.&#8221; He cautioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>Inflation is going to get worse. The debt problems are going to get worse, and the U.S. is going to suffer.</p></blockquote>
<p>Drawing a comparison between the present circumstances and the 1980s, a period marked by significant inflation, he stressed, “The inflation now is worse,&#8221; noting that the U.S. is now the “largest debtor nation in the history of the world.”</p>
<p>While stating that “things are okay at the moment,” Rogers noted that it won’t last forever. “Somebody has got to pay this debt. Somebody has to print more money. Somebody has to borrow more money. And when you borrow huge amounts of money, interest rates will go higher and higher, inflation will go higher because so much money has been printed,” he detailed, emphasizing:</p>
<blockquote><p>The value of the U.S. dollar will lose more and more value as [the U.S.] prints more. It always happens this way.</p></blockquote>
<p>Using the British Empire as an example, Rogers highlighted that during the 1920s, Britain held the position as the wealthiest and most influential nation globally, surpassing all others. However, five decades later, the country found itself in a dire financial state, to the extent that the International Monetary Fund (IMF) had to intervene.</p>
<p>&#8220;That will happen to the U.S.,&#8221; Rogers predicted, clarifying that “It won&#8217;t happen this year, but it will happen.&#8221;</p>
<p>Last month, U.S. Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/us-treasury-secretary-defends-dollar-dominance-as-emerging-markets-push-to-de-dollarize/">defended</a> the dominance of the U.S. dollar, arguing that the USD is used widely in trade because the U.S. has &#8220;deep, liquid, open capital markets, rule of law, and long and deep financial instruments.&#8221; However, she acknowledged in April that over time, the use of financial sanctions “could undermine the hegemony of the dollar.” She also said earlier this month that the ongoing trend of countries seeking to establish an alternative reserve currency to rival the U.S. dollar “is something that we simply have to expect.” Nonetheless, she emphasized that no country is able to replicate the USD, including China.</p>
<p>While concurring with Yellen, Rogers pointed out that the treasury secretary left out the fact that the U.S. is &#8220;the largest debtor in history and the debt is skyrocketing and the money printing is skyrocketing.&#8221;</p>
<p>He cautioned: “Eventually we have to pay the price. Every country in history has had to pay the price. Yes, she will print huge amounts of money. She will borrow and spend huge amounts of money, and they will think they are okay for a while, just as they have for other countries in the past. But, unless something has changed in world history and in world economics, this will not go on forever.&#8221;</p>

<p>Commenting on U.S. dollar alternatives, the famous investor said, &#8220;I don&#8217;t see anything on the horizon yet,&#8221; adding:</p>
<blockquote><p>That may cause a big problem if and when things really go wrong with the U.S. and with the U.S. dollar, the world will have a serious financial crisis for a while anyway, unless we can bond something else.</p></blockquote>
<p>&#8220;It is extremely important, especially when a crisis comes, that you have your money in a place that you yourself understand a lot about,&#8221; he concluded.</p>
<p>Rogers has repeatedly warned about the <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/renowned-investor-jim-rogers-expects-worst-bear-market-in-his-lifetime-says-you-should-be-extremely-worried/">worst bear market in his lifetime</a>, stating that investors should be worried. He said in May that the U.S. dollar&#8217;s time is <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/renowned-investor-jim-rogers-warns-us-dollars-time-coming-to-an-end-as-countries-seek-alternatives/">coming to an end</a> as a growing number of nations worldwide seek to de-dollarize.</p>
<p>Others have similarly sounded the alarm about inflation, the debt crisis, and the demise of the U.S. dollar, including economist Peter Schiff and Rich Dad Poor Dad author <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/rich-dad-poor-dad-author-robert-kiyosaki-says-america-is-bankrupt-amid-us-debt-crisis/">Robert Kiyosaki</a>. Schiff said in June that the U.S. dollar decline will be &#8220;<a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/economist-peter-schiff-us-dollar-decline-will-be-far-greater-than-yellen-warns-fed-chair-powell-clearly-worried-about-financial-crisis/">far greater</a>&#8221; than what Yellen described, noting that Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell is &#8220;clearly worried&#8221; about a financial crisis. He also warned of a U.S. dollar crisis, predicting that national debt will &#8220;<a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/economist-peter-schiff-warns-of-us-dollar-crisis-and-catastrophic-end-national-debt-will-spiral-out-of-control/">spiral out of control</a>.&#8221;</p>
<p><em><strong>Do you agree with Jim Rogers? Let us know in the comments section below.</strong></em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/jim-rogers-inflation-debt-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[#JimRogers has warned that "the worst is yet to come” for the U.S. economy, emphasizing that #inflation and the debt problems will get worse. #crisis]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA[The #dollar will lose more and more value as the U.S. prints more, said the renowned investor. "It always happens this way." #inflation #debtcrisis]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Democratic Presidential Candidate Robert Kennedy Jr Holds Up to $250,000 in Bitcoin, Records Show</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/democratic-presidential-candidate-robert-kennedy-jr-holds-up-to-250000-in-bitcoin-records-show/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jamie Redman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 22:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[anti-vaxxer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin 2023 conference]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CNBC report]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Democratic candidate]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dennis Kucinich]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethical considerations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[financial records]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment Advice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Joe Biden]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kennedy Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kennedy BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mainstream media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[miami]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[misinformation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[presidential campaign]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robert F. Kennedy Jr.]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vaccines]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=596853</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/krn-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Democratic Presidential Candidate Robert Kennedy Jr Holds Up to $250,000 in Bitcoin, Records Show" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/krn-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/krn-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/krn-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/krn-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/krn-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/krn-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/krn.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />According to a report published on Friday, Robert F. Kennedy Jr., a Democratic presidential candidate, holds between $100,000 to $250,000 in bitcoin (BTC). The holdings contradict his statements at the Bitcoin 2023 conference in May, where Kennedy claimed he was not an investor. Kennedy&#x2019;s campaign manager maintains that the BTC acquisition occurred subsequent to the [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/krn-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Democratic Presidential Candidate Robert Kennedy Jr Holds Up to $250,000 in Bitcoin, Records Show" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/krn-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/krn-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/krn-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/krn-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/krn-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/krn-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/krn.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>According to a report published on Friday, Robert F. Kennedy Jr., a Democratic presidential candidate, holds between $100,000 to $250,000 in bitcoin (<a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/BTC" 311996  target="_blank">BTC</a>). The holdings contradict his statements at the Bitcoin 2023 conference in May, where Kennedy claimed he was not an investor. Kennedy&#x2019;s campaign manager maintains that the <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/BTC" 311996  target="_blank">BTC</a> acquisition occurred subsequent to the candidate&#x2019;s remarks in May.</strong></p>
<h2>Robert Kennedy Jr&#x2019;s Bitcoin Fortune Revealed</h2>
<p>Financial records <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/07/07/rfk-jr-bitcoin-investment-raises-ethics-concerns.html">uncovered</a> by CNBC reveal that <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/robert-kennedy-jr-promises-to-protect-your-right-to-use-and-hold-bitcoin-as-president/">Robert F. Kennedy Jr.</a>, a Democratic candidate running against U.S. president <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bidenomics-agenda-struggles-to-gain-support-as-joe-bidens-approval-ratings-plummet/">Joe Biden</a>, possesses bitcoin valued between $100,000 and $250,000, equivalent to 3.31 to 8.27 <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/BTC" 311996  target="_blank">BTC</a>. Kennedy, the son of former senator Robert F. Kennedy and nephew of former president John F. Kennedy, allegedly contradicted his earlier remarks at the Bitcoin 2023 conference in Miami, as stated in the CNBC report.</p>
<p>At the time, Kennedy stated, &#x201C;I am not an investor and I am not here to give investment advice,&#x201D; while also informing the audience that his 2024 campaign would <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/robert-kennedy-jr-to-accept-btc-for-campaign-contributions-says-bitcoin-is-an-exercise-in-democracy/">accept BTC donations</a>. According to the <a href="https://fm.cnbc.com/applications/cnbc.com/resources/editorialfiles/2023/07/07/Candidate_Report_RFK_Jr.pdf">financial records</a>, the presidential candidate completed the paperwork on June 30, 2023, over a month following the conference. Subsequent to the publication of CNBC&#x2019;s article, Dennis Kucinich, Kennedy&#x2019;s campaign manager, informed the publication that the bitcoin was acquired post-conference.</p>
<p>In relation to ethical considerations, Kucinich conveyed to CNBC:</p>
<blockquote><p>There is no conflict here.</p></blockquote>
<p>Kennedy has expressed feeling marginalized by the mainstream media, as he himself stated on various occasions. During an interview with the New York Post, Kennedy <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/robert-f-kennedy-jr-advocates-for-bitcoin-and-opposes-cbdcs-in-candid-interview/">clarified</a> that despite being portrayed as an &#x201C;anti-vaxxer&#x201D; by the mainstream media, he is not against vaccines. &#x201C;I urge people to listen to what I actually say instead of listening to the litany of derisive sound bites that the mainstream media offers to mischaracterize and distort my positions on the whole range of issues,&#x201D; Kennedy emphasized during the interview.</p>

<p>The CNBC report, authored by Brian Schwartz, further notes that Kennedy has &#x201C;come under fire for spreading misinformation about vaccines at large,&#x201D; in an article completely unrelated to vaccines. Notably, almost every mainstream article covering Kennedy mentions his purported &#x201C;anti-vaccine&#x201D; position, often employing terms such as &#x201C;conspiracy theorist&#x201D; or &#x201C;anti-vaxxer&#x201D; to marginalize his viewpoint. However, the financial records dated June 30, 2023, do not specify the exact timing of Kennedy&#x2019;s bitcoin (<a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/BTC" 311996  target="_blank">BTC</a>) acquisition.</p>
<p><em><strong>What are your thoughts on Robert F. Kennedy Jr.&#x2019;s bitcoin holdings? Share your thoughts and opinions about this subject in the comments section below.</strong></em></p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/krn-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[According to a recently published report, Robert Kennedy Jr., a Democratic presidential candidate, holds between $100K and $250K in #bitcoin.]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA[According to a recently published report, Robert Kennedy Jr., a Democratic presidential candidate, holds between $100K and $250K in #bitcoin.]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>JPMorgan Analysts Say Spot Bitcoin ETF Approval Is ‘Unlikely to Be a Game Changer for Crypto Markets’</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/jpmorgan-analysts-say-spot-bitcoin-etf-approval-is-unlikely-to-be-a-game-changer-for-crypto-markets/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jamie Redman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 20:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[American banking giant]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Analysts]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[asset manager]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blackrock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[exchange traded fund]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fidelity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Game changer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[international]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Invesco]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investors]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jpmorgan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[market strategists]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[report]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[spot bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SSA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[U.S.Securities and Exchange Commission]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Valkyrie]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vaneck]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wisdomtree]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=596766</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/jpm-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="JPMorgan Analysts Say Spot Bitcoin ETF Approval Is ‘Unlikely to Be a Game Changer for Crypto Markets’" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/jpm-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/jpm-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/jpm-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/jpm-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/jpm-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/jpm-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/jpm.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />In a report published on Thursday, JPMorgan analysts suggest that the approval of a spot bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) is &#x201C;unlikely to be a game changer for crypto markets.&#x201D; The market strategists at the American banking giant emphasize that similar spot bitcoin ETFs already exist internationally, but [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/jpm-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="JPMorgan Analysts Say Spot Bitcoin ETF Approval Is ‘Unlikely to Be a Game Changer for Crypto Markets’" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/jpm-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/jpm-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/jpm-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/jpm-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/jpm-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/jpm-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/jpm.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>In a report published on Thursday, JPMorgan analysts suggest that the approval of a spot bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) is &#x201C;unlikely to be a game changer for crypto markets.&#x201D; The market strategists at the American banking giant emphasize that similar spot bitcoin ETFs already exist internationally, but they have not gained much popularity among investors.</strong></p>
<h2>JPMorgan Analysts Doubt Impact of Spot Bitcoin ETF Approval on Crypto Markets</h2>
<p>Over the past few weeks, there has been substantial discussion among bitcoin proponents regarding the potential approval of a spot <a href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/BTC/">bitcoin (BTC)</a> exchange-traded fund (ETF) by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). In mid-June, Blackrock, the world&#x2019;s largest asset manager, <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/blackrock-files-for-bitcoin-trust-analyst-calls-it-a-real-deal-spot-bitcoin-etf-filing/">filed</a> for a spot bitcoin ETF. Following this registration, numerous other institutions <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/valkyrie-funds-joins-race-for-sec-approval-as-it-files-application-for-spot-bitcoin-etf/">submitted</a> applications for comparable exchange-traded products.</p>
<p>According to market observers, the recent <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/crypto-exchange-backed-by-fidelity-schwab-citadel-launches-with-trading-of-4-cryptocurrencies/">launch</a> of EDX, a cryptocurrency exchange supported by Charles Schwab, Citadel Securities, and Fidelity Digital Assets, coupled with the filings for ETFs, has resulted in an increase in <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/BTC" 311996  target="_blank">BTC</a> prices. <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/jpmorgan-outlines-4-global-outlook-scenarios-warns-of-boil-the-frog-recession-as-global-downturn-looms/">JPMorgan</a> analysts, in a report published on Thursday, express doubt about the transformative impact of a spot bitcoin ETF on the crypto markets, however, even if it receives approval from the SEC.</p>
<p>&#x201C;The potential approval of physically backed bitcoin ETFs by the SEC is unlikely to be a game changer for crypto markets,&#x201D; the analysts said. &#x201C;Spot bitcoin ETFs have existed for some time outside the U.S., in Canada and Europe, but have failed to attract large investor interest.&#x201D; The bank&#x2019;s market strategists noted that Canada&#x2019;s Purpose Bitcoin ETF (<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/chart/?symbol=TSX%3ABTCC">BTCC CN</a>) has been around for two years without much attention.</p>
<p>While there was some initial upside following the launch of derivatives-related <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/BTC" 311996  target="_blank">BTC</a> ETFs, even exchange-traded products based on futures are not generating the institutional interest they previously attracted. The JPMorgan analysts explained, &#x201C;Bitcoin funds overall, including futures-based and physically backed funds, have attracted little investor interest since Q2 2021, also failing to benefit from investor outflows from gold ETFs over the past year or so.&#x201D;</p>

<p>JPMorgan&#x2019;s remarks come in the wake of a recent Wall Street Journal report, which indicated that insiders with knowledge of the securities regulator informed Cboe and Nasdaq, the listing applicants, that their applications were deemed &#x201C;<a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/insiders-say-sec-deems-blackrocks-spot-bitcoin-etf-and-other-applications-as-inadequate/">inadequate</a>.&#x201D; Subsequently, following the report, <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/cboe-resubmits-spot-bitcoin-etf-filings-with-coinbase-as-surveillance-sharing-partner-amid-sec-dissatisfaction/">several ETF filings</a> were <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/nasdaq-resubmits-blackrock-spot-bitcoin-etf-application-inks-agreement-with-coinbase-for-surveillance-sharing/">resubmitted</a>, with Coinbase being named as the partner for the surveillance-sharing agreement (SSA). Fidelity, Vaneck, Invesco, Wisdomtree, and Blackrock resubmitted their filings at the end of June, while Valkyrie <a href="https://listingcenter.nasdaq.com/assets/rulebook/NASDAQ/filings/SR-NASDAQ-2023-019.pdf">refiled</a> on July 3rd.</p>
<p><em><strong>What do you think the impact of a spot bitcoin ETF getting approval by the SEC would be? Share your thoughts and opinions about this subject in the comments section below.</strong></em></p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/jpm-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[JPMorgan analysts say that similar spot #bitcoin ETFs already exist internationally, but they have not gained much popularity among investors.]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA[JPMorgan analysts say that similar spot #bitcoin ETFs already exist internationally, but they have not gained much popularity among investors.]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>NFT Sales Witness 23% Decline This Week, Ethereum Dominates With $130 Million in Sales</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/nft-sales-witness-23-decline-this-week-ethereum-dominates-with-130-million-in-sales/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jamie Redman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 18:30:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets and Prices]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[7-day NFT sales]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Azuki]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bnb]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bored Ape Yacht Club]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Captainz]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptoslam.io]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Degods]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital Collectibles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fram BRC20]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mutant Ape Yacht Club]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFT sales]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFT sales ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFTs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Non-fungible tokens]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sales decline]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales NFTs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[two-week trend]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized Ordinals]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=596782</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/nftsdd-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/nftsdd-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/nftsdd-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/nftsdd-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/nftsdd-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/nftsdd-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/nftsdd-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/nftsdd.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />During the first week of H2 2023, non-fungible token (NFT) sales witnessed a 23.39% decline compared to the previous week, marking a two-week downward trend. A total of $195.95 million worth of NFT sales occurred, with Ethereum-based NFTs accounting for $130.77 million. NFT Sales Take a Hit: Week-Over-Week Drop of 23% in the First Week [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/nftsdd-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/nftsdd-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/nftsdd-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/nftsdd-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/nftsdd-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/nftsdd-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/nftsdd-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/nftsdd.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>During the first week of H2 2023, non-fungible token (NFT) sales witnessed a 23.39% decline compared to the previous week, marking a two-week downward trend. A total of $195.95 million worth of NFT sales occurred, with Ethereum-based NFTs accounting for $130.77 million.</strong></p>
<h2>NFT Sales Take a Hit: Week-Over-Week Drop of 23% in the First Week of July 2023</h2>
<p>Cryptoslam.io <a href="https://www.cryptoslam.io/">data</a> reveals a 23.39% drop in NFT sales this week compared to the earlier week. Along with this downturn, there was a notable 96.48% decrease in NFT buyers and a 15.26% slide in the number of NFT sales. ETH-based NFT sales led the pack with 66.73% of total sales, reaching $130.77 million last week.</p>

<p>Despite their dominance, <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/ETH" target="_blank">ETH</a> NFT sales saw a 14.77% dip compared to the previous week. Among 22 networks, Bitcoin (<a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/BTC" 311996  target="_blank">BTC</a>) ranked second in terms of sales, recording $23.37 million last week and experiencing a 34.99% slump week-over-week. Ethereum and Bitcoin were followed by Solana, <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/BNB" target="_blank">BNB</a>, and Polygon in weekly sales.</p>

<p>Bored Ape Yacht Club (BAYC) emerged as the highest-selling NFT collection over the past week, generating $22.57 million in revenue and growing by 1% compared to the prior week. Azuki, Mutant Ape Yacht Club (MAYC), Uncategorized Ordinals, and Fram BRC20 trailed behind BAYC. Fram BRC20 NFT sales surged by an impressive 97.47%. Captainz and Degods also recorded significant gains between 43% and 70%, respectively.</p>

<p>Of the top five NFT collectible sales this week, three originated from the Bitcoin blockchain while two were based on Ethereum. The priciest sale was an Uncategorized Ordinal that fetched $832K; however, no single NFT or digital collectible breached the million-dollar mark this week.</p>
<p><em><strong>What do you think is driving the recent decline in weekly NFT sales? Share your thoughts and insights in the comments section below.</strong></em></p>



]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/nftsdd-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[On July 8, 2023, Cryptoslam data reveals a 23.39% drop in #NFT sales this week compared to the earlier week.]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA[On July 8, 2023, Cryptoslam data reveals a 23.39% drop in #NFT sales this week compared to the earlier week.]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Monero Maintains Stability Amid Crypto Market Volatility, Remains Top Privacy Token With $3B Market Cap</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/monero-maintains-stability-amid-crypto-market-volatility-remains-top-privacy-token-with-3b-market-cap/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jamie Redman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 16:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anonymity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto assets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[leap]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Capitalization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Monero]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Performance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Privacy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[privacy coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[privacy crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[privacy token]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[privacy-focused cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[remarkable]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stability]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Surge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Value]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[volatility]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xmr]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=596799</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/monero-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Monero Maintains Stability Amid Crypto Market Volatility, Remains Top Privacy Token With $3B Market Cap" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/monero-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/monero-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/monero-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/monero-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/monero-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/monero-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/monero.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />In the last half-year, there has been a remarkable surge in the value of crypto assets such as bitcoin and ethereum. BTC has skyrocketed by 77%, while ETH has experienced an impressive 44% leap. On the other hand, the leading privacy-focused cryptocurrency, monero (XMR), has displayed a rather unimpressive performance during the initial six months [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/monero-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Monero Maintains Stability Amid Crypto Market Volatility, Remains Top Privacy Token With $3B Market Cap" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/monero-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/monero-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/monero-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/monero-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/monero-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/monero-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/monero.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>In the last half-year, there has been a remarkable surge in the value of crypto assets such as bitcoin and ethereum. <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/BTC" 311996  target="_blank">BTC</a> has skyrocketed by 77%, while <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/ETH" target="_blank">ETH</a> has experienced an impressive 44% leap. On the other hand, the leading privacy-focused cryptocurrency, monero (<a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/XMR" target="_blank">XMR</a>), has displayed a rather unimpressive performance during the initial six months of 2023, with a modest increase of 7.6% in H1. Nonetheless, following the resolution of the aftermath caused by the collapse of the Terra ecosystem, <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/XMR" target="_blank">XMR</a>&#x2019;s worth has remained relatively stable since July 2022.</strong></p>
<h2>Resilient Privacy Coin Monero Defies Crypto Market Volatility for 12 Months</h2>
<p><a href="https://archive.ph/8mJh4">Monero (XMR)</a> remains the top privacy token among numerous crypto tokens claiming to offer anonymity, with a current market capitalization of $3 billion. The second-leading privacy-centric coin, <a href="https://archive.ph/buIj9">dash (DASH)</a>, holds a significantly lower market valuation of $380 million. Over the past six months, <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/DASH" target="_blank">DASH</a> has experienced a 29% decline in value against the U.S. dollar, while <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/XMR" target="_blank">XMR</a> has seen a modest 7.6% increase in H1.</p>

<p>Notably, while many cryptocurrencies have encountered substantial volatility in the past year, <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/XMR" target="_blank">XMR</a> has maintained a relatively stable trajectory. For instance, in mid-July 2022, following the collapse of Terra, the privacy token was traded at $151 per unit. Since then, <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/XMR" target="_blank">XMR</a> has reached its highest point at $186 on January 22, 2023, and its lowest at $127 per unit after the collapse of FTX.</p>

<p>In December 2022, <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/XMR" target="_blank">XMR</a> was valued at $144.73 per coin, demonstrating resilience compared to the downturn experienced by most crypto assets during that month. On the other hand, <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/XMR" target="_blank">XMR</a> is down 69% from its all-time high of $542 per unit obtained on January 9, 2018. On May 2, 2021, <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/XMR" target="_blank">XMR</a> rose to a high of $484 per coin but it dropped to $315 per unit by August 2021.</p>

<p>While <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/XMR" target="_blank">XMR</a> has remained steady, a <a href="https://captainaltcoin.com/monero-xmr-price-prediction/">price prediction</a> from captainaltcoin.com indicates that <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/XMR" target="_blank">XMR</a> could end up trading for $144.29 per unit in December 2023. A year from now, the captainaltcoin.com prediction forecasts <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/XMR" target="_blank">XMR</a> at $196.50 per unit in July 2024. Despite the lackluster market performance, <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/XMR" target="_blank">XMR</a> has been the most dominant privacy coin in terms of market cap over the past few years.</p>
<p><em><strong>What are your thoughts on Monero&#x2019;s stable trajectory and its significance in the evolving crypto market? Share your thoughts and opinions about this subject in the comments section below.</strong></em></p>




]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/monero-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[After the collapse of the Terra ecosystem over a year ago, #XMR's worth has remained relatively stable since July 2022. #Monero #PrivacyCoins ]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA[After the collapse of the Terra ecosystem over a year ago, #XMR's worth has remained relatively stable since July 2022. #Monero #PrivacyCoins ]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Biggest Movers: SOL Surges to 2-Month High on Saturday, Extending Recent Bull Run</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/biggest-movers-sol-surges-to-2-month-high-on-saturday-extending-recent-bull-run/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Eliman Dambell]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 14:30:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Avalanche]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AVAX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOL]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technical Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=596821</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2244456519-1-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="SOL Surges to 2-Month High on Saturday, Extending Recent Bull Run" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2244456519-1-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2244456519-1-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2244456519-1-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2244456519-1-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2244456519-1-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2244456519-1-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2244456519-1.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />Solana extended recent gains on Saturday, as the token rose for a third straight session to start the weekend. Today’s move came following a breakout of a key price level, despite the global crypto market cap consolidating. Avalanche also rallied, climbing by as much as 10%. Solana (SOL) Solana (SOL) was a notable gainer in [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2244456519-1-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="SOL Surges to 2-Month High on Saturday, Extending Recent Bull Run" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2244456519-1-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2244456519-1-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2244456519-1-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2244456519-1-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2244456519-1-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2244456519-1-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2244456519-1.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>Solana extended recent gains on Saturday, as the token rose for a third straight session to start the weekend. Today’s move came following a breakout of a key price level, despite the global crypto market cap consolidating. Avalanche also rallied, climbing by as much as 10%.</strong></p>
<h2>Solana (SOL)</h2>
<p>Solana (SOL) was a notable gainer in the crypto market for a third straight day, with today’s move taking price to an eight-week high.</p>
<p>Following a low of $20.19 on Friday, SOL/USD jumped to an intraday peak of $22.40 to start the weekend.</p>
<p>As a result of the surge, solana raced past a ceiling of $22.00, hitting its highest point since May 6 in the process.</p>

<p>From the chart, the move occurred as the relative strength index (RSI) jumped beyond a ceiling at the 69.00 mark.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, the index is tracking at 70.70, with the next visible point of resistance at 75.00.</p>
<p>Should the index reach this point, there is a good chance that SOL will climb to $23.00.</p>

<h2>Avalanche (AVAX)</h2>
<p>Another notable gainer on Saturday was avalanche (AVAX), which rose by nearly 10% in today’s session.</p>
<p>AVAX/USD climbed to a high of $13.85 earlier in today’s session, a day after trading at a low of $12.60.</p>
<p>The move resulted in avalanche jumping to its strongest level since June 9, after breaking out of a resistance level of $13.50.</p>

<p>One of the catalysts of this rally was the 14-day RSI breaking out of its own ceiling at the 57.00 mark.</p>
<p>The index is now tracking at 58.73, and looks to be making strides for a higher point of resistance at 62.00.</p>
<p>Additionally, the 10-day (red) moving average has just avoided a downward crossover, with momentum once again shifting upward.</p>
<p><em>Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:</em></p>
<p><em><strong>Do you expect avalanche to hit $15.00 in the next few days? Let us know your thoughts in the comments.</strong></em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2244456519-1-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[#SOL races to 2-month high, as #AVAX climbs 10% on Saturday.]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA[#SOL races to 2-month high, as #AVAX climbs 10% on Saturday.]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin, Ethereum Technical Analysis: BTC Consolidates to Start Weekend, ETH Remains Below $1,900</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-ethereum-technical-analysis-btc-consolidates-to-start-weekend-eth-remains-below-1900/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Eliman Dambell]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 12:30:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=596747</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1251778627-2-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Bitcoin, Ethereum Technical Analysis: BTC Consolidates to Start Weekend, ETH Remains Below $1,900" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1251778627-2-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1251778627-2-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1251778627-2-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1251778627-2-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1251778627-2-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1251778627-2-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1251778627-2.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />Bitcoin was hovering near the $30,000 level to start the weekend, as markets continued to digest the latest U.S. nonfarm payrolls report. Payrolls came in at 209,000, less than the 225,000 expected, putting slight doubt in a potential July rate hike. Ethereum continued to trade below $1,900 on Saturday. Bitcoin Bitcoin (BTC) started the weekend [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1251778627-2-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Bitcoin, Ethereum Technical Analysis: BTC Consolidates to Start Weekend, ETH Remains Below $1,900" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1251778627-2-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1251778627-2-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1251778627-2-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1251778627-2-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1251778627-2-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1251778627-2-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1251778627-2.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>Bitcoin was hovering near the $30,000 level to start the weekend, as markets continued to digest the latest U.S. nonfarm payrolls report. Payrolls came in at 209,000, less than the 225,000 expected, putting slight doubt in a potential July rate hike. Ethereum continued to trade below $1,900 on Saturday.</strong></p>
<h2>Bitcoin</h2>
<p>Bitcoin (<a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/BTC" 311996  target="_blank">BTC</a>) started the weekend consolidating around the $30,000 level, following the latest U.S. nonfarm payrolls report.</p>
<p><a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/BTC" 311996  target="_blank">BTC</a>/USD dropped to an intraday low of $30,094.87, a day after trading at a one-year high above $31,000.</p>
<p>The price has marginally increased following today&#x2019;s earlier row, and is now trading at $30,240.85.</p>

<p>Overall, it appears that a failed breakout of a ceiling at 58.00 on the relative strength index (RSI) was the catalyst of this drop.</p>
<p>Price strength is now tracking at the 57.63 level, with a support point at 55.00 a possible target for traders.</p>
<p>Should it reach this point, it is highly likely that <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/BTC" 311996  target="_blank">BTC</a> will move below $30,000.</p>

<h2>Ethereum</h2>
<p>Ethereum (<a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/ETH" target="_blank">ETH</a>) also started the weekend consolidating, with the cryptocurrency once again moving below $1,900.</p>
<p>Since hitting a peak at $1,957 on Thursday, <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/ETH" target="_blank">ETH</a>/USD has failed to trade above $1,900, with today&#x2019;s drop taking price to a low of $1,854.92.</p>
<p>After reaching a two-month high on June 3, ethereum has struggled, with price falling lower in consecutive sessions.</p>

<p>These declines have pushed price strength to a floor at 47.00, however this support point has so far been stable, helping to stop the prior bleeding.</p>
<p>The index is now tracking at a reading of 49.59, with an upcoming resistance level of 51.00 the next test for traders.</p>
<p>In the event they pass this test, the next destination for price will likely be back above $1,900.</p>
<p><em>Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:</em></p>
<p><em><strong>Do you still expect ethereum to hit $2,000 in July? Leave your thoughts in the comments below.</strong></em></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1251778627-2-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[#BTC consolidates around $30,000 to start the weekend, following Friday's U.S. nonfarm payrolls report.]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA[#BTC consolidates around $30,000 to start the weekend, following Friday's U.S. nonfarm payrolls report.]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Central Bank of Russia: Digital Ruble Could Be Launched as Soon as 2025</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/central-bank-of-russia-digital-ruble-could-be-launched-as-soon-as-2025/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sergio Goschenko]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 11:30:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anatoly Aksakov]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[central bank digital currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Bank of Russia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital ruble]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Olga Skorobogatova]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[State Duma]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=596479</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2164243381-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Central Bank of Russia: Digital Ruble Could Be Launched as Soon as 2025" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2164243381-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2164243381-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2164243381-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2164243381-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2164243381-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2164243381-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2164243381.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />Olga Skorobogatova, first deputy chairman of the Central Bank of Russia, indicated that the launch of the digital ruble, the Russian central bank digital currency (CBDC), could happen in 2025. The pilot test for the CBDC will be organized later this year after the State Duma, the lower house of the Russian parliament, passes the [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2164243381-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Central Bank of Russia: Digital Ruble Could Be Launched as Soon as 2025" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2164243381-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2164243381-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2164243381-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2164243381-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2164243381-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2164243381-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2164243381.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>Olga Skorobogatova, first deputy chairman of the Central Bank of Russia, indicated that the launch of the digital ruble, the Russian central bank digital currency (CBDC), could happen in 2025. The pilot test for the CBDC will be organized later this year after the State Duma, the lower house of the Russian parliament, passes the bill regulating the operations of the digital ruble.</strong></p>
<h2>Central Bank of Russia Indicates Digital Ruble Could Be Launched in 2025</h2>
<p>The Central Bank of Russia expects the digital ruble, a Russian central bank digital currency (CBDC), to be launched as soon as 2025, according to the reports of Olga Skorobogatova, first deputy chairman of the institution. Skorobogatova also stated that a pilot test of the digital currency is expected to take place this year after the State Duma, the lower house of the Russian parliament, passes the digital ruble law.</p>
<p>The official explained the introduction of a digital currency would be a long process for Russia. Skorobogatova <a href="https://iz.ru/1540121/2023-07-06/tcentrobank-nazval-sroki-vnedreniia-tcifrovykh-rublei" target="_blank" rel="noopener">stated</a>:</p>
<blockquote>
<p>It is important to us that everything is safe and works perfectly.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Furthermore, she detailed that, unlike the digital yuan that is currently being <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/china-pushes-digital-yuan-for-wage-payments-in-changshu/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">used</a> as a means of paying wages for some workers in China, the digital ruble will not be used to pay for pensions or benefits for citizens and will have an account limit of 300,000 rubles (a little less than $3,300).</p>

<h2>State Duma to Pass Digital Ruble Law in July</h2>
<p>While the Central Bank of Russia had planned to start pilot test in April, the State Duma had not yet passed the regulations for digital ruble operations.</p>
<p>However, Anatoly Aksakov, head of the State Duma Financial Market Committee, told <a href="https://iz.ru/1540186/2023-07-06/v-gd-mogut-priniat-zakonoproekty-o-tcifrovom-ruble-uzhe-v-iiule" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Izvestia</a> on Thursday that he expected the digital ruble-relevant bills to be passed this July. In this case, Izvestia states that the pilot test could start in August.</p>
<p>Aksakov had <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/digital-ruble-law-likely-to-be-passed-in-june-according-to-russian-official/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">stated</a> in May that he expected the digital ruble law to be passed in June. However, this did not happen. Aksakov had also <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/russia-to-enact-laws-to-regulate-crypto-exchange-action-profiles-use-of-cryptocurrency-to-bypass-sanctions/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">profiled</a> crypto before as a way of sidestepping the international sanctions of the country, rejecting the idea of having a sole Russian exchange due to the possibility of it being sanctioned by Western nations.</p>
<p>The digital ruble bill was <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bill-on-digital-ruble-submitted-to-russian-parliament/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">introduced</a> to the State Duma in January by Aksakov and other members of the Financial Market Committee after the Central Bank of Russia <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bank-of-russia-accelerates-schedule-for-digital-ruble-project/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">accelerated</a> the roadmap for the digital ruble project in 2022.</p>
<p><em><strong>What do you think about the timeline of the launch of the digital ruble? Tell us in the comment section below.</strong></em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2164243381-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[The Central Bank of #Russia expects the digital #ruble, a #Russian central bank digital currency (#CBDC), to be launched as soon as 2025, according to the reports of Olga Skorobogatova.]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA[Skorobogatova stated that unlike the digital #yuan that is currently being used as a means of payment for some workers in #China, the digital #ruble will not be used to pay for pensions or benefits.]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Report: Zimbabwe Central Bank Begins Gold-Backed Digital Currency &#8216;Dry Run&#8217;</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/report-zimbabwe-central-bank-begins-gold-backed-digital-currency-dry-run/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Terence Zimwara]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 08:30:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Africa]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gold-backed digital currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[John Mangudya]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nelson Mupunga]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reserve Bank of Zimbabwe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US Dollar]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=596714</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1211210776-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Report: Zimbabwe Central Bank Begins Gold-Backed Digital Currency &#039;Dry Run&#039;" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1211210776-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1211210776-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1211210776-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1211210776-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1211210776-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1211210776-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1211210776.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />According to a report, the Reserve Bank of Zimbabwe has commenced trials, or the &#8220;dry run&#8221; test, for the viability of launching a gold-backed digital currency. Nelson Mupunga, the director of economic research at the central bank, reportedly said the digital currency will act as an alternative to foreign currency. Local Residents&#8217; Insatiable Demand for [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1211210776-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Report: Zimbabwe Central Bank Begins Gold-Backed Digital Currency &#039;Dry Run&#039;" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1211210776-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1211210776-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1211210776-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1211210776-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1211210776-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1211210776-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1211210776.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>According to a report, the Reserve Bank of Zimbabwe has commenced trials, or the &#8220;dry run&#8221; test, for the viability of launching a gold-backed digital currency. Nelson Mupunga, the director of economic research at the central bank, reportedly said the digital currency will act as an alternative to foreign currency.</strong></p>
<h2>Local Residents&#8217; Insatiable Demand for the Greenback</h2>
<p>The Zimbabwean central bank has commenced a &#8220;dry run&#8221; to test the feasibility of issuing a gold-backed digital currency which is set to be used as a means of payment, a <a href="https://businesstimes.co.zw/rbz-begins-digital-dollar-dry-run/">report</a> has said. The digital currency, which will be accepted as legal tender for peer-to-peer transactions, is part of the Reserve Bank of Zimbabwe (RBZ)’s raft of measures which are aimed at stabilizing the local currency.</p>
<p>The latest revelation by the Zimbabwean central bank official comes just a few weeks after the RBZ initially <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/report-zimbabwes-central-bank-set-to-launch-p2p-platform-for-facilitating-gold-backed-digital-currency-transactions/">announced</a> plans to launch the P2P platform. As reported by Bitcoin.com News, the launch of the platform will make it possible for holders of digital gold tokens to trade them. John Mangudya, the RBZ governor, has in the past stated that the gold-backed tokens will help the country <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/zimbabwes-de-dollarization-central-bank-to-issue-gold-backed-digital-currency-in-early-may/">diminish</a> its insatiable need for foreign currencies such as the U.S. dollar.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;">
<h2>Gold-Backed Digital Currency as a Store of Value</h2>
<p>According to Nelson Mupunga, the director of economic research and policy implementation for the RBZ, the digital currency will act as an alternative to the greenback and other foreign currencies.</p>
<p>&#8220;We are at an advanced stage; we are at the testing stage now. Soon, we will allow the gold digital token to be used for transaction purposes just like someone buys foreign currency from the parallel market. But at the same time, we can transact with. So, the token is coming and will satisfy the same function,&#8221; said the RBZ official.</p>
<p>The official also added that the central bank had chosen to launch the gold-backed digital currency after observing local residents’ practice of ditching the floundering local currency for the greenback. Therefore, instead of using the greenback to store value, residents in the inflation-hit country will be able to do this using gold-backed digital tokens.</p>
<p><em>Register your email here to get a weekly update on African news sent to your inbox:</em></p>
<p><em><strong>What are your thoughts on this story? Let us know what you think in the comments section below. </strong></em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1211210776-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[The #digital currency is part of the Reserve Bank of Zimbabwe (RBZ)’s raft of measures which are aimed at stabilizing the local currency. #rbz #inflation]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA[Instead of using the #greenback to #store value, residents in the #inflation-hit country will be able to do this using gold-backed digital tokens. #foreigncurrency]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
