<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Magazine - Bitcoin News, Articles and Expert Insights]]></title><description><![CDATA[Established in 2012, Bitcoin Magazine is the oldest and most established source of trustworthy news, information and thought leadership on Bitcoin.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com</link><image><url>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/site/images/apple-touch-icon.png</url><title>Bitcoin Magazine - Bitcoin News, Articles and Expert Insights</title><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com</link></image><generator>Tempest</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 04:42:10 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.rss/full/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 04:42:10 GMT</pubDate><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><atom:link href="https://pubsubhubbub.appspot.com/" rel="hub"/><item><title><![CDATA[Voltage Partners With Google Cloud To Expand Lightning Network Solutions Globally]]></title><description><![CDATA[Voltage and Google Cloud are collaborating to offer global Lightning Network solutions, enabling real-time payments with near-zero fees for enterprises.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/voltage-partners-with-google-cloud-to-expand-lightning-solutions</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/voltage-partners-with-google-cloud-to-expand-lightning-solutions</guid><category><![CDATA[Google]]></category><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[Lightning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Nodes]]></category><category><![CDATA[Voltage]]></category><category><![CDATA[Business]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[BtcCasey]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 01:11:13 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTgzMjM5NTgzMDQxODU2OTMw/img_6139.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p><a href="https://voltage.cloud/">Voltage</a>, a Lightning as a Service (LaaS) provider, has partnered with <a href="https://cloud.google.com/">Google Cloud</a> to expand its hosting capabilities and locations, enabling customers to create Bitcoin and Lightning Nodes globally. According to <a href="https://cloud.google.com/blog/topics/startups/how-voltage-uses-google-cloud-to-scale-its-bitcoin-lightning-network/">an announcement</a> by Google Cloud, the collaboration will allow enterprises to leverage the Lightning Network's real-time payment settlement with near-zero fees, revolutionizing money transfers and creating new business models.</p><p>Voltage stated in the announcement that their solution helps enterprises overcome three key challenges. First, they cited the ability to facilitate money transfers over the Lightning Network, offering a cost-effective alternative for financial and fintech companies. Second, by adopting the interoperable Lightning Network standard, Voltage described how businesses can reach a global customer base. Lastly, Voltage highlighted how it enables microtransactions, which have been difficult to implement with traditional payment methods, but can enhance customer retention, decrease acquisition costs and increase customer lifetime value.</p><p>By utilizing Google Cloud's vast network infrastructure, Voltage said it can address user needs more efficiently. The announcement described the partnership’s several benefits, including the ability to serve a global audience across various regions, initial operations in Iowa, the Netherlands and Singapore as well as deployments on a leading cloud platform with superior availability and networking. Moreover, the announcement explained how running Bitcoin infrastructure alongside existing workloads becomes seamless with the assistance of Google Cloud's resources.</p><p>Google Cloud's commitment to supporting Bitcoin showcases its dedication to advancing this technology and bringing it to a wider audience. The company's expertise in cloud-native technologies, like Kubernetes, also provides Voltage with the scalability required to meet enterprise adoption requirements.</p><p>As Voltage expands its services through the collaboration with Google Cloud, enterprises in the financial and fintech sectors will be able to leverage the Lightning Network's capabilities to streamline their payment processes, reduce costs and explore new business opportunities.</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTgzMjM5NTgzMDQxODU2OTMw/img_6139.png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[BTCPay Server Releases 1.10.0 Update With New Store Management System And Privacy Features]]></title><description><![CDATA[Along with these announced features are a drag-and-drop form builder, plugin updates, bug fixes and a caution against scammers.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/technical/btcpay-server-releases-1-10-0-update</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/technical/btcpay-server-releases-1-10-0-update</guid><category><![CDATA[Merchants]]></category><category><![CDATA[Updates]]></category><category><![CDATA[Payments]]></category><category><![CDATA[btcpay server]]></category><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[Technical]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[BtcCasey]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 21:36:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkwOTE3NzExNjQ2MTcyNzU3/aa-btc-4.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p><a href="https://btcpayserver.org/">BTCPay Server</a> has released its latest major update, version 1.10.0, featuring a range of enhancements and new features.</p><p>One notable addition is the drag-and-drop form builder UI, which allows users to easily design customizable forms for collecting customer information during checkout. According to <a href="https://blog.btcpayserver.org/btcpay-server-1-10-0/">the announcement</a>, the team has been working diligently to address outstanding issues and introduce improvements, including a new store role management system and a toggle to protect private data.</p><p>The custom role management system is a significant upgrade for store owners with teams, offering the ability to create tailored roles to meet specific needs and grant staff access to specific permissions within the store. The release also includes a privacy-enhancing toggle under "Hide Sensitive Information," allowing users to hide wallet balances and invoice amounts from prying eyes.</p><p>In addition to these updates, the release includes improvements to invoice filtering, plugin updates and various quality-of-life enhancements. LNbank, a plugin integrated with BTCPay Server, has released version 1.6, which incorporates the new "Hide Sensitive Info" setting and adds wallet balance graphs. The Nostr plugin has also been updated for improved performance and stability.</p><p>The update also introduces a new plugin called Auto-forward Payments, which automates the redirection of payments to another address, streamlining the payment process. BTC OnChain payments are currently the only supported method for auto-forwarding.</p><p>The release notes also mention bug fixes, addressing issues such as payments not being detected by BTCPay Server when using LNbank and display issues with the dashboard when the default currency is sats.</p><p>However, users are warned to beware of scammers exploiting the BTCPay Server brand and software. The team emphasizes that they will only reach out through official channels and encourages users to verify the identity of anyone claiming to be from the team.</p><p>The BTCPay Server team expresses gratitude to the contributors and supporters who have made version 1.10.0 possible. They also highlight the partnership with OpenSats, which allows individuals to donate to the BTCPay Server project and potentially apply for a tax deduction.</p><p>For more information on the update and its features, users are encouraged to visit the BTCPay Server documentation and <a href="https://chat.btcpayserver.org/landing#/">community chat</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkwOTE3NzExNjQ2MTcyNzU3/aa-btc-4.png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Gemini Exchange To Acquire License To Operate In United Arab Emirates]]></title><description><![CDATA[Gemini’s move is another sign of exchanges seeking alternatives to the American market as regulatory uncertainty takes its toll.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/gemini-exchange-to-acquire-license-to-operate-in-uae</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/gemini-exchange-to-acquire-license-to-operate-in-uae</guid><category><![CDATA[Business]]></category><category><![CDATA[Uae]]></category><category><![CDATA[Gemini]]></category><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[Exchanges]]></category><category><![CDATA[Middle east]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[BtcCasey]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 19:26:47 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk0NDg4MTA1ODc5ODczMDI5/economic-chart-analysis.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p>Gemini, a global cryptocurrency exchange, has <a href="https://twitter.com/Gemini/status/1664107397445550081?s=20">announced</a> its plans to acquire a cryptocurrency license in the United Arab Emirates (UAE) in a move to expand its services. Describing the UAE's position as a forward-thinking financial hub, Gemini aims to tap into the country's growing market. The company is committed to becoming a global entity, according to the announcement, by meeting local regulatory requirements and understanding the needs of UAE crypto investors.</p><div><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><a href="https://twitter.com/Gemini/status/1664107397445550081"></a></blockquote><script async="" src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><p>Gemini's decision to apply for a license comes as a result of its findings from the 2022 Global State of Crypto Report. The report revealed a significant increase in cryptocurrency adoption among individuals in the UAE, with many using it for in-person purchases. Additionally, the study indicated a strong intention among non-owners to enter the cryptocurrency space.</p><p>Speaking about the application, Gemini leadership expressed their vision of providing a safe, secure, and user-friendly platform for customers in the UAE and beyond. The company stated that it is eager to serve the rapidly growing and vibrant crypto community in the region. </p><p>In January, Gemini co-founder Cameron Winklevoss <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/gemini-alleges-dcg-genesis-defrauded-users">wrote a letter to its parent company</a> Digital Currency Group (DCG) alleging that DCG defrauded Gemini customers in relation to Gemini Earn. Prior to that, <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/bitcoin-exchange-gemini-is-being-sued-by-the-cftc">Gemini was sued by the CFTC</a> for “misleading the regulator in conversations concerning the launch of bitcoin futures contracts.” </p><p>Gemini's move into the UAE highlights the country's emerging status as a bitcoin hub. In addition, it highlights the continued flight of major exchanges out of the U.S. as a result of tightening regulations. At the beginning of May, Coinbase <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/markets/coinbase-introduces-international-exchange-with-bitcoin-perpetual-futures">introduced its new international exchange arm</a> called Coinbase International, with the company stating that “countries around the world are increasingly moving forward with responsible crypto-forward regulatory frameworks to strategically position themselves as crypto hubs.”</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk0NDg4MTA1ODc5ODczMDI5/economic-chart-analysis.png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[CleanSpark Announces Purchase Of 12,500 Antminer S19 XP Bitcoin Miners]]></title><description><![CDATA[The publicly traded bitcoin mining company is once again expanding its inventory of deployable miners this year in its quest for 16 EH/s.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/cleanspark-announces-purchase-of-12500-antminer-bitcoin-miners</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/cleanspark-announces-purchase-of-12500-antminer-bitcoin-miners</guid><category><![CDATA[Antminer]]></category><category><![CDATA[Mining]]></category><category><![CDATA[Business]]></category><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[CleanSpark]]></category><category><![CDATA[Public Miners]]></category><category><![CDATA[Asics]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[BtcCasey]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 17:18:37 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTgwODA0OTg3MjcyODMyMDg4/mining-rigs.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p><a href="https://www.cleanspark.com">CleanSpark Inc.</a> has announced the purchase of 12,500 Antminer S19 XP bitcoin mining machines for a total price of $40.5 million. The machines were acquired at a lower price than the current market average, costing $23 per terahash, according to a press release shared with Bitcoin Magazine. The purchase agreement states that 6,000 of the machines will be shipped in June, with the remaining 6,500 set for shipping in August.</p><p>Zach Bradford, CEO of CleanSpark, expressed his confidence in the purchase, stating, "This purchase ensures that we are prepared to meet and potentially exceed our year-end target of 16 EH/s and also positions us to be one of the most power-efficient miners on an energy-per-hashrate basis." He further highlighted the optionality provided by the additional machines, allowing the company to replace less efficient units if the economics support it.</p><p>CleanSpark reported that it has been taking advantage of discounted machine purchases during the crypto bear market. In February, the company acquired <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/cleanspark-acquires-20000-bitcoin-miners">20,000 Antminer S19j Pro+ units,</a> followed by the purchase of <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/cleanspark-to-nearly-double-bitcoin-mining-capacity">45,000 Antminer S19 XP units in April</a>. <br><br>Gary A. Vecchiarelli, CFO at CleanSpark, emphasized the importance of these purchases in preparation for the upcoming bitcoin halving, stating, "the efficiency of these machines also results in less power consumed per bitcoin mined compared to older generation miners, which should translate to higher margins."</p><p>CleanSpark's recent purchases of bitcoin mining machines demonstrate the company's commitment to expanding their mining capacity and staying competitive in the market. With fees from Ordinals inscriptions boosting the revenue for miners, it is expected that large players like CleanSpark will continue to bolster their miner inventory.</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTgwODA0OTg3MjcyODMyMDg4/mining-rigs.jpg"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Should A Bitcoin Wallet Have Rights?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Like corporate entities or intelligent robots, Bitcoin wallets are poised to gain legal rights of their own.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/legal/why-bitcoin-wallets-should-have-legal-rights</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/legal/why-bitcoin-wallets-should-have-legal-rights</guid><category><![CDATA[Regulation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Legal]]></category><category><![CDATA[Legal]]></category><category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Wallets]]></category><category><![CDATA[Opinion]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Artem Afian]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk0MzI5NzY4OTU4MTc0ODk3/bitcoin-legal-regulation.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p><em>This is an opinion editorial by Artem Afian, a lawyer and “legal futurist” at Hiveon, a crypto mining ecosystem that offers services for Bitcoin mining hardware.</em></p><p>I want to draw your attention to the fact that Bitcoin transactions <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/guides/what-are-bitcoin-wallets">ultimately occur between wallets</a>. There are humans behind wallets, but this connection is not really what’s important. The pseudonymity of Bitcoin is thanks to the fact that there is no direct connection between the wallet and the person who owns it. It is what distinguishes a Bitcoin wallet from any other financial instrument. No matter how much regulators try to change this, the core of the technology remains the same. </p><p>What does this mean? It means that, soon, wallets will be recognized as entities deserving of legal rights.</p><p>First, humanity <a href="https://aldf.org/article/laws-that-protect-animals/">began to recognize animal rights</a>. Now, there is talk about <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/robots-ai-legal-rights-3c47ef40">the legal rights of a robot</a>. Soon, the rights of a Bitcoin wallet will come to the fray. </p><p>When one talks about the rights of robots, they usually refer to some imitation of human will that is deserving of legal recognition. We understand that a robot does not have a soul in the same way that a human does, but at the same time, it performs rather complex actions, which gives rise to legal consequences. For many of us, a robot or a Bitcoin wallet is something inanimate and devoid of a soul and, perhaps, therefore undeserving of legal protections. But we recognize the rights of companies and corporations and, of course, it is difficult to imagine more soulless forms than those. It turns out that the subjects of law can be inanimate.</p><p>So, what is the difference between a Bitcoin wallet and a legal entity? A legal entity is simply a set of files in a specific registry. Lawyers even have a theory of the “<a href="https://www.law.cornell.edu/wex/legal_fiction#:~:text=Legal%20fiction%20is%20an%20assumption,letter%20of%20the%20law%20unchanged.">fiction of a legal entity</a>.” We will calmly confirm that the legal entity is an American corporation. We can quickly check this. But how to check that a legal entity was created, say, under the laws of the country of Swaziland? Even if I show you documents that prove it, they are unlikely to tell you anything. So, if I tell you that you are dealing with a foreign company, you most probably just have to believe it. </p><p>Nevertheless, this legal entity, displayed as it is only on paper, has some rights. So, the Bitcoin wallet that exists is even more tangible than many legally-protected entities. Therefore, one more conclusion: Since legal entities have rights, then a wallet may have rights. Just like legal entities, wallets perform transactions, and just like legal entities, wallets can change their owners. This fact never changes: if robots or legal entities are deserving of legal rights, so too are Bitcoin wallets.</p><p>I think Bitcoin is an exciting new space and that we still have a lot to explore. Now, my idea that Bitcoin wallets will inevitably receive legal rights of their own may seem crazy, but many more discoveries await us.</p><p><em>This is a guest post by Artem Afian. Opinions expressed are entirely their own and do not necessarily reflect those of BTC Inc or Bitcoin Magazine.</em></p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk0MzI5NzY4OTU4MTc0ODk3/bitcoin-legal-regulation.png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Debate Around “Cursed” Ordinal Inscriptions]]></title><description><![CDATA[Inscriptions that do not get indexed by the ord protocol are known as “cursed,” but whether or not to include them is an ongoing conversation.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/technical/the-debate-around-cursed-ordinal-inscriptions</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/technical/the-debate-around-cursed-ordinal-inscriptions</guid><category><![CDATA[Inscriptions]]></category><category><![CDATA[Technical]]></category><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[Debate]]></category><category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Developer]]></category><category><![CDATA[Ordinals]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Craig Deutsch]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkwMzM1ODc0ODQyNTAyNTQ4/fiat-morals-angel-devil.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p>After only four months since the protocol was launched, ord has its first contentious debate about what are known as “cursed” inscriptions.</p><p>The simplest definition of a cursed inscription is any inscription that does not currently get indexed and identified by ord. This term came about as a catchall when some people incorrectly used or purposefully misused opcodes to create inscriptions that were not able to be indexed by ord and would therefore be unrecognized and not given an inscription number. </p><p>This issue was first mentioned on April 25 in the <a href="https://github.com/ordinals/ord/issues/2045">ord github</a> and the interim fix proposed by then lead developer Casey Rodarmor was to, “Modify ord to recognize the above currently invalid inscriptions, including retroactively in old blocks, but consider these new inscriptions ‘cursed’ and assign them negative inscription numbers.”</p><p>Funnily enough, the example inscription code on the Ordinals docs website would have been a cursed inscription.</p><div><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><a href="https://twitter.com/cbspears/status/1663292796306874369"></a></blockquote><script async="" src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><p><em><a href="https://twitter.com/cbspears/status/1663292796306874369">Link to embedded Tweet.</a></em></p><p>There are many ways cursed inscriptions can be created. Any inscription with multiple inputs/outputs would be considered cursed. As shown above, certain misuse of opcodes such as OP_1 can lead to cursed inscriptions. Alternatively, the introduction of OP_66 using a value of “cursed” intentionally made these types of inscriptions by having an even numbered opcode which is not indexed by ord. Unless already defined in the spec, even numbered opcodes are not recognized because they are reserved for future protocol development.&nbsp;<a href="https://github.com/ordinals/ord/issues/2045">Issue #2045</a>&nbsp;lists some of the ways it's possible to create cursed inscriptions:</p><ul><li>Multiple inscriptions per transaction, for efficient batching.</li><li>Inscriptions on inputs after the first, which is useful for collections.</li><li>Multiple inscriptions on the same sat, so that the entire history of a sat doesn’t need to be checked to determine if a new inscription is valid.</li><li>Inscriptions with unrecognized even headers, so that new even headers don't cause upgraded clients to disagree about inscription numbers.</li></ul><p>There are a couple specific debates around cursed inscriptions. One of the disputes comes from the way that these inscriptions are currently numbered. Cursed inscriptions are numbered negatively in the order of their creation. Because of this numbering system and naming convention, some people purposefully chose to create inscriptions and collections that appear “cursed” whether by flipping the image of a positively numbered inscription or using a more sinister image theme when inscribing. The question is: Should these be appended to the index of positively numbered inscriptions or should they keep their negative inscription number when the code is updated?</p><p>Additionally, another contentious conversation is what to do about the certain type of cursed inscriptions that used the OP_66 opcode in their creation. Because this opcode is not recognized by ord and even numbered opcodes are intentionally left out for future development use, it is debatable whether inscriptions using this opcode should be included in the cursed set or if they should be rejected.</p><p>At the present time, the <a href="https://github.com/ordinals/ord/pull/2109">issue around the even number opcode</a> is listed in the ord github. There are many comments in support of including these inscriptions in the index, but the lead maintainers of the protocol seem to be against it. As of now, the current stance by the developers is that these inscriptions would be unbound, meaning that they would not be assigned to a specific satoshi.</p><p>Remember, ordinal theory works based on a first in, first out tracking system for satoshis. Each inscription is assigned to the first satoshi in the genesis transaction when the inscription is created. This type of lens for looking at bitcoin allows images, files, text, etc. to be tracked and transferred. If a cursed inscription is unbound, it would not be associated with a specific satoshi and therefore would be unable to be transferred to another address. Many people who are inscribing are hoping to be able to sell or transfer their inscription to another person. While the inscriptions using this opcode will live forever on the Bitcoin blockchain, if these inscriptions are classified as unbound and unassigned to a specific satoshi, users who minted cursed inscriptions using this opcode would be unable to sell or transfer them.</p><p>Herein lies one of the bigger concerns for people who are spending money on transaction fees to create cursed inscriptions. If they are unable to sell them in the future, significant funds would have been wasted on fees. Many users have responded to the github issue, expressing support for including these inscriptions, but the code’s maintainers are not in favor of recognizing cursed inscriptions using the OP_66 even numbered opcode.</p><p>On May 30, the new lead maintainer of ord, Raphjaph, <a href="https://github.com/ordinals/ord/pull/2109#issuecomment-1568125568">wrote</a>, “As the protocol currently stands inscriptions are not valid if they use an unrecognized even tag, so this change already makes a concession by recognizing them. For now they are unbound but we might reconsider this and bind them in the future if there are strong reasons.”</p><p>This response is not what many inscribers were hoping to hear. Similar to Bitcoin, ord is open-source software so users can fork the code if they wish to recognize these specific types of cursed inscriptions. This contentious debate is ongoing and the path forward for ord remains to be seen. Users who spent significant sums on transaction fees may be willing to switch to a new version of ord that will recognize their cursed inscriptions, but this is only a theoretical path forward at this time.</p><p>Regardless, Ordinals are a new technology being built on Bitcoin. Whether inscriptions are a flash in the pan or if they have lasting power may depend on how this issue gets resolved.</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkwMzM1ODc0ODQyNTAyNTQ4/fiat-morals-angel-devil.png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Liquidators Of Sam Bankman-Fried’s Alameda Research Have Scavenged $110 Million Of Bitcoin After Losing Billions]]></title><description><![CDATA[Analysis by Arkham Intelligence indicates that Alameda's liquidators have managed to acquire slightly more than 4,000 bitcoin.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/sam-bankman-frieds-alameda-research-has-scavenged-110-million-of-bitcoin</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/sam-bankman-frieds-alameda-research-has-scavenged-110-million-of-bitcoin</guid><category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category><category><![CDATA[Business]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried]]></category><category><![CDATA[Bankruptcy]]></category><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[chainanalysis]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[BtcCasey]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 18:51:45 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkzMDI2MTUyOTY3NzEwNDE2/markets-trade-analysis-of-bitcoin-price.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p>Liquidators in charge of the recovery of assets for the <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/sam-bankman-fried-and-ftx-largest-crypto-fraud-history">now-disgraced Alameda Research</a> hedge fund founded by Sam Bankman-Fried currently control over $110 million worth of bitcoin held in various wallets, according to a report supplied by blockchain analysis firm <a href="https://www.arkhamintelligence.com/">Arkham Intelligence</a>. These wallets have been receiving BTC from exchanges and cold wallets as recently as March 2023, the report revealed.</p><p>The aggregation of these wallets provides insights into the liquidators' collection of BTC from Alameda's holdings. A recent transaction in April involved a 1 BTC test from Alameda's Merchant wallet. This BTC was later sent to a holding address now under the control of Alameda's Liquidators, known as 'Alameda Merchant 1.' Since the beginning of 2023, this address has accumulated 3,581 BTC, worth approximately $97.19 million at current prices.</p><p>The report states that “In total, Alameda’s liquidators have managed to secure 4,083 BTC (currently $110.81M) sourced from:</p><ul><li>Other Alameda Wallets: 34.94 BTC (currently worth $948.27K)</li><li>Deribit: 467.366 BTC (currently worth $12.68M)</li><li>WBTC Custodian: 2997 BTC (currently worth $81.34M)</li><li>Bitfinex: 298.027 BTC (currently worth $8.09M)</li><li>Unlabelled Wallets (possibly an Exchange): 286.7 BTC (currently worth $7.78M)”</li></ul><figure>
        <img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk4MzM5OTgxMjY0MDM3NzE3/image1.png" height="303" width="620">
        
        
        <figcaption>A screenshot from the provided report.</figcaption>
    </figure><p>“However, this is only a fraction of the BTC that Alameda controlled in the past,” the report noted. “Wallets connected to this network of Alameda’s BTC activity were worth at peak over $800M, with Alameda likely holding more BTC in Centralized Exchanges or unlinked Cold Wallets.”</p><p>Arkham Intelligence stated that it will continue to monitor the on-chain activity of Alameda’s liquidators.</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkzMDI2MTUyOTY3NzEwNDE2/markets-trade-analysis-of-bitcoin-price.png"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk4MzM5OTgxMjY0MDM3NzE3/image1.png" height="303" width="620" medium="image" type="image/png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Did The New York Times Publish Manipulated Footage Of A Bitcoin Mine?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Footage accompanying a New York Times article critical of Bitcoin mining appears to have been manipulated to reinforce the paper’s bias.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/did-the-new-york-times-manipulate-bitcoin-mine-footage</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/did-the-new-york-times-manipulate-bitcoin-mine-footage</guid><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[New York Times]]></category><category><![CDATA[Opinion]]></category><category><![CDATA[Bitcoin mining]]></category><category><![CDATA[Media]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Level39]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk4MzEzOTk0ODMyODQ4NDMw/alcoa-lake.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p><em>This is an opinion editorial by Level39, a researcher focused on Bitcoin, technology, history, ethics and energy.</em></p><p>Did The New York Times manipulate aerial drone photography for its recent article attacking Bitcoin mining, in order to make the air in Rockdale, Texas appear smoggy? </p><p>On April 9, 2023, the paper published its article, "<a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2023/04/09/business/bitcoin-mining-electricity-pollution.html">The Real-World Costs Of The Digital Race For Bitcoin</a>," which included attacks on Bitcoin miners who purchase energy through sanctioned <a href="https://www.ercot.com/services/programs/load/laar">demand-response programs</a> within the state’s energy grid.</p><figure>
        <img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk4MzEzOTk0NTY0NzQwOTQ5/comparison1.jpg" height="255" width="620">
        
        
        <figcaption><em>Sources: </em><a href="https://twitter.com/nytimes/status/1645551313068097537"><em>Twitter</em></a><em>, </em><a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2023/04/09/business/bitcoin-mining-electricity-pollution.html"><em>nytimes.com</em></a></figcaption>
    </figure><p>The article featured a sweeping <a href="https://www.tributemedia.com/blog/what-is-a-hero-banner">hero video banner</a>, which was also used as a still image for social media sharing, <a href="https://vp.nyt.com/video/2023/03/27/107205_1_bitcoin_wg_1080p.mp4">showing smog-filled aerial drone footage</a> over operations run by Bitdeer, a Bitcoin mining company that occupies a previously-abandoned aluminum smelting plant on the outskirts of Rockdale. However, evidence suggests that the footage may have either been <a href="https://youtu.be/oN-dFfRPEkg?t=95">manipulated</a> or lacks the necessary color grading that would have maintained photojournalistic integrity and adhered to ethical standards.</p><h2>Color Histograms And Image Manipulation</h2><p>Color histograms are <a href="https://www.bhphotovideo.com/explora/photography/tips-and-solutions/how-to-read-your-cameras-histogram">useful for analyzing the exposure and color balance of an image</a>. A color histogram is essentially a bar chart where the left side of the x-axis is black and the right side is white. The y-axis represents the number of pixels found in the image, for each part of the tonal scale between black and white. A properly exposed photograph, where the full spectrum of tonal blacks and whites are naturally found in a scene, will have <a href="https://digital-photography-school.com/histograms-your-guide-to-proper-exposure/">pixels that span across the entire x-axis, from left to right</a>. When color data fails to span the entire x-axis, it can show that either those tones were entirely unavailable to the camera sensor, or that manipulation was performed to purposefully omit those colors.</p><p>In the side-by-side comparison below, the color histogram in <a href="https://vp.nyt.com/video/2023/03/27/107205_1_bitcoin_wg_1080p.mp4">the aerial footage published by the Times</a> (left) has no pixels approaching the black point. This is particularly strange for footage that has bright sun and stark shadows that are clearly visible as the camera moves over the scene. When color parameters are enhanced and corrected (as shown below in the version on the right), a brighter and more stunning scene emerges.</p><figure>
        <img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk4MzEzOTk0NTY0NDc4ODA1/comparison-new.jpg" height="349" width="620">
        
        
        <figcaption><em>The </em><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Color_histogram"><em>color histogram</em></a><em> for the image on the left, </em><a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2023/04/09/business/bitcoin-mining-electricity-pollution.html"><em>featured on The New York Times</em></a><em>’ website, has a distinct gap between its color data and its black point, possibly indicating either an </em><a href="https://digital-photography-school.com/rescuing-poorly-exposed-photos-with-photoshop-levels/"><em>improperly exposed image</em></a><em> or </em><a href="https://youtu.be/oN-dFfRPEkg?t=95"><em>manipulation to add a smog effect</em></a><em>. The photo on the right has been color corrected, showing a normalized histogram with the full range of colors and indicating that the Times’ version seems to have been altered for effect.</em></figcaption>
    </figure><p>The hazy footage used by the Times may give readers a false impression that rural Texas air has been polluted by Bitcoin mining. Bitcon mines are fully electrified and, like <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Zero-emissions_vehicle">electric vehicles</a>, the mining facilities photographed by The Times have <a href="https://twitter.com/RiotPlatforms/status/1645473961004892162">zero Scope 1 carbon emissions. In other words,</a> there are <a href="https://youtu.be/JKXeeiCa5Wg?t=1266">no direct greenhouse (GHG) emissions</a> that occur from sources that are controlled or owned by the operators of the mines. Any indirect <a href="https://www.epa.gov/climateleadership/scope-1-and-scope-2-inventory-guidance">Scope 2 emissions</a> associated from mining’s energy use comes from the grid’s normal emissions.</p><h2>Reply Hazy, Try Again</h2><p><br>The alleged manipulation appears to have been indirectly confirmed by Jordan Vonderhaar, the freelance photographer who took the aerial footage in question. Vonderhaar published <a href="https://archive.ph/QVUQ9">another photo from the same drone</a> flight on his <a href="https://www.jordanvonderhaar.com">personal website</a>, showing that the weather was perfectly clear within moments of the hazy photo published by the Times. This clear photo, from a different angle, indicates that the missing color data in the hazy photo was not due to weather conditions.</p><figure>
        <img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk4MzEzOTk0NTY0ODA2NDg1/jordan-vonderhaar.jpg" height="369" width="620">
        
        
        <figcaption><em>Vonderhaar published a clear weather photo on his </em><a href="http://jordanvonderhaar.com"><em>personal website</em></a><em>, taken </em><a href="https://twitter.com/yeolddoc/status/1652079301553004545"><em>within minutes</em></a><em> of the photo that showed smog surrounding the same Bitdeer mine.</em></figcaption>
    </figure><p>Vonderhaar's clear and sunny photo was also featured on the <a href="https://static01.nyt.com/images/2023/04/11/nytfrontpage/scan.pdf">front page of the Times’ print edition</a> (from April 11, 2023), with a color histogram that had similarities to the one found in the smoggy photo — another extended black point. Normalizing the black and white points on Vonderhaar's portfolio image reveals vibrant colors and a sunny morning in Rockdale. Notice in the side-by-side comparison below that the Times intentionally cropped out some of the blue skies when it published this particular shot:</p><figure>
        <img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk4MzEzOTk0NTY0NjA5ODc3/sunny-comparison.jpg" height="332" width="620">
        
        
        <figcaption><em>The image on the left was published on the April 11, 2023, </em><a href="https://static01.nyt.com/images/2023/04/11/nytfrontpage/scan.pdf"><em>front page of the Times’ print edition</em></a><em>. In addition to cropping out the blue skies, it appears to have had its black point extended, to wash out colors, as </em><a href="https://youtu.be/oN-dFfRPEkg?t=95"><em>evidenced by the gap</em></a><em> between the color histogram data and the black point. </em><a href="https://digital-photography-school.com/rescuing-poorly-exposed-photos-with-photoshop-levels/"><em>Normalizing</em></a><em> the color histogram (right), brings out the full color spectrum.&nbsp;</em></figcaption>
    </figure><p>Vonderhaar’s photo on his portfolio site included full <a href="https://archive.is/Bqamk">Exif metadata</a> that shows details about the imaging, such as the fact that it was taken on the morning of February 28, 2023, at 8:02 a.m. in <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Raw_image_format">raw</a> format, with a DJI FC220, the <a href="https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/Category:Taken_with_DJI_FC220">camera supplied by the DJI Mavic Pro drone</a>.</p><p>Analysis of the shadows in the photo not only confirms this timing, but further analysis also indicates that <a href="https://vp.nyt.com/video/2023/03/27/107205_1_bitcoin_wg_1080p.mp4">the smoggy video footage</a> was taken <a href="https://twitter.com/yeolddoc/status/1652079301553004545">only nine minutes after</a> the photo that showed clear and smog-free air surrounding the mine. Yet, the golden hues from the morning sunlight and blue skies are completely missing from the hazy hero footage. That a perfectly gorgeous moment in Rockdale could suddenly become hazy, at all altitudes and distances only nine minutes later, is nearly impossible.</p><figure>
        <img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk4MzEzOTk0NTY0NDEzMjY5/shadows-timing-2.jpg" height="903" width="620">
        
        
        <figcaption><em>Footage filmed nine minutes apart shows both clear weather and smog. Photos by Jordan Vonderhaar (top, middle), </em><a href="https://shademap.app/@30.56217,-97.07004,17.18778z,1677592959182t,0b,45p,0m!1677589048364!1677630432709,qMzAuNTYyNDIwLCAtOTcuMDY5OTQx!30.56242!-97.06994"><em>Shademap</em></a><em> (bottom), via&nbsp;</em><a href="https://twitter.com/yeolddoc/status/1652079301553004545"><em>@yeolddoc</em></a><em>.</em></figcaption>
    </figure><p>Responding to allegations of manipulation, Vonderhaar — who described miners as “<a href="https://twitter.com/jordan_vondy/status/1645446668635058176">massive polluters</a>” — <a href="https://twitter.com/jordan_vondy/status/1645455851006640130">publicly stated on Twitter</a> that, “Nothing about the footage was doctored. It’s humid most mornings in Texas and when the sun rises you get low level haze. This is very common.”</p><p>Leaving aside for a moment that Vonderhaar appears to be admitting that he was perhaps intentionally seeking out hazy weather for his photojournalistic spread, the nearest <a href="https://www.ncei.noaa.gov/products/land-based-station/automated-surface-weather-observing-systems">automated weather observation station</a>, located at Hearne Municipal Airport — <a href="https://www.google.com/maps/dir/Alcoa+Lake,+Texas/Hearne+Municipal+Airport,+Crennan+Ln,+Hearne,+Texas+77859,+United+States+Crennan+Ln,+Hearne,+TX+77859/@30.7454462,-97.0029044,11z/data=!3m1!4b1!4m13!4m12!1m5!1m1!1s0x8644565ac202de19:0x7acb102f329d74aa!2m2!1d-97.0565663!2d30.5768948!1m5!1m1!1s0x8645cfa9fc4816af:0x37f2f4dc3c4a3e63!2m2!1d-96.6193961!2d30.8697362">40 miles to the Northeast</a> and well out of view of the aerial photography — <a href="https://weatherspark.com/h/d/145983/2023/2/28/Historical-Weather-on-Tuesday-February-28-2023-at-Hearne-Municipal-Airport-Texas-United-States">reported low-level fog</a> at that same moment. </p><p>Indeed, Vonderhaar's clear and sunny photo shows low-level fog on the distant horizon, many miles beyond Alcoa Lake. “Low-level” fog is not a high-altitude phenomenon, and sure enough, Vonderhaar's photo shows blue skies in the upper atmosphere and golden hues that are conspicuously missing in his smoggy footage, taken a few minutes later.</p><h2>Problems Uncovered</h2><p><br><a href="http://twitter.com/roryhighside">Rory Highside</a> — a VFX artist who has <a href="https://youtu.be/MT9PA5EvMuo">expertise in CGI video effects</a> — was among the first to notice problems with the footage that the Times had used. Analyzing the video and color histograms, Highside suspected that either the color grading was mishandled or the color balance <a href="https://twitter.com/roryhighside/status/1645726015233351680">had been manipulated</a>. One of the most noticeable issues was that the “black point” was extended, which is indicative of footage <a href="https://photo.stackexchange.com/questions/18821/how-to-best-methods-to-correct-washed-out-jpegs">that is washed out</a>. This was evidenced by the fact that, as colors approached black, there was a noticeable and unnatural gap between pitch black and the available color data where darker colors should be. Vonderhaar did not respond to these allegations on Twitter, and did not respond to questions about them by email.</p><figure>
        <img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk4MzEzOTk0NTY0NTQ0MzQx/manipulation.jpg" height="289" width="620">
        
        
        <figcaption><em>Analysis </em><a href="https://twitter.com/roryhighside/status/1645726015233351680"><em>by Rory Highside</em></a><em> of Vonderhaar’s Times footage.</em></figcaption>
    </figure><h2>The Hazy Truth Of Photojournalism</h2><p>Determining truth in photojournalism is a murky endeavor. The raw footage captured by professional-grade digital cameras can be thought of as the digital version of undeveloped film. Camera sensors capture raw data, which <a href="https://www.loc.gov/preservation/digital/formats/fdd/fdd000241.shtml">retains maximum image information and flexibility</a> during post-processing, but requires processing and interpolation to produce an accurate final image. The photographer must adjust various parameters, such as contrast, white balance, exposure, and color saturation — meaning the photographer always has some artistic leeway in the final product. Color manipulations are trivial adjustments in post production. It only takes <a href="https://twitter.com/level39/status/1646204720963371014">one slight adjustment</a> to wash out an image. Minor adjustments are very common, and typically not an issue. But, at the end of the process, photographers have to walk a fine line between ​​enhancing an image for visual impact and maintaining its authenticity.</p><h2>Unedited Raw Drone Footage Is Visibly Hazy</h2><p><br>There is perhaps an alternate explanation for why Vonderhaar’s video footage was so hazy and lacking in contrast, while his still photograph taken nine minutes earlier was sunny and cinematic. The FC220 camera on Vonderhaar’s DJI Mavic Pro drone is <a href="https://www.dpreview.com/articles/4978813437/how-to-shoot-log-video-using-dji-s-d-log-color-profile">capable of capturing video footage in a logarithmic (log) color profile</a>. Raw log footage is a flat and low-contrast format — not intended for publishing — that preserves a wide dynamic range of details, which allows for greater flexibility during post-processing. Much like how <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Negative_(photography)">negative film</a> has inverted colors that enable positive images to be developed, log video footage <a href="https://youtu.be/pI9vIUwqLO0">always appears hazy when its raw, unedited format isn’t properly color graded</a>. It would be the photojournalist’s responsibility, then, to accurately map to the colors they witnessed in real life.</p><figure>
        <img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk4MzEzOTk0NTY0NDEyOTc0/color-grading.jpg" height="329" width="620">
        
        
        <figcaption><em>DJI drones can record in a logarithmic (log) color profile, </em><a href="https://www.dpreview.com/articles/4978813437/how-to-shoot-log-video-using-dji-s-d-log-color-profile"><em>which appears hazy if it isn’t color graded in post-processing</em></a><em>. Source: “</em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ccPJWVTdyA8"><em>Shooting In D-Log - DJI Mavic Pro</em>.”</a></figcaption>
    </figure><p>To convert log footage to an accurate color profile, a process called “<a href="https://youtu.be/o1m4LQu6BGQ">color grading” or “color correction” is typically performed</a>. This involves adjusting the image's color and tonal properties to achieve a more visually pleasing and accurate representation of the scene. <a href="https://www.dpreview.com/articles/4978813437/how-to-shoot-log-video-using-dji-s-d-log-color-profile">The proper conversion from log</a> involves mapping the tonal values in the log footage to their corresponding values, such as with lookup tables, or LUTS, to color grade the final footage.</p><p>Vonderhaar could very well have been telling the truth when he <a href="https://twitter.com/jordan_vondy/status/1645455851006640130">claimed</a> that “Nothing about the footage was doctored.” Indeed, publishing unedited log footage without proper color grading would quite literally result in a misleading smog effect, without having to do anything. Doing this deliberately, of course, would be unethical if it intentionally misleads viewers into seeing smog that did not exist.</p><p><a href="https://nppa.org/resources/code-ethics">Photojournalists have a duty</a> to maintain journalistic integrity and adhere to ethical standards to truthfully convey the events they witnessed. While there is no definitive "correct" color to any image, intentionally misleading readers by failing to color grade log footage is a breach of ethical standards. Photojournalists must depict the scene as faithfully as possible, avoiding anything that might distort reality. Publishing raw and uncorrected video footage, which actively removes colors from a scene and creates a misleading smog effect, is effectively a passive form of photographic manipulation. If not manipulation, then it is an egregious example of <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hanlon%27s_razor">Hanlon’s razor</a>.</p><p>It should be noted that Vonderhaar’s lack of color grading may not be due to malice or even artistic bias. While a professional photographer <a href="http://jordanvonderhaar.com">who has expertise in color correcting raw still images</a> to JPEG may possess a solid foundation in color correction and a good understanding of color theory, it does not automatically mean they have the necessary skills to color grade log video footage. Color grading log video <a href="https://youtu.be/DBo3zsQq6mY">involves a different set of skills and considerations</a> compared to <a href="https://youtu.be/mPvJkhnB4xg">color correcting raw still images</a>. Expertise in video editing software and a specific understanding of the technical aspects of working with video formats — such as frame rates, codecs and color spaces — is a requirement to adeptly work with log footage. Managing temporal continuity and ensuring consistent color grading is critical to maintaining visual coherence. It’s entirely plausible that Vonderhaar was simply unable to color grade log video. But, whether it be malice or inability, the Times should issue a correction.</p><h2>The Signature Style Of The Times</h2><p><br>The Times has a <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/photography/comments/jz4ver/what_creates_a_new_york_timesstyle_photograph/">signature style for its photographs</a>, where it typically&nbsp;extends the white point to darken&nbsp;images when it wants to portray a somber or moody tone. However, an extended black point — resulting in washed out colors — is the direct opposite of this iconic style.</p><figure>
        <img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk4MzEzOTk0NTY0Njc1NDEz/nyt-signature-style-histogram.jpg" height="476" width="620">
        
        
        <figcaption><em>The Times’ </em><a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2020/11/22/world/europe/russia-stalin-gulag-kolyma-magadan.html"><em>signature photographic style</em></a><em> uses an extended white point that slightly darkens the image.</em></figcaption>
    </figure><h2>The Ethics Of Photo Manipulation</h2><p>All photography requires some form of color correction. Minor stylistic choices aside, adjustments that actively mislead readers <a href="http://spj.org/ethicscode.asp">are unethical</a>. A <a href="https://archive.nytimes.com/lens.blogs.nytimes.com/2015/02/17/world-press-photo-manipulation-ethics-of-digital-photojournalism/">2015 article in the Times</a> about a World Press Photo research project, for instance, explained that photo editors cross an ethical line, which becomes explicit manipulation, when their processing obscures an image to create conditions that were not actually in the scene:</p><blockquote><p>“The only point at which processing becomes manipulation is when the toning is so great — usually by transforming significant parts of an image to opaque black or white — that it obscures substantial detail.”&nbsp;</p><p>–“<a href="https://archive.nytimes.com/lens.blogs.nytimes.com/2015/02/17/world-press-photo-manipulation-ethics-of-digital-photojournalism/">Debating The Rules And Ethics Of Digital Photojournalism</a>,” The New York Times</p></blockquote><p>According to Highside, the extent of the manipulation and our ability to restore the full color potential will remain unknown unless Vonderhaar releases his original raw footage. The Society of Professional Journalists (SPJ) recommends in its <a href="http://spj.org/ethicscode.asp">code of ethics</a> that journalists need to be proactive about addressing concerns and allegations of improper conduct:</p><blockquote><p>“Ethical journalism means taking responsibility for one’s work and explaining one’s decisions to the public. Journalists should: Explain ethical choices and processes to audiences. Encourage a civil dialogue with the public about journalistic practices, coverage and news content. Respond quickly to questions about accuracy, clarity and fairness. Acknowledge mistakes and correct them promptly and prominently. Explain corrections and clarifications carefully and clearly. Expose unethical conduct in journalism, including within their organizations. Abide by the same high standards they expect of others.”&nbsp;</p><p>–<a href="http://spj.org/ethicscode.asp">SPJ code of ethics</a></p></blockquote><p>Despite the missing color data, which can only be sourced from Vonderhaar’s unreleased raw footage, Highside was able to partially restore the washed out footage to demonstrate what the imaging could have looked like if a proper color grading had been applied. The results are striking when compared alongside the video that was published by the Times:</p><figure><iframe width="640" height="360" src="https://content.jwplatform.com/players/J0dequ6B-6eHuiRBi.html" allowfullscreen="" webkitallowfullscreen="" mozallowfullscreen=""></iframe><figcaption>New York Times Color Profile Comparison (; 0:27) </figcaption></figure><p>Intentionally deciding not to color grade or fully correct log footage is a breach of ethical standards in photojournalism. However, if it was due to lack of ability, it can still be considered a breach of ethical standards, particularly if the Times fails to correct the misinformation or take appropriate action to rectify the situation. A <a href="https://nppa.org/resources/code-ethics">fundamental principle</a> of photojournalism is to provide an accurate and truthful representation of events. Misrepresenting the visual aspects of a scene goes against this principle and compromises the integrity of the profession. It undermines the credibility of photojournalists and the publication, it damages the reputation of the profession and erodes public trust in the media.</p><p>It should not go unnoticed that the actual substance of the Times article included <a href="https://www.btcpolicy.org/articles/the-absurdity-of-the-nyts-latest-bitcoin-hit-piece">significant misinformation</a>. Why the Times <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/why-the-new-york-times-attacks-bitcoin">is seemingly motivated</a> to deliberately portray Bitcoin mining in such a negative light is unclear. But it&nbsp;appears to fit <a href="https://www.thegrayladywinked.com">a long pattern of distortions and bias</a> from the newspaper, which has become more evident to readers in recent years. When the public is being misled by photojournalists into believing a small and rural Texas town has thick smog typically found in populated and polluted cities, it’s necessary and appropriate to question the paper’s ethical choices.</p><p>Vonderhaar could clear up suspicions over his work by releasing the original raw log footage. This would allow members of the public to <a href="https://youtu.be/fG95ikKV_AE">properly assess the color grading of the footage and reveal the true details that were present</a>. If indeed the log footage was intentionally left in a low contrast state, it would be an embarrassment for the Times. </p><p><em>This is a guest post by Level39. Opinions expressed are entirely their own and do not necessarily reflect those of BTC Inc or Bitcoin Magazine.</em></p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk4MzEzOTk0ODMyODQ4NDMw/alcoa-lake.png"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk4MzEzOTk0NTY0NzQwOTQ5/comparison1.jpg" height="255" width="620" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk4MzEzOTk0NTY0NDc4ODA1/comparison-new.jpg" height="349" width="620" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk4MzEzOTk0NTY0ODA2NDg1/jordan-vonderhaar.jpg" height="369" width="620" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk4MzEzOTk0NTY0NjA5ODc3/sunny-comparison.jpg" height="332" width="620" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk4MzEzOTk0NTY0NDEzMjY5/shadows-timing-2.jpg" height="903" width="620" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk4MzEzOTk0NTY0NTQ0MzQx/manipulation.jpg" height="289" width="620" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk4MzEzOTk0NTY0NDEyOTc0/color-grading.jpg" height="329" width="620" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk4MzEzOTk0NTY0Njc1NDEz/nyt-signature-style-histogram.jpg" height="476" width="620" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Pro-Bitcoin Legislation Reigns Victorious In Texas This Year As The Legislative Session Ends]]></title><description><![CDATA[In addition to the Texas bills, the latest proposed debt ceiling deal did not include the Biden Administration’s proposed 30% tax on Bitcoin miners.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/legal/pro-bitcoin-legislation-reigns-victorious-in-texas-as-legislative-session-ends</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/legal/pro-bitcoin-legislation-reigns-victorious-in-texas-as-legislative-session-ends</guid><category><![CDATA[Regulation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Mining]]></category><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[Legislation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Texas]]></category><category><![CDATA[Legal]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[BtcCasey]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 20:56:39 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTg1MDk0MzA2Njg2NjQxNDk3/img_7058.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p>Bitcoin policy advocates celebrated several victories in the recent quarter, including the success of Texas SB 1929, a pro-mining bill, and the defeat of Texas SB 1751, an anti-mining bill. VP of Research at Riot Platforms Pierre Rochard <a href="https://twitter.com/BitcoinPierre/status/1663587667764736001?s=20">expressed gratitude</a> to everyone involved, stating, "Texas will continue to be #Bitcoin country!"</p><p>These legislative outcomes will contribute to the growth and stability of Bitcoin mining operations in Texas. As Brian Morgenstern, head of public policy at Riot Platforms <a href="https://twitter.com/MorgensternNJ/status/1663601172651835425?s=20">reported</a>, SB 1751 did not pass, ensuring the continuation of the state's usage of Bitcoin miners’ flexibility in balancing and stabilizing the power grid. </p><p>In contrast, SB 1929 successfully passed, establishing a registration process for Bitcoin miners to share information with ERCOT, enhancing transparency and grid reliability. Additionally, HB 591 was approved, providing a tax incentive for utilizing gas that would otherwise be flared into the atmosphere for on-site Bitcoin mining, promoting emissions reduction.</p><p>Another significant development was the passing of HB 1666, which introduced a proof-of-reserves regime, positioning Texas as a leader in building confidence within the digital asset ecosystem. These legislative achievements reflect the collaborative efforts of various stakeholders and industry participants, including Riot Platforms, The Texas Blockchain Council and the Chamber of Digital Commerce according to Morgenstern.</p><p>In addition to these developments, public miner stocks also surged on the news that the U.S. debt ceiling deal may be finalized soon, and that it does not include President Joe Biden’s <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/legal/biden-administration-proposes-30-tax-on-energy-used-by-bitcoin-miners">proposed 30% tax</a> on energy used for Bitcoin mining. </p><p>While these successes mark important milestones, advocates acknowledge that their work is far from over. But the Bitcoin community remains optimistic about the future and the continued growth of the industry, with the positive outcomes achieved in Texas during this legislative session setting a favorable precedent for Bitcoin-related policies and innovation in the United States.</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTg1MDk0MzA2Njg2NjQxNDk3/img_7058.png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Paxful Announces Appointment Of Interim CEO Roshan Dharia]]></title><description><![CDATA[Dharia will act as CEO as the exchange continues its transition from previous leadership under Ray Youssef.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/paxful-announces-appointment-of-interim-ceo-roshan-dharia</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/paxful-announces-appointment-of-interim-ceo-roshan-dharia</guid><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[CEO]]></category><category><![CDATA[Paxful]]></category><category><![CDATA[Exchanges]]></category><category><![CDATA[peer to peer]]></category><category><![CDATA[Business]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[BtcCasey]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 20:12:51 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTg4MTEzNjMyOTkzNzQ4ODg1/img_0295.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p><a href="http://paxful.com/">Paxful</a>, a global peer-to-peer Bitcoin platform, has announced the appointment of Roshan Dharia as the new Interim Chief Executive Officer, effective immediately. This comes after a<a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/peer-to-peer-bitcoin-exchange-paxful-suspends-marketplace"> brief shutdown period</a> of the exchange prior to the departure of Co-Founder and former CEO Ray Youssef.</p><p>According to a press release sent to Bitcoin Magazine, Dharia will be responsible for strengthening operations and exploring strategic alternatives for the company. With years of experience in similar roles, Dharia expressed his enthusiasm, stating, "It's a great honor to become CEO of Paxful. Over the last eight years, Paxful has been a pioneer in establishing the real use cases of Bitcoin and helping millions of people in the process."</p><p>Previously a senior executive at TrustToken (now known as Archblock), Dharia led the DeFi institutional lending business. He also founded and built the investment platform PTHL Affiliates, specializing in distressed private company acquisitions and turnarounds. </p><p>Srinivas Raju, the Custodian of Paxful, expressed his confidence in Dharia's leadership, stating, "I'm delighted that Roshan has joined Paxful and will take over day-to-day management of the company. I'm confident under his leadership the business will keep building a financial system that truly serves the 100%."</p><p>Youssef’s recent departure at Paxful was <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/04/08/drugs-erratic-dismissals-and-feuding-founders-behind-bitcoin-marketplace-paxfuls-unraveling/">reportedly</a> a result of a feud involving a myriad of accusations and legal disputes with co-founder Artur Schaback, who is currently the COO of the exchange.</p><p>Since its establishment in 2015, Paxful has experienced significant growth, attracting over 12 million users worldwide and facilitating billions of dollars in trades on its platform, according to the press release.&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTg4MTEzNjMyOTkzNzQ4ODg1/img_0295.png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stablecoin Issuer Tether To Begin Bitcoin Mining Operations In Uruguay]]></title><description><![CDATA[The company behind the most widely used U.S. dollar stablecoin is set to enter the mining industry through collaborations in Uruguay.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/stablecoin-issuer-tether-to-begin-bitcoin-mining-operations-in-uruguay</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/stablecoin-issuer-tether-to-begin-bitcoin-mining-operations-in-uruguay</guid><category><![CDATA[Mining]]></category><category><![CDATA[Uruguay]]></category><category><![CDATA[Tether]]></category><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[Business]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[BtcCasey]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 19:23:08 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkyMDI3NjE5NTEwNzI0MzAy/solar-bitcoin-mining-miners.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p>Tether, the company behind the widely popular USD stablecoin, has announced its foray into energy production and sustainable Bitcoin mining operations in Uruguay. According to the<a href="https://tether.to/en/tether-invests-in-energy-production-and-sustainable-bitcoin-mining-in-uruguay/"> announcement</a>, Tether’s collaboration with a local licensed company marks the company’s expansion into the energy sector as part of its goal to become a global tech leader.&nbsp;</p><p>By investing in renewable energy sources, Tether said it aims to support and promote sustainable Bitcoin mining, ensuring a “minimal ecological footprint while upholding the security and integrity of the Bitcoin network.” Paolo Ardoino, CTO of Tether, emphasized the company's commitment to renewable energy, stating, "Tether is proud to spearhead a movement that combines cutting-edge technology, sustainable practices, and financial innovation." </p><p>Uruguay has gained recognition as a leader in renewable energy, with an impressive 94% of electricity generation sourced from renewable sources such as wind and solar power according to the announcement. The country's favorable conditions for renewable energy production, including wind farms, solar parks and hydropower projects, make it an ideal location for Tether's sustainable mining operations. The company also stated that Uruguay's robust and reliable grid system further ensures efficient and sustainable mining activities.</p><p>Tether is actively seeking experts in the energy sector to join its team and contribute to this innovative project. For more information on Tether's energy initiative and potential career opportunities, interested individuals can visit their website at <a href="https://tether.recruitee.com/energy">tether.recruitee.com/energy</a>.&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkyMDI3NjE5NTEwNzI0MzAy/solar-bitcoin-mining-miners.png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Sabre56 Announces New Partnership With GEM Mining To Host More Than 4,500 Bitcoin Miners]]></title><description><![CDATA[The partnership will see half of the machines come online in Wyoming by May, with the other half coming the next month.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/sabre56-announces-new-partnership-with-gem-mining</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/sabre56-announces-new-partnership-with-gem-mining</guid><category><![CDATA[Mining]]></category><category><![CDATA[Business]]></category><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[Partnership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Wyoming]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[BtcCasey]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 17:16:08 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTgzMjM5NTgzMDQxODU2NTUw/img_4392.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p>Sabre56, a Bitcoin mining hosting provider and digital asset mining consultancy, has announced a significant hosting deal with GEM Mining, an institutional-grade Bitcoin mining company. The agreement entails Sabre56 hosting 4,510 BTC miners that belong to GEM in its newly constructed facilities in Wyoming. Half of the miners will come online in May, with the remaining miners joining in June. This deal marks a significant milestone for Sabre56 as it transitions from consulting on mining projects to constructing and hosting its own facilities.</p><p>The CEO of Sabre56, Phil Harvey, expressed his enthusiasm for the partnership with GEM Mining, emphasizing their shared values and dedication to advancing the mining industry. Harvey stated, "Sabre56 is rapidly implementing a strategic shift to build full-service hosting facilities with the highest technical and environmental standards ... This initial placing of 4,510 machines by GEM Mining proves our ability to support the market's most mature players and provide industry-leading hosting solutions."</p><p>GEM Mining's CEO, John S. Warren, echoed the sentiment, emphasizing the importance of finding a partner like Sabre56 that operates in a similarly efficient manner. Warren commented, "We are delighted to place our machines with a hosting provider of such outstanding capabilities."</p><p>According to a press release sent to Bitcoin Magazine, Both Sabre56 and GEM Mining are committed to environmentally responsible growth, with Sabre56's facilities adhering to strict regulatory standards. The data centers are built for maximum energy efficiency, the announcement states, and the companies work in cooperation with utility providers, allowing for load shedding to benefit the grids they operate on.</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTgzMjM5NTgzMDQxODU2NTUw/img_4392.png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Bitcoin Standard Author Saifedean Ammous Joins El Salvador’s National Bitcoin Office As Economic Advisor]]></title><description><![CDATA[Ammous’ expertise in Bitcoin and economics will be a valuable addition to the Bitcoin Office’s mission.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/el-salvador-bitcoin-news/saifedean-ammous-joins-el-salvadors-bitcoin-office-as-economic-advisor</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/el-salvador-bitcoin-news/saifedean-ammous-joins-el-salvadors-bitcoin-office-as-economic-advisor</guid><category><![CDATA[El Salvador]]></category><category><![CDATA[Saifedean ammous]]></category><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[the bitcoin standard]]></category><category><![CDATA[el salvador]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[BtcCasey]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 15:38:45 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkxOTg4NDM3NTk3ODg5OTkx/20220830_better-the-four-pillars-of-bitcoin-adoption---stefan-ristic.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p>Dr. Saifedean Ammous, prominent economist and author of "The Bitcoin Standard," is poised to take on a new role as an Economic Advisor to El Salvador's Bitcoin Office. This appointment comes after El Salvador made history by becoming the first country to adopt <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/el-salvador-to-declare-bitcoin-as-legal-tender">bitcoin as legal tender</a> in September 2021.</p><p>“Having Saifedean Ammous on team El Salvador is fantastic,” Max Keiser, Senior Bitcoin Advisor to the country said in a statement to Bitcoin Magazine. “Ammous brilliantly captured the role of Bitcoin as, ‘The alternative to Central Banking’ in his now classic, ‘The Bitcoin Standard’ as well as the philosophy of Bitcoin including popularizing the idea of 'time preference' as a life-hack. This news makes me very happy.”</p><p>Ammous, known for his expertise in Bitcoin and monetary economics, is expected to provide valuable guidance and insights to the Bitcoin Office as it navigates the implementation and integration of Bitcoin into the country's economy. His extensive knowledge and research on the subject have earned him recognition within the community and beyond.</p><p>The Bitcoin Law, proposed by El Salvador's President Nayib Bukele and approved by the Legislative Assembly, has set the stage for a new era in the country's financial landscape. With Ammous joining as an Economic Advisor, El Salvador aims to leverage his expertise to maximize the benefits and address potential challenges associated with adopting bitcoin as legal tender.</p><p>The Bitcoin Office, established to oversee the implementation of the Bitcoin Law, will likely benefit from Ammous' insights on monetary policy, sound money principles and the potential economic implications of embracing a decentralized digital currency. His appointment signals El Salvador's commitment to incorporating expert opinions into their strategy and decision-making process.</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkxOTg4NDM3NTk3ODg5OTkx/20220830_better-the-four-pillars-of-bitcoin-adoption---stefan-ristic.png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Umbrel Announces New Umbrel Home Plug-And-Play Server]]></title><description><![CDATA[The new Umbrel Home comes with a 2TB SSD and outperforms Raspberry Pi 4-based servers in many capacities.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/umbrel-announces-new-umbrel-home-plug-and-play-server</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/umbrel-announces-new-umbrel-home-plug-and-play-server</guid><category><![CDATA[Nodes]]></category><category><![CDATA[Business]]></category><category><![CDATA[Hardware]]></category><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[umbrel]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[BtcCasey]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 13:35:38 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkzMjU1NjA1NDIxNjE0NjU5/city-of-the-future.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p><a href="https://umbrel.com/">Umbrel</a>, the company behind <a href="https://umbrel.com/#umbrelos">umbrelOS</a>, has introduced a new home server solution called Umbrel Home with the intent of providing users control over their data, privacy and digital lives, according to a press release sent to Bitcoin Magazine. Priced at $699, Umbrel Home is aimed at making self-hosting accessible to everyone. By leveraging umbrelOS, users can eliminate the need for third-party cloud services by utilizing a wide range of self-hosted apps available in the Umbrel App Store including a Bitcoin/Lightning node, Nextcloud, Plex and Home Assistant.</p><figure>
        <img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk4MzExNzU4NDk3MDY0NDk0/umbrel-home---bitcoin-magazine-cover.png" height="388" width="620">
        
        
        
    </figure><p>According to the press release, Umbrel Home offers accelerated performance, featuring a 2.9GHz Quad-Core Intel CPU, 2TB NVMe SSD, 16GB dual-channel RAM, and an active cooling system while consuming just 10 watts of power. This compact home server outperforms a Raspberry Pi 4-based solution in terms of CPU performance, SSD read and write speeds, RAM and memory bandwidth the release states.</p><p>Mayank Chhabra, Umbrel's Co-founder and CEO, highlighted the company's vision for Umbrel Home, saying that "Building a plug-and-play home server that was specifically engineered for umbrelOS has been our dream since day one. With the recent challenges in Raspberry Pi pricing and supply chain, we knew it was time to bring our vision to life, set a new benchmark in self-hosting, and make it accessible to users of all skill levels."</p><p>With privacy and data ownership concerns on the rise, self-hosting presents a modern solution that allows users to take ownership of their data, storage, access and sharing. In addition, Umbrel Home’s zero-configuration and one-click app installations from the Umbrel App Store make it easy to build a customized ecosystem tailored to individual needs.</p><p>Pre-orders for Umbrel Home are now available on <a href="http://umbrel.com/">umbrel.com</a>, with shipping set to begin in June 2023. With its exceptional performance, user-friendly features and affordability, Umbrel Home aims to make self-hosting accessible to a global audience.</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkzMjU1NjA1NDIxNjE0NjU5/city-of-the-future.png"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk4MzExNzU4NDk3MDY0NDk0/umbrel-home---bitcoin-magazine-cover.png" height="388" width="620" medium="image" type="image/png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Filmmaker Alana Mediavilla On Bitcoin’s Energy Consumption, Education And Closing The Gender Gap]]></title><description><![CDATA[Filmmaker and entrepreneur Alana Mediavilla discusses her documentary “Dirty Coin,” misconceptions about Bitcoin’s energy use and more.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/alana-mediavilla-on-bitcoin-energy-use</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/alana-mediavilla-on-bitcoin-energy-use</guid><category><![CDATA[Education]]></category><category><![CDATA[Film]]></category><category><![CDATA[women]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Feature]]></category><category><![CDATA[energy consumption]]></category><category><![CDATA[Documentary]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Becca Bratcher]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkzOTk5NDg5MTkzODEzNTA5/bitcoin-domino.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p>It’s no secret that those who feel threatened by Bitcoin will attack it. Just a month ago, The New York Times published a malicious <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2023/04/09/business/bitcoin-mining-electricity-pollution.html">article</a> on Bitcoin mining’s energy usage. Senator Elizabeth Warren from Massachusetts has repeatedly attacked Bitcoin from a variety of angles, going so far as to launch an “<a href="https://www.politico.com/news/2023/02/14/elizabeth-warren-anti-crypto-ftx-00082624">anti-crypto army</a>” targeting Bitcoin as a hazard to consumers, all while misleading the public on the environmental impact of Bitcoin. </p><p>These verbal assaults are not isolated and the examples above represent only a small piece of the uphill climb Bitcoin has to mass adoption. To put it mildly, Bitcoin is disrupting countless industries, making centralized authorities fearful of losing their monopoly on money and the power that accompanies it. Bitcoin essentially “calls the bluff” on corrupt bureaucrats and infinitely-inflatable fiat currencies that further enrich those who own assets while eating away at the purchasing power of those living paycheck to paycheck. Because Bitcoin is location-agnostic and capable of utilizing flexible loads, it naturally increases demand for the cheapest energy sources, <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/bitcoin-uses-mostly-sustainable-energy">which are often stranded natural gas or renewables</a>. </p><p>So, why do many elected officials and companies attempt to denigrate and work to outlaw Bitcoin mining? Likely because their egos prevent them from understanding the value proposition of Bitcoin, but the facts speak for themselves. </p><p>Alana Mediavilla is a wife, mother, entrepreneur, business owner, filmmaker and Bitcoiner. She has a hell of a resume and a passion for storytelling. Armed with her knowledge of Bitcoin and skillset, Mediavilla decided to film and produce the documentary “<a href="https://www.dirtycointhemovie.com/">Dirty Coin</a>,” which highlights the value of Bitcoin mining while simultaneously busting the theory that Bitcoin mining is bad for the environment. </p><p>It was a privilege to hear her story and I know you will find her passion for Bitcoin inspiring.</p><p><strong>What is your professional background?&nbsp;</strong></p><p>I've been an artist and entrepreneur my whole life. Couldn't help it. Started my production company in Silicon Valley 11 years ago and got recruited to be a video producer at Google Cloud for almost five years while I moonlit still running my creative agency for other big tech folks. In 2021, I parted my full-time ways with Google to focus my efforts on my company and my own IP and films.</p><p><strong>How did you first learn about Bitcoin and what categorically drew you to it?&nbsp;</strong></p><p>I learned about Bitcoin during my daughter's ballet class in Campbell, California. A friend of mine that also had his daughter in the same class told me to buy as much as I could waste on bitcoin that week. He told me it would go up, so I degened into Bitcoin. That got me paying attention to it and when my Cuban grandfather told me he knew people sending bitcoin to Cuba, I dug into what the heck Bitcoin really was. What I found out blew my mind and continues to do so to this day.</p><p><strong>How do you typically respond to those who are dismissive of Bitcoin, especially those close to you?&nbsp;</strong></p><p>I make a feature documentary explaining my position to them XD.</p><p>It's understandable to be against Bitcoin. Crypto is a clown show and many don't see the difference between Bitcoin and shitcoins. Add to that that many people were raised with an energy scarcity mentality so having some crypto "hog all the energy" definitely sounds alarming. The issue is that this is just not the case. Is the industry perfect? Hell no! But are we scrutinizing the energy use of other industries the same way? Are we studied enough to know about the situations where having an energy-hungry industry like Bitcoin mining can be a good thing, as in the cases with flare mitigation or becoming a buyer of last resort in the middle of nowhere?</p><p>Understanding more factual information about the space can't help but create better conversations about Bitcoin.</p><p><strong>In your opinion, why is it important to close the gender gap in Bitcoin interest and adoption?</strong></p><p>Bitcoin is for everyone. Closing the gender gap is bringing diversity of users and advocates into Bitcoin. Women are particularly good at influencing their social circles and communities. More women in the Bitcoin space means more women advocating for Bitcoin in a grassroots way. We need all kinds of people to root for financial sovereignty and that starts with conversations around the dinner table that mothers are very often responsible for leading. Whether a woman is financially independent or supporting her partner who is taking on that responsibility for the family, women understanding the importance of Bitcoin means more support to other women, people in their community, and most importantly, their families.</p><p><em>This is a guest post by Becca Bratcher. Opinions expressed are entirely their own and do not necessarily reflect those of BTC Inc or Bitcoin Magazine.</em></p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkzOTk5NDg5MTkzODEzNTA5/bitcoin-domino.png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Memorial Day Reflections: Reinvigorating Critical Thought, Bitcoin Can Honor Service Members]]></title><description><![CDATA[For Bitcoiners, honoring service members on Memorial Day does not have to mean siding with the military industrial complex.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/bitcoin-and-memorial-day</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/bitcoin-and-memorial-day</guid><category><![CDATA[U.s.]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Military]]></category><category><![CDATA[Opinion]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Mickey Koss]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTgxNzU1NDUwOTE4NzczOTI2/us-america.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p><em>This is an opinion editorial by Mickey Koss, a West Point graduate with a degree in economics. He spent four years in the infantry before transitioning to the Finance Corps.</em></p><blockquote><p>“That was before my time… Of course it’s true, everybody knows it’s true.”</p></blockquote><p>The quote above is from the movie “The Sea Beast.”<em> </em>And although the film never mentions Bitcoin specifically, it might just be one of the best Bitcoin movies I’ve ever seen.&nbsp;</p><figure>
        <img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk3NTAzMTMyMTE5MzQ0MTM0/the-sea-beast.png" height="930" width="620">
        
        
        <figcaption><a href="https://twitter.com/BetterMovieBot/status/1626491739513974786/photo/1"><em>Source</em></a></figcaption>
    </figure><p>It is set in a fictional world gripped by perpetual war between a sea-faring economic power and a population of monsters who appear to attack ships out of nowhere. The hunters, the heroes of the story, patrol the seas in a near-constant state of combat, fighting to keep trade routes open and safe. In exchange, they are paid after presenting proof of their monster kills to the monarchy. </p><p>It was a fairly overt critique of the military industrial complex, though the deeper theme that I saw was the toxic effects that the media propaganda complex has on a society, reducing peoples’ ability to exercise discernment, and obscuring objective truth. </p><h2>Learn History Or Repeat It</h2><p>I think the reason why “The Sea Beast”<em> </em>had such an impact on me is because at its core, it is a story of what can happen to society when truth becomes obscured by revisionist history and propaganda. In the end, it was up to individuals to exercise discernment, and break the societal trance that had been propagating violence for generations. In the end, the rulers only ever had power because the people had allowed them to.</p><p>American culture and history is rich with individualism and critical thought, such as the idea that taxation without representation is immoral. This ideal <a href="https://constitutioncenter.org/blog/no-taxation-without-representation">ultimately led to the Revolutionary War which founded this country</a>. But now, people are afraid to have real and engaging conversations, especially in public, because it might be considered “wrong think” or offensive, ultimately leading to the cancellation of their public lives and digital exile.</p><div><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><a href="https://twitter.com/midyreyes/status/1629917053808148486"></a></blockquote><script async="" src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><p>Bitcoin reinvigorates many things, but the most important I think is the discernment of truth.</p><p>Bitcoin is fundamentally an exercise in regaining your power of discernment. One must sift through a slew of propaganda and fear, uncertainty and doubt (FUD) in order to learn the truth and see true value. The journey that one must take in order to truly understand Bitcoin necessitates discernment and critical thought. And once we reach a critical mass, the intransigent minority becomes entrenched in the culture.</p><p>Furthermore, once you are able to store your hard-earned wealth in a self-sovereign way, the courage to speak freely becomes self evident. No more are the worries of cancellation and debanking. The changes in time preference as well will likely increase your savings rate, making people more financially stable and less fearful of leaving or losing a job that may be holding them back. </p><h2>‘You Can Be A Hero But Still Be Wrong.’</h2><p>I know that many Bitcoiners criticize the military and governments especially. They detest war in all its forms and hope to bring about the end of it with the dawn of a new, hard-money standard. This is, of course, a worthy goal. But I must urge Bitcoiners to separate the service members from the policy decisions they are charged with executing. </p><p>According to analysis from Jordan Peterson that I have seen, one of the main reasons individuals join the military is the desire to find meaning and purpose in life. Peterson argues that young men often lack a clear sense of direction and purpose, and the structure and discipline of military life can provide them with a sense of belonging and fulfillment. Additionally, the military can offer opportunities for personal growth, challenge and adventure, as well as providing a sense of pride and accomplishment.</p><p>Many have died in the pursuit, hence the day of remembrance that we celebrate on Memorial Day. And yet, some much-needed criticism has been quashed in the name of the troops. </p><p>The line, “You can be a hero and still be wrong” from “The Sea Beast” was especially striking in this context. Without the ability to see objective facts, it is difficult to ascertain objective truth. Discernment is a skill, a skill that has atrophied drastically throughout society in the passing years. It is perhaps one of the reasons why cries for the government to protect us have grown so loud.</p><div><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><a href="https://twitter.com/mindingottawa/status/1629959701227077633"></a></blockquote><script async="" src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><p>There is no truth without debate and disagreement, characterizations of which have been elevated from being uncomfortable to becoming outright unsafe. And yet, creeping protectionism has its costs as well; the slow erosion of freedoms that we may never get back. The very freedoms that many service members have died to protect, the very service members who we are charged with remembering on Memorial Day. </p><p>If we are to remember and honor those sacrifices, perhaps the best way to do so in the current age is to exercise our discernment. Critical thinking is a skill that can be learned, or relearned in certain cases. Bitcoin helps those seeking to regain responsibility in their lives, and yes, exercise some critical thinking in order to discern fact from fiction, propaganda from news. </p><p>Bitcoin reinvigorates critical thought, critical thought leads to truth. Some have the humility to accept it. Others have to be slapped across the face with it, ultimately experiencing the pain of ego death. Truth is the only way to honor the fallen. Have the courage to choose truth, and live not by lies. </p><p><em>This is a guest post by Mickey Koss. Opinions expressed are entirely their own and do not necessarily reflect those of BTC Inc or Bitcoin Magazine.</em></p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTgxNzU1NDUwOTE4NzczOTI2/us-america.jpg"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk3NTAzMTMyMTE5MzQ0MTM0/the-sea-beast.png" height="930" width="620" medium="image" type="image/png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[How Bitcoin Can Preserve The Life Savings Of Refugees]]></title><description><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s unique properties make it the best way to preserve wealth in a time of crisis. But there are some things to keep in mind to prepare.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/how-bitcoin-can-preserve-refugees-savings</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/how-bitcoin-can-preserve-refugees-savings</guid><category><![CDATA[Opinion]]></category><category><![CDATA[refugees]]></category><category><![CDATA[War]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Custody]]></category><category><![CDATA[Saving]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Josef Tětek]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk0MjMxNzYxODMwNDIyMDIx/security-lock-and-fingerprint-key.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p><em>This is an opinion editorial by Josef Tětek, a Bitcoin analyst at Trezor.</em></p><p>Suppose you lead an ordinary family life in an undisclosed country. Suddenly, a crisis hits. This could be the rise of an autocratic regime, a democide or an armed conflict. Whatever the circumstances, you will most likely have two pressing problems on your mind. First and foremost, you need to get everyone to safety, preferably abroad. Second, you need to preserve as much of your savings as possible to set up your life elsewhere. Since a safe escape from a disaster-stricken country depends heavily on individual circumstances, this article will focus on a savings preservation strategy that is globally applicable.</p><h2>Preserving Your Savings The Traditional Way</h2><p>Protecting the value of one’s savings while fleeing a country has never been easy. Those fortunate enough to have had any wealth before a crisis strikes may find it difficult to save it when there is a sudden need to leave the country.</p><h3>Real Estate</h3><p>So, you own your house, and chances are that you have benefited greatly from the easy money policies of the past decade as it has grown a lot in value over the years. You may be moderately well off on paper, but how easy is it to actually turn your house into money in a short time frame? The market demand might be heavily impacted by the very crisis that is forcing you to flee — for example in a case of foreign invasion, the demand for houses in the affected region will come to a halt, while the number of homeowners looking to sell will skyrocket. So, unless you foresaw a crisis looming ahead and sold before others, chances are you won’t be able to extract much of your home’s value when you need it the most.</p><h3>Savings In The Bank</h3><p>But let’s say you had good foresight and sold your house in time. Now you have a lot of money in the bank. Again, if the crisis affects the entire country, chances are you won't be able to withdraw or move your money fast enough. There are many examples in history where a "bank holiday" was announced and depositors were denied their money when they needed it the most. One of the more recent examples comes from Lebanon, where <a href="https://apnews.com/article/financial-services-lebanon-business-8ca0f73931d60e36c1dd7d40e77c25de">banks simply shut their doors and ATMs</a> to prevent clients from withdrawing their money in the midst of an ongoing economic crisis. If you think you can protect yourself against a national currency’s devaluation by owning a dollar account, you better think twice: In Lebanon, the dollar accounts were forcefully converted to a Lebanese pound that had <a href="https://apnews.com/article/financial-services-lebanon-business-8ca0f73931d60e36c1dd7d40e77c25de">lost 97% of its value against the dollar since 2019</a>. In fact, bank accounts may not be safe anywhere, as banks around the world operate in fractional-reserve mode, making them vulnerable to runs and subsequent collapses. Recent collapses of a <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/03/17/regulators-shut-down-banks-raising-questions-about-neutrality/?sh=ddc2b5b71853">trio of U.S. banks</a> — Silvergate Bank, Signature Bank and Silicon Valley Bank — have proven this vulnerability.</p><p>However, it's worth noting that there is usually a several days’ delay between an emerging crisis and a full-blown bank holiday. If you suspect that banks might prohibit you from accessing your money soon, you can use this window of opportunity to withdraw your money in the form of cash or quickly convert it into bitcoin while it's still possible.</p><h3>Cash</h3><p>Let’s say you withdrew all of your money and kept it in cash. Hopefully, it’s in dollars or euros, as otherwise it might be hard to find a use for your local currency abroad, especially if the crisis that forced you to leave impacts the exchange rate, as it often does — the Ukrainian hryvnia<a href="https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/ukraines-central-bank-devalues-hryvnia-by-25-against-us-dollar-2022-07-21/"> has devalued by 25%</a> since the start of the Russian invasion. </p><p>Traveling with large amounts of dollars or euros also involves risks, though. The first of those is a risk of theft, either by common criminals or corrupt border patrols. The second risk is that, if you’re traveling with cash worth more than $10,000 or the equivalent in euros, you need to declare them when crossing the borders of many countries, <a href="https://help.cbp.gov/s/article/Article-195?language=en_US">including the U.S.</a> Failure to declare can result in the confiscation of the full amount. </p><p>Did you know that the U.S. customs guards confiscate more than $200,000 from travelers <a href="https://www.cbp.gov/newsroom/local-media-release/dulles-cbp-officers-seize-over-350k-during-14-currency-reporting">on average every day</a>? And if you do in fact declare that you’re traveling with large amounts of cash, you never know where that information might end up — sensitive data that is collected can also leak. For example, in 2020, there was <a href="https://thehackernews.com/2020/03/us-property-records-database.html">a major leak of detailed personal data</a>, including the property records of 200 million Americans. Criminals can use this data for targeted attacks.</p><p>Cash is also getting gradually useless in the western world. In the euro area, cash usage <a href="https://www.ecb.europa.eu/press/pr/date/2022/html/ecb.pr221220~62a7c988ef.en.html">fell</a> from accounting for 72% of all point-of-sale transactions in 2019 to 59% in 2022, and this trend is encouraged by governments that impose strict cash limits. So, even if you make it abroad with your savings in the form of cash, you’ll likely need to set up a bank account fast, which might not be a straightforward or easy task for a new migrant.</p><h3>Gold</h3><p>Gold used to be the most popular way to transfer value intact in the past, given that it has a worldwide demand and can be sold at relatively little discount (assuming investment-grade coins or bars are being used). Gold is also quite dense in value, as the price of 1 kilogram of gold is <a href="https://www.chards.co.uk/gold-price/weekly-gold-price-usd-per-kilo">around $60,000 at the time of this writing</a>. Otherwise, it faces the same risks as cash as it can be easily stolen along the way. Moreover, gold isn’t accepted as a means of payment and isn’t divisible, so you’d need to exchange your full coins or bars into the local currency after you arrive in your destination country.</p><h3>Stocks And Bonds</h3><p>Stocks and bonds are great fair-weather instruments, but they might become as useless as bank accounts when things get hairy. Local stocks and bonds will likely be worthless abroad and their value might be impacted by the given crisis. International financial instruments (e.g., U.S.-based exchange-traded funds) would fare better, though such instruments aren’t available in most parts of the world. And even if they are available to you, access to these instruments may be affected by newly-imposed sanctions.</p><h2>Does Bitcoin Fix This?</h2><p>You might have noticed that all of the usual instruments for wealth preservation have common traits in the form of limited transferability and/or value tied to a specific location or jurisdiction. Physical instruments such as cash and gold always carry a risk of loss or theft along the way, while intangible instruments such as real estate, bank accounts and stocks are, for the most part, valuable only locally.</p><p>Bitcoin indeed fixes this.</p><p>First, bitcoin is intangible and is therefore very easy to transfer. You can either send bitcoin to anyone globally within minutes, or you can remember the recovery seed and literally carry the bitcoin in your head (though that carries its specific risks as well, as we’ll cover below). Compared to other intangible assets, such as bank or brokerage accounts, there is no counterparty risk — you never need to worry about your money becoming inaccessible due to bank holidays, institutional failures or newly-imposed sanctions.</p><p>Second, bitcoin is a global asset, and as such, its value isn’t linked to any specific jurisdiction. A good example of this fact is the <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/latest-china-ban-impacting-bitcoin">2021 bitcoin mining ban in China</a>, which seemed like a big deal at the time, since most bitcoin mining operations were located in China. Nevertheless, bitcoin miners simply moved elsewhere, and there was virtually no impact on the price (on the contrary, <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/how-china-ban-improved-bitcoin-in-2021">bitcoin reached new highs several months after the ban</a>). Bitcoin is a global asset, but unlike gold, it can be bought or sold in all kinds of ways — on regulated exchanges, on decentralized exchanges, in ATMs, or from person to person; and the chances are, you will face a minimum spread on your exchanges.</p><p>Bitcoin’s intangibility, zero reliance on third parties and global liquidity makes it a perfect candidate for savings preservation in critical situations.</p><p>So, what are the specific methods for using bitcoin when fleeing a country?</p><h2>Traveling With Bitcoin Safely</h2><p>The main concern when traveling with bitcoin is to eliminate a single point of failure. If you just write down your recovery seed and put it in your back pocket, you undertake a great risk, as anyone who sees, takes or photographs your recovery seed has the ability to steal all your bitcoin. To travel safely with bitcoin, you need to minimize the possibility of loss or theft. Below are some tips on how to tackle this problem.</p><h3>Bitcoin In Your Mind</h3><p>To keep access to your bitcoin, the only thing you need to do is remember your recovery seed i.e., an ordered list of English words that is either 12- or 24-words long. Remembering 12 words is obviously easier than remembering 24 words, so it’s advisable to go for that option (e.g., by generating your seed on a Trezor Model T, which supports this format). Use a memory-enhancement technique such as the <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Method_of_loci">memory palace</a>. If you’re traveling with your family, have all the family members remember the same recovery seed; that way, if someone forgets some of the words, you’ll still be able to reconstruct the full seed.</p><p>After you memorize your seed, try recovering your bitcoin in an offline wallet, preferably a hardware device (on Trezor devices, you can perform a<a href="https://trezor.io/learn/a/test-recovery-seed-on-model-t"> dry run recovery</a> that doesn’t wipe the device). Once you’re certain you have your recovery seed firmly embedded in your memory, wipe the wallet. If you want to carry your hardware wallet with you on your travels, make sure it is wiped, so that if you lose it or someone takes it away from you, there will be no possibility of its misuse.</p><p>On arrival, recover your bitcoin again in the wallet of your choice (make sure you type in your seed in an offline environment though!).</p><p>Don’t rely on your memory for longer periods. Traveling in an adversarial environment is the only situation when relying on your memory might be a good idea, but aim to minimize the time span in which you store your recovery seed in your head. For long-term storage, always write your seed down, or better yet, stamp or engrave it into steel (there are many products for this on the market; before you make a purchase, I recommend checking out <a href="https://jlopp.github.io/metal-bitcoin-storage-reviews/">Jameson Lopp’s stress tests</a>).</p><h3>Relying On Your Web Of Trust</h3><p>Another way to transfer your wealth via bitcoin is to simply send it as a bitcoin transaction to someone you trust. The person doesn’t even have to be in the country you aim to travel to; the important thing is that they will be able to keep your bitcoin safe during your travels, and send it back to you when you’re able to set up your new wallet in a safe environment. The most important factor here is trust. This may be off-putting to some (after all, we all know the mantra of “don’t trust, verify”), but the fact is that for some people this may be the way to go if they don’t want to rely on their memory and are certain that the person on the other side would never betray them. The person you’re sending your bitcoin to needs to be proficient in bitcoin, and ideally should own a well backed-up hardware wallet — after all, you don’t want them to hold your life savings on their mobile phones, right?</p><p>If you want to increase the security of this process, you can do so via a multisig wallet. Let’s say you set up a two-out-of-three multisig wallet and transfer your bitcoin into such a wallet. Now you can send one of the keys to Person A, the second one to Person B and carry the third one with you. Person A and Person B shouldn’t know about each other, so that there is no way to steal the bitcoin that is stored in this way. And if you lose your key during your travels, you will still be able to recover your bitcoin using the keys of Person A and Person B. You can set up your multisig wallet using Electrum, Sparrow or Nunchuk. To distribute the keys, make sure to use a secure, encrypted communicator such as <a href="https://support.signal.org/hc/en-us/articles/360007318911-How-do-I-know-my-communication-is-private-#:~:text=Signal%20messages%20and%20calls%20cannot,encrypted%2C%20private%2C%20and%20secure.">Signal</a> messenger (do not use Telegram, as it <a href="https://usa.kaspersky.com/blog/telegram-why-nobody-uses-secret-chats/27662/#:~:text=By%20default%2C%20Telegram%20chats%20do,about%20the%20secure%20chat%20option.">isn’t encrypted by default!</a>).</p><p>Alternatively, you can utilize a Shamir backup, a cryptographically-sound method for splitting your recovery seed into multiple shares (use time-tested wallets such as the Trezor Model T to do this safely). Let’s say you do a two-out-of-three Shamir backup — the next steps are the same as we described above with multisigs. It’s advisable to reinforce the security of your Shamir backup by setting up a <a href="https://trezor.io/learn/a/passphrases-and-hidden-wallets">passphrase</a> on top of it.</p><h3>Plausible Deniability</h3><p>Ideally, there should be no indication that you are a Bitcoiner. That means carrying no hardware wallets, having no Bitcoin stickers on your laptop or phone, not carrying any Bitcoin books and deleting any Bitcoin/cryptocurrency apps from your phone. Do not talk about bitcoin with strangers or the border guards. If someone asks a seemingly-innocent question about bitcoin or cryptocurrencies, act ignorant or just say that you think it’s a scam. Simply said, you should look and act as a “normie.”</p><h3>Do Not Rely On Exchanges</h3><p>Some readers might be tempted to use their bitcoin exchange account — after all, you can log into it from anywhere in the world, right? I personally strongly advise against relying on exchanges with any portion of your savings. Aside from frequent exchange failures (just in the last twelve months, we saw the collapses of <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/legal/ftx-files-for-bankruptcy-ceo-resigns">FTX</a>, <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/celsius-files-for-chapter-11-bankruptcy">Celsius</a> and <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/blockfi-files-for-bankruptcy">BlockFi</a>, and a <a href="https://blockworks.co/news/gemini-earn-users-lose-savings">freeze on Gemini Earn users</a>), the exchange may block your funds, for example, because of sanctions or logging in from an IP address in a "wrong" country. In short, if you hold your bitcoin on an exchange, you don't really own it.</p><h2>Not Just A Theory Anymore</h2><p>Bitcoin is already used as a means of preserving one's savings in times of crisis. In recent years, we have seen success stories of this kind from countries as diverse as <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/bitcoin-financial-freedom-in-afghanistan">Afghanistan</a>,<a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2019/02/23/opinion/sunday/venezuela-bitcoin-inflation-cryptocurrencies.html"> Venezuela</a> and <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/23/ukrainian-flees-to-poland-with-2000-in-bitcoin-on-usb-drive.html">Ukraine</a>. Due to its global liquidity and direct controllability, bitcoin is proving to be a valuable tool in critical situations. The more knowledgeable you are about the safe transfer of bitcoin, the better prepared you'll be in the event of such a situation arising.</p><p><em>This is a guest post by Josef Tětek. Opinions expressed are entirely their own and do not necessarily reflect those of BTC Inc or Bitcoin Magazine.</em></p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk0MjMxNzYxODMwNDIyMDIx/security-lock-and-fingerprint-key.png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[How I Preserve My Wealth With Bitcoin]]></title><description><![CDATA[“I will explain why I allocate a share of my wealth to bitcoin and how I see it as ideal for preserving the value of my net worth.”]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/how-i-preserve-my-wealth-with-bitcoin</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/how-i-preserve-my-wealth-with-bitcoin</guid><category><![CDATA[Opinion]]></category><category><![CDATA[store of value]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[inflation]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Konstantin Rabin]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk0NDg4MTA1ODc5NzQyMTI5/bitcoin-bank-vault.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p><em>This is an opinion editorial by Konstantin Rabin, a finance and technology writer.</em></p><p>Good ol’ bitcoin, the granddaddy of cryptocurrency, is increasingly being used as a reliable store of value for those looking to move away from the more established asset classes as it is continually proving itself as a solid <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/markets/inflation-hedge-bitcoin-surges-to-record-highs-as-cpi-soars">hedge against inflation</a>. </p><p>In fact, this is something I have been doing for some time now and, in this article, I will explain why I allocate a share of my wealth to bitcoin and how I see it as ideal for preserving the value of my net worth.</p><h2>Why Allocate A Share Of Your Wealth To Bitcoin?</h2><p>Despite the volatility and fear-mongering that is prevalently posterized when talking about bitcoin as a revolutionary investment vehicle, there is plenty to be said about why it is a valid contender in this market. It should be noted that no investor worth their salt would tell you to put your life savings into crypto, but there is plenty of upside potential for those looking to make long-term returns or preserve a portion of their wealth this way.</p><p>Let me just mention a few of these advantages that make this investment in bitcoin worth looking more deeply into:</p><ul><li>Alternative store of value: Bitcoin is as good as it gets when looking for a store of value outside of third-party manipulation. Being decentralized means that it circumvents many of the red-tape aspects and fees that come with leaving your money in the hands of financial institutions. As a result, it is not subject to the same inflationary pressures that are so prevalent with companies operating in the government-controlled fiat currency system.</li><li>Potential for long-term growth: There is no doubt that bitcoin's value is extremely volatile in the short term, but its long-term trend has historically been a fairly bullish affair. The idea of <a href="https://www.investopedia.com/terms/h/hodl.asp">HODLing</a> comes into play here, as you will really only be able to see the true value of your investment when ignoring the spikes and holding on for dear life.</li><li>Diversification: As I said before, investing in bitcoin does not mean that you dump all of your hard-earned eggs into the chaotic basket that is crypto, but you can provide some much-needed, future-oriented diversification for your investment portfolio. As <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/03/30/bitcoins-correlation-with-stocks-is-at-its-lowest-since-2021-as-investors-grapple-with-the-cryptocurrencys-narrative-shift.html">bitcoin's price is increasingly uncorrelated to those of traditional assets</a>, such as stocks and bonds, adding some of these digital coins to your portfolio can help spread out the overall risks that your investments might face from the old guard. In fact, what we have seen over the past few years is that bitcoin has become a new sort of semi-safe-haven asset class which many investors flock to the moment that old-school investment vehicles and fiat currencies come under pressure.</li><li>Accessibility: This goes down two lanes. On the one side, <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/qai/2023/02/14/how-to-invest-in-bitcoin-for-beginners/?sh=25ed62097697">investing in bitcoin is becoming easier to do</a>, with many platforms and exchanges now offering a simple and secure way to buy and hold your BTC; while at the same time, it has never been easier to liquidate this asset and get fiat cash in hand when the need arises. This scores a massive point over the stock, bond or real estate markets, which are forever plagued by liquidity issues; especially in times of large-scale financial instability.</li></ul><p>In the long run, spending a share of your income on BTC is unlikely to make you poor. On the flip side, not allocating anything to BTC might ruin your prosperity, especially in these uncertain times when <a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/what-caused-silicon-valley-banks-failure-2023-03-10/">banks can go bust without warning</a>,<a href="https://www.imf.org/en/Blogs/Articles/2022/09/09/cotw-how-food-and-energy-are-driving-the-global-inflation-surge"> inflation seems to be ever on the rise</a> and several countries <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/markets/as-peso-inflates-argentina-needs-bitcoin">witness their fiat currencies turn into toilet paper.</a></p><h2>Why I Don’t Buy Or Mine BTC</h2><p>In the pursuit of acquiring bitcoin, there are always the obvious channels of hitting up some form of cryptocurrency exchange or peer-to-peer marketplace and just exchanging fiat for BTC. While there is nothing wrong with this approach, and it might be the easiest and perhaps the only option for many people out there, it is, in my humble opinion, not the best way to get your coins for wealth preservation. </p><p>You could instead go the route of the miner and spend a large fortune on buying all the equipment needed to try and get some BTC that way, but in this day and age with the <a href="https://www.visualcapitalist.com/cp/the-cost-of-mining-bitcoin-in-198-different-countries/">average mining cost per coin being over $30,000 in many countries</a>, it is more likely that you will end up with zilch long before you ever mine your first coin.</p><p>So, what would I suggest? Earn it.</p><p>Sure, not everyone can convince their boss to pay them in bitcoin, but these days, many people have a side hustle that can easily be employed in generating some digital dosh. Five years ago, offering your clients the ability to pay in crypto for your services was a nonexistent concept, but <a href="https://www.statista.com/statistics/1290483/crypto-payment-acceptance-by-industry/">today, it is a no-brainer</a>. Right now, a large number of my clients, especially those operating in the online world, are really into paying for services via crypto. While most of them like to use stablecoins such as USDT, you can easily flip these over to BTC and keep padding your Bitcoin wallet.</p><p>One more notable online activity that I partake in to stack some BTC is for the over-18-year-olds only. No, I don’t mean OnlyFans. I do some work in and around the gambling industry and also enjoy a bit of a gamble myself from time to time, but I solely gamble for BTC. </p><p><a href="https://cryptobetting.net/online-gambling-industry-growth-infographic/">Bitcoin betting sites have been gaining traction lately</a>, thanks to their ability to protect privacy, offer deals (e.g., bonuses, commissions, etc.) and general improvements over the annoying bureaucracy inherent in fiat betting sites. Obviously, I don't recommend gambling to anyone, but this is something I enjoy occasionally, such as when my favorite UFC fighter jumps into the octagon, as it adds a bit of excitement while watching the fights, and obviously, the winnings are added to my wealth-preservation BTC fund. </p><h2>My BTC Wealth Preservation Strategy</h2><p>You might be wondering why I am hammering on bitcoin and not paying much heed to the rest of the crypto pack. Frankly, as <a href="https://www.cityam.com/price-of-bitcoin-slips-as-other-cryptocurrencies-follow-suit/">most of the top tokens are following the bitcoin price like a donkey chasing a carrot</a>, I don’t typically diversify things or allocate a share of my crypto investments into other major coins and tokens. Don’t get me wrong, I believe that some of the cryptocurrencies out there are useful, but, as bitcoin is what determines the value of many of the top dogs on the list, sticking with BTC as my investment coin just makes sense. (For those keen on diversifying into other crypto projects, I do have one bit of advice; stay away from meme and <a href="https://www.investopedia.com/terms/s/shitcoin.asp">shitcoins</a>.) </p><p>Now, let’s get down to business. Here is my advice for preserving wealth via bitcoin based on my own strategy:</p><ul><li>Plan: Whether you are investing with fiat currencies that you get from working a day job or getting paid directly in crypto via your own projects, make sure to have a well-defined goal. Set certain annual or even quarterly amounts that you would like to reach and try your best to make it happen. </li><li>Don't panic: Always work on increasing your BTC holdings and be ready to HODL until kingdom comes. Don't pay much attention to the fiat value and don't panic sell just because you see some of those crazy price swings that bitcoin is so famous for. It is all good and well to compare exchanges and cryptocurrencies, but do not sit there stressing about where the price of BTC is sitting. Short-term dips are bound to come and go, but if you believe in BTC as much as I do, then you can rest assured that your wealth is being preserved. Keep in mind that there are only 21M BTC available, ever. As this is a finite supply and the <a href="https://www.census.gov/popclock/world">world's population is close to eight billion</a>, with more people being added every day, the value of this asset is sure to increase over time as more governments and people take hold of this new shift in finance. If and when fiat finally goes completely bust and bitcoin takes over as the major currency, an average BTC per capita in the world is going to be around 0.0025, and you most certainly want to be in the top 5% of those holding it.</li><li>Keep it secure: Bitcoin is digital, and hackers are always on the lookout for those who are not keeping a watchful eye on their money. So, to preserve my wealth safely, I keep all of my bitcoin holdings in hardware wallets stashed in a safe place. There are plenty of good exchanges and hot wallets to choose from, but if you are serious about preserving your wealth, keep it cold, keep it offline.</li></ul><h2>Why You Shouldn’t Wait To Diversify</h2><p>Allocating a portion of your wealth to bitcoin can be an effective way to preserve it, and even grow it, but as the saying goes, “the best time to start is yesterday, the second best time is now.” </p><p>Don’t wait for <a href="https://fortune.com/2023/04/23/bitcoin-to-rally-past-50000-due-to-halving-process-say-crypto-analysts/">BTC to hit $50,000</a> before you suddenly wake up and start buying in. Set up a plan today and start diversifying your portfolio in this future-proof asset class, so you know your wealth is safe, no matter how bad your government might be.</p><p><em>This is a guest post by Konstantin Riban. Opinions expressed are entirely their own and do not necessarily reflect those of BTC Inc or Bitcoin Magazine.</em></p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk0NDg4MTA1ODc5NzQyMTI5/bitcoin-bank-vault.png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ordinals Is Bringing The NFT Industry To Bitcoin]]></title><description><![CDATA[NFT influencer and founder Farokh talked to Bitcoin Magazine about the future of Ordinals and Bitcoin NFTs.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/ordinals-is-bringing-the-nft-industry-to-bitcoin</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/ordinals-is-bringing-the-nft-industry-to-bitcoin</guid><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Inscriptions]]></category><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[Ordinals]]></category><category><![CDATA[NFTs]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[BtcCasey]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 20:19:23 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTgyMDU1MzM1MTk5MDU3MDI3/bitcoin-numbers.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p>The Ordinals protocol has taken the Bitcoin world by storm. Quickly amassing over 9,000,000 inscriptions, the new protocol allows for arbitrary data to be embedded on the Bitcoin blockchain. In addition to attracting attention from the NFT industry, Ordinals have led to a major increase in the fees required to send bitcoin, eliciting new debate on how Bitcoin should deal with <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/technical/bitcoins-high-fees-create-controversy-and-challenges">high fee environments</a>.&nbsp;</p><p>In a recent interview with Bitcoin Magazine, <a href="https://twitter.com/farokh">Farokh</a>, founder of the Rug Radio platform and a well-known collector within the NFT industry, shared insights into the world of Bitcoin NFTs and his vision for the Bitcoin inscription market’s future. Reflecting on his own Bitcoin and NFT journey, Farokh acknowledged the initial confusion surrounding Bitcoin in 2012, given the lack of development and user-friendly platforms at the time. However, he highlighted the rapid growth and development of NFT platforms in 2021, and how that is reflected now in the context of Bitcoin NFTs’ sudden rise in popularity.</p><p>When discussing the advantages of Ordinals, Farokh emphasized the security aspect of storing art on the Bitcoin blockchain, stating, "Ordinals now enable art to be stored on the most secure blockchain in the world, without keeping this data in external databases where it can be vulnerable to manipulation." He identified this as the biggest benefit of Ordinals over NFTs on other, less secure blockchains, recognizing the need for censorship-resistant and immutable storage solutions.</p><p>Regarding the future of Bitcoin NFTs, Farokh expressed his optimism. He also acknowledged the current challenges, such as high costs and the need for infrastructure development, but believed that with the continuous growth of the Bitcoin ecosystem, improved solutions would emerge.</p><p>Farokh also discussed the entry of luxury brands into the Bitcoin NFT space, mentioning the collaboration between <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/bugatti-and-asprey-announce-bitcoin-inscriptions">Asprey and Bugatti</a>. He expressed his curiosity about high-end brands embracing ordinals and leveraging the security and authenticity provided by the Bitcoin blockchain.</p><p>When asked about the reaction of projects transitioning to Bitcoin NFTs, Farokh noted the generally positive response. He drew parallels to the early days of NFTs, where skepticism was common but ultimately proven wrong. He also highlighted the positive reception of projects like <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/yuga-labs-introduces-first-bitcoin-ordinals-collection">Yuga Labs’ TwelveFold</a>, indicating that the acceptance of Bitcoin NFTs was gradually gaining momentum.</p><p>Looking ahead, Farokh envisioned a mature Bitcoin NFT market with user-friendly platforms accessible to retail users. He remarked, "Look how much the [NFT] marketplace has evolved ... at first, it was complicated to make a wallet. Now we have proper marketplaces." Farokh's optimistic outlook suggested a future where the Bitcoin NFT market becomes more mainstream and user-friendly, ultimately driving further adoption.</p><p>Overall, Farokh's interview shed light on the growing importance of Bitcoin NFTs, their unique advantages and the evolving landscape of the Ordinals protocol.&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTgyMDU1MzM1MTk5MDU3MDI3/bitcoin-numbers.jpg"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Core Version 25.0 Released Bringing New Features And Transaction Use Cases]]></title><description><![CDATA[Bitcoin Core users should be sure to read through the release notes before updating their software to the latest release version.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/technical/bitcoin-core-version-25-0-released</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/technical/bitcoin-core-version-25-0-released</guid><category><![CDATA[Bitcoin core]]></category><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[software]]></category><category><![CDATA[Updates]]></category><category><![CDATA[Technical]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[BtcCasey]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 16:22:14 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkzMjU1NjA1NDIxNTQ5MTIz/technical-bitcoin-development-pixel.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p>Bitcoin Core version 25.0 has been released, bringing new features, bug fixes and performance improvements to the software. Users can download the latest version from the official <a href="https://bitcoincore.org/">Bitcoin Core</a> website or update their existing installations. The release notes outline the changes and provide instructions on how to upgrade.</p><p>One notable change is the allowance of transactions of non-witness size 65 bytes and above, which opens up new use cases and enhances protections against vulnerabilities like CVE-2017-12842. Another addition is the scanblocks RPC, which allows for fast wallet rescans by returning relevant blockhashes from a set of descriptors.</p><p>In terms of RPC updates, all JSON-RPC methods now accept a new named parameter called "args" for passing positional parameter values conveniently. Additionally, the verifychain RPC will now return false if checks couldn't be completed at the desired depth and level, providing more accurate feedback.</p><p>The release also includes changes to the build system, updated settings and new features. For instance, the shutdownnotify option allows users to specify a command to execute before Bitcoin Core begins its shutdown sequence. In the wallet section, new options like minconf and maxconf have been added to various RPCs, providing greater control over UTXO confirmations.</p><p>Bitcoin Core 25.0 introduces several improvements and optimizations, enhancing the user experience and security of the software. As with any release, users are encouraged to report any bugs they encounter to the official GitHub issue tracker.</p><p>Bitcoin Core is widely supported and tested on major operating systems such as Linux, macOS, and Windows. However, it is not recommended to use Bitcoin Core on unsupported systems. Users should ensure they are running a compatible operating system before upgrading to the latest version. In addition, users are encouraged to review the release notes for a detailed understanding of the improvements in this version if upgrading.</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkzMjU1NjA1NDIxNTQ5MTIz/technical-bitcoin-development-pixel.png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tax Attacks Won’t Kill Bitcoin: Regulators Must Learn To Accept New Technology]]></title><description><![CDATA[Calling Bitcoiners “tax evaders” or imposing arbitrary tariffs can’t stop the inevitable progression of technology.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/bitcoin-tax-attacks-are-regulatory-fear</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/bitcoin-tax-attacks-are-regulatory-fear</guid><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Politics]]></category><category><![CDATA[Opinion]]></category><category><![CDATA[Taxes]]></category><category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Conor Chepenik]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTg3OTAzMzI3NzcyNjE1NzM0/a-bitcoin-tax-reporting-nightmare-is-coming-in-2023-.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p><em>This is an opinion editorial by Conor Chepenik, an organizer for the MassAdoption Bitcoin meetup.</em></p><figure>
        <img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk4MTczOTE3Njk1NzE0NDk0/brad-sherman-tax-evaders.png" height="601" width="620">
        
        
        <figcaption><a href="https://twitter.com/BradSherman/status/1653928972026093569?s=20"><em>Source</em></a></figcaption>
    </figure><p>Congressman Brad Sherman's recent tweet attacking Bitcoiners as "tax evaders" is a prime example of how Bitcoin has become a mainstream phenomenon. It's ironic that politicians like Sherman, who have sworn an oath to uphold the Constitution and the presumption of innocence, are so quick to label Bitcoin supporters as criminals without any evidence. Such remarks undermine the fundamental principles of justice and fairness that underpin our legal system. </p><p>The fact that politicians like Sherman are attacking Bitcoin serves as a signal to those on the fence that there may be something to this "freedom money" that is constantly under attack by those who are corrupt and compromised by legacy systems. In a way, even those who attack Bitcoin may be unwittingly working for its success and adoption.</p><p>And clearly, politicians are expecting Bitcoiners to shoulder some kind of tax burden that they do not impose on anyone else.</p><p>Imagine if a politician tried to tax people for using computational power to do math or use English to express their views. They would be ridiculed and mocked because, on top of that being an insane policy, both of these subjects are essential to a functional society. </p><p>Instead of imposing arbitrary taxes, the government should focus on creating a regulatory environment that supports innovation and economic growth. Unfortunately, in opposition to that seemingly-obvious edict, the Biden administration <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/legal/biden-administration-proposes-30-tax-on-energy-used-by-bitcoin-miners">has proposed a 30% tax on Bitcoin mining</a>, which is not only unfair, but also hypocritical to the values that make the United States great. </p><p>If a market participant has paid for their energy, they should be free to use it as they wish. So, why is Bitcoin mining being targeted when other industries, such as pornography, video games or gambling, also use energy to allow people to indulge in their vices online? I’m not vying for a tax on other industries. I firmly believe that if a market participant has paid for their energy they can do whatever they want with it. My intent is to point out that this proposal seems to be a clear example of government overreach and intervention in the private sector. </p><h2>Reacting To Change</h2><p>And it's not just Bitcoin mining that is being targeted. It is the entire Bitcoin network. When new and innovative ideas challenge the status quo, both humans and technology can exhibit resistance or embrace the change. Technology mimics many things about human biology, including the way we respond to change. Established industries or entities may resist new technologies to protect their own interests, just like how our immune system responds to foreign pathogens to protect our body. However, just as humans can adapt to changing environments, technology can also evolve and adapt to better serve our needs. People can either fight against Bitcoin or embrace it, but either way, this technology is changing the world rapidly.</p><p>It's important to remember that new technology, including Bitcoin, is not inherently bad, but rather a tool that can be used for both good and bad purposes. Instead of fighting against progress, we should embrace the opportunities that new technology provides and work together to shape a better future. Sherman's tweet may not win him any votes, but it shows his lack of understanding and respect for the rights of his constituents.</p><p>The comparison between a technology network and human biology may seem unconventional, but it provides valuable insights into the evolution and growth of new technologies like Bitcoin. Kevin Kelly’s book “<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/What_Technology_Wants">What Technology Wants</a>” highlights the importance of this. There are three quotes that really stood out to me:</p><blockquote><p>“Technologies do not exist in isolation, but rather in networks that amplify their power and reach.”&nbsp;</p></blockquote><blockquote><p>“Innovation is a team sport, and the best innovations are produced by networks of people working together.”</p></blockquote><blockquote><p>“The more interconnected our technologies become, the more emergent properties they exhibit, and the harder they are to predict or control.”</p></blockquote><p>Technology is always evolving based on human needs. It starts with a small idea and then grows into something larger than anyone could have imagined. This evolution is not always linear, as new technologies often emerge from existing technologies. These networks grow exponentially faster as new technologies enable stuff we never thought possible. FaceTime would seem magical to someone 100 years ago in the same way that a medical device that can regenerate limbs for people would seem magical in the modern day. I assume that type of technology will come someday and with it many more innovations that I could never have hoped to imagine until I saw them.</p><p>But, just like humans, technology has its own set of rules and laws. We have to follow these rules to make the most out of technology’s potential. Imagine if someone called a conference about <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Internet_protocol_suite">TCP/IP</a> a “conference for gang members.” It would seem ridiculous. Especially from a politician who should be encouraging innovation in their district. </p><p>Attacking people because they enjoy using a protocol is insane. However, if your job was dedicated to maintaining legacy technology and adopting new technology could make you irrelevant, I suppose you wouldn't react favorably toward the new technology either.</p><h2>Embracing The Evolution Of Technology</h2><figure>
        <img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk4MTczOTE3Njk1NzgwMDMw/college-tuition-prices-rising.png" height="587" width="620">
        
        
        <figcaption><a href="https://twitter.com/ConorChepenik/status/1653942571465416704?s=20"><em>Source</em></a></figcaption>
    </figure><p>In the end, we are all part of the network of technology, whether we like it or not. We must embrace the evolution of technology, and understand its potential to shape the world for the better. We are at the beginning of all the things that will be built on these new protocols, so it is up to us to harness their power and make the most out of their potential. </p><p>I can’t say I know for a fact that bitcoin is going well above $1 million, but I think it’s pretty damn possible and that, as more network effects get added, both in meatspace and cyberspace, the more likely it becomes.</p><blockquote><p>“When zero reached Europe roughly 300 years later in the High Middle Ages, it was met with strong ideological resistance. Facing opposition from users of the well-established Roman numeral system, zero struggled to gain ground in Europe.”&nbsp;</p><p>–Robert Breedlove, “<a href="https://breedlove22.medium.com/the-number-zero-and-bitcoin-4c193336db5b">The Number Zero And Bitcoin</a>”</p></blockquote><p>Now, the idea of not using zero in math is a non-starter. It seems highly likely Bitcoin will have a similar fate as zero and the idea of not using Bitcoin and all the things built on top of it will be preposterous. <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/nostr-and-bitcoin-can-change-social-media">Just look at Nostr, for an example</a>. There is no way the protocol would have thrived had it not been for both Bitcoin and Bitcoiners bringing so much value onto the network.</p><p>I believe a similar effect will take place for more innovations around the world, whether regulators understand Bitcoin or not.</p><p><em>This is a guest post by Conor Chepenik. Opinions expressed are entirely their own and do not necessarily reflect those of BTC Inc or Bitcoin Magazine.</em></p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTg3OTAzMzI3NzcyNjE1NzM0/a-bitcoin-tax-reporting-nightmare-is-coming-in-2023-.png"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk4MTczOTE3Njk1NzE0NDk0/brad-sherman-tax-evaders.png" height="601" width="620" medium="image" type="image/png"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk4MTczOTE3Njk1NzgwMDMw/college-tuition-prices-rising.png" height="587" width="620" medium="image" type="image/png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bankrupt Lending Platform Celsius Agrees To Purchase Bid By Fahrenheit]]></title><description><![CDATA[A new company will be formed by the acquisition of embattled lender Celsius, which went bankrupt amidst the larger turmoil of 2022.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/celsius-agrees-to-purchase-bid-by-fahrenheit</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/celsius-agrees-to-purchase-bid-by-fahrenheit</guid><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[Celsius network]]></category><category><![CDATA[Bankruptcy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Business]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[BtcCasey]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 20:38:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkxNDAxMTQ0NTc1MDc1ODcz/border-wallets-seed-phrase-recovery-top-photo.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p>Bankrupt lending platform Celsius Network LLC has announced that it has selected a proposal by Fahrenheit as the winning bid to lead the company out of bankruptcy, according to reporting by <a href="https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/crypto-lender-celsius-picks-fahrenheits-bid-bankruptcy-exit-2023-05-25/">Reuters</a>.</p><p>Celsius, which filed for <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/celsius-files-for-chapter-11-bankruptcy">Chapter 11 protection in July</a>, sought a buyer to manage its cryptocurrency lending and bitcoin mining businesses. The chosen consortium, Fahrenheit, includes Arrington Capital, a blockchain-based venture capital firm. In addition to the consortium acquiring the company, a new board of directors, primarily appointed by creditors, will oversee the new company formed as a result of the purchase.</p><p>Celsius also revealed that it has secured a backup bid from the Blockchain Recovery Investment Consortium (BRIC), a holding company affiliated with Gemini Trust, owned by the Winklevoss twins, ensuring an alternative option in case the deal with Fahrenheit falls through.</p><p>According to Celsius, Fahrenheit will provide the necessary capital, management expertise, and technology to navigate the bankruptcy. The consortium's selection indicates a potential positive outcome for Celsius and its creditors, allowing the company to move forward under new management and ownership.</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkxNDAxMTQ0NTc1MDc1ODcz/border-wallets-seed-phrase-recovery-top-photo.png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Payments App Bottlepay To Shutdown Services]]></title><description><![CDATA[The company is encouraging users to withdraw their funds and to save transaction statements before the app’s closure.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/bitcoin-payments-app-bottlepay-to-shutdown-services</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/bitcoin-payments-app-bottlepay-to-shutdown-services</guid><category><![CDATA[Business]]></category><category><![CDATA[Payments]]></category><category><![CDATA[Bottlepay]]></category><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[Apps]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[BtcCasey]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 17:36:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk0MzI5NzY4OTU4MTA5MzYx/bitcoin-code.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p><a href="https://bottlepay.com/">Bottlepay</a>, a popular consumer app for Bitcoin transactions, has <a href="https://help.bottlepay.com/en/articles/7902589-the-bottlepay-app-is-closing-down">announced</a> its closure on Monday, July 24, 2023, leaving users with the task of withdrawing their funds. The company stated that all accounts will be closed, and users are urged to withdraw their funds either as Bitcoin or fiat currency (GBP/EUR) from the Bottlepay app before the closure date.&nbsp;</p><p>Failure to withdraw funds by the closure date will result in Bitcoin being converted to fiat currency and returned to the nominated bank account, while any fiat left in the account will be returned to the nominated bank account as well.</p><p>In a statement, Bottlepay advised users to utilize the app's downloads feature to save transaction statements before the closure date. The company emphasized that Bitcoin transactions can have tax implications, making the downloaded information valuable for future reference. As the closure date approaches, Bottlepay may contact users who still have Bitcoin or fiat currency in their accounts, either through the app or via email. However, the company cautioned users to be aware of potential scams and never initiate an offboarding process outside of the app.</p><p>Regarding the next steps, users are advised to download their transaction history and close their Bottlepay accounts. Instructions on how to withdraw funds from Bitcoin and fiat accounts, as well as how to download transaction history and close accounts, can be found on the app.</p><p>In a closing note, Bottlepay expressed gratitude to its customers and apologized for the inconvenience caused by the closure. While the company refrained from making specific recommendations about what to do with Bitcoin funds, users were encouraged to exercise due diligence when selecting alternative custodial wallets or converting Bitcoin to fiat currency. The Financial Conduct Authority (FCA) register can be consulted for information on other FCA-registered cryptoasset businesses operating in the UK.</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk0MzI5NzY4OTU4MTA5MzYx/bitcoin-code.png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Introducing The Rolling-Block Method: A New Way To Forecast Bitcoin Mining Difficulty]]></title><description><![CDATA[Luxor describes its newly-released methodology for improving the accuracy of Bitcoin mining difficulty predictions.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/technical/predicting-bitcoin-mining-difficulty</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/technical/predicting-bitcoin-mining-difficulty</guid><category><![CDATA[Feature]]></category><category><![CDATA[Hash Price]]></category><category><![CDATA[Bitcoin mining]]></category><category><![CDATA[Technical]]></category><category><![CDATA[hash rate]]></category><category><![CDATA[difficulty]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Colin Harper]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTg5NzA2OTgwMjI5NjUzNzAx/bitcoin-mining-miner.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p>Since Bitcoin’s inception, network <a href="https://data.hashrateindex.com/chart/bitcoin-price-and-difficulty">difficulty</a> has grown from 1 to as much as 48.71 trillion hashes that a miner would theoretically need to generate to find the winning one. This means it is 48.71 trillion times harder to mine a Bitcoin block today than when mining first began in 2009 — a compound increase of 20.64% per month.</p><p>At the time of this writing, Bitcoin’s difficulty is at an all-time high, which means that miners — on a BTC basis — are making less in rewards per unit of hash rate than ever before. Next to bitcoin’s price, Bitcoin’s difficulty is a primary factor that influences <a href="https://data.hashrateindex.com/network-data/btc">hash price</a> (<a href="https://data.hashrateindex.com/chart/bitcoin-hashprice-index">mining revenue per unit of hash rate</a>), so miners are interested in projecting Bitcoin’s <a href="https://data.hashrateindex.com/chart/bitcoin-network-hashrate">hash rate</a> growth and difficulty trends for business planning.</p><p>To this end, miners and Bitcoiners devised the constant-block-time method for estimating upcoming adjustments, but this method typically over or under estimates difficulty changes at the beginning of each difficulty epoch.</p><figure>
        <img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk4MTczODQxMTkxNjc0OTUy/average-difficulty-adjustment-by-year.png" height="72" width="620">
        
        
        <figcaption><em>Source: </em><a href="https://hashrateindex.com/"><em>Hashrate Index</em></a></figcaption>
    </figure><p>To improve on this, the team at Luxor Technologies developed a new method called the “rolling-block method,” which we describe in more detail in <a href="https://hashrateindex.com/blog/difficulty-forecasting-101-for-bitcoin-miners-hosters-lenders-and-hashrate-traders/">a recent report on forecasting Bitcoin mining difficulty.</a></p><p>It’s our hope that the rolling-block method for forecasting Bitcoin difficulty could provide miners, investors and hash rate traders a better tool to plan for difficulty changes</p><h2>Luxor's ‘Rolling Block Method’ For Forecasting Difficulty Adjustments</h2><p>For this report, we developed a new time series forecasting method for upcoming difficulty adjustments, which improves accuracy at the beginning of the epoch compared to the constant block time method. We call this the succinctly-named “rolling-2,015-block, square-root-weighted, epoch-adjusted block time method” (or just “rolling-block method,” “adjusted-block-time method,” or “dual-epoch method”).</p><p>This new method improves upon the constant-block-time method early in the epoch by including block times from the previous 2,015 blocks, instead of just the blocks from the current epoch, which can skew forecasts early in the epoch for lack of data points. To account for the change in network difficulty between epochs, block times in the previous epoch are adjusted by the previous adjustment. And finally, we weight the average block times of the current epoch with the square of the proportion through the epoch. This final step is to diminish the impact of block times from the previous epoch as the current epoch progresses since these values do not actually determine the upcoming adjustment.</p><p>In the chart below, we can see through confidence intervals that the new method performed better than the old model at the beginning of the epoch up to block 650, but it performed slightly more poorly thereafter:</p><figure>
        <img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk4MTczODQxMTkxNzQwNDg4/difficulty-adjustment-projection-confidence-intervals.png" height="388" width="620">
        
        
        <figcaption><em>Difficulty forecast confidence intervals. Sources: Luxor, Hashrate Index.</em></figcaption>
    </figure><p>This forecast, of course, is only for projecting the next difficulty adjustment. What if we wanted to forecast, say, a year into the future?</p><h2>Long-Term Bitcoin Mining Difficulty Forecasting</h2><p><a href="https://hashrateindex.com/blog/the-search-for-a-hashprice-floor-or-downside-resistance/">Luxor has developed models for long-term difficulty forecasting</a>, as well, but these models are obviously much more complex, since they span a longer time frame.</p><p>Our model takes the bitcoin price, transaction fees and block subsidy as inputs on the demand side, and internal data on ASIC production estimates and operating cost distributions across the industry on the supply side. Using these inputs, the model produces an equilibrium hash rate, difficulty and hash price for 18-month periods.</p><p>The model structure reflects reality; hash rate, difficulty and hash price are endogenous to the system, not exogenous determinants of one another. We can conduct sensitivity analyses with the model across all inputs as well. For example, we can forecast an equilibrium hash rate, difficulty, and hash price across a range of bitcoin prices.</p><p>The charts below present projections from our updated hash rate supply and demand model. It provides estimates for flat, bull and bear bitcoin price scenarios.</p><figure>
        <img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk4MTczODQxMTkxNjA5NDE2/hash-price-and-hash-rate.png" height="1071" width="620">
        
        
        <figcaption><em>Flat, bull and bear scenarios for hash rate and hash price. Sources: Luxor, Hashrate Index.</em></figcaption>
    </figure><h2>Hash Rate, Difficulty And Hash Price Projection Updates</h2><p>Hash rate is an emerging asset class and digital commodity market. Hash rate market participants like Bitcoin miners, hosters, lenders, investors and traders need access to the rigorous economic analysis and data available in other commodity markets.</p><p>Luxor will be committed to providing this analysis and forecasting on a quarterly basis. If you’d like to learn more, please <a href="https://hashrateindex.com/blog/difficulty-forecasting-101-for-bitcoin-miners-hosters-lenders-and-hashrate-traders/">visit this post.</a></p><p><em>This is a guest post by Colin Harper. Opinions expressed are entirely their own and do not necessarily reflect those of BTC Inc or Bitcoin Magazine.</em></p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTg5NzA2OTgwMjI5NjUzNzAx/bitcoin-mining-miner.png"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk4MTczODQxMTkxNjc0OTUy/average-difficulty-adjustment-by-year.png" height="72" width="620" medium="image" type="image/png"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk4MTczODQxMTkxNzQwNDg4/difficulty-adjustment-projection-confidence-intervals.png" height="388" width="620" medium="image" type="image/png"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk4MTczODQxMTkxNjA5NDE2/hash-price-and-hash-rate.png" height="1071" width="620" medium="image" type="image/png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[MicroBT COO Jordan Chen Discusses The Company's Long-Term Goals And The Newest Whatsminers At Bitcoin 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[Chen elaborated on the mission of MicroBT and how the updates in the new machines exemplify this focus.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/microbt-coo-jordan-chen-discusses-the-newest-whatsminers-at-bitcoin-2023</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/microbt-coo-jordan-chen-discusses-the-newest-whatsminers-at-bitcoin-2023</guid><category><![CDATA[MicroBT]]></category><category><![CDATA[Asics]]></category><category><![CDATA[Business]]></category><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[Solar Power]]></category><category><![CDATA[Mining]]></category><category><![CDATA[whatsminer]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[BtcCasey]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 21:03:28 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTgzMjM5NTgzMDQyMDUzMTU4/img_6181.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p>MicroBT, a leading manufacturer of Bitcoin mining rigs, is focused on addressing the need for upgraded power sources in bitcoin mining. In an interview conducted at Bitcoin 2023 in Miami Beach, MicroBT's COO, Jordan Chen, emphasized the company's commitment to developing a solar power mining solution. According to Chen, "Solar power is a perfect power source for bitcoin mining, both in terms of decentralization and sustainability." He further explained that MicroBT is working with partners along the value chain to provide a mature solution that utilizes solar power for mining worldwide.</p><p>Chen elaborated on the adjustment of voltage and frequency in MicroBT's Whatsminer rigs to adapt to the change in solar power. He stated, "The mining machine has to adapt to the power changes so as to keep mining throughout the day with various working voltage and frequency." Chen highlighted that this dynamic adjustment only costs about "1% to 2% efficiency compared to traditional shut-down-and-reboot method," ensuring continuous mining operations and optimizing revenue.</p><p>Discussing the cooling methods in <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/microbt-releases-new-line-of-whatsminer-m50-series">the new Whatsminer M50 series</a>, Chen provided insights into the benefits and unique features of each method. He explained, "Air-cooling is taking away heat via fans, while hydro-cooling uses water-cooling pads which eliminate the need for fans, heat sinks, and offer a longer lifetime." Regarding immersion cooling, Chen highlighted its advantages, stating, "It's really no dust, no exposure to corrosive air, low noise and a longer lifetime."</p><p>Chen shared MicroBT's focus on heat utilization scenarios, stating, "The heat generated during the mining process will be transferred to an outside heating loop through a heat exchanger." He further explained that the heat recovery ratio can be as high as 95%. Chen emphasized MicroBT's collaboration with customers on various applications, such as providing heating services to communities and generating steam for industrial uses like food processing.</p><p>When discussing MicroBT's vision for the future of Bitcoin mining, Chen emphasized their commitment to leveraging renewable energies and maximizing the reuse of heat generated during mining. He stated, "Our vision is allowing bitcoin mining to make a bigger and bigger positive contribution to society," with a focus on minimizing carbon emissions and carbon footprint.</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTgzMjM5NTgzMDQyMDUzMTU4/img_6181.png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[BIT Mining And Chain Reaction Partner To Create New Bitcoin Mining Systems]]></title><description><![CDATA[The partnership will leverage Chain Reaction’s ASIC announced at Bitcoin 2023 to further develop systems for miners.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/bit-mining-and-chain-reaction-partner-to-create-new-bitcoin-mining-systems</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/bit-mining-and-chain-reaction-partner-to-create-new-bitcoin-mining-systems</guid><category><![CDATA[Mining]]></category><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[Business]]></category><category><![CDATA[BIT Mining]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[BtcCasey]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 19:58:54 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkyNjA3MTM2MjI2NzQ4MTUz/20220926_good-gdog-proof-collaborative-custody-multisig-by-will-schoellkopf_.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p>BIT Mining Limited has announced a collaboration with semiconductor company Chain Reaction to develop next-generation systems for bitcoin mining. According to a <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/bit-mining-and-chain-reaction-form-collaboration-for-bitcoin-hashing-systems-301829444.html?ref=nobsbitcoin.com">press release</a>, the collaboration aims to leverage Chain Reaction's ‘<a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2023/05/16/2669890/0/en/Chain-Reaction-Launches-EL3CTRUM-the-Most-Powerful-Blockchain-Technology-on-the-Market.html">EL3CTRUM ASIC</a>’ solution to create hardware that delivers industry-leading performance with low power consumption.</p><p>The press release states that Chain Reaction specializes in designing hardware for blockchain, privacy, high-performance computing (HPC) and the cloud. With a team experienced in analog and circuit design, the company has successfully produced 30 ASIC tapeouts for high-volume manufacturing. The recently launched EL3CTRUM ASIC by Chain Reaction is described as a “groundbreaking blockchain chip that serves as the foundation for sustainable, high-performance blockchain technologies.”</p><p>Alon Webman, CEO of Chain Reaction, explained what the partnership hopes to yield, saying that "Chain Reaction's bleeding-edge ASICs will enable BIT Mining to build next-gen systems to advance the Bitcoin mining industry towards faster, more power efficient computing." </p><p>“We believe through this collaboration we can leverage our individual strengths to provide the mining community systems that enhance long-term benefits and capabilities,” Xianfeng Yang, CEO of BIT Mining reiterated. “With the crypto mining industry continuing to evolve, BIT Mining looks to develop systems that are more efficient, accessible, and sustainable."</p><p>The systems developed through this collaboration are expected to launch later this year.&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkyNjA3MTM2MjI2NzQ4MTUz/20220926_good-gdog-proof-collaborative-custody-multisig-by-will-schoellkopf_.png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[When Bitcoin Meets Artificial Intelligence: Woke Madness Or Awakened Sanity?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Ideological battle lines are being drawn around artificial intelligence, and Bitcoiners need to enter the fray.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/are-bitcoin-and-artificial-intelligence-compatible</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/are-bitcoin-and-artificial-intelligence-compatible</guid><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Regulation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Opinion]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Aleksandar Svetski]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkzODM5Njc4ODI5MzcyOTEy/network-nodes.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p><em>This is an opinion editorial by Aleksander Svetski, author of “The UnCommunist Manifesto,” The Bitcoin Times and the “Remnant Series,” and head of growth and strategy at Lucent Labs.</em></p><p>I know, I know. Your Twitter feed has probably been drowning in threads and tips from AI bros who have discovered 99 ways for you to save 99 hours every week using ChatGPT or some other list of 99 AI apps.</p><p>I’m sick of it too. Trust me, especially considering that most of these AI “experts” were Web3 “experts” last year, NFT “experts” the year before and DeFi or crypto “experts” before that. Trend hopping at its finest.</p><p>That’s not to say there’s no value here to be found here. Somewhere beneath or behind the almost-deafening noise coming from these influencooors there is a possible paradigm shift, and a genuine set of use cases. We’ve seen some already, of course. </p><p>You can chat with these models to reason out a problem, you can summarize thoughts and ideas, find correlations between ideas, search for <em>some</em> information better than you could with Google and, of course, build more linguistically-functional chatbots. Perhaps the best use case thus far are the <a href="https://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2023/05/google-jumps-into-the-ai-coding-assistant-fray-with-codey-and-studio-bot/">dev-assistant tools</a>, but I get the sense that we’ve not yet seen the “Uber moment.”</p><p>There is also — somewhere beneath and behind all of the scary talk of <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Artificial_general_intelligence">artificial general intelligence (AGI)</a> and the idiocy being proposed by <a href="https://www.whitehouse.gov/ostp/ai-bill-of-rights/">bureaucrats and would-be regulators</a> — a more human-centric, human-enhancing use for these tools.</p><p>The idea of a language user interface as the next step from the thumb tapping we’ve become used to over the past decade is fascinating, and what we should be thinking about is how to make these tools new “<a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ebenbayer/2023/05/15/ai--biotechnology-show-its-time-to-think-past-bicycles-for-the-mind/?sh=2c7868754ea1">bicycles for the mind</a>,” as Steve Jobs said about computers. It’s very important that we push back against doomer narratives that lean the world toward “approved AI” in order to avoid such tools becoming yet another appendage of the State.</p><p>In this short article, I’d like to explore the ideological AI battlefield and its relationship to Bitcoin. Some pretty important battle lines have been drawn, and we must all be aware of them.</p><h2>Bitcoin Remains The Most Important Thing In The World</h2><p>Energy is still the currency of the universe. That’s not changing, and will never change. At the risk of sounding like too much of a hippie: It’s all energy.</p><p>People often forget that, and this recent AI hype cycle is a clear example. Most people you talk with, even otherwise smart people, think that AI is the biggest thing happening in the world today, and that it’s mankind’s most important innovation.</p><p>I think they’re wrong, in a big way. They’re missing something more foundational.</p><p>AI is a tool. When applied well, it’s a very effective tool. But however effective a tool it may be, it needs energy to run. Yes, it can and will enhance how we use and allocate energy, but ultimately, it is an amplifier. A tool. An “engine,” so to speak.</p><p>What is Bitcoin?</p><p>Well, Bitcoin is <em>like</em> energy. <em>Before the Saylor-haters out there screech about that not being literally accurate: I know! It’s a metaphor, and in my opinion, a useful one</em>. It’s useful because, in the same way we can essentially use energy to measure everything else, money is a measure that helps us (implicitly) account for energy, time and material resources. </p><p>If we understand that Bitcoin, on a long enough time scale (generationally speaking, not civilizationally) becomes <em>money</em>, then here’s the truth that AI people are missing:</p><p><strong>Bitcoin benefits from all of it, because Bitcoin is the foundation. Everything that happens, every technology, every tool, every innovation, enlarges the total Bitcoin pie.</strong></p><p>So, don’t get it twisted: AI is big, <em>but Bitcoin remains king.</em></p><p>Of course, in terms of financial returns, VC money and the like, AI companies will probably outpace both bitcoin returns (in the short term) and also Bitcoin company returns, but that’s to be expected in a fiat world where hype prevails over sanity, and we experience abnormal cyclicality.</p><p>AI is also undergoing a sort of renaissance, so there is lots of buzz. This will, in time, stabilize and as bitcoin becomes the unit of account, lo and behold, all of the <em>real</em> value generated from AI will ultimately accrue to bitcoin and bitcoin holders.</p><p>So, don’t stress if you’re feeling FOMO on AI. Don’t worry about changing your entire life around because some ex-crypto-turned-AI-expert guy wrote a viral tweet telling you about some new, generative AI tool that will obsolete some and make others mega rich.</p><p>Slow and steady continues to win the race. Bitcoin continues to be king.</p><h2>AI Is An Amplifier</h2><p>The second thing we need to realize is this: AI is like the computer or any other technology, for that matter.</p><p>It’s an engine. <em>It’s an amplifier.</em></p><p>It will amplify madness, stupidity and lies, or it will amplify soundness, sanity and truth.</p><p>It can be used as a tool of control and stupidification, or it can be used as a tool for liberating oneself from minutia and for enhancing one’s intelligence.</p><p>The direction we wind up ultimately depends on you.</p><p>Which tools are you using? Which do you demand? Which are you building? Which are you supporting?</p><p>Companies like <a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2023/apr/19/snapchat-making-ai-chatbot-similar-to-chatgpt-available-to-every-user">Snapchat are building AI tools</a> to infect your mind with nonsense:</p><figure>
        <img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk4MTUwNTgyMDY0NzE5MDM4/snapchat-ai.jpg" height="826" width="620">
        
        
        <figcaption><a href="https://substackcdn.com/image/fetch/f_auto,q_auto:good,fl_progressive:steep/https%3A%2F%2Fsubstack-post-media.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fpublic%2Fimages%2Fa6ecce10-7633-4e3b-8383-39672339268c_886x1181.jpeg"><em>Source</em></a></figcaption>
    </figure><p>OpenAI is busy guard-railing ChatGPT to such a degree that it spends <a href="https://www.pcmag.com/news/openai-sorry-chatgpt-bug-leaked-payment-info-to-other-users">more time apologizing and moralizing</a> than it does answering actual questions.</p><p>Bard is, likewise, <a href="https://www.the-sun.com/tech/7719664/googles-bard-ai-chatbot-accused-left-wing-bias/">regurgitating the same kind of garbage</a>, likely because it’s been neutered by “bias-removal” tools and toxicity filters.</p><p>These stupidities only serve to constrain people’s accepted thinking and speech, which results in a homogenization of thought. This can have two effects. In the worst case, so-called “safety concerns” lead to “approved AI” which ultimately leads to an internet that is accessed through chat filters with approved speech conditions. The alternative is if we push back and build alternatives. Their ignorance becomes our opportunity. While they focus on wokeness, we can build utility and authenticity. </p><p>Which brings me to my final point:</p><h2>We’re In A Global AI Arms Race</h2><p>The race is between two versions of the world:</p><ol><li>On the one hand, we have woke, generalist AIs that everyone is forced to use because newly-formed regulatory bodies deem them “safe” (see the <a href="https://garymarcus.substack.com/p/how-china-might-crush-the-west-in?utm_source=substack&amp;utm_campaign=post_embed&amp;utm_medium=web">ridiculously-moronic work being done by Gary Marcus</a> to set up such a global committee).</li><li>On the other, we have a future of distributed, more sovereign tools that people can choose from, that the user evaluates on merits they deem important.</li></ol><p>I know which future I want to see, and instead of sitting on the sidelines complaining, I’m working toward building alternative or parallel solutions.</p><p>In a future article, I’ll lay out what myself and a few really talented individuals have been working on. A beautiful marriage of Bitcoin as the focal point and Ai as the engine. </p><p>In the meantime, know this: <strong>The battle lines have been drawn.</strong></p><p>It’s iris-scanning, central bank digital currencies (CBDCs) <a href="https://www.ft.com/content/f1de2aee-ee13-45e1-bd61-0a269cd650d3">like World Coin</a> on one end, conveniently run by the same leadership as OpenAI, versus Bitcoin and smaller, more accurate, specialized and open-source language models on the other.</p><figure>
        <img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk4MTUwNTgyMDY0NjUzNTAy/world-coin.jpg" height="739" width="620">
        
        
        <figcaption><a href="https://twitter.com/nwilliams030/status/1540409206532186116"><em>Source</em></a></figcaption>
    </figure><p>We all have to make a choice about the kind of world we want to live in. Woke madness, or awakened sanity? Mainstream and generalized, or local and specialized?</p><p>In my next piece, I will present a potential solution, or at least a way forward. Until then, think deeply about what I have said. Don’t get flustered by all the hype. Remain steady in your conviction, remain vigilant with the narratives being pushed and be ready for the next battle — because it’s coming.</p><p><em>This is a guest post by </em><a href="https://linktree.com/Svetski"><em>Aleksandar Svetski</em></a><em>, founder of </em><a href="https://bitcointim.es"><em>The Bitcoin Times</em></a><em> and </em><a href="http://amber.app"><em>The Amber App,</em></a><em> author of “</em><a href="http://www.uncommunist.com/"><em>The UnCommunist Manifesto</em></a><em>,” “</em><a href="https://authenticintelligence.substack.com"><em>Authentic Intelligence</em></a><em>” and the up-coming “Bushido Of Bitcoin.” Opinions expressed are entirely their own and do not necessarily reflect those of BTC Inc or </em>Bitcoin Magazine<em>.</em></p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkzODM5Njc4ODI5MzcyOTEy/network-nodes.png"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk4MTUwNTgyMDY0NzE5MDM4/snapchat-ai.jpg" height="826" width="620" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk4MTUwNTgyMDY0NjUzNTAy/world-coin.jpg" height="739" width="620" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Upstream Data Files Lawsuit Against Crusoe Energy Systems For Bitcoin Mining Operations]]></title><description><![CDATA[The lawsuit alleges that Crusoe’s mining operations utilizing stranded natural gas infringe upon Upstream’s patent.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/upstream-data-files-lawsuit-against-crusoe-energy-systems</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/upstream-data-files-lawsuit-against-crusoe-energy-systems</guid><category><![CDATA[Business]]></category><category><![CDATA[Miners]]></category><category><![CDATA[Crusoe]]></category><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[Upstream data]]></category><category><![CDATA[Patents]]></category><category><![CDATA[Mining]]></category><category><![CDATA[Lawsuit]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[BtcCasey]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 19:11:38 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkzMzUxMjcwOTg2MTYzNzc5/mining-pick-axe.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p>Canadian Bitcoin mining corporation <a href="https://blog.upstreamdata.ca/">Upstream Data Inc</a>. has filed a patent infringement lawsuit against Delaware limited liability company <a href="https://www.crusoeenergy.com/">Crusoe Energy Systems</a> LLC in the United States District Court for the District of Colorado.&nbsp;</p><p><a href="https://media.licdn.com/dms/document/media/D561FAQHWC4EiAxmGog/feedshare-document-pdf-analyzed/0/1684512495590?e=1685577600&amp;v=beta&amp;t=_NRwT6YvH0ydEyWm5GBg8E-lglYTuqL8TWWIsBJ1K84">The lawsuit</a> alleges that Crusoe has infringed on Upstream's patent related to bitcoin mining technology used to convert stranded natural gas into bitcoin. According to the complaint, Upstream holds the patent for a system that powers a blockchain mine at remote oil well sites using stranded gas to generate electricity for cryptocurrency mining. According to the filing, the company has deployed over 350 bitcoin mining systems across the U.S. and Canada, addressing the issue of stranded gas venting and flaring.</p><p>Crusoe, which manufactures and operates cryptocurrency mining systems connected to stranded natural gas sources, is accused of competing with Upstream by selling and operating similar systems. The complaint claims that Crusoe's "Digital Flare Mitigation" systems infringe on Upstream's patented technology. The lawsuit further alleges that Crusoe was aware of Upstream's patented technology during the development of its own products. The lawsuit filing highlights instances where Crusoe identified Upstream as a competitor in blog posts and claims made in patent applications.</p><p>The lawsuit seeks damages and injunctive relief against Crusoe for patent infringement. Upstream argues that Crusoe's actions have caused harm to its business by infringing on its patent rights and creating unfair competition in the market.&nbsp;</p><p>The case will be heard in the United States District Court for the District of Colorado, where Crusoe has regular and established places of business according to the filing. Also noted in the lawsuit is a complaint filed against a customer of Upstream in Crusoe Energy Systems LLC v. Alkane Midstream LLC, which the lawsuit says "further confirm[s] Crusoe’s significant and substantial contacts with this district." Upstream asserts in the lawsuit that the court has jurisdiction over the case.</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkzMzUxMjcwOTg2MTYzNzc5/mining-pick-axe.png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[How To Figure Out If You Should Start Mining Bitcoin]]></title><description><![CDATA[Turning a profit from Bitcoin mining is a challenge, but not impossible. Here are some factors to consider if you want to start.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/should-i-start-mining-bitcoin</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/should-i-start-mining-bitcoin</guid><category><![CDATA[Halving]]></category><category><![CDATA[Bitcoin mining]]></category><category><![CDATA[energy costs]]></category><category><![CDATA[Opinion]]></category><category><![CDATA[Business]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Keaton Reckard]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTg5MjcxMzMyMzAxNTc5Mzky/20220504_btcfinal_zack-voell---so-what-if-bitcoin-miners-fees-are-low.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p><em>This is an opinion editorial by Keaton Reckard, the community engineer at Hiveon, </em><em>a mining ecosystem that includes an operating system for Bitcoin mining hardware.</em></p><p><a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/guides/bitcoin-mining">Bitcoin mining</a> refers to the process through which new bitcoin is introduced into circulation. The mining process plays a crucial role in confirming new transactions and maintaining the Bitcoin blockchain ledger as an immutable record of transactions. In essence, miners use ASIC hardware to solve complex computational problems, with the first one to find the solution earning a reward of bitcoin before the cycle restarts. </p><p>Though Bitcoin mining can be time-consuming, expensive and can yield inconsistent rewards depending on price volatility, it still holds a strong allure for investors drawn to the idea of earning bitcoin as compensation for their efforts. For tech-savvy individuals and hobbyists, mining can be an intriguing opportunity for many different reasons.</p><p>As opposed to traditional investment assets, such as standard bank deposits, real estate property or stocks, bitcoin can offer much higher returns. It’s an environmentally-conscious business that can prevent energy waste by utilizing excess energy, such as the natural gas that gets burned during oil extraction, idle wind turbines and surplus energy from hydroelectric or nuclear power plants. </p><p>Hiveon’s long-term predictions are that bitcoin’s value will rise after the halving (more on that below), so we’re accumulating coins now to multiply that money into the future. We also believe that, in the future, an alternative global financial system based on blockchain technology like Bitcoin’s will be dominant, and network validators will be able to make money from processing transactions.</p><p>But with mining difficulty and hash rate <a href="https://www.theblock.co/post/225359/bitcoin-difficulty-hashrate-miner-revenue">continuously hitting new highs</a> and <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-network-overwhelmed-by-390000-unconfirmed-transactions-and-surging-fees/">fees surging</a>, many may wonder if the practice is still worth investing in.</p><h2>Is Mining Bitcoin Worth It?</h2><p>To determine if Bitcoin mining will be “worth it” for them, equipment, prospective miners should conduct cost-benefit analyses to determine their break-even points. Factors to consider include power costs, hardware costs and efficiency, time and the market value of bitcoin. You can choose to factor in the current BTC price ($28,190 at the time of writing) or, attempt to extrapolate where you believe the price of BTC will be in the future.</p><h3>Power Costs</h3><p>At the time of this writing, Bitcoin mining can be profitable for individuals who pay <a href="https://whattomine.com/miners/163-bitmain-antminer-s19j-pro-96th?cost=0.11&amp;cost_currency=USD&amp;button=">$0.10 or less per kilowatt hour (kWh)</a> of power.</p><p>Access to energy at this price, however, can vary significantly across different regions, with some areas offering notably cheaper electricity than others. In terms of <a href="https://www.statista.com/statistics/263492/electricity-prices-in-selected-countries/">household electricity prices</a>, several Middle Eastern countries would make good homes for Bitcoin miners, including Iran, Qatar and Saudi Arabia. Meanwhile, prices in European countries like Denmark, Germany and the U.K., would make Bitcoin mining a difficult proposition.</p><h3>Hardware Costs</h3><p>Acquiring ASIC equipment has become relatively easy, although the price of ASICs ranges from a few hundred dollars to five-figure sums. I recently found a used Antminer S19 for sale in the U.K., listed at £2,700 (or about $3,343.38).</p><h3>Market Value</h3><p>Bitcoin achieved its highest price ever at <a href="https://99bitcoins.com/bitcoin/historical-price/">$67,549 in November 2021</a>. During this period, as the 2021 bull market reached its peak, miners’ bitcoin rewards were naturally more valuable in fiat terms than they are at the time of this writing, with the bitcoin price around $27,600. However, with <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/technical/bitcoins-high-fees-create-controversy-and-challenges">bitcoin transaction fees rising</a> as a result of ongoing experimentations with block space, miners are benefitting.</p><p>A <a href="https://btc.com/tools/mining-calculator">profitability calculator</a> can help potential miners evaluate the cost-benefit ratio of Bitcoin mining. These calculators can vary in complexity and may provide slightly different results. </p><h2>What Are The ‘Other’ Reasons For Bitcoin Mining?</h2><p>But for some Bitcoin miners, a simple cost-benefit analysis may not be the only factor in deciding whether mining is “worth it” or not in 2023.</p><p>Mining is an essential aspect of Bitcoin's decentralized transaction recording and validation process. Bitcoin mining serves a critical purpose by addressing an issue called “double spending,” a problem inherent in any digital currency system. Double spending is the digital equivalent of counterfeiting, which is kept in check in the physical world by middlemen like governments and banks. </p><p>For Bitcoin, this need to trust third parties has been replaced largely because of the computational effort provided by miners. Maintaining that freedom from middlemen, in addition to collecting revenue, may be a motivation to contribute to the mining network for some.</p><h2>Bitcoin Halving Cycles And What to Expect In 2024</h2><p>The <a href="https://www.coinwarz.com/mining/bitcoin/halving#:~:text=When%20is%20the%20Next%20Bitcoin%20Halving%20Date%3F,to%203.125%20Bitcoin%20per%20block.">next anticipated Bitcoin halving in April 2024</a> will likely have a significant impact on the mining dynamic.</p><p>A Bitcoin halving is an event in which the reward for mining new blocks is reduced by 50%, resulting in miners receiving half as many bitcoin in their reward for solving a block. Scheduled to occur every 210,000 blocks, Bitcoin halvings continue until the maximum supply of 21 million bitcoin has been issued.</p><p>The impact of the next halving on Bitcoin's price remains uncertain. Some analysts predict that the price will follow a similar pattern to previous halvings, rising post-event due to the constrained supply of new coins. However, any price increase will ultimately depend on demand for bitcoin and it should be noted that the market has matured significantly since the 2020 halving, and numerous well-established cryptocurrencies now compete for users.</p><p>Anyone considering whether Bitcoin mining will be profitable in 2023 will likely want to factor the impact of the next Bitcoin halving into their calculus as well.</p><h2>Difficult, But Not Impossible</h2><p>Profitable Bitcoin mining is a challenge, but it’s not impossible. Bitcoin is priced relatively low at the time of writing, yet an Antminer S19 can run profitably at a maximum power cost of $0.10 per kWh. While this rules out areas of the world like the U.K., there are many global locations where power is cheaper. Naturally, renewable sources of energy (solar panels in particular) really help improve profitability and, as the world transitions from oil and gas to renewable sources of energy, it’s hoped that the price of electricity will fall once again.</p><p>Access to cheap electricity, the quickly-evolving nature of Bitcoin and upcoming events like the halving are just some of the many factors to consider when you ask, is Bitcoin mining profitable?</p><p><em>This is a guest post by Keaton Reckard. Opinions expressed are entirely their own and do not necessarily reflect those of BTC Inc or Bitcoin Magazine.</em></p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTg5MjcxMzMyMzAxNTc5Mzky/20220504_btcfinal_zack-voell---so-what-if-bitcoin-miners-fees-are-low.png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Developer Introduces Ark, A Layer 2 Protocol For Fast And Efficient Payments]]></title><description><![CDATA[Ark promises easier access to a scalable Layer 2, negating the need for channel management.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/technical/bitcoin-developer-introduces-new-layer-2-protocol-ark</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/technical/bitcoin-developer-introduces-new-layer-2-protocol-ark</guid><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[Technical]]></category><category><![CDATA[Ark]]></category><category><![CDATA[Layer 2]]></category><category><![CDATA[development]]></category><category><![CDATA[scalability]]></category><category><![CDATA[Scaling]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[BtcCasey]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 20:58:15 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk0MjMxNzYxODMwNTUzMDkz/bitcoin-stack.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p>A Bitcoin developer by the name of <a href="https://twitter.com/brqgoo?lang=en">Burak</a> recently unveiled Ark, a Layer 2 protocol designed to enable fast and secure transactions. According to <a href="https://lists.linuxfoundation.org/pipermail/bitcoin-dev/2023-May/021694.html">a post on the Bitcoin dev mailing list</a>, Ark offers an alternative scaling approach that allows users to send and receive funds without liquidity constraints, making it easier for recipients to get paid without an onboarding setup. Unlike other Layer 2 solutions like Lightning, Ark does not require the opening and closing of channels, reducing the on-chain footprint significantly.</p><figure>
        <img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk4MTMzMzIzODEyMzE2MjMy/image1.png" height="304" width="620">
        
        
        <figcaption><a href="https://www.arkpill.me/deep-dive"><em>Image source</em></a></figcaption>
    </figure><p>The protocol operates using virtual UTXOs (vTXOs), which are short-lived notes that expire after four weeks. When a payment is made, existing vTXOs are redeemed, and new ones are created. The anonymity of coin ownership is improved by restricting vTXO values to a range of sats values. Users can acquire vTXOs from others or use a process called lifting, which allows them to lift their on-chain UTXOs off the chain for virtual UTXOs.</p><p>The protocol introduces an intermediary called the Ark Service Provider (ASP), which serves as a liquidity provider, CoinJoin coordinator and Lightning service provider. ASPs create rapid, blinded CoinJoin sessions every five seconds, known as pools, which ensure the atomicity of payment schedules. Recipients can claim their funds through a txlock condition that requires the connector outpoint to remain unchanged.</p><p>Ark's integration with the Lightning Network allows users to attach HTLCs (or PTLCs) to a pool transaction, enabling interoperability between the two protocols. Multiple ASPs can be used to pay Lightning invoices from different vTXO sources using multi-part payments. Payments on Ark are credited every five seconds, allowing users to spend their zero-conf vTXOs immediately without waiting for on-chain confirmations.</p><p>The developer behind Ark highlighted the protocol's potential for future extensions and improvements. A hypothetical data manipulation opcode could disincentivize double-spending, and users could forge an ASP's signature to reclaim their vTXOs in case of a double-spend. Overall, Ark offers a promising solution for efficient and secure off-chain transactions on the Bitcoin network.</p><p>For more information on Ark and its technical details, curious users are encouraged to visit <a href="https://arkpill.me/deep-dive">https://arkpill.me/deep-dive</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk0MjMxNzYxODMwNTUzMDkz/bitcoin-stack.png"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk4MTMzMzIzODEyMzE2MjMy/image1.png" height="304" width="620" medium="image" type="image/png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Neutronpay And Pouch.ph Partner To Offer Affordable Remittances For Canada And Vietnam Using Lightning]]></title><description><![CDATA[Canadians who want to send money back to the Philippines can now leverage the Lightning Network to do so.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/neutronpay-and-pouch-ph-now-offer-lightning-remittances-for-canada-and-vietnam</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/neutronpay-and-pouch-ph-now-offer-lightning-remittances-for-canada-and-vietnam</guid><category><![CDATA[Philippines]]></category><category><![CDATA[Business]]></category><category><![CDATA[Lightning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Remittances]]></category><category><![CDATA[Canada]]></category><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[BtcCasey]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 17:06:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkzMDI2MTUyOTY3NzA5OTE3/global-hyperbitcoinization.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p><a href="https://neutronpay.com/">Neutronpay</a>, a digital payment platform based in Canada, has partnered with <a href="https://pouch.ph/">Pouch.ph</a> to offer fast and affordable remittance services for Filipinos living in Canada and Vietnam. According to a press release sent to Bitcoin Magazine, the partnership aims to provide a secure and cost-effective solution for Filipino expatriates who want to send money to their loved ones in the Philippines. By leveraging Bitcoin's Lightning Network, the partnership enables the conversion of Canadian dollars or Vietnamese dong into bitcoin, which is then converted into Philippine pesos and transferred directly to the recipient's bank or mobile money account.</p><p>Albert Buu, the founder and CEO of Neutronpay, expressed his excitement about the collaboration, stating, "Our integration with Bitcoin's Lightning Network is a major step forward in improving the lives of our customers, and we look forward to exploring new ways to innovate cross-border payments."</p><p>The demand for remittances to the Philippines has been growing steadily, with personal remittances reaching a record high of $36.14 billion in 2022, according to data from the Banko Sentral ng Pilipinas. Canada accounted for 3.6% of total remittances to the Philippines, highlighting the importance of providing efficient and cost-effective remittance services to the Filipino community in Canada.</p><p>Ethan Rose, the CEO of Pouch, emphasized the significance of the partnership in empowering overseas Filipino workers (OFWs) to easily send money back home. He stated, "Working with Neutronpay is consistent with our endeavor to empower OFWs to easily send money to their families and loved ones."</p><p>The NeutronPay app is currently available exclusively on Canadian and Vietnamese app stores, while the Pouch.ph app can be downloaded from the Google Play Store and Apple Store. This collaboration between Neutronpay and Pouch.ph brings lightning-fast remittance services to Filipinos in Canada and Vietnam, offering a convenient and cost-effective way to support their families and loved ones back home in the Philippines.</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkzMDI2MTUyOTY3NzA5OTE3/global-hyperbitcoinization.png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ordinals Have Proven Demand On Bitcoin, But Fees Will Push Users To Layer 2]]></title><description><![CDATA[The surge of Ordinals demonstrates a significant market, but not one that Bitcoin is built to sustain on the base layer.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/bitcoin-ordinal-problems-solved-by-layer-2</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/bitcoin-ordinal-problems-solved-by-layer-2</guid><category><![CDATA[Layer 2]]></category><category><![CDATA[Transactions]]></category><category><![CDATA[Fees]]></category><category><![CDATA[Ordinals]]></category><category><![CDATA[Opinion]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Steven Hay]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkwMjY2NTkxMzgyODczMjQx/bitcoin-lightning-network.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p><em>This is an opinion editorial by Steven Hay, a writer, former trader and art dealer.</em></p><p>The <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/questioning-bitcoin-magazine-ordinal-auction">Ordinals controversy</a> is still simmering and seems set to flare up again soon. Although Ordinals’ block space usage had been<a href="https://dune.com/queries/2009834/3326390"> trending down</a> since March 23, 2023, the release of<a href="https://arthodl.net/2023/04/05/bugatti-and-asprey-bringing-high-tech-faberge-style-eggs-to-ordinals/"> notable collections</a> and a <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/technical/bitcoins-high-fees-create-controversy-and-challenges">burgeoning mania</a> for BRC-20 tokens seems to have reversed that trend. </p><p>Should competition for block space between Ordinals, BRC-20 tokens and purely monetary transactions remain high, so will fees. And, should fees climb sufficiently high, the ghastly shades of the<a href="https://blog.bitmex.com/the-blocksize-war-chapter-1-first-strike/"> blocksize war</a> may rise once more to torment all Bit-kind.</p><h2>The Case Against Ordinals</h2><p>Fees aren't the only flashpoint. While Bitcoin has certainly had its share of negative headlines over the years, the protocol itself has thus far escaped the same level of recrimination. Exchange failures, drug sales, countless scams — these are all things people did <em>with</em> the tech, rather than any intrinsic fault of the tech itself. Not so with, say, Ethereum, where sketchy smart contracts are virtually part of the machine. </p><p>With Ordinals popularizing the integration of Bitcoin's blockchain with all manner of infamous Ethereum innovations (such as NFTs, tokens and, perhaps soon,<a href="https://thebitcoinmanual.com/articles/what-are-brc-721-tokens/"> smart contracts</a>), reputational risk to the Bitcoin protocol grows. How long until a token is issued directly on Bitcoin which passes the<a href="https://www.investopedia.com/terms/h/howey-test.asp"> Howey Test</a> and so falls afoul of the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission? </p><p>Further in this regard, Ordinals also greatly lower the barrier to introducing illicit or classified content into Bitcoin's blockchain.</p><figure>
        <img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk3OTg3MjYyNDQzNTYyNzgx/rug-pull.jpg" height="310" width="620">
        
        
        <figcaption><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/destroying-substratum-appeal-payingreceiving-judgment-jayapal/"><em>Source</em></a><em> (modified by author).</em></figcaption>
    </figure><p>As for the loss of user funds due to rug pulls, bugs, hacks and takedowns, all of these boxes have already been ticked under Ordinals. Most recently,<a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ordinals-finance-has-conducted-a-1m-rug-pull-certik"> Ordinals Finance</a> pulled a $1 million rug, albeit on the Ethereum side of the ledger. Just prior to that,<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/news/coinedition:bd9364062094b:0/"> UniSat</a> fumbled the launch of its BRC-20s marketplace, resulting in costly double-spend attacks and a lengthy market halt. Before <em>that</em>, several major marketplaces bowed to legal pressure from<a href="https://arthodl.net/2023/04/11/magic-eden-market-delists-ape-collections/"> Yuga Labs</a> and delisted ape-related collections. </p><p>Furthermore, all of these "hiccups" occurred against the background of a<a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-ordinals-community-debates-fix-after-inscription-validation-bug"> bug</a> discovered within Ordinals' all-important indexing system. Finally — and I hate to say this — further problems of this nature are anticipated. Consider that one of the largest<a href="https://dune.com/domo/ordinals-marketplaces"> marketplaces by users and volume</a>, Ordinals Wallet as well as the significant Ordswap marketplace both keep keys in browser<a href="https://snyk.io/blog/is-localstorage-safe-to-use/"> </a>local storage, according to what I’ve heard on Discord, which <a href="https://snyk.io/blog/is-localstorage-safe-to-use/">runs contrary to recommended security practices</a> (to say the least).</p><p>I believe the above paragraphs summarize the case against Ordinals from the perspective of many Bitcoin Maximalists — among whose ranks I myself numbered, at least until the Ordinals<a href="https://www.urbandictionary.com/define.php?term=Purity%20Spiral"> purity spiral</a> went helter-skelter. And while these concerns have merit, there's one particular complaint which I believe deserves to go unmentioned; that Ordinals are a scam. </p><p>When willing buyers and willing sellers exchange goods with informational symmetry, without any claims made as to future price appreciation, well, that's the definition of honest business — and that's the current situation within Ordinals marketplaces. Prove me wrong.</p><h2>In Defense Of Ordinals</h2><p>A point in favor of Ordinals is that <a href="https://decrypt.co/125556/bitcoin-stamps-nfts-are-gaining-on-ordinals">it's possible to prune their content from stored blockchain data</a>. Pruning resolves the blockchain file size bloat issue, which is fairly trivial considering that I expect the bloat to be easily outpaced by the growth of affordable data storage. More importantly, pruning ensures that anyone running a full node can opt out of storing any illegal material (which, to be fair, existed on Bitcoin's blockchain long before Ordinals).</p><p>In regards to the reputational and legislative risks to Bitcoin arising from Ordinals content stored on the blockchain, these can be mitigated — but not eliminated — by proper communication. The point must be hammered home (and not just for the sake of Ordinals) that Bitcoin's uncensorable and permissionless structure has certain unavoidable drawbacks which, on balance, are vastly outweighed by its advantages.</p><p>On the technical front, it's possible that post-traumatic stress from the blocksize war is leading some to view Ordinals as a big-blocker-style assault on Bitcoin's base layer... but as an entirely optional Layer 2, Ordinals have far more in common with the Lightning Network than with Bcash and its ilk. Granted, content insertion into witness data is also occurring, but that process is moderated by fees... </p><p>Fees? Lightning? Let's not jump ahead to the resolution of this Ordinals controversy!</p><p>As for the loss of user funds to cyber bandits or technical gremlins, such losses are likely to remain limited due to the relatively small size of the Ordinals economy. As the<a href="https://www.ordinalhub.com/price-tracking?dateRange=All&amp;page=1"> estimated total value</a> of all Ordinals collection at the time of this writing is currently around 1,628 BTC, worth some $45 million, nothing approaching the scale of the infamous fiascos that have plagued crypto is even possible at this stage:</p><figure>
        <img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk3OTg3MjYyMTc1MTI2Njg5/most-costly-crypto-hacks.jpg" height="337" width="620">
        
        
        <figcaption><a href="https://techmonitor.ai/technology/cybersecurity/biggest-cryptocurrency-hacks-of-all-time"><em>Source</em></a></figcaption>
    </figure><p>So much for playing defense. The fact is that Ordinals are attracting new users, developers, artists and companies to the Bitcoin space. This will surely have multiple benefits beyond the immediate boost to the value and prestige of the entire ecosystem. Onboarding more users of all kinds is the surest path to accelerating hyperbitcoinization. And if Bitcoin succeeds, the world will be liberated from the death grip of central banking — but let's put our ruby-quartz visor back on and refocus.</p><figure>
        <img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk3OTg3MjYyMTc1MTkyMjI1/cyclops-visor.jpg" height="310" width="620">
        
        
        <figcaption><a href="https://marvel.fandom.com/wiki/Cyclops%27_Visor"><em>Source</em></a></figcaption>
    </figure><p>While most early Bitcoiners got on board due to technical curiosity or ideological motivation, later adoption waves were likely driven by economic factors. Many of these later entrants stuck around because they realized<a href="https://twitter.com/ChadsBitcoin/status/1258854925884362755"> Bitcoin is a revolution disguised as a get-rich-quick scheme</a>. While we await the next bull cycle, Ordinals are attracting a fresh set of users, composed largely of young creatives. </p><p>Should we really turn these hopefuls away, to wander in the shitcoin swamps?</p><h2>The Solution</h2><p>Ordinals have proven the strong demand for Bitcoin NFTs, tokens and smart contracts. Although such things have been tried on Bitcoin in the past, through whatever confluence of factors, the time is now demonstrably ripe for them. A<a href="https://dune.com/dgtl_assets/bitcoin-ordinals-analysis"> quick glance</a> at inscription count over time (currently over five million after about five months) is enough to confirm this. The associated impact on fees has been equally obvious:</p><figure>
        <img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk3OTg3MjYyNDQzNTYyMTQ1/bitcoin-mempool-weight.jpg" height="269" width="620">
        
        
        <figcaption><a href="https://jochen-hoenicke.de/queue/#BTC,all,weight"><em>Source</em></a></figcaption>
    </figure><p>Note that the two previous spikes, around the starts of 2018 and 2021, coincided with the resolution of massive bull markets. From January of this year, the markets have been fairly calm and the latest spike is attributable to Ordinals. This raises the question of how horrifically high fees will get if the current Ordinals volume persists into the climax of another bull cycle... </p><p>In my view, this is the only critical issue presented by Ordinals; a looming problem with the potential to outweigh the benefit of the adoption boost. With <a href="https://decrypt.co/139259/bitcoin-ddos-ordinals-inscriptions-attack">fees hitting the 600-plus sat per virtual byte (vB) nosebleed levels</a> last seen in late 2017 and early 2018, Bitcoin might lose as many (or more) users to other chains as it gains from Ordinals.</p><p>The solution to high fees back in the day was the<a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/guides/what-is-segwit"> SegWit</a> soft fork, which greatly reduced the size and fees of conforming transactions. SegWit also enabled the launch of the Lightning Network, a layer atop Bitcoin designed to process low-value transactions. One quirk of Bitcoin is its flat fee and data structure, whereby the cost and block space required to send $1 in BTC is equal to those for sending $1 billion in BTC. Offloading low-value transactions to Lightning frees up block space, resulting in lower bitcoin fees. In combination, these two upgrades ensured that when bitcoin pushed to its all-time high in 2021, fees remained reasonable.</p><p><strong>So, why should the solution to high fees arising from Web3 stuff on Bitcoin be any different?</strong></p><p><a href="https://www.rgbfaq.com/">RGB</a>,<a href="https://lightning.engineering/posts/2022-9-28-taro-launch/"> Taro</a>,<a href="https://www.stacks.co/"> Stacks</a> — these are all technologies to shunt Web3 transactions and data from the Bitcoin blockchain and onto Layer 2. While the approach seen in Ordinals and Stamps of writing content directly to the base layer offers unrivaled permanence and immutability, it's also extremely costly. For example, an artist I spoke with recently told me that he spent $3,800 to inscribe a collection. Especially in these tough economic times, that's a lot for a young creative to gamble in an unpredictable market!</p><p>Consider that, as of this writing, 200 of the collections tracked by<a href="https://www.ordinalhub.com/price-tracking?dateRange=All&amp;page=1&amp;sort=volume_btc%3Aasc"> OrdinalHub</a> have seen <em>zero</em> all-time volume, as in no sales at all. This figure barely scratches the surface of market failures. Sorting the 1,000-plus collections on <a href="https://bestinslot.xyz/ordinals/collections/#order=7d_sales_asc&amp;page=35">Best In Slot</a> by inverse weekly sales volume reveals hundreds with zero sales.<a href="https://ordinalswallet.com/collections"> See for yourself</a> how many low-value collections on Ordinals Wallet have had zero volume or sales over the last week. Pending a proper analysis, my intuition is that fewer than one in 100 inscriptions listed on a marketplace will turn a profit.</p><p>The novelty of Ordinals will fade, but the high costs will remain. Given that Layer 2 solutions don't store data on the blockchain, their creation costs will be orders of magnitude lower. High-end collections, like<a href="https://arthodl.net/2023/04/05/bugatti-and-asprey-bringing-high-tech-faberge-style-eggs-to-ordinals/"> Asprey Bugatti Eggs</a>, may still inscribe to Ordinals as the perceived luxury and maximum-permanence option, but the vast majority of creators will opt for the inexpensive alternatives still linked to Bitcoin, even if indirectly.</p><p>Cost isn't the only factor behind the inevitable migration of most users to Layer 2. The size constraints of Bitcoin blocks make bulky content (like high-resolution images or audio, complex code and all but the shortest video clips) unaffordable or even impossible to inscribe. With generative AI making it easy to create high-resolution image content — and soon audio and video content, too — how much longer will the average creator be content to pay a relative fortune to inscribe text and small, static images?</p><h2>Base Layer To Layer 2</h2><p>The way I see things playing out, Ordinals has proven the market demand for Bitcoin-based NFTs, tokens, DeFi, etc. — as unpalatable as some may find that demand. Regardless, the cost and relative slowness of these assets on the base layer should eventually drive most users to Layer 2 solutions, already nearing completion. The base layer will perhaps become the digital equivalent of the Louvre, housing only the most significant works under the tightest security. Layer 2 will host everything else.</p><p>Ordinal antagonists should take note. Twitter screeds denouncing inscribers as attackers for adding monkey JPEGs to the blockchain only incite hilarity and encourage defiance. A $100 or even a $25 inscription fee is a far more effective disincentive, already established and requiring no keyboard bashing. To defuse the looming threat of high fees, the proactive strategy would be to contribute or donate to the development of Layer 2 solutions.</p><p><em>This is a guest post by Steven Hay. Opinions expressed are entirely their own and do not necessarily reflect those of BTC Inc or Bitcoin Magazine.</em></p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkwMjY2NTkxMzgyODczMjQx/bitcoin-lightning-network.png"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk3OTg3MjYyNDQzNTYyNzgx/rug-pull.jpg" height="310" width="620" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk3OTg3MjYyMTc1MTI2Njg5/most-costly-crypto-hacks.jpg" height="337" width="620" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk3OTg3MjYyMTc1MTkyMjI1/cyclops-visor.jpg" height="310" width="620" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk3OTg3MjYyNDQzNTYyMTQ1/bitcoin-mempool-weight.jpg" height="269" width="620" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Decoding Bitcoin’s Transaction Surge: The Emergence Of History’s Greatest Accounting Innovation]]></title><description><![CDATA[The rise of Ordinals has brought massive transaction volume to Bitcoin and its promise as a historic accounting innovation is starting to show.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/accounting-for-bitcoin-transaction-spike</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/accounting-for-bitcoin-transaction-spike</guid><category><![CDATA[Ordinals]]></category><category><![CDATA[Accounting]]></category><category><![CDATA[mempool]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Transactions]]></category><category><![CDATA[Opinion]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Darin Feinstein]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkxNDAxMTQ0NTc1MDc1ODcz/border-wallets-seed-phrase-recovery-top-photo.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p><em>This is an opinion editorial by Darin Feinstein, the co-founder and co-chairman of Bitcoin mining firm Core Scientific.</em></p><p>The <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/08/binance-lifts-block-on-bitcoin-withdrawals-amid-heavy-volumes.html">recent surge in transaction volume</a> on the Bitcoin network has sparked conversation and debate about <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/technical/bitcoins-high-fees-create-controversy-and-challenges">heightened transaction fees</a> and Bitcoin's overall goals and purpose. This has resulted in questions regarding the network's future and its ability to handle the increasing demand. </p><p>In response to those questions, it can be helpful to consider the intricacies of Bitcoin’s transaction volume through an accounting lens, as the Bitcoin network, at its foundation, is an accounting ledger with its data written to a public chain and recorded forever. Through this lens, we’ll delve into why Bitcoin’s transaction volume matters, how often such surges will occur and whether or not this growth is sustainable.</p><h2>The Accounting Innovation Of Bitcoin</h2><p>As an accounting ledger, Bitcoin represents the first true accounting innovation in <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Double-entry_bookkeeping">more than 700 years</a>, marking a transition from the legacy, stakeholder-controlled, <em>private</em>, double-entry accounting systems to a <em>public</em>, triple-entry system. </p><p>“Triple entry” simply means that two-party transactions (debit and credit) are written to a public, immutable ledger (the third entry). “Public” means that the ledger is accessible at any time by anyone on the Bitcoin network.</p><p>The accounting innovation here is simply the removal of stakeholders (humans) in exchange for machines (aka, servers and nodes) that run difficulty-adjusted proof of work (PoW). Bitcoin uses PoW to substantiate the entries, instead of relying on stakeholders who may be biased or incentivized to commit fraud or manipulate the ledgers. This means that the miners and nodes control the network in an unbiased, free-from-manipulation environment, not humans.</p><p>In contrast, all legacy accounting technologies relied on trusted third parties, known as the “stakeholders.” The fatal problem with a stakeholder-controlled system is that humans are flawed, and the ledgers are subject to human error, fraud, censorship and manipulation.</p><p>Until Bitcoin, every government, every bank, and every corporation on earth has used private, double-entry accounting systems controlled 100% by the stakeholders. This means that the stakeholders can alter the books and records of all of these legacy systems in secret, away from the public eye. In order to catch fraud, corruption or even error, the entire stakeholder-controlled system — including every transaction traced back to its root — would need to be audited. This process is time consuming, complicated and cumbersome, and like all legacy systems, the audits are conducted by humans, further subjecting the audit system to fraud, corruption and error. </p><p>Bitcoin solves this in three ways:</p><ol><li>By turning private ledgers into public ledgers</li><li>By removing stakeholder control and using difficulty-adjusted PoW to record transactions</li><li>By eliminating the need for a human audit as the network self-audits the timechain, every block</li></ol><p>Altogether, this creates the first unalterable ledger in human history.</p><h2>Accounting For The Truth With Bitcoin</h2><p>Accounting can be simply viewed as verifying the truth of the data involved. The role of accounting is to ensure that the data you are being shown is true. And accounting has never been more important in society than it is today, as truth is under constant attack in every arena. All systems rely on accounting, and the massive amount of available information makes discerning the truth difficult.</p><p>Truth is the most important commodity on the planet earth. How do you record the truth, aggregate the truth and then disseminate the truth if all the records are corruptible by humans?</p><p>Because the Bitcoin ledger is public, self-auditing and immutable, it cannot be corrupted or altered by any human. Never before in the history of record keeping could you rely on ledger to be 100% truthful, until the invention of Bitcoin.</p><p>If you are a member of a legacy, stakeholder-dominated business that relies on legacy accounting, and you have been historically able to manipulate the truth via control of the ledgers, a Bitcoin ledger is fatal.</p><p>In terms of who controls the information on ledgers, at the top of the food chain are totalitarian governments that want to control the truth. Bitcoin decimates these systems as the government, as key stakeholders, no longer has control of the information/data. That is why Bitcoin is <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/bitcoin-is-a-trojan-horse-for-freedom">often referred to as a “Trojan horse.”</a> On its face, it's presented as a technology based on money, but diving deeper, Bitcoin represents a new accounting technology that will provide increased freedom to the people within every nations' borders.</p><p>When you give people immutable data that cannot be seized, you give them freedom in the form of property rights, sound/hard money, truth, control and much more.</p><h2>Bitcoin Will Be The Ledger Of Choice For Everything</h2><p>The somewhat abbreviated way of explaining the “why” motivating people to choose Bitcoin to transact on is that the underlying ledger controlling the data is the best ledger system ever invented, free from fraud, control and manipulation, and providing freedom to those who use it. </p><p>Simply put: If you value the data you wish to record, you are incentivized to choose the only ledger in human history that will record it for eternity without being subject to human manipulation.</p><p>If you believe that an immutable unalterable ledger is superior to legacy, alterable, stakeholder ledgers, intuition suggests that all data will eventually be recorded on the Bitcoin network, from wills and trust, to corporate data, to climate data, to vaccine data, to title/ownership data and so on. The list of possibilities is endless. </p><p>All businesses, governments, and banks rely on ledgers. Nearly all industries have made groundbreaking discoveries and inventions since their inception, except for accounting. After 700 years, triple-entry systems have just now been invented (double entry <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Double-entry_bookkeeping">was invented in earnest in the 1400s</a>), and legacy stakeholder hesitance to accept an analog system moving to a digital, unalterable system should be questioned.</p><h2>Ordinals Are Just The Beginning</h2><p>Ordinals and NFTs are important to some people. The beauty of a free system is that everyone has the option to pursue what has value to them. If you believe they have zero value, you do not have to engage with them, but Bitcoin as a free market will not censor certain transactions because others do not value them. The network will always allow for innovation and free choice. Those who want to pay the appropriate fee can record Ordinals or NFT transactions on the Bitcoin network. The Bitcoin mempool in the future will always have a base layer of transactions waiting for the fees to drop low enough to be written on chain.</p><p>Since all data will want to be recorded on this network, this will not be the first or last time there is a wait to record your transaction. For smaller transactions, there are Layer 2 solutions, such as the Lightning Network, that live on top of Bitcoin and can be used immediately. Ordinals and NFTs all might go away in the future, and the transaction volume might wane, but eventually they will be replaced by other projects that similarly want to utilize this ledger, the cycle will repeat no matter what the product or data is.</p><p>Since the Bitcoin innovation is the removal of the requirement to trust the stakeholders, anyone who is advocating to censor the Bitcoin network's content is inherently anti-Bitcoin or does not understand Bitcoin. Those who seek to exploit control and power over the Bitcoin network are the exact problem that Bitcoin solves for.</p><p>As the world realizes that the only way to preserve truth (i.e., data and information) is on the Bitcoin network, the traffic will increase. This increased traffic creates a robust atmosphere for entrepreneurs to build on top of the Bitcoin network and a variety of products and services will emerge that aggregate content and write to the Bitcoin base layer.</p><p>Bitcoin fear, uncertainty and doubt (FUD) is spread by those who are challenged or fear this technology — understanding this network is no small task, it takes thousands of hours. Anyone who says they understand Bitcoin after a cursory examination is lying or ignorant. Similarly, transaction fee FUD is generated by people arguing both sides, that there are both too few transactions to support the network as well as too many transactions to support the network. </p><p>The truth is that the network is working as intended, and a full mempool that requires free market discovery to price transactions is unavoidable and thus, intended.</p><p>Accounting is the operating system that runs the world. All systems and information need to be honestly recorded, analyzed and then truthfully distributed in order to make sense of the data. Historically, ledgers have been protected by physical human violence, which means whoever has the monopoly on violence (aka, governments) can alter the records and/or its distribution. </p><p>Recording truth on the Bitcoin ledger is the only way to record data that does not rely on human violence to protect or disseminate it, for the first time in history.</p><p><em>This is a guest post by Darin Feinstein. Opinions expressed are entirely their own and do not necessarily reflect those of BTC Inc or Bitcoin Magazine.</em></p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkxNDAxMTQ0NTc1MDc1ODcz/border-wallets-seed-phrase-recovery-top-photo.png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Zoltan Pozsar, Who Just Left Credit Suisse, Addresses Issues Facing The Federal Reserve And The Dollar At Bitcoin 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[Markets analyst Zoltan Pozsar addressed issues facing the Fed, the dollar’s diminishing power and whether bitcoin can be the world’s money.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/markets/zoltan-pozsar-on-bitcoin-financial-system</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/markets/zoltan-pozsar-on-bitcoin-financial-system</guid><category><![CDATA[u.s. dollar]]></category><category><![CDATA[Bitcoin 2023]]></category><category><![CDATA[banks]]></category><category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Peter Chawaga]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 23:38:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk4MDkwMzUyMTI3NjQ4OTU4/zoltan-pozsar-bitcoin-2023.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p>Zoltan Pozsar, who <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/zoltan-pozsars-writing-is-dense-esoteric-and-a-hit-now-hes-left-credit-suisse-f2ec2483">until recently</a> worked as the managing director of investment bank Credit Suisse, offered his insight into financial markets and the issues that are weakening the dollar’s dominance around the world.</p><p>In his role at Credit Suisse, Pozsar’s insight into the ins and outs of the legacy financial system and market dynamics was highly sought after. His recent departure from the bank came shortly after <a href="https://www.investopedia.com/what-happened-at-credit-suisse-and-why-did-it-collapse-7369825">it was purchased by UBS in March</a> as an attempt to keep it from collapsing amid <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/markets/recap-of-last-weeks-banking-contagion-and-bitcoin">existential turmoil</a> for banks around the world. On stage at Bitcoin 2023, Pozsar addressed how U.S. banks have been impacted.</p><p>"This is basically an episode where the large banks are largely insulated from the problems," Pozsar said. "It's basically lessons in not being able to run interest rate risk, not knowing how to make a loan that will be weathering a rising interest rate storm.”</p><p>He described the Federal Reserve’s responses to these banking failures as only addressing “half the problem.”</p><p>“I think it's more like foaming the runway for any of the large banks that might be having problems down the road,” he added.</p><p>Pozsar was interviewed on stage by BitMEX co-founder Arthur Hayes, who pressed him on whether he owns any bitcoin.</p><p>“I don't own any,” Pozsar responded. “I'm observing it. I don't like to dabble in things that I don't understand well.”</p><p>Pozsar outlined his pessimism that bitcoin could ever really serve as money, as his historical research has shown him that money has to have a direct link to a government to endure. As a fundamentally decentralized, peer-to-peer network, Bitcoin could not support money that fits his definition.</p><p>“The one thing I will say about bitcoin is that money, if you will, is something that is purely public or a public-private partnership,” Pozsar explained. “When I look at Bitcoin, it’s a purely-private initiative. It’s clearly lacking a state link. But then again, things are evolving, there are a number of countries that have adopted bitcoin as a legal tender, so things are definitely in flux there.”</p><p>In his writing, Pozsar has underscored the <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/danrunkevicius/2022/03/10/after-this-war-is-over-money-will-never-be-the-same-what-credit-suisses-shocking-prediction-means-for-bitcoin-and-crypto-prices/?sh=2c32f3776c25">evolving role that Bitcoin is playing around the world as institution-backed money like the U.S. dollar becomes weaker</a>. At Bitcoin 2023, he listed several global market trends, including the rising economic power of China, that are threatening its role as the global reserve currency.</p><p>“There’s a number of changes happening that I think we need to keep an eye on because it’s all going to be at the expense of the dollar’s share of commodity finance, trade finance, share of reserve assets and so on,” Pozsar said.</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk4MDkwMzUyMTI3NjQ4OTU4/zoltan-pozsar-bitcoin-2023.jpg"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[The World’s Largest Bitcoin Conference Will Take Place In Nashville For 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[The Bitcoin Conference will be heading to Music City next year as it brings together Bitcoiners from around the world.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/industry-events/worlds-largest-bitcoin-conference-will-take-place-in-nashville-for-2024</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/industry-events/worlds-largest-bitcoin-conference-will-take-place-in-nashville-for-2024</guid><category><![CDATA[Nashville]]></category><category><![CDATA[Industry Events]]></category><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[The Bitcoin Conference]]></category><category><![CDATA[Events]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[BtcCasey]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 20:32:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk4MDg2MjkwOTY3NjM1MDE2/b24_press_release.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p><em>Disclaimer: The Bitcoin Conference and Bitcoin Magazine are both operated by BTC Inc.</em></p><p><a href="http://b.tc/conference">The Bitcoin Conference</a>, the world's largest and most prestigious gathering of the Bitcoin industry, is set to take place in Nashville, Tennessee, from July 25-27, 2024. The decision to move the conference to Nashville underscores the organizers' efforts to promote Bitcoin adoption beyond traditional financial centers. With a focus on fostering local adoption, the conference aims to unite thought leaders, industry experts and businesses in exploring the limitless possibilities presented by Bitcoin.</p><p>David Bailey, CEO of Bitcoin Magazine, expressed his optimism about Nashville's potential for Bitcoin growth, stating, "We believe that Nashville possesses the ideal blend of freedom-loving mindset and entrepreneurial spirit that will enable Bitcoin to thrive." The organizers are actively collaborating with local restaurants and businesses to ensure seamless bitcoin payments, transforming Nashville into a hub of bitcoin acceptance. The initiative seeks to empower both merchants and customers and establish a solid foundation for economic growth.</p><p>Mike Germano, President at BTC Inc., highlighted the significance of the conference for Nashville, stating, "We aim to foster a community where Bitcoin payments are widely accepted, unlocking new opportunities and creating a strong foundation for economic growth and preparing the city for bitcoiners to descend next July." The move has been met with enthusiasm by Bill Hagerty, United States Senator of Tennessee, who welcomed the conference, noting, "I couldn't be more excited that the 2024 Bitcoin Conference is coming to Nashville Tennessee."</p><p>Beyond the conference sessions, attendees can anticipate networking opportunities, exhibitions showcasing cutting-edge technology and interactive workshops aimed at educating and empowering individuals in the Bitcoin landscape. The inclusive environment fosters collaboration and meaningful connections among beginners and seasoned professionals alike.</p><p>Tickets for the conference are now available for purchase on the <a href="http://b.tc/conference/2024">official conference website</a>, with organizers advising interested individuals and organizations to secure their spots early due to the expected high demand. For sponsorship opportunities, media inquiries, or further information about the Bitcoin Conference, contact media@btcmedia.org.</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk4MDg2MjkwOTY3NjM1MDE2/b24_press_release.png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[First RGB-Powered NFT Marketplace Launches At Bitcoin 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[DIBA, the announced marketplace, also introduces the BitMask Bitcoin-only wallet capable of storing unique digital assets.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/first-rgb-powered-nft-marketplace-launches-at-bitcoin-2023</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/first-rgb-powered-nft-marketplace-launches-at-bitcoin-2023</guid><category><![CDATA[Business]]></category><category><![CDATA[RGB]]></category><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[NFTs]]></category><category><![CDATA[Marketplace]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[BtcCasey]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 18:54:43 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk0MzI5NzY4OTU4MjQwNDMz/bitcoin-price-market-analysis.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p><a href="https://diba.io">DIBA</a>, the first Bitcoin NFT marketplace utilizing <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/tags/rgb">RGB</a> smart contracts, has officially launched on mainnet. According to a press release sent to Bitcoin Magazine, the platform also introduces BitMask, an exclusive Bitcoin-only wallet capable of storing unique digital assets (UDAs) such as music and art. The UDAs will be hosted on high availability storage and cloud services provided by <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/tags/hut-8">Hut 8</a>, a publicly traded bitcoin miner in North America.</p><p>DIBA aims to bring Bitcoin utility to the masses by enabling the exchange of UDAs on a decentralized and censorship-resistant network. Notable bitcoin investors, including Tim Draper of Draper Associates and Bill Tai of ACTAI Unicorn Fund, support the venture. Gideon Nweze, founder and CEO of DIBA, expressed his excitement about the launch, stating, "This marks a major milestone in the transition of the internet onto Bitcoin."</p><p>Tim Draper also commended DIBA's innovative approach, emphasizing the potential of NFTs on Bitcoin. He said, "What Gideon and the team at DIBA have built is a testament to the potential NFTs on Bitcoin hold in capturing the creative and sovereign spirit of this next generation."</p><p>DIBA's partnership with Hut 8 is another example of the optimism surrounding Bitcoin and Layer 1 and 2 protocols. Josh Rayner, VP of High Performance Computing at Hut 8, expressed support for the Bitcoin NFT platform, stating, "We are bullish on Bitcoin and the potential of Layer 1 and 2 protocols, and are proud to support DIBA's Bitcoin NFT platform with high availability storage and cloud services."</p><p>According to the press release, the DIBA marketplace utilizes both the RGB smart contract protocol on Bitcoin, as well as the Lightning Network to maximize the efficiency of the marketplace’s functions.</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk0MzI5NzY4OTU4MjQwNDMz/bitcoin-price-market-analysis.png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Strike Expands Global Reach, Introduces USDT Support And Unveils Enhanced App At Bitcoin 2023 Conference]]></title><description><![CDATA[Strike announced its availability in 65 additional countries, a new app design and USDT support at Bitcoin 2023.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/strike-expands-globally-introduces-usdt-support-and-more-at-bitcoin-2023</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/strike-expands-globally-introduces-usdt-support-and-more-at-bitcoin-2023</guid><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strike]]></category><category><![CDATA[Wallet]]></category><category><![CDATA[Lightning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Business]]></category><category><![CDATA[app]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[BtcCasey]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 21:30:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk4MDY0MjU4MzIyMzQzMTAy/dscf3538-1.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p>At Bitcoin 2023 in Miami Beach, global bitcoin payments service <a href="https://strike.me">Strike</a> announced that their service is now available in 65 more countries spread across six continents. This coincides with the introduction of the ability to receive funds in U.S. dollar equivalents, namely USDT. In addition, the app received a major facelift and overhaul that has made the UI cleaner, the UX friendlier and also includes a new logo.</p><p>Many of the countries that have been requested by users of Bitcoin Twitter are now able to instantly send and receive money utilizing the Lightning Network. In an interview with Strike’s VP of Product, Manuela Rios, she explained that the app now has an effective reach of 3 billion people. </p><p>“With <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/bitcoin-enables-instant-fiat-transfers-to-africa">Send Globally,</a> the value prop is that you send dollars and receive as a local currency directly in a bank account on the other side … this one’s different — what we found through user research that people on the other side in jurisdictions with weak currencies would say ‘Hey this experience is amazing, but can I have a dollar equivalent?’” </p><p>In regards to purchasing Bitcoin, Rios said that “globally, you don’t see a seamless experience.” So the new Strike app also functions as a Lightning wallet where you can buy and sell bitcoin via dollar equivalent rails. </p><p>At his speech at Bitcoin 2023, Strike CEO Jack Mallers explained the wider vision of the updates, saying "We’re delivering a cash balance that the global south can rely on, and an awesome beautiful punk unconventional black and white brand, as the Fed is driving our own banks insolvent."</p><p>He also highlighted the company’s response to feedback, displaying a set of tweets asking for LNURL support, shortly after announcing that the new app has LNURL support — all <a href="mailto:usernames@strike.me">usernames@strike.me</a> function as a LNURL as of the launch.</p><p>“We made a lot of product changes to support what we hope to become an amazing global money app,” Mallers said. “As a company, we know what we’re fighting for, we know who we are, we changed the way we looked, but we never changed the way we felt.” </p><p>In addition to the new features and access, the app includes a simplified sign-up process in order to make signing up easier. “The end goal for us is to serve 7-8 billion people, and we’ll be stepping our way to make it to the countries that didn’t make it in this MVP,” Rios explained. </p><p>Rios explained the impact of the launch and additional features, saying that “For the Bitcoiners, you can expect a beautiful Lightning wallet and a cost effective way to buy bitcoin, and for the people not yet so familiar with bitcoin, but are familiar with 109% inflation, giving them access to a U.S. dollar equivalent stablecoin is massive — now you can save in something that won’t be so quickly devalued.”&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk4MDY0MjU4MzIyMzQzMTAy/dscf3538-1.jpg"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[‘Big Short’ Author Michael Lewis On The Financial Crisis, FTX And Bitcoin’s Freedom From Intermediaries]]></title><description><![CDATA[At Bitcoin 2023, best-selling author and journalist Michael Lewis shared his views on Bitcoin, FTX and the ills of the financial system.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/big-short-author-michael-lewis-on-bitcoin</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/big-short-author-michael-lewis-on-bitcoin</guid><category><![CDATA[Financial crisis]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[Bitcoin 2023]]></category><category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Peter Chawaga]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 21:06:32 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk4MDYzODk3Mjc2NTg5MTI4/bitcoin-2023-michael-lewis.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p>Best-selling author and journalist Michael Lewis, known for writing “The Big Short,” “Moneyball” and “The Blind Side,” offered his perspective on the current financial landscape and the rapidly-changing world of cryptocurrency on stage today at Bitcoin 2023.</p><p>“When I first encountered the idea of being able to use the blockchain technology to disintermediate financial intermediaries, I thought, ‘thank God,’” Lewis said of his realizations when first researching Bitcoin. “There are lots of unnecessary hands touching money when financial transactions occur. They've just been kind of hard baked into the system.”</p><p>As the author of “The Big Short,” Lewis outlined the fundamental inequalities and short-sighted policies of the contemporary financial system that led to the economic crisis of 2007 and 2008. At Bitcoin 2023, he acknowledged how Bitcoin is designed as an escape from the problems that caused that crisis.</p><p>“If you go back to Satoshi’s original paper, you know, line one, paragraph two, you eliminate the need for a trusted financial intermediary,” Lewis said. “Clearly, the very beginning of the spirit of the enterprise is mistrust of existing financial institutions, well earned mistrust, on the backend of the financial crisis.”</p><p>Across his books and news reporting, Lewis has been praised for his ability to condense complicated financial concepts into digestible prose and demonstrate systemic issues through the experiences of the individuals within them. This skillset makes him uniquely qualified to digest and interpret the emerging cryptocurrency ecosystem, which experienced unprecedented turmoil last year with the implosion of numerous crypto projects, <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/legal/ftx-files-for-bankruptcy-ceo-resigns">most notably FTX</a>. </p><p>At Bitcoin 2023, he discussed his next book and movie project, which will focus on FTX, and described some of the insight he gained from spending time with former CEO Sam Bankman-Fried before and after its collapse.</p><p>"Not in a million years did I think I was going to write about Sam Bankman-Fried," Lewis recalled, adding that he was first asked to meet with Bankman-Fried by a friend on Wall Street, and found himself intrigued by his unique personality. "There's so obviously the potential for a great movie in it... so you want to let people know it's out there."</p><p>Lewis was joined on stage by Arthur Hayes, the co-founder of cryptocurrency exchange BitMEX. Hayes asked Lewis if he owned bitcoin, and Lewis quipped that it was “in the FTX bankruptcy.”</p><p>Hayes and Lewis also touched on the current banking crisis, with Lewis sharing the view that things have not really changed in the institutional system since 2008 — that, if anything, things are worse for retail investors.</p><p>“It seems inherently unstable right now,” he said. “You essentially created a handful of institutions that are too big to fail, and everyone knows their deposits are insured, so no other institution can actually compete in that environment… It’s not going to end until there’s some structural reform.”</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk4MDYzODk3Mjc2NTg5MTI4/bitcoin-2023-michael-lewis.jpg"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Speaking At Bitcoin 2023, Tulsi Gabbard Describes How A U.S. CBDC Threatens Freedom]]></title><description><![CDATA[Former congresswoman and presidential candidate Tulsi Gabbard described how CBDCs threaten freedom at the Bitcoin 2023 event.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/tulsi-gabbard-on-u-s-freedom-at-bitcoin-2023</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/tulsi-gabbard-on-u-s-freedom-at-bitcoin-2023</guid><category><![CDATA[U.s.]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Bitcoin 2023]]></category><category><![CDATA[cbdc]]></category><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Peter Chawaga]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 20:32:15 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk4MDYzMzM5NDY3NzExNjc4/tulsi-gabbard-bitcoin-2023.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p>Former congresswoman and presidential candidate Tulsi Gabbard addressed the audience at Bitcoin 2023 today, focusing on the institutional problems with U.S. politics and elected leaders who seek to consolidate power rather than serve constituents.</p><p>“I served in Congress for eight years and ran for president in 2020, and while we like to have this idea that we have great courageous leaders in Washington … unfortunately, that’s not the case,” Gabbard said. “Ultimately, they’re driven by a fear of losing power and losing control and, at the heart of it, they’re afraid of us. They’re afraid of a free society.”</p><p>In particular, she highlighted the Biden administration’s<a href="https://www.whitehouse.gov/briefing-room/statements-releases/2022/03/09/fact-sheet-president-biden-to-sign-executive-order-on-ensuring-responsible-innovation-in-digital-assets/"> exploration of a central bank digital currency (CBDC)</a>, underscoring how such a project would be antithetical to the privacy- and freedom-preserving qualities of cash transactions. As outlined in its white paper by Satoshi Nakamoto, “<a href="https://bitcoin.org/bitcoin.pdf">Bitcoin: A Peer-To-Peer Electronic Cash System</a>,” Bitcoin was designed to preserve these qualities in a digital way.</p><p>“The Biden administration’s move toward implementing a central bank digital currency is their latest effort towards exerting control and taking away our freedom,” Gabbard said. “No matter how many flowery words they use to deny that there is ill intent… no matter how many times they say, ‘Hey this is for your own good’... But ultimately, we know this is about their insatiable mission and desire for total control.”</p><p>She also suggested that those in power are combative toward or disinterested in Bitcoin because it cannot be manipulated by any third parties.</p><p>“You would think they would be interested in how Bitcoin is transforming the lives of people around the world, but they don’t actually care about people,” she said.</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk4MDYzMzM5NDY3NzExNjc4/tulsi-gabbard-bitcoin-2023.jpg"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Robert Kennedy Jr. Makes Campaign Debut At Bitcoin 2023: ‘Free Money Is As Important As Free Expression’]]></title><description><![CDATA[Making his first public appearance as a presidential candidate, Robert F. Kennedy Jr. outlined his vision for supporting Bitcoin and freedom in the U.S.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/robert-kennedy-jr-debuts-campaign-at-bitcoin-2023</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/robert-kennedy-jr-debuts-campaign-at-bitcoin-2023</guid><category><![CDATA[u.s. president]]></category><category><![CDATA[Politics]]></category><category><![CDATA[U.s.]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[Bitcoin 2023]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Peter Chawaga]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 18:37:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk4MDYxNDk3NzMyMDQ3OTQ0/robert-kennedy-jr-makes-campaign-debut-at-bitcoin-2023.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p>Robert F. Kennedy Jr. made his first public appearance as a presidential candidate at the Bitcoin 2023 conference today, sharing his own experiences with Bitcoin, warning about how technology is enabling government totalitarianism around the world and describing how he would protect the rights of Bitcoiners if elected president.</p><p>“As president, I will make sure that your right to hold and use bitcoin is inviolable,” Kennedy said. "I am an ardent defender and lifelong defender of civil liberties and Bitcoin is both an exercise and a guarantee of those freedoms.”</p><p>Kennedy told the crowd that he was first inspired by Bitcoin as a critical freedom technology after learning about how it was used to circumvent financial restrictions <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/how-bitcoin-fueled-canada-trucker-convoy">during the Canadian trucker protest last year</a>.</p><p>“None of these lawful and peaceful protestors had violated any law… But suddenly, they found that they could not access their money, their bank accounts to pay their mortgages or feed their families,” he recalled. “When I witnessed this … devastating use of government repression, I realized for the first time how free money is as important as free expression.”</p><p>Kennedy has publicly expressed his support for Bitcoin <a href="https://twitter.com/RobertKennedyJr/status/1653808786577010697?lang=en">since May 2023</a>, acknowledging its separation from other cryptocurrencies and indicating that legislators should support its development rather than hinder it, as with regulations like the <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/legal/biden-administration-proposes-30-tax-on-energy-used-by-bitcoin-miners">Biden administration’s proposed tax on energy used by miners</a>. On stage, he reinforced his distaste for such regulations and he outlined the steps his administration would take to drive Bitcoin innovation in the U.S.</p><p>"First, I will defend the right of self custody of bitcoin and other digital assets," he said. “Second, I will uphold the right to run a node at home… Third, I will defend use-neutral, industry-neutral regulation of energy… Fourth, I will make sure that the United States remains the global hub of Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies… I will reverse the government’s growing hostility toward this industry.” </p><p>Finally, he said that he would look closely at “whether individuals like Ross Ulbricht,” the founder of <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/silk-road-ross-ulbricht-from-prison">darknet, bitcoin-based marketplace Silk Road</a> who received a double life sentence in 2013, were prosecuted “for actual crimes, or as a means to crackdown on crypto.”</p><p>“I will consider pardoning them and I will act very quickly to do so,” Kennedy added.</p><p>Kennedy<a href="https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/robert-kennedy-jr-launches-long-shot-presidential-bid/story?id=98691944"> launched his Democratic primary bid</a> shortly before <a href="https://twitter.com/RobertKennedyJr/status/1653808786577010697?lang=en">signaling support for the Bitcoin industry on Twitter</a> and <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/industry-events/bitcoin-2023-is-robert-f-kennedy-jr-s-first-event-as-presidential-candidate">announcing his Bitcoin 2023 appearance</a>. His public stances on issues like vaccine mandates and climate change have contradicted those of most mainstream Democrats and he has positioned himself <a href="https://www.foxnews.com/media/rfk-jr-dems-party-war-americans-cant-afford-emergency">as a party outsider</a>. As of this writing, he sits in second place, though trailing by a significant margin, to Joe Biden <a href="https://www.racetothewh.com/2024/dem">in national polling average</a>.</p><p>At Bitcoin 2023, Kennedy clarified that he is not personally invested in bitcoin and announced that his presidential campaign would be the first in history to accept donations via the Lightning Network.</p><p>"We are now living in this age of turnkey totalitarianism ... and our job is to try and build and fortify democratic institutions at the same rate,” he concluded. “The biggest, most important one on the horizon is Bitcoin, because it can't be manipulated.”</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk4MDYxNDk3NzMyMDQ3OTQ0/robert-kennedy-jr-makes-campaign-debut-at-bitcoin-2023.jpg"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Governor Ridwan Kamil And Samson Mow Describe The Future Of Bitcoin In Indonesia At Bitcoin 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[The populous country would benefit greatly from taking advantage of the abundant renewable energy available.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/the-future-of-bitcoin-in-indonesia-at-bitcoin-2023</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/the-future-of-bitcoin-in-indonesia-at-bitcoin-2023</guid><category><![CDATA[Renewable Energy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Indonesia]]></category><category><![CDATA[Bitcoin 2023]]></category><category><![CDATA[Mining]]></category><category><![CDATA[Adoption]]></category><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[BtcCasey]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 15:13:36 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk4MDU4MjAxMzQ0NjQ4MjY0/keh_8762.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p>Governor of the Indonesian Province of West Java, Ridwan Kamil and prominent Bitcoin global advocate and JAN3 CEO Samson Mow, revealed in a fireside chat titled "The Indonesia Bitcoin Mining Campaign" that the government of Indonesia is researching various ways in which bitcoin adoption in the country could benefit its people.</p><p>Governor Kamil explained the specific environment that makes Indonesia a potential major player in the bitcoin mining space, saying “[Indonesia has] the second most geothermal potential in the world — more than 800 rivers with hydropower. As bitcoin allows the transformation of energy into money, bitcoin could be transformative for indonesia”</p><p>He also explained that the country is already on a steady path towards adoption, with more than 12 million cryptocurrency investors, 70% of which are invested in bitcoin. According to Governor Kamil, this number grows by half a million a year. </p><p>In addition, the Governor touched on how bitcoin could bring financial technology to people in his country who currently do not have access to that. “Bitcoin is a solution in my opinion to unbankable parts of my society,” he explained. “40% of my people are unbankable.” </p><p>Another topic touched on was the recent introduction of an Omnibus bill that allows for 100% foreign investment into renewable energy projects above 1 MW. This bill could lead to increased investment and attention in the region. “Come to indonesia, lets have this big reserve of renewable energy dedicated to the bitcoin mining business,” Governor Kamil said. </p><p>Mow touched on the opportunity at hand for Indonesia, saying that “The first [countries] that adopt bitcoin in a meaningful way will have a big advantage.” Afterwards, Governor Kamil inquired about the way that El Salvador’s bitcoin bonds function. Mow replied that “The bonds can finance the buildout of new energy infrastructure … Indonesia could have a volcano bond too.”</p><p>Overall, the talk indicated that Governor Kamil is cautiously optimistic, and that he sees bitcoin as a potential game changer for the economy of his country and the livelihood of his people. As a country with access to major amounts of renewable energy and large portions of the population unbanked, it is seemingly ripe for bitcoin adoption. </p><p>"The new generation is buying Bitcoin as a reserve," Governor Kamil concluded. “Hopefully Indonesia will be a Bitcoin heaven in the future."</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk4MDU4MjAxMzQ0NjQ4MjY0/keh_8762.jpg"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[The World’s Largest Payroll Providers Can Now Use Bitwage To Pay Employees In Bitcoin]]></title><description><![CDATA[Employers using payroll providers like ADP, Paychex and Paycom can now utilize Bitwage to easily pay their employees in their preferred currency.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/bitwage-announces-payroll-solution-compatible-with-major-providers</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/bitwage-announces-payroll-solution-compatible-with-major-providers</guid><category><![CDATA[Bitwage]]></category><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[Paycheck]]></category><category><![CDATA[Payroll]]></category><category><![CDATA[Business]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[BtcCasey]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 15:05:52 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkzODM5Njc4ODI5MzcyOTEy/network-nodes.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p><a href="https://www.bitwage.com">Bitwage</a>, a leading provider of Bitcoin payroll and invoicing, has introduced a solution that allows employers to seamlessly connect their payroll providers to Bitwage's service. This development simplifies and ensures compliance for workers who wish to receive a percentage of their paycheck in Bitcoin, stablecoins or USD. Notably, this solution is compatible with various payroll providers, including ADP, Paychex, Paycom, Gusto, Trinet and many others.</p><p>According to a press release sent to Bitcoin Magazine, what sets Bitwage apart is its non-custodial experience, ensuring that employees receive their payments directly into the wallet of their choice, maximizing security and minimizing risk. </p><p>To implement this solution, companies need to sign up on the Bitwage platform and connect their payroll provider through the Bitwage Automated Connection. From there, Bitwage creates a custom, post-tax benefit on the payroll provider's portal, allowing employees to opt-in. Employees can then choose the amount they wish to be deducted from their paycheck and distributed through Bitwage.</p><p>With each pay cycle, Bitwage automatically generates a payroll for each employee based on their payroll preferences, extracting the necessary data directly from the payroll system. Employees can receive their payments directly into their preferred Bitcoin, crypto or stablecoin wallet or even as their local currency into their bank accounts.</p><p>Bitwage's CEO, Jonathan Chester, emphasized their mission to enable workforces to be paid in their preferred method, whether it's bitcoin or fiat. “We recognize that crypto can be scary for employers, so to enable this mission, we are building out fully compliant solutions and removing the complexities and custodial risk of crypto from the equation,” Chester said.</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkzODM5Njc4ODI5MzcyOTEy/network-nodes.png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Brink Announces $1 Million Donation-Matching Campaign From Marathon Digital Holdings For Bitcoin Development]]></title><description><![CDATA[Marathon Digital Holdings will match donations made to Brink to support Bitcoin development, for as much as a $1 million total this year.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/brink-million-dollar-bitcoin-donation-campaign</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/brink-million-dollar-bitcoin-donation-campaign</guid><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[brink]]></category><category><![CDATA[development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Bitcoin 2023]]></category><category><![CDATA[Marathon Digital Holdings]]></category><category><![CDATA[Donations]]></category><category><![CDATA[Business]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Peter Chawaga]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 21:43:13 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk4MDQxMjk5NTc0NTk2Njgw/bitcoin-2023-brink-marathon-digital-donation-campaign.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p>On stage at the Bitcoin 2023 conference, <a href="https://brink.dev/">Brink</a> announced a matching campaign for donations from Bitcoin mining firm <a href="https://marathondh.com/">Marathon Digital Holdings</a> to support the work of Bitcoin Core developers. Marathon will match donations made to Brink on a two-for-one basis for the duration of the conference, which ends on May 20, and then match donations one for one through the end of the year, up to $1 million total.</p><p>“We’re going to match dollar for dollar $500,000-worth of donations that Brink receives for Core developers. More importantly, we will donate two-for-one if you donate money during this conference,” said Fred Thiel, Marathon’s CEO. “So, if you believe in the importance of supporting Core development efforts … then I strongly urge you (to) donate 50 cents, $1, whatever you can during the conference.”</p><p>By committing to match all third-party donations up to an aggregate of $500,000 until December 31, 2023, Marathon hopes to advance Brink’s support for the developers who maintain and upgrade Bitcoin’s code. <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/technical/john-newberys-new-nonprofit-brink-will-train-and-support-bitcoin-developers">Since 2020</a>, Brink has supported numerous developers in their work to make Bitcon more accessible and advanced through grants, mentorship and education, including <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/bitcoin-non-profit-brink-funds-11-bitcoin-lightning-developers">former lead maintainer Marco Falke, Lightning Network white paper author Tadge Dryja</a> and <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/bitcoin-non-profit-brink-funds-11-bitcoin-lightning-developers">Bitcoin Core PR Review Club’s Gloria Zhao</a>.</p><p>“We have nine developers in five different countries that are all independent developers funded by Brink,” explained Mike Schmidt, the executive director of Brink. “I think we would all agree that we would want this Bitcoin software that’s powering all of this innovation on top to be better reviewed, better tested, better maintained, easier to run and more performant. So that’s why at Brink we fund grantees that are spending upwards of 50% of their time on testing and reviewing the Bitcoin Core code, proposing changes to the Core codebase and basically making that software more secure.”</p><p>Donations made to Brink through <a href="https://brink.dev/donate">its website</a> are now eligible for the match. Thiel framed the campaign as part of Marathon’s larger commitment to securing the Bitcoin network as a significant contributor of hash rate, the computing power that ensures Bitcoin’s immutability.</p><p>“We believe that it’s the most secure protocol out there and we think we and the rest of the industry should do everything they can to support the developers and really foment as much activity in the space as possible,” Thiel said.&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk4MDQxMjk5NTc0NTk2Njgw/bitcoin-2023-brink-marathon-digital-donation-campaign.jpg"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[IBEX Mercado Announces Partnership With Grupo Salinas Bringing Lightning Access To Millions Of Mexican Citizens]]></title><description><![CDATA[The partnership kicked off with one of Mexico’s largest internet providers, Total Play, partnering with IBEX to integrate bitcoin Lightning payments.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/bitcoin-lightning-service-ibex-mercado-announces-partnership-with-grupo-salinas</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/bitcoin-lightning-service-ibex-mercado-announces-partnership-with-grupo-salinas</guid><category><![CDATA[Ricardo Salinas]]></category><category><![CDATA[Mexico]]></category><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[Lightning]]></category><category><![CDATA[IBEX Mercado]]></category><category><![CDATA[Business]]></category><category><![CDATA[IBEX]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[BtcCasey]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 21:42:41 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkyODY4MzAyMTgyMjI5NzEy/markets-price-chart.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p><a href="https://www.poweredbyibex.io/">IBEX Mercado</a>, a bitcoin Lightning payment service provider, has announced a new partnership with Grupo Salinas, one of the largest corporate conglomerates in Mexico.</p><p>“Over four million Mexicans can now pay with bitcoin for their cable, internet, and phone service,” IBEX’s CEO Jose Lemus said on stage as he announced the partnership. “With this partnership, we’re opening the doors to every bitcoin and Lightning company and financial tech company that wants to leverage Lightning technology … [we will be] rolling out new technology with Grupo Salinas that will enable mexicans to pay their groceries with bitcoin, electronics and to receive remittances.” Lemus explained his excitement about the announcement, saying that this is the “tip of the iceberg of what will go on in Mexico.” </p><p>The collaboration signifies a major step in Mexico's adoption of bitcoin and Lightning. In addition, the integration of Lightning payments via IBEX with Total Play opens up new possibilities for fast and efficient transactions for Total Play customers.</p><p>“The true value of this technology is not about paying for a cup of coffee in a different way,” Lemus said. “In a world where we’re going to have increasing digitization of our products and services, we need better payment technology … we did not have a good enough payments technology — but now we do, with Lightning.” </p><p>Integration of bitcoin Lightning in Grupo Salinas’ products and services via IBEX can place Mexico at the forefront of the digital revolution, providing citizens with a secure, modern and efficient payment option.</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkyODY4MzAyMTgyMjI5NzEy/markets-price-chart.png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[MicroBT Releases New Line Of WhatsMiner M50 Series At Bitcoin 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[The M50S++, M53S++ and M56S++ boast impressive stats that maximize efficiency while simultaneously boosting potential environmental benefits.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/microbt-releases-new-line-of-whatsminer-m50-series</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/microbt-releases-new-line-of-whatsminer-m50-series</guid><category><![CDATA[Mining]]></category><category><![CDATA[MicroBT]]></category><category><![CDATA[whatsminer]]></category><category><![CDATA[Business]]></category><category><![CDATA[Asics]]></category><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[Bitcoin 2023]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[BtcCasey]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 20:25:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkwOTE3NzExNjQ2MTcyNzU3/aa-btc-4.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p>MicroBT, the Bitcoin ASIC manufacturer behind the <a href="https://www.whatsminer.com/index.html">WhatsMiner</a> line of ASIC mining machines, unveiled its latest offerings at Bitcoin 2023 in Miami Beach. Dr. Zuoxing Yang, the founder and CEO of MicroBT, highlighted the importance of "High density, low noise, low failure rate and low maintenance” ASIC machines bringing bitcoin mining to a new era.</p><p>The talk started with a roll of film focusing on the energy crisis, green energy and the role that bitcoin can play as a solution. It then posed the question: “What matters more, mining or surviving?” </p><p>“I never stop thinking of better power solutions for bitcoin mining,” Dr. Yang said. </p><p>MicroBT introduced three new models of the WhatsMiner M50 series: the air-cooled M50S++, the hydro-cooled M53S++, and the immersion cooled M56S++. These models offer impressive computing power ranging from 150 to 320 terahash/second (TH/s) respectively, with power efficiencies of 22 joules per terahash (J/TH).</p><p>Dr. Yang highlighted the heat collection capabilities of the mining rigs, which can be utilized for various purposes, such as space heating and industrial processes. He mentioned that the hydro-cooling mining rigs can reach outlet water temperatures of over 70℃ (158℉), enabling 2.4MW of power for a 40-foot container. Additionally, the immersion-cooling solution requires only 10L of oil per miner, demonstrating its efficiency.</p><p>He emphasized that “every M56 miner only requires as low as 10L oil with our specified tank.” </p><p>MicroBT's focus since its inception in 2016 has been the development of high-efficiency Bitcoin mining rigs. The company aims to support miners in adhering to Bitcoin's decentralization principles while prioritizing network stability. Dr. Yang emphasized MicroBT's commitment to working with partners to promote sustainable mining practices, zero-carbon emissions and social responsibility.</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkwOTE3NzExNjQ2MTcyNzU3/aa-btc-4.png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[BitMEX To Send Physical Bitcoin To The Moon In Partnership With Astrobiotic Technology And Bitcoin Magazine]]></title><description><![CDATA[A physical coin loaded with 1 BTC, along with the Genesis Block text, will venture beyond the atmosphere on a space launch this summer.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/bitmex-to-send-physical-bitcoin-to-the-moon</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/bitmex-to-send-physical-bitcoin-to-the-moon</guid><category><![CDATA[Moon]]></category><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[Moon Landing]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Bitmex]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[BtcCasey]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 19:55:12 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkzMjU1NjA1NDIxNDgzNTg3/bitcoin-to-the-moon.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p>BitMEX, a leading bitcoin derivatives exchange, has announced that it will be sending the first physical bitcoin to the Moon in partnership with Astrobotic Technology Inc. and Bitcoin Magazine. The rocket carrying a physical Bitcoin wallet is scheduled to launch from the Kennedy Space Center this summer, marking a significant milestone for both space exploration and the bitcoin industry.</p><p>The bitcoin, engraved with a public address and private key, is loaded with 1 BTC and will become the first-ever financial asset sent to space. This endeavor symbolizes the exploration of Bitcoin's use cases beyond Earth and opens up possibilities for future interaction with the token. Stephan Lutz, Acting CEO and Group CFO at BitMEX, expressed pride in the achievement, stating, "This is not just an achievement for BitMEX, but a breakthrough in human history."</p><p>According to a press release sent to Bitcoin Magazine, the mission has undergone rigorous testing and preparation to ensure the Bitcoin wallet's readiness for space flight.</p><p>In addition to the physical bitcoin, the text of the Genesis Block, the first block of Bitcoin ever mined, will be carried to the Moon as a homage to Satoshi's protocol. The Genesis Block will be displayed on a metal plate with raw hex data and a hologram of the Bitcoin Magazine logo.</p><figure>
        <img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk4MDgzODE0OTE4OTg4ODcy/bitcoin-moon-rock---front.jpg" height="464" width="620">
        
        
        
    </figure><figure>
        <img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk4MDgzODE0OTE5MDU0NDA4/bitcoin-moon-rock---left-34.jpg" height="464" width="620">
        
        
        
    </figure><p>A replica of the coin and Genesis Block metal plate, placed on a "moon rock" will be auctioned in partnership with Bitcoin Magazine at Bitcoin 2023. In addition, a limited edition series of commemorative coins and Ordinals will be auctioned closer to the launch date.</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkzMjU1NjA1NDIxNDgzNTg3/bitcoin-to-the-moon.png"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk4MDgzODE0OTE4OTg4ODcy/bitcoin-moon-rock---front.jpg" height="464" width="620" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk4MDgzODE0OTE5MDU0NDA4/bitcoin-moon-rock---left-34.jpg" height="464" width="620" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lava Introduces Self-Custody Wallet And Bitcoin DeFi Platform At Bitcoin 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[Lava utilizes discreet log contracts and other Bitcoin-native mechanisms to provide a full-fledged Bitcoin financial service platform.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/lava-introduces-self-custody-wallet-and-bitcoin-defi-platform</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/lava-introduces-self-custody-wallet-and-bitcoin-defi-platform</guid><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[Self Custody]]></category><category><![CDATA[Wallet]]></category><category><![CDATA[dlcs]]></category><category><![CDATA[defi]]></category><category><![CDATA[Lending]]></category><category><![CDATA[Business]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[BtcCasey]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 16:54:13 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkxNzU0OTcxNDk3MTEzMjUx/20220819_best-sidechain-recap---shinobi.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p><a href="http://lava.xyz/">Lava</a>, a financial technology company, has unveiled a new self-custody wallet and decentralized finance (DeFi) platform on Bitcoin. Utilizing Lava's loan protocol, users can borrow stablecoins against native bitcoin, eliminating the risks associated with bridge hacks and custodian rehypothecation.</p><p>CEO Shehzan Maredia highlighted the advantages of Lava's borrowing mechanism, stating, "With Lava, people can borrow transparently without rehypothecation risk and without relying on bridges or custodians. Users won't have to trust their counterparty and can borrow using a system that gives users cryptographic assurance that the rules of their contracts will be honored." Lava achieves this through invisible smart contracts called <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/technical/dlcs-on-lightning-and-bitcoin-smart-contracts">discreet log contracts</a> (DLCs), which ensure collateral integrity and enable programmable loan initiation and repayment without the need for intermediaries.</p><p>According to a press release sent to Bitcoin Magazine, Lava wallet aims to empower individuals who face challenges with traditional banking, offering innovative security solutions and safety checks to prevent transaction errors. Maredia said that he envisions bitcoin and dollars as the two most crucial assets of the coming decade. Lava's goal, the press release stated, is to create a bitcoin and dollar-centric financial experience that grants users true financial freedom, enabling them to take control of their finances and simplify money management.</p><p>In an interview, Maredia expressed gratitude to his cofounder, team, investors, and supporters, emphasizing that this is only the beginning for Lava. The company said it intends to continue advancing its mission of making finance sovereign and simple.</p><p>Lava's self-custody wallet is currently available on mobile platforms, including iOS and Android, with plans for additional interfaces in the future. </p><p>The company said it intends to differentiate itself from other self-custody wallets through its user-centered financial utility experience including offering borrowing against bitcoin, direct purchases of bitcoin and stablecoins, seamless bank account transfers and simplified transactions. Security is a top priority — Lava stated that there will be future enhancements like collaborative custody and cold wallet integration.</p><p><em>Disclosure: Lava is a portfolio company of BTC Inc., the parent company of Bitcoin Magazine.</em></p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkxNzU0OTcxNDk3MTEzMjUx/20220819_best-sidechain-recap---shinobi.png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cash App, Lighting Labs, Lightspark Executives Discuss Bringing Bitcoin Payments To The World]]></title><description><![CDATA[In a panel discussion at Bitcoin 2023, leaders from some of the largest Bitcoin-focused companies discussed building on the Lightning Network.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/building-lightning-network-companies</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/building-lightning-network-companies</guid><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[Lightspark]]></category><category><![CDATA[Cash App]]></category><category><![CDATA[Lightning network]]></category><category><![CDATA[Business]]></category><category><![CDATA[Lightning Labs]]></category><category><![CDATA[Bitcoin 2023]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Peter Chawaga]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 16:13:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk4MDM2MTQxNTg3MzEwMDE5/fwbgj1mwaaqn5h9.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p>In a panel discussion at the Bitcoin 2023 conference moderated by CNBC technology reporter <a href="https://twitter.com/KenzieSigalos">MacKenzie Sigalos</a>, leaders from some of the biggest businesses building services based on the Lightning Network discussed the opportunities and challenges for Bitcoin’s payments-focused second layer protocol.</p><p>The discussion, titled “Building Lightning-Native Companies,” featured <a href="https://twitter.com/starkness">Elizabeth Stark</a>, the CEO of software development firm Lightning Labs; <a href="https://twitter.com/davidmarcus">David Marcus</a>, the CEO of <a href="https://www.lightspark.com/">Lightspark</a>, a firm focused on making Lightning adoption easier and more accessible; and <a href="https://twitter.com/milessuter">Miles Suter</a>, the Bitcoin product lead at <a href="https://cash.app/">Cash App</a>, a mobile payment platform that <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/cash-app-enables-bitcoin-lightning-payments-for-40-million-users">introduced Lighting payments to its more than 40 million users in 2022</a>.</p><p>"We've really reached the point right now where Lightning is maturing and we're seeing more and more adoption,” Stark said, summarizing the momentum she has seen since she co-founded Lightning Labs in 2016. “People are adopting the network because it is solving real problems for them."</p><p>By allowing peers to create closed payment channels between themselves, which are only settled on the underlying Bitcoin blockchain when closed, the Lightning Network <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/guides/lightning-network">enables bitcoin payments that can take place in seconds while still benefiting from the security of Bitcoin’s base ledger</a>. But as this second layer is <a href="https://lightning.network/lightning-network-paper.pdf">relatively young</a>, adoption represents <a href="https://bitcoinvisuals.com/lightning">just a fraction</a> of the larger digital payments volume across the world.</p><p>The panelists highlighted the importance of developing products and services that make Lightning easier to use and solve some of its outstanding issues, like the network’s relatively-low liquidity and limited number of nodes.</p><p>“A channel-based payment network is still very complicated,” Sigalos pointed out. “There’s not a ton of liquidity sitting on the nodes right now” for instance.</p><p>In response, Suter noted that many of the challenges in making Lightning more accessible derive from Bitcoin’s most important qualities.</p><p>"It's hard to develop on Bitcoin,” he explained. “We see that everyday... but it's an intentional decision because we believe that's what allows it to maintain a very minimal attack surface.”</p><p>But the panelists all agreed that when there are significant problems for Lightning to solve, like in countries where it can help people access the dollar or enable more efficient cross-border transactions, adoption is evident. As more of those problems emerge and companies like these continue to build products and services on top of Lightning, they expect adoption to accelerate.</p><p>“Making it easy will drive more adoption,” Marcus said. “Between now and next year when we gather again, we’ll be in a much better place when it comes to Lightning adoption.”</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk4MDM2MTQxNTg3MzEwMDE5/fwbgj1mwaaqn5h9.jpg"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Lightning Company Lightspark Introduces Lightspark Wallet SDK]]></title><description><![CDATA[The SDK is designed to offer businesses and platforms an easily accessible Lightning wallet experience.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/lightspark-introduces-lightspark-wallet-sdk</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/lightspark-introduces-lightspark-wallet-sdk</guid><category><![CDATA[Business]]></category><category><![CDATA[Lightning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Lightspark]]></category><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[BtcCasey]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkyNjA3MTM2MjI2NzQ4MTUz/20220926_good-gdog-proof-collaborative-custody-multisig-by-will-schoellkopf_.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p>Lightspark has announced the launch of the Lightspark Wallet SDK, a tool designed to enable businesses of all sizes the ability to offer their customers a Lightning wallet. According to a press release sent to Bitcoin Magazine, Lightspark aims to make the Lightning Network more accessible and mainstream, ensuring that payments are open, secure and instant.</p><p>The press release explained that the Lightspark Wallet SDK is the result of careful consideration of businesses' needs and feedback from customers. The SDK is tailored for seamless usage by businesses of all sizes and stages, the company stated, with easy integration and the ability to add unique UI and brand identity. It aims to simplify the complexity of Lightning payments, allowing businesses to focus on building exceptional user experiences without worrying about technical intricacies such as setting up channels and rebalancing liquidity.</p><p>The SDK also incorporates Lightspark Predict, which offers low latency, high payment success rates, and low costs, ensuring reliable and capital-efficient Lightning payments, according to the press release. By leveraging Lightspark Predict, the release explained, businesses gain better connectivity to the wider Lightning Network, enhancing reliability and certainty when sending and receiving Lightning payments.</p><p>Also highlighted by the company, were recent partnerships which proved the growing adoption of Lightning amongst businesses. Xapo Bank <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/xapo-bank-first-bank-to-offer-bitcoin-lightning">became the first bank to integrate</a> with the Lightning Network via Lightspark, allowing its members to pay for small purchases with bitcoin directly, without converting to USD first. </p><p>In addition, Lightspark highlighted partnerships with Rain, the largest crypto-asset platform in the MENA region, which is enabling its users to execute real-time bitcoin transactions using Lightspark, and Flexa, a digital commerce integration provider that has leveraged Lightspark “to help businesses navigate to the next era of commerce.”</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkyNjA3MTM2MjI2NzQ4MTUz/20220926_good-gdog-proof-collaborative-custody-multisig-by-will-schoellkopf_.png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[With Rushed Moratorium On Bitcoin Mining, North Carolina County Stifles Innovation]]></title><description><![CDATA[“This improperly-enacted moratorium is low-hanging fruit and Bitcoiners need to press public officials like those in Buncombe County…”]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/north-carolina-bitcoin-mining-moratorium</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/north-carolina-bitcoin-mining-moratorium</guid><category><![CDATA[Regulation]]></category><category><![CDATA[North Carolina]]></category><category><![CDATA[Opinion]]></category><category><![CDATA[Business]]></category><category><![CDATA[Bitcoin mining]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Dennis Fassuliotis]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTg4NDU1MzQ3MzAyNzA0NzU2/bitcoin-mining-asic-security.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p><em>This is an opinion editorial by Dennis Fassuliotis, founder of South Carolina Blockchain Inc. and co-founder of South Carolina Emerging Technology Association, Inc.</em></p><p>Why is the <a href="https://www.citizen-times.com/story/news/local/2023/05/04/buncombe-county-approves-a-1-year-moratorium-on-cryptocurrency-mining/70179529007/">Buncombe County, North Carolina moratorium on Bitcoin mining</a> so important?</p><p>Because they got caught. </p><p>There is a contagion running through Western North Carolina and this time, we know it was man made in a lab. It is called a “moratorium on bitcoin mining.” Its origins <a href="https://www.clayconc.com/_files/ugd/fe4bcd_163aefda66f243cfb4f8c41bd27ebce5.pdf">date back to August 2022 in Clay County</a>, and Buncombe County has mutated it into this newest strain based on broadly construing a North Carolina zoning statute to authorize a development moratorium. </p><p>When properly used, North Carolina’s <a href="https://www.ncleg.gov/EnactedLegislation/Statutes/PDF/BySection/Chapter_160D/GS_160D-107.pdf">development moratorium statute</a> <a href="https://www.sog.unc.edu/resources/legal-summaries/land-use-and-development-moratoria">seeks to ensure that a new type of development does not proceed until changes to regulations or environmental issues are appropriately addressed</a>. This allows for more effective planning and management of growth and development while minimizing potential negative impacts on the community.</p><p>Because a moratorium is a drastic restriction on property rights, the statute imposes conditions that an administrative authority must satisfy to get one. Even then, such a moratorium can only span <a href="https://www.ncleg.gov/EnactedLegislation/Statutes/PDF/BySection/Chapter_160D/GS_160D-107.pdf">a minimum of 61 days</a> and a maximum of one year, as noted by the planning commissioner <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=A3e09Xulteg">during a recent public briefing</a>. </p><p>In this case, Buncombe County commissioners, <a href="https://www.citizen-times.com/story/news/local/2023/05/04/buncombe-county-approves-a-1-year-moratorium-on-cryptocurrency-mining/70179529007/">under the direction of Planning Director Nathaniel Pennington</a>, argued that they needed a one-year moratorium on cryptocurrency mining in the unincorporated areas of Buncombe County <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=A3e09Xulteg">so they could study the industry</a> and “<a href="https://www.citizen-times.com/story/news/local/2023/05/04/buncombe-county-approves-a-1-year-moratorium-on-cryptocurrency-mining/70179529007/">craft standards for the newly-defined use.</a>” </p><p>But we already have a workable definition for a bitcoin mine, <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/legal/drive-bitcoin-right-through-south-carolina">as confirmed in my last opinion editorial</a>,<a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/legal/drive-bitcoin-right-through-south-carolina"> </a>where I referred to a bitcoin mine as a “digital asset data center.” So, let’s just simply define a “bitcoin mining center” as a data center that produces an intangible product. </p><p>That’s now where the rubber meets the road. At the February 2023 commission meeting, armed with the American Planning Association’s “<a href="https://www.planning.org/publications/document/9249180/">Zoning for Data Centers and Cryptocurrency Mining</a>,” <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=A3e09Xulteg">Pennington argued</a> that cryptocurrency mining centers don’t meet the definition of a data center under existing North Carolina law. </p><p>The North Carolina statute that enables data mining center tax breaks <a href="https://www.datacenterknowledge.com/archives/2015/10/01/north-carolina-makes-data-center-tax-breaks-easier-to-get">was enacted in 2015</a>, just six years after the birth of bitcoin. Consequently, most states, including North Carolina, are living with statutes tailored for centralized data center operations and incentives that were carved out to attract corporate data centers built by companies like Google, which include large campuses, consume vast amounts of water and require huge amounts of power. Qualified data centers receive sales tax exemption on electricity. </p><p>As a result, North Carolina’s data mining center laws <em>in practice</em> offer big money for the benefit of a select few tech corporations, but the overarching <em>intent</em> of this legal framework was to promote economic development in North Carolina. Rather than follow the original intent of the data center definition to create opportunities, it’s now the club that is being used to discourage siting digital asset data centers in some western North Carolina counties. </p><p>However, in his rush to pass an ordinance where there were no permit applications pending, the planning director failed to include a “statement of the problems or conditions necessitating the moratorium <em> </em>and [that’s the operative word] what courses of action, alternative to a moratorium, were considered … and why those alternative courses of action were not adequate,” as is required by the <a href="https://www.ncleg.gov/EnactedLegislation/Statutes/PDF/BySection/Chapter_160D/GS_160D-107.pdf">North Carolina General Assembly’s moratoria guidelines</a>.</p><p>So, in my eyes, the planning commission has failed to complete the due diligence legally required to impose a moratorium and appears to be acting with a bias intended to discourage Bitcoin miners from locating in Buncombe County. </p><p>Now that Buncombe County’s overreach has been caught and called out, do we catch and release or seize the opportunity to counter <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=A3e09Xulteg">unfounded claims</a> of e-waste, noise, water consumption and public safety concerns to get this moratorium overturned by the county’s commissioners or the court system?</p><p>This improperly-enacted moratorium is low-hanging fruit and Bitcoiners need to press public officials like those in Buncombe County who don’t do their job properly or exert a bias without doing their homework. Someone should be held accountable and, in this case, all fingers point in the direction of the Buncombe County Planning Commission and the American Planning Association. </p><p>The way in which Bitcoin mining is treated presents a pivotal moment for Buncombe County’s innovation economy. With their hastily and improperly enacted moratorium, Buncombe County’s commissioners failed to rise to the occasion. </p><p>Rather than ban a perfectly-legal activity that they do not fully understand, the commissioners could have created a countywide task force, but that was never presented as an option. A task force could study the pros and cons of digital assets, while planning could have a seat at the table and serve all of their constituents, not just a vocal minority. That should have been the objective. Instead, the adopted policy stifles innovation and advances a false narrative. </p><p>I know this has not gone unnoticed at the state level and the <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/legal/north-carolina-house-passes-bill-banning-cbdc-payments">recent <em>unanimous</em> vote to advance an anti-central-bank-digital-currency (CBDC) bill</a> after <a href="https://twitter.com/NC_Blockchain/status/1649571425726898176?s=20">public uproar</a> resulted in revising a prior anti-Bitcoin bill tells me that progress can be made. Education on all levels is still the key. Hopefully, the Buncombe County commissioners will learn to join the cause or miss out on one of the most important emerging tech industries driving adoption of the soundest money ever invented.</p><p><em>This is a guest post by Dennis Fassuliotis. Opinions expressed are entirely their own and do not necessarily reflect those of BTC Inc or Bitcoin Magazine.</em></p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTg4NDU1MzQ3MzAyNzA0NzU2/bitcoin-mining-asic-security.png"/></item></channel></rss>