<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:bnmedia="https://news.bitcoin.com/">

<channel>
	<title>Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/</link>
	<description>Daily Bitcoin News</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 19:57:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Binance US Halts USD Deposits, Withdrawals — Asks Users to Withdraw Dollars by June 13</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/binance-us-halts-usd-deposits-withdrawals-asks-users-to-withdraw-dollars-by-june-13/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Kevin Helms]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 01:30:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchanges]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance US crypto only]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance US USD deposits]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance.us]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Changpeng Zhao]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=592660&#038;preview=true&#038;preview_id=592660</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/binance-us-usd-deposits-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Binance US Suspends USD Deposits Following SEC Lawsuit, Shifts to Crypto-Only Platform" decoding="async" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/binance-us-usd-deposits-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/binance-us-usd-deposits-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/binance-us-usd-deposits-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/binance-us-usd-deposits-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/binance-us-usd-deposits-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/binance-us-usd-deposits-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/binance-us-usd-deposits.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />Binance US has informed its users that U.S. dollar deposits have been suspended and USD withdrawals will no longer be processed. The crypto exchange has asked customers to withdraw dollars by June 13 as it transitions into a crypto-only trading platform. The move followed a lawsuit against the crypto exchange and several other Binance entities [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/binance-us-usd-deposits-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Binance US Suspends USD Deposits Following SEC Lawsuit, Shifts to Crypto-Only Platform" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/binance-us-usd-deposits-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/binance-us-usd-deposits-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/binance-us-usd-deposits-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/binance-us-usd-deposits-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/binance-us-usd-deposits-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/binance-us-usd-deposits-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/binance-us-usd-deposits.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>Binance US has informed its users that U.S. dollar deposits have been suspended and USD withdrawals will no longer be processed. The crypto exchange has asked customers to withdraw dollars by June 13 as it transitions into a crypto-only trading platform. The move followed a lawsuit against the crypto exchange and several other Binance entities by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).</strong></p>
<h2>Binance US Suspends Dollar Deposits, Withdrawals</h2>
<p>Binance US made an announcement Thursday regarding the suspension of U.S. dollar deposits and withdrawals following an &#x201C;aggressive&#x201D; enforcement action taken by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).</p>
<p>The securities watchdog <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/binance-faces-legal-action-by-sec-for-violating-us-securities-laws/">filed charges</a> against several  entities on Monday, including Binance Holdings, which operates Binance.com; its U.S.-based affiliate BAM Trading Services, which operates Binance US; and Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao (CZ). The regulator followed up with an emergency action application the next day, seeking a temporary restraining order to <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/sec-seeks-court-approval-to-freeze-binance-us-crypto-assets-citing-customer-safety-concerns/">freeze</a> assets held by Binance US. The SEC also filed charges against the Nasdaq-listed crypto exchange <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/coinbase-becomes-the-latest-target-of-sec-accused-of-unregistered-brokerage-and-securities-violations/">Coinbase</a> on Tuesday.</p>
<p>&#x201C;The SEC has taken to using extremely aggressive and intimidating tactics in its pursuit of an ideological campaign against the American digital asset industry,&#x201D; the official Twitter account for Binance US wrote Thursday, adding that the SEC&#x2019;s action &#x201C;has created challenges for the banks with whom we work.&#x201D; The exchange continued:</p>
<blockquote><p>In an effort to protect our customers and platform, today we are suspending USD deposits and notifying customers that our banking partners are preparing to pause fiat (USD) withdrawal channels as early as June 13, 2023. We encourage customers to take appropriate action with their USD.</p></blockquote>
<p>In addition, Binance US <a href="https://support.binance.us/hc/en-us/articles/15133607064983-Binance-US-Will-Remove-10-Trading-Pairs-Has-Paused-OTC-Trading-Updated-">informed</a> customers that it will remove select <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/BTC" 311996  target="_blank">BTC</a> and BUSD advanced trading pairs. &#x201C;We have also decided to streamline our buy, sell & convert offering and have paused our OTC trading portal,&#x201D; the exchange noted.</p>

<p>The platform additionally clarified that it is transitioning into a crypto-only exchange, stating on its website:</p>
<blockquote><p>Binance.US will become a crypto-only exchange. Please withdraw USD by June 13, 2023.</p></blockquote>
<p>&#x201C;Any USD balances remaining on the platform after June 15, 2023, may be converted to stablecoin that can be withdrawn on-chain,&#x201D; Binance US noted, emphasizing that &#x201C;Cryptocurrency services remain fully operational, including crypto trading, staking, deposits, and withdrawals.&#x201D; Moreover, Binance US stressed that it maintains a 1:1 reserve for all customer assets.</p>
<p>In a letter to its users, Binance US stated that &#x201C;the SEC has brought unjustified civil claims against our business, from which we will continue to vigorously defend ourselves, our customers, our partners, and industry.&#x201D; The exchange similarly tweeted Thursday that it &#x201C;will continue to vigorously defend ourselves, our customers, and industry against the meritless attacks of the SEC.&#x201D;</p>
<p><em><strong>What do you think about Binance US becoming a crypto-only trading platform? Let us know in the comments section below.</strong></em></p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/binance-us-usd-deposits-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[#Binance US has informed its users that U.S. dollar #deposits have been suspended and USD #withdrawals will no longer be processed. #SEC #crypto #cryptocurrency]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA["Please withdraw USD by June 13, 2023," #Binance US wrote. #crypto #cryptocurrency]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitmex Group CEO: US Crypto Crackdown May Drive Top Talent to &#8216;Markets With More Regulatory Certainty and Lower Risk&#8217;</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/bitmex-group-ceo-us-crypto-crackdown-may-drive-top-talent-to-markets-with-more-regulatory-certainty-and-lower-risk/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Terence Zimwara]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 23:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Interview]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BitMex]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitmex ceo]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MiCA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web3]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=592535</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/mex-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Bitmex Group CEO: US Crypto Crackdown May Drive Top Talent to &#039;Markets With More Regulatory Certainty and Lower Risk&#039;" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/mex-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/mex-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/mex-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/mex-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/mex-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/mex-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/mex.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />Unlike in the United States where authorities are cracking down on the crypto industry, the regulations governing the industry are &#8220;more clearly defined and commercially viable in markets like Hong Kong, Singapore, and the UAE,&#8221; Stephan Lutz, the group CEO and CFO of the crypto exchange Bitmex, has said. U.S. Crackdown Driving Away Talent In [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/mex-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Bitmex Group CEO: US Crypto Crackdown May Drive Top Talent to &#039;Markets With More Regulatory Certainty and Lower Risk&#039;" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/mex-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/mex-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/mex-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/mex-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/mex-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/mex-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/mex.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>Unlike in the United States where authorities are cracking down on the crypto industry, the regulations governing the industry are &#8220;more clearly defined and commercially viable in markets like Hong Kong, Singapore, and the UAE,&#8221; Stephan Lutz, the group CEO and CFO of the crypto exchange Bitmex, has said. </strong></p>
<h2>U.S. Crackdown Driving Away Talent</h2>
<p>In his written answers to questions from Bitcoin.com News, Lutz hailed regulatory frameworks such as the one adopted by Hong Kong&#8217;s Securities and Futures Commission because it &#8220;provide[s] standards for digital assets that are crucial for this fast-growing asset class.&#8221;</p>
<p>Concerning the likely impact on innovation of the United States government&#8217;s so-called Operation Choke Point 2.0, the  Group CEO concurred with many crypto proponents who argue that such a clampdown will only drive away talent. The crackdown has and will indirectly benefit Hong Kong which according to Lutz is attempting to make itself &#8220;the epicenter of the crypto industry in Asia.&#8221; The CEO also touched on Bitmex&#8217;s product offering and why the crypto exchange is not offering services such as high-risk lending services.</p>
<p>Below are Lutz&#8217;s detailed answers to all questions sent to him via Telegram.</p>
<p><strong>Bitcoin.com News (BCN): Stephen, regulators in the U.S. appear to have stepped up enforcement actions against crypto companies. There are also allegations that the regulators are trying to &#8220;de-bank&#8221; crypto. Can you shed light on the recent developments and what this so-called Operation Choke Point 2.0 is all about?</strong></p>
<p><strong>Stephan Lutz (SL):</strong> After months of growing regulatory scrutiny and legal enforcement against crypto companies and their service providers in the United States, aka Operation Choke Point 2.0, we started to see the first evasion effects with local champions such as Coinbase and Gemini announcing plans to grow in offshore markets &#8211; evidence that they are shifting resources to attract international clients, with Asia being the focus.</p>
<p>While the U.S. is choking the crypto industry and the EU has lower interest from users combined with a smaller market, Asian markets have a broad customer base with access to services. Consequently, Asia is the horse to bet on in the near-midterm, with some CIS markets like Turkey and UAE as the second fastest-growing market segment.</p>
<p>Foreseeing competition to intensify and embracing forthcoming changes, we double down on our commitment to product innovation and building the best trading experience for crypto derivative traders.</p>

<p><strong>BCN: The U.S. regulatory crackdown against crypto could scare some developers and companies. If the enforcement actions continue without regulatory clarity, do you think it could slow the pace of innovation in the United States?</strong></p>
<p><strong>SL:</strong> Yes, as there is a risk of top talent moving to markets that offer more regulatory certainty and lower risk, such as Singapore, Hong Kong, Europe, and the UAE.</p>
<p><strong>BCN: Even if some crypto projects want to shift base to another location, it often takes more than just favorable regulations to convince them to move to a different country or jurisdiction. What makes Asian jurisdictions like Hong Kong, Singapore, or Dubai attractive destinations for such companies?</strong></p>
<p><strong>SL:</strong> I believe that the Asian digital assets market is poised for a bright future, with a supportive regulatory environment, an active venture capital market, and a diversified talent pool. Regulation is more clearly defined and commercially viable in markets like Hong Kong, Singapore, and the UAE. Since China is experimenting with CBDCs, Chinese banks in Hong Kong are now actively asked to support crypto businesses. To a money manager that means China is preparing for the asset class, making it a much lower risk to allocate funds to it than say six months ago.</p>
<p>Those who visited Hong Kong in the past few weeks must have observed the Web3 spirit in the city. It’s clearly positioning itself to reclaim its position as the epicenter of the crypto industry in Asia, with a government that is embracing blockchain technology and actively competing with other Fintech hubs around the world.</p>
<p><strong>BCN: Your company Bitmex has most of its operations and users in Asia meaning you may have some first-hand experience with Asian regulatory and market conditions. Despite China&#8217;s apparent anti-crypto stance, do you think Hong Kong can thrive as a crypto hub?</strong></p>
<p><strong>SL:</strong> Historically, Hong Kong has not just been one of the most popular breeding grounds for crypto innovations, but also where Bitmex first emerged. We believe the Securities and Futures Commission’s regulatory framework is a significant milestone for our industry as it will provide standards for digital assets that are crucial for this fast-growing asset class.</p>
<p>On a personal level, I’m delighted to see the administration&#8217;s commitment to building a Web3 digital economy, starting with establishing clear guardrails and regulations. We are optimistic that Hong Kong will achieve its ambition of becoming a world-leading Web3 role model city and potentially the Web3 hub for China in years to come.</p>
<p><strong>BCN: Bitmex primarily offers crypto derivatives trading to institutional and professional traders rather than the retail crypto audience. What does your exchange offer to institutions and professionals that other exchanges don’t?</strong></p>
<p><strong>SL:</strong> Bitmex offers the safety of assets, a solid and reliable exchange business without offering any high-risk lending services that could potentially derail the organization, an active community of experienced traders connected in the Bitmex Trollbox, leading BTC-margined contracts, and one of the fastest API-trading interfaces in the market. And, in all honesty, we are one of the few platforms that are not printing fake volumes.</p>
<p><strong>BCN: Crypto has financial as well as non-financial use cases, with applications in a wide range of industries. So, what, in your opinion, are the key points that regulators should look at to build a fair regulatory model?</strong></p>
<p><strong>SL:</strong> Unlike the United States, we can see Europe moving forward with a regulatory framework called Markets In Crypto Assets (MICA) for cryptocurrencies and stablecoins that are not regulated by its existing financial services legislation.</p>
<p><em><strong>What are your thoughts about this interview? Let us know what you think in the comments section below. </strong></em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/mex-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA["There is a risk of top talent moving to markets that offer more regulatory certainty and lower risk, such as Singapore, Hong Kong, Europe and the UAE," the CEO warned. #cryptoregulation #mica]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA["We are optimistic that Hong Kong will achieve its ambition of becoming a world-leading #Web3 role model city and potentially the Web3 hub for China in years to come," Lutz said. ]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Digital Asset Trust Firm Bitgo Sets Sights on Prime Trust Acquisition </title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/digital-asset-trust-firm-bitgo-sets-sights-on-prime-trust-acquisition/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jamie Redman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 21:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abra]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Acquisition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[banking partners]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bankruptcy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BitGo]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ceo]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Collaboration]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto assets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto custodian]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[custody]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Base]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital Asset]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Equity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[exchange network]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[financial struggles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[founder]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[funding round]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[infrastructure]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[legal dispute]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[letter of intent]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Liquidity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[network]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nevada]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OKcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[parent company]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[payment networks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prime Trust]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[regulated]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Settlement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Speculation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Swan Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[trust firm]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=592621</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/bitgo-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Digital Asset Trust Firm Bitgo Sets Sights on Prime Trust Acquisition " decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/bitgo-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/bitgo-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/bitgo-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/bitgo-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/bitgo-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/bitgo-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/bitgo.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />In a recent development, Bitgo, the digital asset trust firm, disclosed that it has penned a letter of intent to acquire Prime Trust, a crypto custodian based in Nevada. Should the acquisition proceed, Prime Trust would become an integral part of Bitgo&#8217;s network of regulated trust companies. Bitgo Signs Letter of Intent to Acquire Crypto [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/bitgo-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Digital Asset Trust Firm Bitgo Sets Sights on Prime Trust Acquisition " decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/bitgo-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/bitgo-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/bitgo-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/bitgo-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/bitgo-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/bitgo-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/bitgo.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>In a recent development, Bitgo, the digital asset trust firm, disclosed that it has penned a letter of intent to acquire Prime Trust, a crypto custodian based in Nevada. Should the acquisition proceed, Prime Trust would become an integral part of Bitgo&#8217;s network of regulated trust companies.</strong></p>
<h2>Bitgo Signs Letter of Intent to Acquire Crypto Custodian Prime Trust Amid Speculative Chatter</h2>
<p><a href="https://www.bitgo.com/">Bitgo</a> reports that they have signed a letter indicating their intent to acquire <a href="https://www.primetrust.com/">Prime Trust</a>. The announcement follows <a href="https://twitter.com/DavidFBailey/status/1666573243879178246?s=20">speculative chatter</a> and <a href="https://twitter.com/ODELL/status/1666856343259561984?s=20">multiple rumors</a> on <a href="https://twitter.com/epodrulz/status/1666868685242335232?s=20">social media</a> that <a href="https://twitter.com/i/spaces/1ynJOapoVLWKR">suggest</a> Prime Trust was grappling with financial struggles and potential bankruptcy. Last year, Prime Trust found itself in a legal dispute with the now-defunct crypto lender <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/crypto-lender-celsius-to-be-acquired-by-novawulf-exiting-chapter-11/">Celsius</a> after they accused the custodian of failing to return $17 million in crypto assets in August 2022.</p>
<p>In October 2022, Prime Trust consented to return the $17 million and stated that it would transfer the funds to a wallet designated by Celsius. Prior to Celsius&#8217; grievance in August, the custodian had <a href="https://www.crunchbase.com/organization/prime-trust">secured</a> $107 million during a Series B funding round over a month earlier in June. Preceding the Series B, Prime Trust&#8217;s Series A round raised $65 million in July 2021. Following the crypto winter in 2022, however, two unnamed sources <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/01/30/crypto-services-company-prime-trust-lays-off-one-third-of-staff/">reported</a> that Prime Trust laid off one-third of its employees in early 2023.</p>
<p>On June 8, 2023, Bitgo <a href="https://blog.bitgo.com/bitgo-signs-letter-of-intent-to-acquire-prime-trust-to-expand-digital-asset-and-fintech-b1868391784a">unveiled</a> its intention to procure Prime Trust and obtain full equity from parent company Prime Core Technologies.</p>
<p>“This is a landmark transaction, leading a greater shift in the digital asset landscape toward a more secure and sustainable future,” Bitgo CEO and co-founder Mike Belshe said on Thursday. “With the expected acquisition of Prime Trust, Bitgo is well positioned to enhance its best-in-class, trusted solutions and to service the combined customer base.”</p>

<p>Prime Trust collaborated with entities such as <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/abra-ceo-bullish-ethereum-predicts-eth-could-hit-40000/">Abra</a>, Okcoin, Augeo, <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/wealthy-investors-and-family-offices-embrace-btc-following-bank-failures-says-swan-bitcoin-executive/">Swan Bitcoin</a>, and Trusttoken. Swan Bitcoin <a href="https://help.swanbitcoin.com/hc/en-us/articles/14874253038743-New-Partners-at-Swan-May-2023-">disclosed</a> this May that it had shifted its assets into custody with Fortress Trust and Bitgo. <a href="https://twitter.com/nic__carter/status/1666800690235158528?s=20">Speculation</a> has also circulated on social media regarding Scott Purcell founding both Prime Trust — which he left in August 2021 after over five years — and Fortress Trust in October 2021. In a <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/feed/update/urn:li:activity:7072603363242086400/">Linkedin post</a>, Purcell rejected any connection between the two companies, highlighting he exited Prime Trust two years prior.</p>
<p>“There is absolutely zero connection between Fortress Trust and Prime Trust,” Purcell wrote. “Quite the opposite as at times we find ourselves competing with them. We are a very different company, from our exec team to our technology infrastructure.”</p>
<p>On Thursday, Bitgo announced that incorporating Prime Trust&#8217;s infrastructure and exchange network will fortify Bitgo&#8217;s offerings in terms of &#8220;custody, liquidity, settlement, and regulatory compliance.&#8221; Additionally, the Palo Alto-based firm will acquire Prime Trust&#8217;s banking partners, crypto IRA, and existing payment networks if the acquisition materializes. “The combination of Prime Trust and Bitgo would be a significant enhancement for the industry,” stated Jor Law, Prime Trust&#8217;s interim CEO and president on Thursday.</p>
<p><em><strong>What are your thoughts on Bitgo&#8217;s planned acquisition of Prime Trust? Share your thoughts and opinions about this subject in the comments section below.</strong></em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/bitgo-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[Digital asset trust firm #Bitgo reports that they have signed a letter indicating their intent to acquire Prime Trust. ]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA[Digital asset trust firm #Bitgo reports that they have signed a letter indicating their intent to acquire Prime Trust. ]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Two Russians Charged for Infiltrating Mt Gox and Operating Illicit Crypto Exchange, BTC-e</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/two-russians-charged-for-infiltrating-mt-gox-and-operating-illicit-crypto-exchange-btc-e/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jamie Redman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 19:30:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Aleksandr Verner]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Alexander Vinnik]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Alexey Bilyuchenko]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin theft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC-e]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cyber-criminals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hacking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[indictment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Money Laundering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mt Gox]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Russian individuals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[unauthorized access]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[unlawful exchange]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=592681</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/cheee68888-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Two Russians Charged for Infiltrating Mt Gox and Operating Illicit Crypto Exchange, BTC-e" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/cheee68888-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/cheee68888-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/cheee68888-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/cheee68888-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/cheee68888-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/cheee68888-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/cheee68888.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />In a statement issued on Friday, the U.S. Department of Justice (DOJ) revealed that two Russian individuals have been accused of infiltrating a cryptocurrency exchange and running an unlawful exchange. Reportedly, the pair gained unauthorized access to Mt Gox&#8217;s servers from 2011 to 2014 and purportedly pilfered 647,000 bitcoins from the now-dissolved exchange. Russian Duo [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/cheee68888-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Two Russians Charged for Infiltrating Mt Gox and Operating Illicit Crypto Exchange, BTC-e" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/cheee68888-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/cheee68888-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/cheee68888-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/cheee68888-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/cheee68888-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/cheee68888-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/cheee68888.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>In a statement issued on Friday, the U.S. Department of Justice (DOJ) revealed that two Russian individuals have been accused of infiltrating a cryptocurrency exchange and running an unlawful exchange. Reportedly, the pair gained unauthorized access to Mt Gox&#8217;s servers from 2011 to 2014 and purportedly pilfered 647,000 bitcoins from the now-dissolved exchange.</strong></p>
<h2>Russian Duo Accused of Orchestrating Mt Gox Heist and Operating Underground Crypto Exchange</h2>
<p>The U.S. government has <a href="https://www.justice.gov/opa/pr/russian-nationals-charged-hacking-one-cryptocurrency-exchange-and-illicitly-operating-another">charged</a> two Russians for breaching Mt Gox and managing the former crypto exchange BTC-e. The defendants, Alexey Bilyuchenko and Aleksandr Verner, are believed by authorities to have collaborated with Alexander Vinnik in running BTC-e.</p>
<p>As stated in the indictment, “As alleged in the indictments, starting in 2011, Bilyuchenko and Verner stole a massive amount of cryptocurrency from Mt Gox, contributing to the exchange’s ultimate insolvency. Armed with the ill-gotten gains from Mt Gox, Bilyuchenko allegedly went on to help set up the notorious BTC-e virtual currency exchange, which laundered funds for cyber criminals worldwide,” remarked Kenneth Polite Jr., the assistant attorney general of the Justice Department&#8217;s Criminal Division.</p>
<p>A <a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.cand.299278/gov.uscourts.cand.299278.1.0.pdf">2016 indictment</a> was unveiled alongside the press release, revealing more details about the relationship between Mt Gox and BTC-e. The indictment alleges that &#8220;Bilyuchenko, Verner, and their co-conspirators&#8221; initially accessed Mt Gox in September 2011 and managed to siphon funds from its wallets. “From September 2011 through at least May 2014, Bilyuchenko, Verner, and their co-conspirators allegedly caused the theft of at least approximately 647,000 bitcoins from Mt Gox,” asserts the DOJ.</p>

<p>BTC-e, <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/us-may-consider-alexander-vinnik-for-prisoner-exchange-with-russia-lawyer-says/">Alexander Vinnik</a>, and Russian nationals have all been implicated in hypotheses surrounding Mt Gox&#8217;s demise long ago. In 2019, reports <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2019/09/12/2-billion-lost-in-mt-gox-bitcoin-hack-can-be-recovered-lawyer-claims/">stated</a> that Russian attorney Alexander Zheleznikov from ZP Legal alleged his firm was aware of who the Russian nationals were and tied Mt Gox to the operators of BTC-e. In their latest discovery, the DOJ claims that the pair worked with an unnamed bitcoin brokerage service, referring to it as the &#8220;New York Bitcoin Broker&#8221; in the indictment.</p>
<p>A fabricated advertising agreement was allegedly concocted between Bilyuchenko, Verner, and the New York Bitcoin Broker to camouflage and liquidate bitcoins taken from Mt Gox. &#8220;Bilyuchenko and Verner supposedly made regular requests to the owner and operator of the New York Bitcoin Broker to transfer large sums into various offshore bank accounts, including those under the names of shell corporations managed by Bilyuchenko, Verner, and their co-conspirators,&#8221; details the DOJ&#8217;s charges and unveiled court indictment.</p>
<p><em><strong>What do you think about the DOJ’s charges against the two Russian nationals? Share your thoughts and opinions about this subject in the comments section below.</strong></em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/cheee68888-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[The U.S. government has charged two Russians for breaching #MtGox and managing the former crypto exchange BTC-e.]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA[The U.S. government has charged two Russians for breaching #MtGox and managing the former crypto exchange BTC-e.]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Robinhood to Delist Cardano, Solana, and Polygon Amidst SEC Regulatory Pressure</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/robinhood-to-delist-cardano-solana-and-polygon-amidst-sec-regulatory-pressure/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jamie Redman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 17:30:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ada]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto firm]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[delisting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fintech]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[matic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[regulatory scrutiny]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robinhood]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robinhood Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robinhood Polygon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robinhood Solana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC enforcement actions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOL]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=592662</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/rob-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Robinhood to Delist Cardano, Solana, and Polygon Amidst SEC Regulatory Pressure" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/rob-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/rob-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/rob-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/rob-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/rob-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/rob-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/rob.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />Fintech and crypto firm Robinhood has announced the delisting of cardano (ADA), solana (SOL), and polygon (MATIC) on June 27, 2023. This development comes after the publicly-listed company revealed that it was &#x201C;actively reviewing&#x201D; its coin listings in the wake of recent U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) enforcement actions against Binance and Coinbase. Robinhood [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/rob-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Robinhood to Delist Cardano, Solana, and Polygon Amidst SEC Regulatory Pressure" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/rob-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/rob-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/rob-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/rob-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/rob-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/rob-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/rob.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>Fintech and crypto firm Robinhood has announced the delisting of cardano (<a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/ADA" 312018  target="_blank">ADA</a>), solana (SOL), and polygon (MATIC) on June 27, 2023. This development comes after the publicly-listed company revealed that it was &#x201C;actively reviewing&#x201D; its coin listings in the wake of recent U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) enforcement actions against Binance and Coinbase.</strong></p>
<h2>Robinhood Shakes Up Crypto Offerings, Delists Cardano, Solana, and Polygon</h2>
<p>Robinhood, a financial services company headquartered in Menlo Park, California, intends to remove the 8th, 10th, and 11th largest crypto assets by market capitalization on June 27. The decision was disclosed in a <a href="https://robinhood.com/us/en/support/articles/cardano-polygon-solana-update/">blog post</a> published on June 9, which indicates that cardano (<a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/ADA" 312018  target="_blank">ADA</a>), solana (SOL), and polygon (MATIC) will be taken off Robinhood&#x2019;s platform.</p>
<p>In a statement released on Friday, Robinhood said, &#x201C;We regularly review the crypto we offer on Robinhood. Based on our latest review, we&#x2019;ve decided to end support for cardano (<a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/ADA" 312018  target="_blank">ADA</a>), polygon (MATIC), and solana (SOL) on June 27th, 2023 at 6:59 PM ET.&#x201D; The company further reassured users that &#x201C;no other coins are affected and your crypto is still safe on Robinhood.&#x201D;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This announcement comes amid increasing regulatory scrutiny of <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/us-sec-identifies-12-crypto-tokens-as-securities-in-binance-lawsuit/">Binance</a> and <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/coinbase-becomes-the-latest-target-of-sec-accused-of-unregistered-brokerage-and-securities-violations/">Coinbase</a> by the U.S. SEC. After lawsuits were filed against both companies by the SEC, Robinhood </span><a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/robinhood-actively-reviewing-listed-coins-after-sec-sues-binance-and-coinbase/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">declared</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> that it was &#x201C;actively reviewing&#x201D; its coin offerings. Dan Gallagher, Robinhood&#x2019;s Chief Legal Compliance and Corporate Affairs Officer, told Bloomberg that this review aimed to &#x201C;determine what, if any, actions to take.&#x201D;</span></p>

<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Should Robinhood clients fail to sell or transfer their <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/ADA" 312018  target="_blank">ADA</a>, MATIC, or SOL holdings before the deadline, the company will dispose of the assets at their fair market value. &#x201C;After the deadline, any <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/ADA" 312018  target="_blank">ADA</a>, MATIC, and SOL still in your Robinhood Crypto account will be sold for market value and the proceeds will be credited to your Robinhood buying power,&#x201D; Robinhood elaborated.</span></p>
<p><em><strong>What are your thoughts on Robinhood&#x2019;s delisting of Cardano, Solana, and Polygon? Do you believe it&#x2019;s a necessary move in light of regulatory actions, or do you see it as a potential setback for the platform&#x2019;s crypto offerings? Share your thoughts and opinions about this subject in the comments section below.</strong></em></p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/rob-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA["Based on our latest review, we’ve decided to end support for #Cardano (ADA), #Polygon (MATIC), and #Solana (SOL)," Robinhood said. ]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA["Based on our latest review, we’ve decided to end support for #Cardano (ADA), #Polygon (MATIC), and #Solana (SOL)," Robinhood said. ]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Revolutionizing AI: GAIMIN Unleashes the Power of High-Powered, Distributed Gaming PCs to Fuel AI Models</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/revolutionizing-ai-gaimin-unleashes-the-power-of-high-powered-distributed-gaming-pcs-to-fuel-ai-models/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Media]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press release]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[GAIMIN]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=592507&#038;preview=true&#038;preview_id=592507</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="436" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/unnamed-2023-06-08t202945-058-768x436.png" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/unnamed-2023-06-08t202945-058-300x170.png 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/unnamed-2023-06-08t202945-058-1024x581.png 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/unnamed-2023-06-08t202945-058-768x436.png 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/unnamed-2023-06-08t202945-058-1536x872.png 1536w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/unnamed-2023-06-08t202945-058-190x107.png 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/unnamed-2023-06-08t202945-058.png 1600w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />PRESS RELEASE. GAIMIN (www.gaimin.io), the world’s leader in delivering decentralised data processing power through gaimin.cloud (www.gaimin.cloud), is delighted to announce GAIMIN is the world’s first company to power AI modelling computations through high powered distributed gaming PCs. AI processing requires significant amounts of computational power, typically handled by the GPU due to its high performance [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="436" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/unnamed-2023-06-08t202945-058-768x436.png" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/unnamed-2023-06-08t202945-058-300x170.png 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/unnamed-2023-06-08t202945-058-1024x581.png 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/unnamed-2023-06-08t202945-058-768x436.png 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/unnamed-2023-06-08t202945-058-1536x872.png 1536w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/unnamed-2023-06-08t202945-058-190x107.png 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/unnamed-2023-06-08t202945-058.png 1600w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>PRESS RELEASE. </strong><b>GAIMIN (</b><a href="http://www.gaimin.io"><b>www.gaimin.io</b></a><b>), the world’s leader in delivering decentralised data processing power through gaimin.cloud (<a href="http://www.gaimin.cloud">www.gaimin.cloud</a>), is delighted to announce GAIMIN is the world’s first company to power AI modelling computations through high powered distributed gaming PCs. </b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">AI processing requires significant amounts of computational power, typically handled by the GPU due to its high performance mathematical processing capabilities. However, the GPU as a device is very much in demand across a number of different industries, more notably within the growing gaming community who use the GPU to enhance their gaming experience, thereby spreading the reach and availability of devices. Research by GAIMIN indicates that GPUs in high performance computers, such as a gaming PC, are underutilised. The most powerful devices are more than capable of supporting competing processing requirements, such as gaming, whilst also delivering other data processing services with no impact on performance. Also, with most gaming computers typically only used for 20% of the day, there is a significant amount of underutilised data processing power available. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">GAIMIN has created a distributed high-powered computing (HPC) network (</span><a href="http://www.gaimin.cloud"><span style="font-weight: 400;">www.gaimin.cloud</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">), harnessing the underutilised processing power within gaming PCs. Users participating in gaimin.cloud receive payment and rewards for allowing their devices to accept data processing jobs from GAIMIN. Designed with flexibility for service provision, gaimin.cloud currently supports the rendering of videos and powering of blockchain computations and has recently been extended to support the data processing requirements of various AI Models. Following a period of testing, this service will be added into gaimin.cloud to extend the monetization options through the GAIMIN app (www.gaimin.gg).</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Martin Speight, CEO of GAIMIN commented, “With the global limited availability of GPU devices combined with the growing need for GPU-based processing power, GAIMIN’s world-wide network of GPU-based data processing power distributes data processing services globally, using devices that are already operational. GAIMIN rewards users in GAIMIN’s soon to be listed cryptocurrency, GMRX, and also through the ability to earn Digital Game Assets (DGAs), enhancing their gaming experience.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Buki Ben-Natan, CTO for GAIMIN, and the designer of this solution, stated, “By innovatively harnessing the power of existing CPU and GPU resources, we have successfully bridged the gap between AI applications and computational scarcity, unlocking endless possibilities for industries seeking to take the next big leap forward.&#8221;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Martin added, “GAIMIN will offer a cost-effective and hassle-free solution for small and medium-sized businesses to access the power of AI without the need for expensive infrastructure and technical expertise. With our pay-per-use service, businesses can easily integrate AI into their workflows and achieve better results without having to worry about hosting servers or managing complex systems.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Over the coming months, GAIMIN will be adding more AI Models into its platform, augmenting the AI data processing capabilities of the GAIMIN app and extending the monetization aspects available to GAIMIN users participating in gaimin.cloud and helping mitigate the world-wide demand for data processing services. </span></p>
<p><b>About GAIMIN</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">GAIMIN.IO Ltd (GAIMIN) is a UK and Swiss-based gaming company focused on helping the gaming community monetize the computational power of their gaming PC. GAIMIN has created a decentralized data processing network harnessing underutilized processing power typically found in gaming PCs to create a world-wide decentralized data processing network, delivering supercomputer performance. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">With a free-to-download PC-based application, GAIMIN monetizes the under utilised performance through innovative approaches to delivering supercomputer-level data processing performance from a world-wide network of independent processing devices which power GAIMIN.CLOUD. Focusing initially on video rendering and AI data processing, with an always available service to power blockchain computations, the GAIMIN data processing network is continuously delivering data processing services and returning rewards back to its user community. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">GAIMIN rewards users in its own cryptocurrency, GMRX which can then be used for purchases on the GAIMIN Marketplace for NFTs, in-game assets, accessories, and merchandise, or it can be converted to fiat or a different cryptocurrency.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">For more information on GAIMIN click on this link: </span><a href="http://www.gaimin.io/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">www.gaimin.io</span></a></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">To download the GAIMIN app, please go to </span><a href="http://www.gaimin.gg"><span style="font-weight: 400;">www.gaimin.gg</span></a></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">For up-to-date information, please follow the following GAIMIN social media accounts:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Facebook: </span><a href="https://www.facebook.com/Gaimin.io"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.facebook.com/Gaimin.io</span></a></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Instagram: </span><a href="https://www.instagram.com/gaimin_io/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.instagram.com/gaimin_io/</span></a></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Twitter: </span><a href="https://twitter.com/GaiminIo"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/GaiminIo</span></a></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">LinkedIn: </span><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/gaimin/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.linkedin.com/company/gaimin/</span></a></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">YouTube: </span><a href="https://www.youtube.com/c/Gaimin"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.youtube.com/c/Gaimin</span></a></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Telegram: </span><a href="https://t.me/officialgaimin"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://t.me/officialgaimin</span></a></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Discord: </span><a href="https://discord.gg/SmYsmVS8x7"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://discord.gg/SmYsmVS8x7</span></a></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">TikTok: </span><a href="https://www.tiktok.com/@gaimin.gg"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.tiktok.com/@gaimin.gg</span></a></li>
</ul>
<p><strong>For further information, please contact:</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Americas, Middle East and Australian Pacific &#8211; Andrew Faridani, Chief Marketing Officer for GAIMIN (based in Toronto, Canada): <a href="mailto:andrew@gaimin.io">andrew@gaimin.io</a></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">UK and Europe &#8211; Marc Bray, Chief Communications Officer for GAIMIN (based in Manchester, UK): <a href="mailto:marc@gaimin.io">marc@gaimin.io</a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<hr />
<p><small><i>This is a press release. Readers should do their own due diligence before taking any actions related to the promoted company or any of its affiliates or services. Bitcoin.com is not responsible, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused or alleged to be caused by or in connection with the use of or reliance on any content, goods or services mentioned in the press release.</i></small></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/unnamed-2023-06-08t202945-058-760x428.png</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[Revolutionizing AI: GAIMIN Unleashes the Power of High-Powered, Distributed Gaming PCs to Fuel AI Models]]></bnmedia:barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Biggest Movers: SOL Slightly Higher, as XRP Collides With Key Resistance Level</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/biggest-movers-sol-slightly-higher-as-xrp-collides-with-key-resistance-level/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Eliman Dambell]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 15:30:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robinhood]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOL]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=592652</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_2149938833-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Biggest Movers:  SOL Nears $20.00, as XRP Collides With Key Resistance Level" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_2149938833-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_2149938833-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_2149938833-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_2149938833-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_2149938833-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_2149938833-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_2149938833.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />Solana moved towards the $20.00 mark on Friday, despite reports confirming that Robinhood was set to delist the token from its platform. In addition to solana, cardano and polygon were also removed. XRP also trended higher in today&#x2019;s session. Solana (SOL) Solana (SOL) moved close to the $20.00 level on Friday, despite news that Robinhood [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_2149938833-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Biggest Movers:  SOL Nears $20.00, as XRP Collides With Key Resistance Level" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_2149938833-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_2149938833-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_2149938833-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_2149938833-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_2149938833-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_2149938833-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_2149938833.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>Solana moved towards the $20.00 mark on Friday, despite reports confirming that Robinhood was set to delist the token from its platform. In addition to solana, cardano and polygon were also removed. <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/XRP" 311999  target="_blank">XRP</a> also trended higher in today&#x2019;s session.</strong></p>
<h2>Solana (SOL)</h2>
<p>Solana (SOL) moved close to the $20.00 level on Friday, despite news that Robinhood was removing the token from its platform.</p>
<p>According to reports, the removal will occur on June 27. This comes after the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) determined that several tokens on Coinbase and Binance were securities.</p>
<p>Following a low of $18.56 on Thursday, SOL/USD moved to an intraday high of $19.30 during today&#x2019;s session.</p>

<p>Today&#x2019;s surge came as the 14-day relative strength index (RSI) neared a resistance level of 43.00</p>
<p>At the time of writing, the index is tracking at 41.14, with SOL at the $19.08 level.</p>
<p>Despite earlier gains easing after the reports, SOL remains above yesterday&#x2019;s low.</p>

<h2><a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/XRP" 311999  target="_blank">XRP</a></h2>
<p><a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/XRP" 311999  target="_blank">XRP</a>, formerly ripple, managed to avoid Robinhood&#x2019;s hit list, surging by over 3% on Friday as a result.</p>
<p><a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/XRP" 311999  target="_blank">XRP</a>/USD jumped to a peak at $0.5324 earlier in today&#x2019;s session, which comes less than 24 hours after the price bottomed out at $0.5184.</p>
<p>Friday&#x2019;s surge in price led to the token briefly breaking out of a key resistance level of $0.5320.</p>

<p>This comes as the RSI collided with a ceiling of its own at 64.00, with bears so far rejecting a breakout.</p>
<p>Currently, the index is tracking marginally lower at 63.50, with longer-term bulls targeting a higher ceiling at 70.00.</p>
<p>Should they reach this point, there is a good chance that <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/XRP" 311999  target="_blank">XRP</a> will trade close to $0.5800, which was last hit in March.</p>
<p><em>Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:</em></p>
<p><em><strong>Will Robinhood continue to delist more tokens? Let us know your thoughts in the comments.</strong></em></p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_2149938833-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[#SOL remains higher, despite Robinhood delisting the token from its platform.]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA[#SOL remains higher, despite Robinhood delisting the token from its platform.]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>IMF Urges Fed to Maintain Tightening Policy Amid Inflation Concerns, Citing ‘Challenges’ Ahead</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/imf-urges-fed-to-maintain-tightening-policy-amid-inflation-concerns-citing-challenges-ahead/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jamie Redman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 14:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Benchmark Bank Rate]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Banks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Global Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[IMF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[IMF Fed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[inflation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[interest rates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Julie Kozack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[lending rates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[restrictive monetary policy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spokesperson]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tightening]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[U.S. Federal Reserve]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US Central Bank]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US Fed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[World Economic Outlook]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=592640</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/imfs-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="IMF Urges Fed to Maintain Tightening Policy Amid Inflation Concerns, Citing ‘Challenges’ Ahead" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/imfs-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/imfs-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/imfs-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/imfs-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/imfs-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/imfs-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/imfs.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />On Thursday, International Monetary Fund (IMF) spokesperson Julie Kozack urged the U.S. Federal Reserve and several other central banks to maintain a restrictive monetary policy known as tightening. Kozack stated that the U.S. central bank may need to keep the federal funds rate higher &#8220;for longer&#8221; than anticipated. IMF Calls for Extended High Interest Rates [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/imfs-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="IMF Urges Fed to Maintain Tightening Policy Amid Inflation Concerns, Citing ‘Challenges’ Ahead" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/imfs-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/imfs-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/imfs-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/imfs-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/imfs-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/imfs-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/imfs.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>On Thursday, International Monetary Fund (IMF) spokesperson Julie Kozack urged the U.S. Federal Reserve and several other central banks to maintain a restrictive monetary policy known as tightening. Kozack stated that the U.S. central bank may need to keep the federal funds rate higher &#8220;for longer&#8221; than anticipated.</strong></p>
<h2>IMF Calls for Extended High Interest Rates to Tackle Lingering Inflation Threat</h2>
<p>The IMF is concerned about persistent inflation, and during a press briefing, IMF spokesperson Julie Kozack <a href="https://www.reuters.com/markets/imf-urges-fed-central-banks-keep-tightening-reduce-inflation-2023-06-08/#:~:text=WASHINGTON%2C%20June%208%20(Reuters),remain%20vigilant%20in%20combating%20inflation.">emphasized</a> the need for the Fed and several central banks worldwide to maintain their current course of monetary tightening policy. The Fed is scheduled to meet on June 14, 2023, in less than a week.</p>
<p>However, market observers and financial experts anticipate that the Fed will <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/federal-reserve-chair-powell-hints-at-possible-pause-in-interest-rate-hikes/">pause</a> its rate hikes during this meeting. According to CME&#8217;s <a href="https://www.cmegroup.com/markets/interest-rates/cme-fedwatch-tool.html">Fedwatch tool</a>, there is a greater than 74% probability that the rate will remain unchanged. Inflation in the United States has moderated to some extent, acknowledged Kozack, but if it continues to stay elevated, the Fed may need to maintain high rates.</p>
<p>&#8220;If inflation does prove to be more persistent than expected, then the Fed may need to push interest rates higher for longer,&#8221; Kozack said. Presently, the benchmark bank rate is at its highest point in 16 years, and lending rates throughout the country have surged. For example, the average mortgage on June 8, 2023, carried a 30-year term interest rate of 7.591%.</p>
<p>&#8220;We also see that inflation momentum has slowed, but that inflation does remain a pressing concern,&#8221; Kozack told reporters at the IMF press briefing. &#8220;Our advice remains unchanged, which is that the Fed would need to stay the course on monetary policy to ensure a durable reduction in inflation and to ensure that inflation expectations—remain well-anchored.&#8221;</p>

<p>Kozack stated that the IMF plans to release its World Economic Outlook at the end of July. In early 2023, the IMF had <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/imf-warns-tough-year-ahead-for-world-economy-slowdown-in-us-eu-china/">cautioned</a> that the year would present challenges for the global economy, highlighting anticipated slowdowns in the United States, European Union, and China. Kozack emphasized on Thursday that the organization continues to foresee forthcoming challenges.</p>
<p>&#8220;We see challenges over the medium term for the global economy, and that requires policy measures to be taken now,&#8221; Kozack insisted. &#8220;We believe that central banks should stay the course on monetary tightening to decisively reduce inflation.”</p>
<p><em><strong>What are your thoughts on the IMF&#8217;s call for central banks to maintain a tight monetary policy amid persistent inflation concerns? Share your thoughts and opinions about this subject in the comments section below.</strong></em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/imfs-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[“The Fed may need to push interest rates higher for longer," IMF spokesperson Julie Kozack emphasized on Thursday. ]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA[“The Fed may need to push interest rates higher for longer," IMF spokesperson Julie Kozack emphasized on Thursday. ]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Neon EVM Community Sale Sells out in 29 Minutes – Registering 717k Participants</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/neon-evm-community-sale-sells-out-in-29-minutes-registering-717k-participants/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Media]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 13:45:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=592504&#038;preview=true&#038;preview_id=592504</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="403" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/5977314a-57b5-4f51-8153-b129f0e2a6e9-768x403.png" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/5977314a-57b5-4f51-8153-b129f0e2a6e9-300x158.png 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/5977314a-57b5-4f51-8153-b129f0e2a6e9-1024x538.png 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/5977314a-57b5-4f51-8153-b129f0e2a6e9-768x403.png 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/5977314a-57b5-4f51-8153-b129f0e2a6e9-1536x806.png 1536w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/5977314a-57b5-4f51-8153-b129f0e2a6e9-2048x1075.png 2048w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />PRESS RELEASE. Neon EVM is an Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM) on Solana, offering developers the seamless integration of Ethereum dApps within the Solana ecosystem. By eliminating the gap between these two leading blockchains, Neon EVM empowers Ethereum developers to leverage the speed, low transaction costs, and parallel transaction execution capabilities of Solana. The community sale, [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="403" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/5977314a-57b5-4f51-8153-b129f0e2a6e9-768x403.png" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/5977314a-57b5-4f51-8153-b129f0e2a6e9-300x158.png 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/5977314a-57b5-4f51-8153-b129f0e2a6e9-1024x538.png 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/5977314a-57b5-4f51-8153-b129f0e2a6e9-768x403.png 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/5977314a-57b5-4f51-8153-b129f0e2a6e9-1536x806.png 1536w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/5977314a-57b5-4f51-8153-b129f0e2a6e9-2048x1075.png 2048w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>PRESS RELEASE. </strong>Neon EVM is an Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM) on Solana, offering developers the seamless integration of Ethereum dApps within the Solana ecosystem. By eliminating the gap between these two leading blockchains, Neon EVM empowers Ethereum developers to leverage the speed, low transaction costs, and parallel transaction execution capabilities of Solana.</p>
<p>The community sale, hosted on CoinList, allowed individuals to participate in this major ecosystem innovation. With 50,000,000 tokens available at a price of $0.10 per token, the sale attracted a substantial influx of 717,320 registrations from individuals keen to secure their interest in the Neon EVM&#8217;s groundbreaking solution.</p>
<p>It is important to note that the Neon EVM Community Sale was not open to persons or residents from restricted jurisdictions, including the United States, Canada, China, and other similar jurisdictions, who did not have the right or access to participate in the token sale.</p>
<p>Neon EVM&#8217;s key features include support for familiar Ethereum developer tools and languages such as Solidity, Vyper, Metamask, Remix, Hardhat, and Truffle. Couple these with high throughput and low-cost transactions, and Neon EVM makes the Solana network an attractive choice for Ethereum developers.</p>
<p>The success of the Neon EVM Community Sale is a significant milestone in the evolution of the Solana ecosystem, as it indicates that there is strong interest in the Neon EVM and other high-performance solutions that enable easy implementation of multichain dApps. Neon EVM&#8217;s pioneering technology positions Solana as a viable and vibrant option for developers — an ecosystem previously untapped by EVM multichain dApps.</p>
<p>For more information about Neon EVM and future updates, please visit <u><a href="https://neonevm.org">neonevm.org</a></u> or follow Neon EVM on Twitter: <u><a href="https://twitter.com/Neon_EVM">https://twitter.com/Neon_EVM</a></u>.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<hr />
<p><small><i>This is a press release. Readers should do their own due diligence before taking any actions related to the promoted company or any of its affiliates or services. Bitcoin.com is not responsible, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused or alleged to be caused by or in connection with the use of or reliance on any content, goods or services mentioned in the press release.</i></small></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/5977314a-57b5-4f51-8153-b129f0e2a6e9-760x428.png</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[Neon EVM Community Sale Sells out in 29 Minutes – Registering 717k Participants]]></bnmedia:barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin, Ethereum Technical Analysis: BTC Moves Higher, as Traders Prepare for Next Week&#8217;s Fed Meeting</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-ethereum-technical-analysis-btc-moves-higher-as-traders-prepare-for-next-weeks-fed-meeting/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Eliman Dambell]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 12:30:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Federal Reserve]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=592615</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_2146701713-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Bitcoin, Ethereum Technical Analysis: BTC Moves Higher, as Traders Prepare for Next Week&#039;s Fed Meeting" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_2146701713-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_2146701713-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_2146701713-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_2146701713-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_2146701713-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_2146701713-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_2146701713.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />Bitcoin edged marginally higher on Friday, as traders began to shift their attention to next week&#x2019;s Fed meeting. Many are expecting that the Federal Reserve will keep rates unchanged for the first time in over a year. Ethereum remains above a floor at $1,830. Bitcoin Bitcoin (BTC) moved marginally higher during Friday&#x2019;s session, as the [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_2146701713-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Bitcoin, Ethereum Technical Analysis: BTC Moves Higher, as Traders Prepare for Next Week&#039;s Fed Meeting" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_2146701713-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_2146701713-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_2146701713-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_2146701713-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_2146701713-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_2146701713-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_2146701713.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>Bitcoin edged marginally higher on Friday, as traders began to shift their attention to next week&#x2019;s Fed meeting. Many are expecting that the Federal Reserve will keep rates unchanged for the first time in over a year. Ethereum remains above a floor at $1,830.</strong></p>
<h2>Bitcoin</h2>
<p>Bitcoin (<a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/BTC" 311996  target="_blank">BTC</a>) moved marginally higher during Friday&#x2019;s session, as the focus for traders begins to be next week&#x2019;s Fed rate decision.</p>
<p>Following a low of $26,339.32 on Thursday, <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/BTC" 311996  target="_blank">BTC</a>/USD jumped to an intraday peak of $26,797.51 earlier today.</p>
<p>The move comes as bulls bounced from a price floor at $26,300, with a ceiling at $27,200 now a potential target.</p>
<div class="tradingview-widget-container">
<div class="tradingview-widget-copyright"><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/?exchange=BITSTAMP" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span class="blue-text">Bitcoin chart</span></a> by TradingView</div>
<p><script type="text/javascript" src="https://s3.tradingview.com/tv.js"></script><script type="text/javascript">
  new TradingView.widget(
  {
  "width": "100%",
  "height": "400",
  "symbol": "BITSTAMP:BTCUSD",
  "interval": "D",
  "timezone": "Etc/UTC",
  "theme": "light",
  "style": "1",
  "locale": "en",
  "toolbar_bg": "#F1F3F6",
  "enable_publishing": false,
  "container_id": "tradingview_1247e"
}
  );
  </script></p>
</div>
<p><!-- TradingView Widget END --></p>
<p>In order to get closer to this point, the 14-day relative strength index (RSI) will need to move past a ceiling at 47.00</p>
<p>At the time of writing, the index is tracking at 46.21, with bitcoin trading around the $26,600 level.</p>
<p>Despite the optimism from bulls, the 10-day (red) moving average remains in a downtrend, following a cross with its 25-day (blue) counterpart.</p>

<h2>Ethereum</h2>
<p>In addition to bitcoin, ethereum (<a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/ETH" target="_blank">ETH</a>) recorded some small gains on Friday, after colliding with its own support point.</p>
<p><a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/ETH" target="_blank">ETH</a>/USD climbed to a peak of $1,861.14 in today&#x2019;s session, which comes less than 24 hours after falling to a bottom at $1,831.26.</p>
<p>Unlike bitcoin, the moving averages have yet to cross, which provides optimism to longer-term bulls of potential upcoming gains.</p>
<div class="tradingview-widget-container">
<div class="tradingview-widget-copyright"><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ETHUSD/?exchange=BITSTAMP" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span class="blue-text">Ethereum chart</span></a> by TradingView</div>
<p><script type="text/javascript" src="https://s3.tradingview.com/tv.js"></script><script type="text/javascript">
  new TradingView.widget(
  {
  "width": "100%",
  "height": "400",
  "symbol": "BITSTAMP:ETHUSD",
  "interval": "D",
  "timezone": "Etc/UTC",
  "theme": "light",
  "style": "1",
  "locale": "en",
  "toolbar_bg": "#F1F3F6",
  "enable_publishing": false,
  "container_id": "tradingview_1247e"
}
  );
  </script> As well as the price, the RSI has also avoided a breakout below a floor at 47.00, and is now at a reading of 48.23.</p>
</div>
<p>The next target appears to be the 52.00 mark, and should this be hit, ethereum will likely be above $1,900.</p>
<p><em>Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:</em></p>
<p><em><strong>Do you expect the Federal Reserve to hike rates next week? Let us know your thoughts in the comments.</strong></em></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_2146701713-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[#BTC edges higher, as market focus shifts to next week's Fed meeting.]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA[#BTC edges higher, as market focus shifts to next week's Fed meeting.]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
