<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:bnmedia="https://news.bitcoin.com/">

<channel>
	<title>Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/</link>
	<description>Daily Bitcoin News</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 02:21:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Economist Peter Schiff Slams Fed Chair Over Economic Concerns — Claims Powell Overlooks &#8216;Far More Relevant&#8217; Factors</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/economist-peter-schiff-slams-fed-chair-over-economic-concerns-claims-powell-overlooks-far-more-relevant-factors/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Kevin Helms]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 02:30:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fed chair inflation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fed chair powell]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fed chair US dollar reserve currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Peter Schiff]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Schiff Jerome Powell]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=594735&#038;preview=true&#038;preview_id=594735</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/powell-schiff-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Economist Peter Schiff Slams Fed Chair Over Economic Concerns — Claims Powell Overlooks ‘Far More Relevant Common Factors’" decoding="async" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/powell-schiff-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/powell-schiff-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/powell-schiff-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/powell-schiff-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/powell-schiff-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/powell-schiff-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/powell-schiff.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />Economist Peter Schiff has slammed Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell over several key issues concerning the U.S. economy, the banking system, and the U.S. dollar. “Powell is a coward. He is not doing his job,” Schiff claimed, highlighting multiple factors affecting the economy that the Fed chairman overlooked in his statements before Congress this week. [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/powell-schiff-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Economist Peter Schiff Slams Fed Chair Over Economic Concerns — Claims Powell Overlooks ‘Far More Relevant Common Factors’" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/powell-schiff-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/powell-schiff-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/powell-schiff-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/powell-schiff-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/powell-schiff-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/powell-schiff-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/powell-schiff.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>Economist Peter Schiff has slammed Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell over several key issues concerning the U.S. economy, the banking system, and the U.S. dollar. “Powell is a coward. He is not doing his job,” Schiff claimed, highlighting multiple factors affecting the economy that the Fed chairman overlooked in his statements before Congress this week.</strong></p>
<h2>Peter Schiff Disagrees With Fed Chair Powell on Several Key Issues</h2>
<p>Economist and gold bug Peter Schiff has criticized multiple statements made by Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell during his appearances before the House Financial Services Committee on Wednesday and the Senate Banking Committee on Thursday. Powell appeared before Congress this week to present the Federal Reserve’s semiannual Monetary Policy Report.</p>
<p>Schiff expressed his disagreement with Powell&#8217;s remarks through a series of tweets over the past couple of days. In one tweet, he wrote:</p>
<blockquote><p>Powell acknowledged that the Fed&#8217;s growing balance sheet is a concern, but failed to address the primary challenge that the balance sheet will never stop growing because every time an economic or financial problem arises, the Fed quickly expands the balance sheet to new highs.</p></blockquote>
<p>Furthermore, the gold bug stressed in a follow-up tweet: &#8220;Powell is wrong to claim that the economy is being driven by a strong labor market. A weak economy and falling real wages are driving more workers to seek second and third jobs, and inflation causes retirees to return to the labor force to keep up with a rising cost of living.&#8221;</p>
<p>Schiff detailed in another tweet that the Federal Reserve chairman “claims the common factor that explains why so many countries are now experiencing high inflation is the global pandemic.” However, he pointed out:</p>
<blockquote><p>What he overlooks are the far more relevant common factors of artificially low interest rates, quantitative easing, and government deficit spending.</p></blockquote>
<p>The economist added that the Fed chair stated that the Federal Reserve’s “massive losses on its bond portfolio don&#8217;t count, as they&#8217;re just paper losses.” Schiff exclaimed: “That&#8217;s BS. Plus, the Fed pays more on deposits than it earns on Treasuries. Those losses are real. The bills are sent to the U.S. government and become obligations of taxpayers.”</p>

<p>Commenting on Powell reiterating his assurance to lawmakers during his Senate hearing that the U.S. banking system is<a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/federal-reserve-raises-interest-rate-by-25bps-insists-us-banking-system-is-sound-and-resilient/"> sound and resilient</a>, Schiff stressed: &#8220;The truth is that thanks to Fed monetary policy and Federal government interference, subsidies, and regulation, the U.S. banking system is insolvent and would have collapsed without government backstops.&#8221; Schiff similarly warned earlier this month that the Fed is <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/economist-peter-schiff-says-the-fed-destroyed-us-banking-system-its-insolvent/">destroying</a> the banking system.</p>
<p>The gold bug also commented on U.S. Senator Elizabeth Warren’s statements regarding the banking system. He said that while the senator from Massachusetts “is correct that our banking system is broken, she is wrong about who broke it.” The economist explained: “The problem is not too little government regulation, but too much. What we need is to get the government and the Fed out of the U.S. banking system, to allow free market forces back in.”</p>
<p>Schiff further stated: &#8220;Powell is wrong to claim that increased government spending stimulates the economy. It doesn&#8217;t stimulate the economy, it actually stifles the economy. What it stimulates is spending and inflation. But the Fed Chairman doesn&#8217;t really understand economics. He&#8217;s a Keynesian.&#8221; He opined:</p>
<blockquote><p>Former Fed Chair Paul Volcker repeatedly advised Congress to cut spending or raise taxes, sharply criticized Federal deficit spending that he warned would stifle economic growth, lead to higher long-term interest rates and inflation. Powell is a coward. He is not doing his job.</p></blockquote>
<p>Another area in which Schiff disagreed with Powell concerns the U.S. dollar. The Fed chairman told lawmakers that he believes the USD’s status as the global reserve currency is a <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/gofrom/most_popular/federal-reserve-chair-discusses-de-dollarization-threat-risk-of-us-dollar-losing-reserve-currency-status">consequence</a> of America’s economic dominance. Schiff argued: “Powell is wrong. The dollar&#8217;s reserve currency status was originally a consequence of America&#8217;s economic dominance, but it has since become the main prop upon which that economic dominance now rests. Once the dollar&#8217;s reserve status is lost, U.S. economic dominance will topple.”</p>
<p><em><strong>Do you agree with economist Peter Schiff? Let us know in the comments section below.</strong></em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/powell-schiff-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[#PeterSchiff has slammed Fed Chair Jerome #Powell over several issues concerning the U.S. economy, the #bankingsystem, and the U.S. #dollar.]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA["Powell is a coward. He is not doing his job," said #PeterSchiff. #economy #inflation]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Ordered to Cease All Crypto Services in Belgium</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/binance-ordered-to-cease-all-crypto-services-in-belgium/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Kevin Helms]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 00:30:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[belgium]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance Belgium]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance cease operations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance ceases crypto offerings]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao CZ]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MiCA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=594726&#038;preview=true&#038;preview_id=594726</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/binance-belgium-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Binance Ordered to Cease All Crypto Services in Belgium" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/binance-belgium-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/binance-belgium-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/binance-belgium-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/binance-belgium-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/binance-belgium-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/binance-belgium-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/binance-belgium.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />Crypto exchange Binance has been ordered by Belgium&#8217;s Financial Services and Markets Authority (FSMA) to cease providing any crypto exchange and custody wallet services in the country. The Belgian financial regulator stressed that it &#8220;takes the view that by offering such services in Belgium from countries that are not members of the European Economic Area, [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/binance-belgium-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Binance Ordered to Cease All Crypto Services in Belgium" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/binance-belgium-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/binance-belgium-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/binance-belgium-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/binance-belgium-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/binance-belgium-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/binance-belgium-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/binance-belgium.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>Crypto exchange Binance has been ordered by Belgium&#8217;s Financial Services and Markets Authority (FSMA) to cease providing any crypto exchange and custody wallet services in the country. The Belgian financial regulator stressed that it &#8220;takes the view that by offering such services in Belgium from countries that are not members of the European Economic Area, Binance is in violation of that prohibition.”</strong></p>
<h2>Belgian Regulator Orders Binance to Cease Crypto Services in the Country</h2>
<p>Belgium&#8217;s Financial Services and Markets Authority (FSMA) announced Friday that it has ordered cryptocurrency exchange  to “cease immediately all offers of virtual currency services in Belgium.”</p>
<p>The FSMA noted that &#8220;Binance is offering and providing exchange services in Belgium between virtual currencies and legal currencies, as well as custody wallet services, from countries that are not members of the European Economic Area.&#8221; The financial regulator emphasized: “The FSMA takes the view that by offering such services in Belgium from countries that are not members of the European Economic Area, Binance is in violation of that prohibition.” The announcement details:</p>
<blockquote><p>By way of its decision dated 23 June 2023, the FSMA has therefore decided to order Binance to cease, with immediate effect, offering or providing any exchange services in Belgium between virtual currencies and legal currencies, as well as custody wallet services.</p></blockquote>
<p>“Failure to comply with this prohibition is subject to criminal sanctions pursuant to Article 136 of the Belgian Law on the prevention of money laundering and terrorist financing,” the regulator warned.</p>
<p>In addition to ordering Binance to cease crypto activities in Belgium, the FSMA stated that it has &#8220;demanded that Binance take immediate measures&#8221; to return to Belgian clients &#8220;all cryptographic keys and/or all virtual currencies that Binance holds for their account, or to transfer these to entities governed by the law of an EEA member state and duly authorized by their domestic law to carry out such activities.&#8221;</p>

<h2>Belgium’s Crypto Regulation</h2>
<p>The financial regulator explained that providing exchange services “between virtual currencies and legal currencies and of custody wallet services (VASP) remains an unregulated activity, except as concerns combating money laundering and terrorist financing (AML/TF).”</p>
<p>The FSMA noted that the European Union&#8217;s Markets in Crypto-Assets (MiCA) regulation, which was published in the Official Journal of the European Union on June 9, &#8220;will introduce more general rules, and in particular prudential rules, governing activities relating to crypto-assets.&#8221; The regulator clarified:</p>
<blockquote><p>These rules, with direct effect in Belgian law, will enter into force in January 2025.</p></blockquote>
<p>In the absence of specific regulations, the common law and relevant provisions of the Belgian Criminal Code are applicable to crypto assets, the FSMA noted.</p>
<p>Binance is facing increased regulatory scrutiny across multiple countries. The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has filed charges against Binance, CEO Changpeng Zhao (CZ), and Binance US. In addition, Binance has ceased operations in the <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/binance-unit-in-britain-cancels-uk-regulatory-authorization/">United Kingdom</a>. The exchange has also pulled out of the <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/binance-pulls-out-of-netherlands-seeks-to-deregister-cyprus-unit/">Netherlands</a> and is seeking to deregister in Cyprus. Furthermore, <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/french-investigation-targets-binance-allegations-of-money-laundering-and-regulatory-violations/">French investigators</a> are investigating Binance on allegations of money laundering and regulatory breaches.</p>
<p><em><strong>What do you think about Binance being ordered to halt its crypto services in Belgium and its decision to withdraw from multiple countries? Let us know in the comments section below.</strong></em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/binance-belgium-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[#Binance has been ordered by #Belgium's regulator to cease providing any #crypto exchange and custody wallet services in the country. #cryptocurrency]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA[“The FSMA takes the view that by offering such services in Belgium from countries that are not members of the European Economic Area, #Binance is in violation of that prohibition.” #crypto]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tanzanian Central Bank Says Quoting Prices in Foreign Currency Against the Law</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/tanzanian-central-bank-says-quoting-prices-in-foreign-currency-violates-the-law/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Terence Zimwara]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 22:30:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Africa]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bank of Tanzania (BOT)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bureau De Change]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[financial stability]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[foreign currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[legal tender]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tanzania shillings]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tanzanian]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=594583</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_1795791064-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Tanzanian Central Bank Says Quoting Prices in Foreign Currency Against the Law" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_1795791064-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_1795791064-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_1795791064-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_1795791064-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_1795791064-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_1795791064-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_1795791064.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />The Bank of Tanzania (BOT) has reiterated that shillings remain the East African country&#8217;s sole legal tender. The apex bank said residents quoting prices in foreign currency or those refusing payment in Tanzanian shillings are in violation of the Bank of Tanzania Act 2006. The central bank said only commercial banks and Bureaux de Change [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_1795791064-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Tanzanian Central Bank Says Quoting Prices in Foreign Currency Against the Law" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_1795791064-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_1795791064-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_1795791064-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_1795791064-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_1795791064-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_1795791064-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_1795791064.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>The Bank of Tanzania (BOT) has reiterated that shillings remain the East African country&#8217;s sole legal tender. The apex bank said residents quoting prices in foreign currency or those refusing payment in Tanzanian shillings are in violation of the Bank of Tanzania Act 2006. The central bank said only commercial banks and Bureaux de Change are allowed to determine exchange rates.</strong></p>
<h2>Rejecting Payment in Shillings a Violation of the Law</h2>
<p>The Tanzanian central bank has said the practice of demanding or quoting prices in foreign currency is illegal and that those refusing to accept payment in Tanzanian shillings are in violation of the Bank of Tanzania Act 2006. In a June 20 <a href="https://www.bot.go.tz/Adverts/PressRelease/en/2023062010495430.pdf">press release</a>, the bank also reiterated that only commercial banks and Bureaux de Change are allowed to determine exchange rates.</p>
<p>The latest warning by the Bank of Tanzania (BOT) came barely a month after the apex bank told the country’s authorized forex dealers to only trade with licensed international foreign currency brokers. As <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/tanzanian-central-bank-says-forex-restrictions-intended-to-safeguard-the-stability-of-the-financial-system/">reported</a> by Bitcoin.com News in early June, the Tanzanian central bank viewed the forex restrictions as a step that helps to &#8220;foster macroeconomic stability and safeguard the stability of the financial system.&#8221;</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"></p>
<h2>2017 and 2007 Forex Prohibitions Still in Effect</h2>
<p>Meanwhile, in a warning apparently aimed at those ostensibly seeking to dollarize the economy, the Tanzanian central bank reiterated that the Aug. 2007 and later, Dec. 2017, prohibition on foreign currency payments between citizens is still in effect. Still, the press release stipulates the few instances wherein the quoting or payment in foreign currency is not forbidden.</p>
<p>&#8220;Prices to be paid by tourists or non-resident customers may be quoted and paid in foreign currency. These include services such as accommodation, travel, airport and visa, transit trade and cargo handling. Tourists and non-residents who pay in foreign currencies must provide their identification documents such as passport and certificate of incorporation for companies for proper capturing and classification of statistics,&#8221; the BOT said in the statement.</p>
<p>However, according to the central bank, for goods and services such as rentals, education and medical fees, prices should be quoted in Tanzanian shillings which remain the only legal tender. The same rules also apply to transport services, electronic products and telecommunication services.</p>
<p><em>Register your email here to get a weekly update on African news sent to your inbox:</em><br />
</p>
<p><em><strong>What are your thoughts on this story? Let us know what you think in the comments section below. </strong></em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_1795791064-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[The central bank also reiterated that only commercial banks and Bureaux de Change are allowed to determine #exchange rates. #regulation #financialstability]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA["Tourists and non-residents who pay in foreign currencies must provide their identification documents such as passport and certificate of incorporation," the central bank said. #dollarization #forex]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Macro Strategist David Hunter Predicts Global Markets&#8217; &#8216;Melt Up&#8217; Surge in Q4 2023, Followed by Impending ‘Bust’</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/macro-strategist-david-hunter-predicts-global-markets-melt-up-surge-in-q4-2023-followed-by-impending-bust/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jamie Redman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 20:30:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[' Great Surprise]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA['Fall Melt-Up of 2011]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[$3000 per ounce]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2023]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bull Market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bull traps]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bullish scenarios]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chief macro strategist]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contrarian Macro Advisors]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[David Hunter]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[disinflation trend]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[downturn]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[forecast]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fourth quarter]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Global Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gold]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[interview]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kitco News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[lofty peaks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[market bust]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[market phenomena]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[melt up]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[melt-up move]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Michelle Makori]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Recession]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[S&P 500]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[secular bull cycle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[short-lived]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[silver]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[underlying fundamentals]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=594668</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/wallstree-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Macro Strategist David Hunter Predicts Global Markets&#039; &#039;Melt Up&#039; Surge in Q4 2023, Followed by Impending ‘Bust’" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/wallstree-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/wallstree-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/wallstree-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/wallstree-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/wallstree-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/wallstree-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/wallstree.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />David Hunter, the chief macro strategist at Contrarian Macro Advisors, predicts an interesting development for global markets in the fourth quarter of 2023. According to him, global markets will experience a remarkable surge, aptly described as a &#8220;melt up.&#8221; However, this surge will be short-lived, as a substantial downturn is expected to follow. Hunter emphasizes [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/wallstree-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Macro Strategist David Hunter Predicts Global Markets&#039; &#039;Melt Up&#039; Surge in Q4 2023, Followed by Impending ‘Bust’" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/wallstree-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/wallstree-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/wallstree-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/wallstree-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/wallstree-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/wallstree-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/wallstree.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>David Hunter, the chief macro strategist at Contrarian Macro Advisors, predicts an interesting development for global markets in the fourth quarter of 2023. According to him, global markets will experience a remarkable surge, aptly described as a &#8220;melt up.&#8221; However, this surge will be short-lived, as a substantial downturn is expected to follow. Hunter emphasizes that after this rise and fall, we won&#8217;t witness the same lofty peaks of the 41-year secular bull cycle for many years to come.</strong></p>
<h2>Contrarian Macro Advisors Exec Anticipates Global Markets&#8217; &#8216;Melt Up&#8217; in Q4 2023, Warns 80% Downturn Will Follow</h2>
<p>In an <a href="https://youtu.be/eEkFruysx5Q">interview</a> with Kitco News&#8217; lead anchor and editor-in-chief, Michelle Makori, David Hunter delved into the realm of the economy, unraveling a compelling narrative of a potential &#8220;melt up&#8221; scenario. Renowned for his remarkable knack for forecasting economic cycles and identifying market trends ahead of the curve, Hunter unveiled his forecast.</p>
<p>He painted a picture of the S&amp;P 500 soaring by a staggering 36%, while the value of gold would ascend to $3,000 per ounce by October. However, Hunter cautioned that these bullish scenarios will be fleeting, as an imminent and significant market bust looms on the horizon, paving the way for a profound recession.</p>
<p>&#8220;My S&amp;P target is six to seven thousand,&#8221; Hunter explained during his interview with Makori. &#8220;My targets are gold to $3,000 pre-bust and silver to $60 pre-bust … We&#8217;ll probably see most of the melt-up move by the end of the summer, which could mean Labor Day, but it could stretch into September.&#8221;</p>

<p>So what exactly is a melt up? Traditionally, these market phenomena resemble bull traps, serving as deceptive and unreliable signals of an impending market surge. The gains experienced during a melt up are often viewed with skepticism because, despite the temporary upward momentum, the underlying fundamentals of the market continue to deteriorate. Throughout history, melt-ups have frequently paved the way for subsequent meltdowns, reminiscent of the notable &#8216;<a href="https://seekingalpha.com/article/296658-the-fall-melt-up-of-2011-or-the-great-surprise">Fall Melt-Up of 2011</a>,&#8217; aptly dubbed the &#8216;Great Surprise.&#8217;</p>
<p>Hunter suggests that we have found ourselves nearing the culmination of a significant 41-year secular bull run that commenced in 1982. Hunter stressed:</p>
<blockquote><p>That is when the disinflation trend began and interest rates peaked out. I think the highs of this bull market will not likely be seen again for decades.</p></blockquote>
<p>Throughout the turbulent economic history of the United States, significant transformations such as the notorious &#8216;Great Depression&#8217; and the formidable &#8216;Great Recession&#8217; were marked by the occurrence of tantalizing melt-ups. These preludes to market busts enticed investors with their deceptive allure. Prior to the infamous stock market crash in 1929, an extended period of prosperity <a href="https://www.pbs.org/fmc/timeline/estockmktcrash.htm">propelled stock prices</a> to unprecedented heights, witnessing a staggering quadrupling in value from 1920 to 1929. Fueled by misguided optimism, investors fell victim to the illusory signals of the melt-up, succumbing to the temptation of borrowing extensively to pour more funds into the market.</p>

<p>According to Hunter, the U.S. Federal Reserve&#8217;s implementation of quantitative tightening measures has surpassed the optimal threshold, pushing it into the realm of going &#8220;too far.&#8221; Economist Steve Hanke echoes this sentiment, as he <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/economist-steve-hanke-warns-of-an-ugly-recession-looming-and-accuses-federal-reserve-of-directionless-policies/">recently emphasized</a> that the current monetary tightening bears an uncanny resemblance to the contractionary policies witnessed in &#8220;1938 or 1939.&#8221; In a recent interview, Hanke drew attention to the parallels between the present circumstances and the historical instances of economic shrinkage. While speaking with Makori, Hunter insists “We are in uncharted territory.”</p>
<p>&#8220;The formula is, really, economic fragility caused by the pandemic, plus potentially the biggest policy error [over-tightening] in history by central banks, and plus leverage,” Hunter said. “You&#8217;ve got a formula which takes a normal recession into something far worse.&#8221;</p>
<p>Hunter explained that the type of &#8220;bust&#8221; he envisions will entail markets recording an 80% drawdown, and while he predicts <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/gold-to-2100-investment-management-firm-says-gold-to-be-key-instrument-in-new-financial-order/">gold</a> will reach an all-time high this year, precious metals like gold and silver will drop back to today&#8217;s levels. &#8220;I don&#8217;t think very many assets are going to be able to escape a deflationary bust,&#8221; Hunter added. The macro strategist concluded, however, that gold and silver will see upsides following the bust, and both could rise ten times higher in value after the bottom.</p>
<p><em><strong>What are your thoughts on David Hunter&#8217;s forecast of a &#8216;melt up&#8217; followed by a significant market downturn? Share your thoughts and opinions about this subject in the comments section below.</strong></em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/wallstree-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA["We'll probably see most of the melt-up move by the end of the summer," the Contrarian Macro Advisors chief macro strategist said. #Economics #Booms #Busts]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA["We'll probably see most of the melt-up move by the end of the summer," the Contrarian Macro Advisors chief macro strategist said. #Economics #Booms #Busts]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance US Restores USD Withdrawals, Suggests Users Withdraw or Spend Their Dollars</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/binance-us-restores-usd-withdrawals-suggests-users-withdraw-or-spend-their-dollars/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lubomir Tassev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 18:30:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchanges]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance.us]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[deposits]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dollar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lawsuit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litigation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[U.S. dollar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[users]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Withdrawals]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=594650</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_1066580147-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Binance US Restores USD Withdrawals, Suggests Users Withdraw or Spend Their Dollars" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_1066580147-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_1066580147-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_1066580147-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_1066580147-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_1066580147-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_1066580147-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_1066580147.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />The U.S. subsidiary of the world&#x2019;s largest crypto exchange, Binance, announced it has resolved the issues with U.S. dollar (USD) withdrawals. The trading platform, which recently averted an asset freeze sought by the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), informed customers, however, that withdrawal services are likely to be discontinued again. Binance US May [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_1066580147-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Binance US Restores USD Withdrawals, Suggests Users Withdraw or Spend Their Dollars" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_1066580147-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_1066580147-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_1066580147-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_1066580147-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_1066580147-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_1066580147-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_1066580147.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>The U.S. subsidiary of the world&#x2019;s largest crypto exchange, Binance, announced it has resolved the issues with U.S. dollar (USD) withdrawals. The trading platform, which recently averted an asset freeze sought by the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), informed customers, however, that withdrawal services are likely to be discontinued again.</strong></p>
<h2>Binance US May Convert Remaining USD Balances to <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/USDT" target="_blank">USDT</a> in the Future</h2>
<p>The American unit of the leading global digital asset exchange <a href="https://support.binance.us/hc/en-us/articles/15507453489943-Binance-US-Provides-Update-on-USD-Withdrawals-Trading-Offerings">announced</a> it has worked with partners to resolve almost all delayed USD withdrawals. Binance US advised users to resubmit previously failed withdrawal requests and said most will be completed within five business days.</p>
<p>At the same time, the crypto trading platform explained that currently its systems remain fully operational but noted it expects its banking partners to discontinue the USD withdrawal service in the near future and suggested:</p>
<blockquote><p>While we continue to pursue new partners to re-establish USD deposits and withdrawals, we encourage users to use, withdraw, or convert their USD fiat balances to stablecoins to continue crypto-to-crypto trading on the platform.</p></blockquote>
<p>Binance US <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/binance-us-halts-usd-deposits-withdrawals-asks-users-to-withdraw-dollars-by-june-13/">halted</a> USD deposits and withdrawals earlier this month and asked customers to withdraw dollars by June 13, pointing out that the SEC&#x2019;s legal action against it &#x201C;has created challenges for the banks with whom we work.&#x201D;</p>
<p>The regulator <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/binance-faces-legal-action-by-sec-for-violating-us-securities-laws/">sued</a> the operators of the American exchange, BAM Trading Services and BAM Management US Holdings, as well as Binance founder Changpeng Zhao (<a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/cz-binance-us-pleased-with-sec-deal-despite-unwarranted-emergency-relief/">CZ</a>), alleging they have been selling unregistered securities in violation of U.S. laws and mishandling user funds. Under a <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/binance-cz-agree-to-repatriate-us-customer-assets-sec-secures-court-order/">deal</a> with the SEC,  managed to avoid the freezing of its U.S. assets.</p>

<p>Binance US also announced it&#x2019;s transitioning to a crypto-only trading platform. As part of the shift, any remaining USD balances in customer accounts may be converted to tether (<a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/USDT" target="_blank">USDT</a>) at a future date, the company said, and revealed it will expand trading offerings with the dollar-pegged stablecoin while it will remove most USD trading pairs on June 26.</p>
<p>&#x201C;Thereafter, USD Advanced Trading pairs will only be available for the following digital assets: <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/BTC" 311996  target="_blank">BTC</a>, <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/ETH" target="_blank">ETH</a>, <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/ADA" target="_blank">ADA</a>, <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/BNB" target="_blank">BNB</a>, <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/LTC" target="_blank">LTC</a>, MATIC, SOL, VET, USDC, and <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/USDT" target="_blank">USDT</a>,&#x201D; the exchange detailed and urged traders to execute or cancel any open orders with the dollar before these pairs are removed.</p>
<p>Binance US also sought to reassure customers that their assets are safe and secure. The American coin trading platform took a hit from the SEC&#x2019;s litigation and recent data showed that its share of the U.S. crypto exchange market has <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/binance-us-market-share-shrinks-amid-legal-battle-with-sec/">shrunk</a> to just around 1.5%.</p>
<p><em><strong>Do you think Binance US will secure new banking partnerships that will allow it to permanently restore USD deposits and withdrawals? Tell us in the comments section below. </strong></em></p>






]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_1066580147-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[#Binance US resolves issues with most #USD #withdrawal requests.  ]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA[#Crypto #exchange #Binance US may convert remaining #USD balances to #USDT in the future. ]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Institutional Interest Fuels Crypto Rally as Market Adds $110 Billion in 7 Days</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/institutional-interest-fuels-crypto-rally-as-market-adds-110-billion-in-7-days/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jamie Redman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 16:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BCH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin cash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Charles Schwab]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[citadel securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto assets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto rally]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital Assets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[etfs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[exchange-traded funds]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fidelity Digital Assets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[financial weakness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gains]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Institutional Interest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Capitalization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Caps]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Meme Coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pepe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tradfi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[VET]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[WOO]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ZIL]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=594682</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/22787-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Institutional Interest Fuels Crypto Rally as Market Adds $110 Billion in 7 Days" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/22787-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/22787-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/22787-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/22787-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/22787-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/22787-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/22787.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />During the past week, crypto assets increased in value by 9.62%, rising from $1.10 trillion to the current $1.21 trillion. Apart from the listed stablecoins, the top 20 crypto assets by market capitalization all experienced gains this week, as $110 billion was injected into the crypto economy. Crypto Market Surges, Rally Led by Pepe, Stacks, [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/22787-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Institutional Interest Fuels Crypto Rally as Market Adds $110 Billion in 7 Days" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/22787-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/22787-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/22787-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/22787-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/22787-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/22787-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/22787.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>During the past week, crypto assets increased in value by 9.62%, rising from $1.10 trillion to the current $1.21 trillion. Apart from the listed stablecoins, the top 20 crypto assets by market capitalization all experienced gains this week, as $110 billion was injected into the crypto economy.</strong></p>
<h2>Crypto Market Surges, Rally Led by Pepe, Stacks, Bitcoin Cash</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, the crypto economy stands at $1.21 trillion, following a 9.62% increase this week. Metrics indicate that bitcoin (<a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/BTC" 311996  target="_blank">BTC</a>) gained 18.1%, while ethereum (<a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/ETH" target="_blank">ETH</a>) rose by 12.5%.</p>
<p>However, numerous other digital assets experienced significantly larger gains, as evident from cryptobubbles.net&#x2019;s <a href="https://cryptobubbles.net/">weekly data</a>. According to the data, <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/BCH" target="_blank">BCH</a>, XRD, PEPE, WOO, ZIL, and VET all recorded double-digit gains.</p>

<p>The meme coin pepe (PEPE) experienced a significant 65% increase this week, while bitcoin cash (<a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/BCH" target="_blank">BCH</a>) jumped over 38%. Pepe led the pack in terms of gains, while stacks (STX) rose by more than 41% over the past seven days.</p>
<p>Conflux (CFX) saw a jump of 40.4%, and kaspa (KAS) gained 26% during the same period. On the other hand, digital currencies such as bittorrent (BTT), kucoin (KCS), terra luna classic (LUNC), and quant (QNT) faced losses ranging from 2.2% to 7.9% this week.</p>

<p>Friday&#x2019;s leaders in terms of 24-hour stats include FTT, which is up more than 14%; VET, up over 11%; <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/BSV" target="_blank">BSV</a>, up more than 8%; LEO, also up more than 8%; ZIL, up 7.6%; and <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/BCH" target="_blank">BCH</a>, up more than 6%.</p>
<p>Although, today&#x2019;s 24-hour losses are led by PEPE and STX. PEPE shed 5.5%, while STX lost 9.8% during the last day. Bitcoin dominance remains high at 48.2%, and <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/ETH" target="_blank">ETH</a>&#x2019;s market dominance stands at 18.6%, according to coingecko.com&#x2019;s <a href="https://www.coingecko.com">current data</a>.</p>

<p>The crypto rally is believed to be driven by institutional interest and the involvement of major traditional finance (tradfi) giants. In the past week and a half, <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/valkyrie-funds-joins-race-for-sec-approval-as-it-files-application-for-spot-bitcoin-etf/">several</a> spot bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) were <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/blackrock-files-for-bitcoin-trust-analyst-calls-it-a-real-deal-spot-bitcoin-etf-filing/">filed</a>, and a <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/crypto-exchange-backed-by-fidelity-schwab-citadel-launches-with-trading-of-4-cryptocurrencies/">crypto exchange</a> backed by Charles Schwab, Citadel Securities, and Fidelity Digital Assets was recently launched.</p>
<p>However, despite the so-called institutional interest, the global trade volume of the crypto economy has been low, and a few crypto businesses are still <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/crypto-firms-face-turmoil-as-prime-trust-fallout-causes-service-disruptions-and-concerns/">exhibiting signs</a> of financial weakness.</p>
<p><em><strong>What are your predictions for the future of the crypto market? Which digital assets do you think will continue to outperform others in the coming weeks? Share your thoughts and opinions about this subject in the comments section below.</strong></em></p>




]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/22787-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[At the time of writing, the #crypto economy stands at $1.21 trillion, following a 9.62% increase this week.]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA[At the time of writing, the #crypto economy stands at $1.21 trillion, following a 9.62% increase this week. ]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Robert F. Kennedy Jr. Advocates for Bitcoin and Opposes CBDCs in Candid Interview </title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/robert-f-kennedy-jr-advocates-for-bitcoin-and-opposes-cbdcs-in-candid-interview/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jamie Redman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 14:30:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[anti-vaxxer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[central bank digital currencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Democratic presidential hopeful]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mainstream media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[New York Post interview]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulatory Agencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robert F. Kennedy Jr.]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[safe vaccines]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[U.S. presidential candidate]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vaccines]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=594609</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/kenn-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Robert F. Kennedy Jr. Advocates for Bitcoin and Opposes CBDCs in Candid Interview " decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/kenn-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/kenn-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/kenn-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/kenn-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/kenn-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/kenn-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/kenn.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />U.S. presidential candidate Robert F. Kennedy Jr. spoke in an interview with the New York Post on June 22, 2023, and discussed a wide range of topics, including vaccines and bitcoin. Kennedy stated that if he becomes president, he will ensure that the U.S. maintains &#x201C;policies that support bitcoin and the freedom to transact.&#x201D; RFK [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/kenn-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Robert F. Kennedy Jr. Advocates for Bitcoin and Opposes CBDCs in Candid Interview " decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/kenn-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/kenn-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/kenn-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/kenn-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/kenn-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/kenn-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/kenn.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>U.S. presidential candidate Robert F. Kennedy Jr. spoke in an interview with the New York Post on June 22, 2023, and discussed a wide range of topics, including vaccines and bitcoin. Kennedy stated that if he becomes president, he will ensure that the U.S. maintains &#x201C;policies that support bitcoin and the freedom to transact.&#x201D;</strong></p>
<h2>RFK Jr. Blasts Mainstream Media Insisting He&#x2019;s &#x2018;Never Been Anti-Vaccine&#x2019;</h2>
<p>On Thursday, <a href="https://twitter.com/RobertKennedyJr">Robert F. Kennedy Jr.</a>, the son of former U.S. attorney general and senator Robert F. Kennedy and the nephew of former U.S. president John F. Kennedy, <a href="https://nypost.com/2023/06/22/robert-f-kennedy-jr-interview-why-im-not-an-anti-vaxxer/">discussed</a> a few specific topics with Lydia Moynihan of the New York Post. Kennedy has recently garnered attention following a challenge from podcaster Joe Rogan to Houston-based scientist Peter Hotez for a vaccine debate with Kennedy. The situation intensified when Elon Musk, owner of Twitter and Tesla executive, <a href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1670219488485154816">tweeted</a> that Hotez is &#x201C;afraid of a public debate, because he knows he&#x2019;s wrong.&#x201D;</p>
<p>In the interview with Moynihan, the Democratic presidential hopeful emphasized that he is not an &#x201C;anti-vaxxer,&#x201D; a term broadly used to describe individuals skeptical of vaccination, including the new Covid-19 vaccines. &#x201C;I am not and have never been anti-vaccine,&#x201D; Kennedy stressed on Thursday. &#x201C;I&#x2019;ve always said that I&#x2019;m for safe vaccines and robust science and for regulatory agencies that are free from conflicts of interest and financial entanglements with the pharmaceutical industry.&#x201D;</p>
<p>Kennedy added:</p>
<blockquote><p>I urge people to listen to what I actually say instead of listening to the litany of derisive sound bites that the mainstream media offers to mischaracterize and distort my positions on the whole range of issues.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Kennedy Reasserts Promise to Protect Bitcoin While Stressing CBDCs Are &#x2018;Instruments of Control and Oppression&#x2019;</h2>
<p>Kennedy also discussed bitcoin (<a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/BTC" 311996  target="_blank">BTC</a>) during the Post interview, after <a href="https://twitter.com/QuintenFrancois/status/1659499618873245696?s=20">expressing his belief</a> last month that the cryptocurrency asset is an &#x201C;exercise in democracy.&#x201D; Following that statement, the U.S. presidential candidate made an <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/robert-kennedy-jr-to-accept-btc-for-campaign-contributions-says-bitcoin-is-an-exercise-in-democracy/">announcement</a> on May 19 that he would accept <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/BTC" 311996  target="_blank">BTC</a> for campaign donations.</p>
<p>&#x201C;I will make sure that we have policies that support bitcoin and the freedom to transact and that allow individuals to manage their own bitcoin wallets, nodes, and passwords,&#x201D; Kennedy told the Post on Thursday. &#x201C;I will allow only the narrowest controls that are necessary to prevent money laundering. I oppose central bank digital currencies because they are instruments of control and oppression, and are certain to be abused.&#x201D;</p>
<p class="p1"></p>
<p>It is not the first instance where Kennedy has discussed central bank digital currencies (CBDCs), as he has previously <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/robert-kennedy-jr-government-could-ban-seize-bitcoin-cbdcs-could-lead-to-financial-slavery-political-tyranny/">expressed concerns</a> that these financial instruments could result in &#x201C;financial slavery&#x201D; and &#x201C;political tyranny.&#x201D;</p>
<p>In late May, Kennedy <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/robert-kennedy-jr-slams-sec-for-protecting-banks-instead-of-american-people-calls-for-crypto-friendly-commissioners/">strongly criticized</a> the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) for its recent crackdown on the crypto industry and advocated for SEC commissioners who are supportive of crypto. &#x201C;What they&#x2019;re doing is obscure, it&#x2019;s not transparent, and it&#x2019;s not bringing transparency to our system,&#x201D; Kennedy said at the time.</p>
<p>Incumbent president Joe Biden may face a challenge, as a <a href="https://wsau.com/2023/06/15/new-yougov-poll-robert-f-kennedy-jr-ranked-most-favorable-2024-presidential-candidate/">poll</a> conducted by The Economist and YouGov pitted him against Kennedy and other 2024 presidential candidates, with Kennedy emerging as the frontrunner. However, the mainstream media swiftly shifted the focus by <a href="https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/4049957-biden-leading-rfk-jr-by-53-points-in-new-survey/">highlighting</a> a Quinnipiac University poll that showed Biden&#x2019;s favorability surpassing Kennedy&#x2019;s. The Washington Post <a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/2023/06/15/kennedy-desantis-polls-favorability/">noted</a> that favorability is a &#x201C;tricky metric&#x201D; in an article published the same week.</p>
<p><em><strong>What are your thoughts on Robert F. Kennedy Jr.&#x2019;s stance on bitcoin and his presidential bid? Share your thoughts and opinions about this subject in the comments section below.</strong></em></p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/kenn-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[“I will make sure that we have policies that support #bitcoin and the freedom to transact," Kennedy said on Thursday. ]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA[“I will make sure that we have policies that support #bitcoin and the freedom to transact," Kennedy said on Thursday. ]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin, Ethereum Technical Analysis: BTC Stays Above $30,000, Despite Traders Moving to Secure Recent Gains</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-ethereum-technical-analysis-btc-stays-above-30000-despite-traders-moving-to-secure-recent-gains/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Eliman Dambell]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 12:30:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technical Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=594661</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_769817014-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="BTC Stays Above $30,000, Despite Traders Moving to Secure Recent Gains" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_769817014-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_769817014-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_769817014-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_769817014-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_769817014-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_769817014-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_769817014.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />Bitcoin consolidated around the $30,000 level on Friday, as traders attempted to maintain bullish sentiment following recent gains. The world&#x2019;s largest cryptocurrency briefly dropped below this point earlier in the day, before bulls swept in to buy the dip in price. However, ethereum fell below a recent high above $1,900. Bitcoin Bitcoin remained above the [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_769817014-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="BTC Stays Above $30,000, Despite Traders Moving to Secure Recent Gains" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_769817014-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_769817014-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_769817014-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_769817014-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_769817014-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_769817014-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_769817014.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>Bitcoin consolidated around the $30,000 level on Friday, as traders attempted to maintain bullish sentiment following recent gains. The world&#x2019;s largest cryptocurrency briefly dropped below this point earlier in the day, before bulls swept in to buy the dip in price. However, ethereum fell below a recent high above $1,900.</strong></p>
<h2>Bitcoin</h2>
<p>Bitcoin remained above the $30,000 level on Friday, as traders attempted to keep sentiment bullish heading into the weekend.</p>
<p>Following a low of $29,679.16 earlier in the day, <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/BTC" 311996  target="_blank">BTC</a>/USD moved to a peak of $30,334.40 as the day progressed.</p>
<p>Price has since gone on to fall from its previous high, as the 14-day relative strength index (RSI) encountered a point of resistance.</p>
<div class="tradingview-widget-container">
<div class="tradingview-widget-copyright"><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/?exchange=BITSTAMP" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span class="blue-text">Bitcoin chart</span></a> by TradingView</div>
<p><script type="text/javascript" src="https://s3.tradingview.com/tv.js"></script><script type="text/javascript">
  new TradingView.widget(
  {
  "width": "100%",
  "height": "400",
  "symbol": "BITSTAMP:BTCUSD",
  "interval": "D",
  "timezone": "Etc/UTC",
  "theme": "light",
  "style": "1",
  "locale": "en",
  "toolbar_bg": "#F1F3F6",
  "enable_publishing": false,
  "container_id": "tradingview_1247e"
}
  );
  </script></p>
</div>
<p><!-- TradingView Widget END --></p>
<p>At the time of writing, the index is tracking at 70.43, which is marginally lower than the aforementioned ceiling at 71.00.</p>
<p>Overall, momentum remains bullish as the 10-day (red) moving average continues its upwards crossover versus its 25-day (blue) counterpart.</p>
<p>Should the RSI move beyond the 71.00 level in the coming days, there is a good chance that <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/BTC" 311996  target="_blank">BTC</a> will be above $32,000.</p>

<h2>Ethereum</h2>
<p>On the other hand, ethereum (<a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/ETH" target="_blank">ETH</a>) moved slightly lower in today&#x2019;s session, with price retreating from a recent multi-month high.</p>
<p><a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/ETH" target="_blank">ETH</a>/USD dropped to an intraday low at $1,866.26, which comes a day after trading at a peak of $1,908.13.</p>
<p>This decline appeared to be a result of profit taking, as bulls moved to secure gains, following a recent upswing.</p>
<div class="tradingview-widget-container">
<div class="tradingview-widget-copyright"><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ETHUSD/?exchange=BITSTAMP" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span class="blue-text">Ethereum chart</span></a> by TradingView</div>
<p><script type="text/javascript" src="https://s3.tradingview.com/tv.js"></script><script type="text/javascript">
  new TradingView.widget(
  {
  "width": "100%",
  "height": "400",
  "symbol": "BITSTAMP:ETHUSD",
  "interval": "D",
  "timezone": "Etc/UTC",
  "theme": "light",
  "style": "1",
  "locale": "en",
  "toolbar_bg": "#F1F3F6",
  "enable_publishing": false,
  "container_id": "tradingview_1247e"
}
  );
  </script></p>
</div>
<p><!-- TradingView Widget END --></p>
<p>Similar to <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/BTC" 311996  target="_blank">BTC</a>, traders abandoned previous positions as the RSI failed to advance beyond a key resistance level.</p>
<p>In this instance, the ceiling was at the 60.00 mark, which has been the highest level the index has hit since April.</p>
<p>As of writing, the RSI now tracks at 59.25, with ethereum trading at $1,878.66.</p>
<p><em>Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:</em></p>
<p><em><strong>What is the highest point ethereum can reach this weekend? Leave your thoughts in the comments below.</strong></em></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_769817014-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[#BTC bulls keep price above $30,000, despite profit taking.]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA[#BTC bulls keep price above $30,000, despite profit taking.]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lawyer Seeks Reopening of Onecoin Case in Bulgaria, Seizure of Assets</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/lawyer-seeks-reopening-of-onecoin-case-in-bulgaria-seizure-of-assets/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lubomir Tassev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 11:30:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[attorney]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bulgaria]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto pyramid]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptoqueen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ignatova]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investigation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[lawyer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[murder]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Onecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ponzi Scheme]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[prosecutor]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pyramid]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pyramid Scheme]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Request]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ruja Ignatova]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[South Africa]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Victims]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=594573</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_1456957025-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Lawyer Seeks Reopening of Onecoin Case in Bulgaria, Seizure of Assets" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_1456957025-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_1456957025-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_1456957025-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_1456957025-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_1456957025-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_1456957025-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_1456957025.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />A lawyer representing Onecoin victims has urged Bulgarian authorities to reopen an investigation into the crypto pyramid scheme and seize assets to compensate his clients. The attorney is asking officials in Sofia to take into account developments he considers related to the case, including the recent murder of a Bulgarian crime figure in South Africa. [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_1456957025-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Lawyer Seeks Reopening of Onecoin Case in Bulgaria, Seizure of Assets" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_1456957025-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_1456957025-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_1456957025-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_1456957025-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_1456957025-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_1456957025-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_1456957025.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>A lawyer representing Onecoin victims has urged Bulgarian authorities to reopen an investigation into the crypto pyramid scheme and seize assets to compensate his clients. The attorney is asking officials in Sofia to take into account developments he considers related to the case, including the recent murder of a Bulgarian crime figure in South Africa. </strong></p>
<h2>Attorney Hopes New Bulgarian Chief Prosecutor Takes on Onecoin Investigation</h2>
<p>Dr. Jonathan Levy, a legal representative for people affected by Onecoin from several countries, has filed a new request that Bulgaria&#x2019;s acting top prosecutor reopens an investigation into the multi-billion dollar crypto Ponzi scheme and seize associated assets for restitution of the victims.</p>
<p>In a letter to the Bulgarian Ministry of Justice, Levy is turning attention to recent events that he believes are connected to the case. These include the murder of Bulgarian organized crime figure Krasimir Kamenov in South Africa, linked to the recently fired chief public prosecutor of Bulgaria, Ivan Geshev, and the fugitive founder of Onecoin, Ruja Ignatova.</p>
<p>Geshev was removed from office by Bulgaria&#x2019;s Supreme Judicial Council earlier in June and replaced by Borislav Sarafov as Acting Prosecutor General. In December 2021, Levy filed a petition with the Bulgarian Constitutional Ombudsman, accusing Geshev of protecting Onecoin which allegedly continued to operate through affiliated entities in Bulgaria.</p>
<p>The U.K. lawyer now insists that Onecoin must be shut down, the responsible persons arrested and their assets seized. In support of his latest <a href="https://www.jlevy.co/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/June-18-2023-OneCoin.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener">request</a>, Levy presents a sworn declaration by Onecoin&#x2019;s former Compliance Officer Duncan Arthur, a citizen of the Republic of Ireland and the Republic of South Africa, which details the scam&#x2019;s contacts in Africa.</p>
<p>Kamenov, who was assassinated in Cape Town in late May, along with his wife and two other victims, has been accused of involvement in the murder of a top police official in Sofia and connected to the disappearance of Ruja Ignatova and a <a href="https://www.bbc.com/news/technology-61966824" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a> 230,000 <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/BTC" 311996  target="_blank">BTC</a> in her possession.</p>

<h2>Cryptoqueen&#x2019;s Whereabouts and Fate Still Unknown</h2>
<p>According to an article published in February by the Bulgarian website Bureau for Investigative Reporting and Data (Bird.bg), the &#x201C;missing Cryptoqueen&#x201D; was <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/onecoin-cryptoqueen-killed-in-greece-in-2018-report-claims/">killed</a> in Greece, in November 2018, a year after she boarded a plane bound for Athens. The report claims the conclusion is based on evidence obtained during the investigation into last year&#x2019;s murder of the ex-head of a criminal police department in the Bulgarian capital.</p>
<p>Both may have been murdered by a crime group associated with Kamenov, according to the information. However, Jonathan Levy requested an investigation suggesting Ignatova&#x2019;s death may have been faked by the criminal organization. &#x201C;Geshev then belatedly sought Kamenov&#x2019;s arrest but not before Geshev claimed he had narrowly escaped a bomb plot,&#x201D; the attorney noted.</p>
<p>&#x201C;I am requesting the Acting Chief Prosecutor review this new material and our previous requests and take action now against the Onecoin organized crime gang in Bulgaria and the former Chief Prosecutor Geshev who we accuse of deliberate nonfeasance. And in particular seize the assets of the OneCoin gang for the benefit and restitution of victims,&#x201D; Levy wrote to the Bulgarian Justice Ministry.</p>
<p>Launched in 2014 as a multi-level marketing (MLM) network based on a non-existent cryptocurrency, Onecoin is believed to have defrauded more than 3 million investors globally of over $4 billion. Its mastermind, Bulgarian-born German national Ruja Ignatova, was last seen on Oct. 25, 2017, at the airport in Athens, and is still wanted by Interpol, <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/onecoin-crypto-queen-ruja-ignatova-listed-among-europes-most-wanted/">Europol</a>, and the U.S. Federal Bureau of Investigation (<a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/onecoins-co-founder-ruja-ignatova-has-been-added-to-the-fbis-10-most-wanted-fugitives-list/">FBI</a>).</p>
<p>According to South Africa&#x2019;s Daily Maverick newspaper, Kamenov may have had information about her. The publication also revealed that around 2018, Ignatova&#x2019;s brother and Onecoin co-founder, Konstantin, posted photos on his Instagram showing he had visited Cape Town. He was arrested in Los Angeles the following year and pleaded guilty to Onecoin-related charges while seeking witness protection in the United States. Ruja&#x2019;s business partner, U.K. and Swedish national Sebastian Greenwood, also <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/onecoin-co-founder-pleads-guilty-to-fraud-charges-in-us/">pleaded guilty</a> in December 2022.</p>
<p><em><strong>Do you think investigators will get to the bottom of the Onecoin case? Share your thoughts on the subject in the comments section below. </strong></em></p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shutterstock_1456957025-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[#British lawyer seeks reopening of #Onecoin investigation in #Bulgaria. ]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA[Attorney for #Onecoin victims hopes Bulgaria’s new chief prosecutor takes on investigation into the multi-billion dollar fraud. ]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Securing Web3 With Zero Trust: Empowering Data, Smart Contracts, and AI on the Blockchain With Mind Network</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/securing-web3-with-zero-trust-empowering-data-smart-contracts-and-ai-on-the-blockchain-with-mind-network/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Media]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 11:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sponsored]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind Network]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=587272&#038;preview=true&#038;preview_id=587272</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/unnamed-88-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/unnamed-88-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/unnamed-88-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/unnamed-88-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/unnamed-88-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/unnamed-88-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/unnamed-88-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/unnamed-88.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />In the rapidly evolving world of Web3, where data security and privacy are paramount, innovative solutions are needed to protect sensitive information and establish trust within the decentralized ecosystem. This sponsored article delves into the concept of Zero Trust and explores how it serves as the foundation for a revolutionary platform called Mind Network. By [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/unnamed-88-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/unnamed-88-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/unnamed-88-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/unnamed-88-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/unnamed-88-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/unnamed-88-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/unnamed-88-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/unnamed-88.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In the rapidly evolving world of Web3, where data security and privacy are paramount, innovative solutions are needed to protect sensitive information and establish trust within the decentralized ecosystem. This sponsored article delves into the concept of Zero Trust and explores how it serves as the foundation for a revolutionary platform called </span><a href="https://mindnetwork.xyz/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Mind Network</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">. By combining the principles of Zero Trust with cutting-edge encryption techniques, Mind Network aims to empower users, developers, and businesses to secure their data, smart contracts, and AI models on the blockchain. Mind Network recently closed its seed round fundraising, led by Binance Labs and co-invested by SevenX Ventures, HashKey Capital, Arweave SCP Ventures, etc. Mind Network was incubated by </span><a href="https://mindnetwork.medium.com/mind-network-was-selected-for-season-5-of-the-binance-labs-incubation-program-64677b30666d"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Binance Incubation Camp Season 5</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> and selected into </span><a href="https://mindnetwork.medium.com/mind-network-joins-chainlink-build-to-accelerate-adoption-of-decentralized-privacy-preserving-data-17b34e2130e0"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Chainlink BUILD Program</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">. </span></p>
<p><strong>The Rise of Zero Trust Security</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Traditional security paradigms in Web2 environments relied on the assumption of trust within a centralized infrastructure. However, the increasing frequency of data breaches and cyberattacks has exposed the vulnerabilities inherent in this approach. Enter Zero Trust Security, a modern strategy built on the principle of &#8220;never trust, always verify.&#8221; Zero Trust assumes that breaches have either already occurred or are imminent, prompting the need for continuous verification of every request, irrespective of its origin.</span></p>
<p><strong>Zero Trust Principles for Enhanced Security</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Zero Trust Security operates on several core principles that ensure robust data protection and access control:</span></p>
<p><b>Verify Explicitly:</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> Each request, regardless of its source, must be explicitly authenticated, authorized, and verified before granting access.</span></p>
<p><b>Use Least-Privilege Access:</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> Access permissions are granted at the most minimal level necessary, reducing the risk of unauthorized access and potential data breaches.</span></p>
<p><b>Assume Breach:</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> Zero Trust assumes that breaches are inevitable, which prompts continuous monitoring, verification, and mitigation measures throughout the system.</span></p>
<p><strong>Challenges in Web3 Security and Why Zero Trust</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The decentralized nature of Web3 introduces unique security challenges that demand innovative solutions. These challenges include:</span></p>
<p><strong>Data Privacy and Ownership</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Web3 emphasizes individuals&#8217; control over their personal data, financial transactions, and user interactions. However, existing applications often lack proper encryption and access control support, risking user privacy.</span></p>
<p><strong>On-Chain Data Protection</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Exposing wallet addresses and smart contract interactions in public ledgers poses security threats and potential financial losses. Protecting this data is crucial to maintaining user trust in decentralized systems.</span></p>
<p><strong>Decentralized Storage Risks</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Decentralized storage systems rely on untrusted node operators to store and compute data, creating potential vulnerabilities and compromising data confidentiality.</span></p>
<p><strong>Trust and Reliability</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ensuring trust and reliability in decentralized systems during computation and state updates is vital to prevent financial losses and maintain the integrity of the network.</span></p>
<p><strong>Why does Web3 need Zero Trust?</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Data Ownership and Privacy challenge needs to remove intermediary or superuser who is assumed to be trusted. It meets the second principles of Zeo Trust to use least-privilege access. Zero Trust assumes breaches are inevitable, which is the foundation to On-Chain Data Protection challenge. Zero Trust can promote verification explicitly to Decentralized Storage Risks challenge. Therefore, a Zero Trust implementation is demanded in Web3. </span></p>
<p><strong>Introducing Mind Network: Empowering Web3 Data Security</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://mindnetwork.xyz/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Mind Network</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> is a pioneering platform that brings Zero Trust principles to the Web3 landscape. Built on the foundation of a Zero Trust Data Lake, Mind Network focuses on securing data, smart contracts, and AI models in a decentralized manner. By utilizing Zero Knowledge Proof (ZKP) and the patented Adaptive Fully Homomorphic Encryption (AFHE) technique, Mind Network enables end-to-end encrypted computation and storage for on-chain private data.</span></p>
<p><a href="https://mindnetwork.xyz?utm_source=bitocoincom&amp;utm_medium=BlockMan&amp;utm_campaign=MindNetworkJune"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Mind Network</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> offers a comprehensive set of solutions designed to enhance security and privacy in Web3 applications:</span></p>
<p><strong>Encrypted Read and Write Solution</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Developers can securely connect their decentralized applications (dApps) to Mind Network, enabling encrypted read and write operations on sensitive data. Encrypted data remains inaccessible to Mind Network and its node providers, ensuring privacy and security.</span></p>
<p><strong>Encrypted Content Sharing Solution</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Mind Network enables the secure sharing of encrypted data between dApps using tokenized access control. This solution is invaluable in data marketplaces, private subscription services, and other scenarios requiring controlled data sharing or monetization.</span></p>
<p><strong>Privacy-Preserving Computation Solution</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Developers can perform privacy-preserving computations on encrypted data within Mind Network. This allows for various use cases, including executing order books, credit evaluations, medical research, and legal protection.</span></p>
<p><strong>Secure Data Verification Solution</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Mind Network provides a solution for verifying users&#8217; encrypted data and computation results. This allows decentralized applications (dApps) to verify specific rules without accessing the content, ensuring the integrity of social connections, voting results, asset positions, risk scores, and more.</span></p>
<p><strong>Secure Data-Driven Smart Contracts Solution</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Mind Network collaborates with Chainlink to address data transfer limitations from off-chain to on-chain smart contracts. Encrypting data and performing computations on encrypted inputs ensures privacy and security for use cases such as trading signals, financial models, on-chain gaming, and more.</span></p>
<p><strong>Securing AI Models with Mind Network&#8217;s Zero-Trust Solution</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Mind Network&#8217;s Zero-Trust AI Solution offers robust protection for AI models, mitigating the risk of unauthorized manipulation and ensuring end-to-end security. Enabling encrypted input and output safeguards against unpredictable damage to financial markets and user interests.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Mind Network&#8217;s Zero-Trust AI Solution defends against unauthorized manipulation and addresses additional risks. It can potentially mitigate model collapse, preventing decreased accuracy and biased outputs over time. Furthermore, it tackles the challenge of &#8216;proof of human data,&#8217; verifying the authenticity and integrity of training datasets. By adopting this secure framework, AI models can operate with transparency and trust, bolstering confidence in AI-driven systems across industries.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Mind Network&#8217;s Zero-Trust AI Solution provides a reliable foundation for deploying AI models in finance, healthcare, and other domains. It promotes responsible AI adoption, safeguarding against potential harm and ensuring the integrity of decision-making processes.</span></p>
<p><strong>Use Cases for Mind Network</strong></p>
<p><b>dWeb Use Case:</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> Mind Network serves as a secure data lake for decentralized web applications, allowing them to persist front-end data using decentralized storage while accessing encrypted data from Mind Network. This use case applies to UGC platforms, social and gaming platforms, DeFi, and middleware protocols.</span></p>
<p><b>TradFi Use Case:</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> Traditional financial institutions can leverage Mind Network to generate risk profiles for crypto investor customers while preserving their privacy. By encrypting customer wallet lists and combining them with on-chain data, risk assessments can be performed without compromising user confidentiality. This use case extends to areas like fraud detection, compliance, and anti-money laundering (AML).</span></p>
<p><b>AI Use Case:</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> Mind Network addresses privacy protection challenges in social networks by combining encryption and social relationships. For instance, photos can be pre-processed, encrypted, and stored on Mind Network, giving users control over their data and access based on their social connections.</span></p>
<p><b>DeFi Use Case:</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> Mind Network enhances transparency and control in trading platforms by encrypting trading positions and order books, enabling secure and private trading without exposing sensitive information. This use case applies to spot, derivative, dark pool, and cross-chain exchanges.</span></p>
<p><strong>Team</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Mind Network team comes from a solid background, with special mentions for the CTO, George, who was a researcher at Cambridge University and has had his research in cryptography adopted by the United Kingdom government and high-street banks, and Dennis, the CSO, is the first white hat hacker to hack Tesla in 2014. The rest of the team is assembled with serial entrepreneurs, award-winning scientists, and Web3 marketing veterans. </span></p>
<p><strong>Investors and Partners</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Mind Network has closed its seed round fundraising. This round is led by Binance Labs and co-invested by Comma3 Ventures, SevenX Ventures, HashKey Capital, Big Brain Holdings, Arweave SCP Ventures, Meridian Capital, etc. Mind Network was incubated by Binance Incubation Camp Season 5 as the only data project and selected into Chainlink BUILD Program. Even early, Mind Network established strong partnerships with Binance, Chainlink, Consensys, and Arweave. It acquired early supporters, including well-known global banks, insurance companies, and various dApps and protocols.</span></p>
<p><strong>Final Recap</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Mind Network&#8217;s innovative Zero Trust Data Lake presents a groundbreaking solution for securing data, smart contracts, and AI in the Web3 ecosystem. By implementing Zero Trust principles and leveraging advanced encryption techniques, Mind Network empowers users, developers, and businesses to maintain privacy, protect sensitive information, and establish trust within the decentralized landscape. Mind Network paves the way for a more secure and privacy-focused Web3 future with its comprehensive suite of solutions.</span></p>
<p><strong>For more information about Mind Network, please reach out to us on:</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Website: </span><a href="https://mindnetwork.xyz/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://mindnetwork.xyz/</span></a></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Twitter: </span><a href="https://twitter.com/mindnetwork_xyz"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/mindnetwork_xyz</span></a></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Medium: </span><a href="https://mindnetwork.medium.com/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://mindnetwork.medium.com/</span></a></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Gitbook: </span><a href="https://mind-network.gitbook.io/mindnetwork/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://mind-network.gitbook.io/mindnetwork/</span></a></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Github: </span><a href="https://github.com/mind-network"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://github.com/mind-network</span></a></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Discord: </span><a href="https://discord.gg/UYj94MJdGJ"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://discord.gg/UYj94MJdGJ</span></a></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Telegram: </span><a href="https://t.me/MindNetwork_xyz"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://t.me/MindNetwork_xyz</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<hr />
<p><small><em>This is a sponsored post. Learn how to reach our audience <a href="https://www.bitcoin.com/advertise/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">here</a>. Read disclaimer below.</em></small></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/unnamed-88-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[Securing Web3 With Zero Trust: Empowering Data, Smart Contracts, and AI on the Blockchain With Mind Network]]></bnmedia:barker_title>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
