<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:bnmedia="https://news.bitcoin.com/">

<channel>
	<title>Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/</link>
	<description>Daily Bitcoin News</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 17:00:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Ethereum Price Set to Reach $2,500 by Year-End, Predicts Finder&#8217;s Panel</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/ethereum-price-set-to-reach-2500-by-year-end-predicts-finders-panel/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jamie Redman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 17:30:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets and Prices]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[$2.5K]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Decentralized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finder]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fintech experts]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mitesh Shah]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Omnia Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[panel]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[prediction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Proof-of-Stake]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Security]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[staking solutions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Swyftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tommy Honan]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=600077</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/227-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/227-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/227-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/227-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/227-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/227-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/227-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/227.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />The price of ethereum (ETH), the world&#x2019;s second-largest cryptocurrency by market cap, is anticipated to hit a high of $2.7K before settling at around $2.5K by the end of 2023, according to the latest report from Finder. The report is based on predictions by a panel of 29 cryptocurrency and fintech experts who also expressed [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/227-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/227-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/227-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/227-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/227-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/227-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/227-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/227.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>The price of ethereum (<a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/ETH" 311998  target="_blank">ETH</a>), the world&#x2019;s second-largest cryptocurrency by market cap, is anticipated to hit a high of $2.7K before settling at around $2.5K by the end of 2023, according to the latest report from Finder. The report is based on predictions by a panel of 29 cryptocurrency and fintech experts who also expressed confidence about the long-term growth of the digital currency. Additionally, most panelists believe it&#x2019;s unlikely the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) will classify <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/ETH" 311998  target="_blank">ETH</a> as a security.</strong></p>
<h2>Ethereum Price Predictions and Market Outlook</h2>
<p>Ethereum&#x2019;s price uptick can be attributed to bitcoin&#x2019;s recent surge, according to Omnia Markets founder and CEO, Mitesh Shah. He noted that as bitcoin&#x2019;s value increases due to factors like institutional adoption, ether&#x2019;s price is also expected to rise as investors look to diversify their portfolios. Shah gave an end-of-year prediction aligning with the panel average at $2,400, in Finder&#x2019;s latest <a href="https://www.finder.com/ethereum-price-prediction-2023">ETH price prediction report</a>.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-600088" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/predicts.jpg" alt="" width="1280" height="500" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/predicts-300x117.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/predicts-1024x400.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/predicts-768x300.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/predicts.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 1280px) 100vw, 1280px"></p>
<p>Swyftx&#x2019;s head of product, Tommy Honan, is even more bullish, predicting ether to end the year at $2,500. He attributes his forecast to the successful upgrade to a proof-of-stake (PoS) consensus mechanism. He thinks the upgrade has made Ethereum more efficient and deflationary and has boosted its appeal among both retail and institutional investors.</p>
<p>&#x201C;Ethereum remains the standout second choice investment for both the retail and institutional investors alike. Following the successful upgrade to proof of stake, which has been akin to &#x2018;changing a jet plane engine, mid-flight,&#x2019; <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/ETH" 311998  target="_blank">ETH</a> has become more efficient and deflationary to mention a few,&#x201D; Honan remarked.</p>
<p>The panel&#x2019;s optimistic view extends beyond 2023. They predict that by the end of 2025, ethereum&#x2019;s price will reach $5,845 and rise further to $16,414 by the end of 2030. Futurist Joseph Raczynski is even more bullish, forecasting a price of $8,000 for <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/ETH" 311998  target="_blank">ETH</a> by 2025, and nearly doubling to $15,000 by 2030.</p>
<p>Raczynski believes that a number of regulatory hurdles will be overcome this year for ethereum, which will contribute to its overall growth. He adds that despite short-term growth, ethereum&#x2019;s real price potential lies in the next 5-10 years.</p>

<h2>Regulatory Uncertainty</h2>
<p>A significant part of the panel discussion revolved around the SEC&#x2019;s potential classification of <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/ETH" 311998  target="_blank">ETH</a> as a security. The majority (67%) of Finder&#x2019;s panel do not believe that <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/ETH" 311998  target="_blank">ETH</a> will be deemed a security. However, 11% believe it is likely, while the remaining 22% are uncertain.</p>
<p>Seasonal Tokens founder Ruadhan O is part of the majority who believe that it&#x2019;s unlikely <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/ETH" 311998  target="_blank">ETH</a> will be deemed a security. He expressed concern that such a ruling would limit the ability of U.S. residents to access smart contract technology.</p>
<p>&#x201C;If ethereum is declared to be a security, then exchanges would not be able to offer it to U.S. residents without violating securities laws,&#x201D; the Seasonal Tokens executive said. &#x201C;This would make the US into the only country in the world where there is no easy access to smart contract technology.&#x201D;</p>
<p>Digital Capital Management Managing Director Ben Ritchie, who falls within the 22% uncertainty bracket, noted that Ethereum&#x2019;s decentralized nature could work in its favor. However, he expressed concerns about the increasing prominence of centralized staking solutions, which could pose a threat to the network&#x2019;s decentralization.</p>
<p>Concluding the report, the majority (56%) of Finder&#x2019;s panel believe now is the right time to buy <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/ETH" 311998  target="_blank">ETH</a>. About 41% advise holding onto the cryptocurrency, and a mere 4% suggest selling. You can read Finder&#x2019;s report in its entirety <a href="https://www.finder.com/ethereum-price-prediction-2023">here</a>.</p>
<p><em><strong>What do you think about the latest ether predictions by Finder&#x2019;s experts? Share your thoughts and opinions about this subject in the comments section below.</strong></em></p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/227-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[Most panelists believe it's unlikely the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) will classify #ethereum as a security.]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA[A significant part of the panel discussion revolved around the SEC's potential classification of #ethereum as a security.]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Unpacking LBank&#8217;s Success: A Strategic Approach to MEME Coins and the Crypto Market</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/unpacking-lbanks-success-a-strategic-approach-to-meme-coins-and-the-crypto-market/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Media]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 17:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=600134&#038;preview=true&#038;preview_id=600134</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/unnamed-2-768x432.png" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/unnamed-2-300x169.png 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/unnamed-2-768x432.png 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/unnamed-2-190x107.png 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/unnamed-2-380x214.png 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/unnamed-2-760x428.png 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/unnamed-2.png 900w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />PRESS RELEASE. In the rapidly evolving crypto landscape, the LBank exchange platform is making waves. Their noteworthy achievement of being ranked among the top 5 global exchanges in CoinMarketCap&#8217;s (CMC) H1 report is reflective of their innovative strategies and an unyielding commitment to driving the industry forward. Strategizing Success with MEME Coins In the first [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/unnamed-2-768x432.png" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/unnamed-2-300x169.png 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/unnamed-2-768x432.png 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/unnamed-2-190x107.png 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/unnamed-2-380x214.png 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/unnamed-2-760x428.png 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/unnamed-2.png 900w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p>PRESS RELEASE. In the rapidly evolving crypto landscape, the LBank exchange platform is making waves. Their noteworthy achievement of being ranked among the top 5 global exchanges in CoinMarketCap&#8217;s (CMC) H1 report is reflective of their innovative strategies and an unyielding commitment to driving the industry forward.</p>
<p><strong>Strategizing Success with MEME Coins</strong></p>
<p>In the first half of the year, LBank, as per the CMC report, showcased an impressive performance with a market share of 4.6%, ranking 5th in spot trading volume. The catalyst for this growth was their strategic focus on MEME coins, an asset class often perceived as high risk due to its volatility. LBank&#8217;s effective MEME Listing strategy has played a crucial role in this achievement, aiding users in selecting quality MEME coins and creating a reputation for reliability.</p>
<p><strong>Risk and Profitability: A Balancing Act</strong></p>
<p>Profitability in the MEME coins market, given its inherently volatile nature, cannot be promised, a fact that LBank&#8217;s founder, Eric He, acknowledges upfront. However, he also stresses that LBank maintains a strong commitment to its users by implementing rigorous vetting and early listing of promising MEME coins.</p>
<p>This commitment is reflected in the platform&#8217;s robust selection process for listing new MEME coins. Each prospective coin undergoes a stringent review process where several factors, including contract quality, founder credibility, trading depth, and market popularity, are meticulously scrutinized. The aim is to ensure that only those assets meeting LBank&#8217;s high standards are listed, enhancing the likelihood of investors trading in quality assets.</p>
<p>But the commitment does not end with rigorous vetting; LBank further secures an advantage for its users by listing coins early. The platform ensures that promising coins are accessible to investors as soon as possible, potentially at lower price points. A testament to this approach was the listing of PEPE on April 18th, arguably the earliest among known centralized exchanges.</p>
<p>This proactive move by LBank provided a notable advantage to its users. After being listed on LBank, PEPE saw an impressive rise in value, with its maximum increase reaching a staggering 6387%. The case of PEPE thus underscores the potential benefits of LBank&#8217;s approach, which couples rigorous selection with early listing, enabling users to access promising MEME coins at potentially more favorable price points.</p>
<p><strong>Supporting the MEME Coin Sector Beyond Listing</strong></p>
<p>The support for MEME coins on LBank extends beyond simply listing. The platform demonstrates tangible commitment through several initiatives. The recently established $10 million MEME Fund by LBank Labs is designed to stimulate early-stage innovative MEME projects, nurture industry growth, and give back to the community. Furthermore, LBank has hosted the MEME Journey voting contest, sparking enthusiasm within the community. The first MemeKing voting event saw impressive participation, with QUACK securing victory with a staggering 500,000 votes, earning the coveted title of MemeKing. The second round saw similar enthusiasm, with 4CHAN triumphing with an impressive 150,000 votes. The event generated over 100 million impressions on Crypto Twitter, which further demonstrated the enthusiastic spirit of the global Memecoin community.</p>
<p><strong>Embracing Innovation Beyond High-Risk Assets</strong></p>
<p>When asked about LBank&#8217;s stance on supporting high-risk MEME coins, Eric He takes a broader view. He asserts that LBank&#8217;s commitment isn&#8217;t confined to MEME coins alone but extends to all innovative blockchain coins. In his view, the embrace of MEME coins represents the first step in LBank&#8217;s larger strategy to support innovation within the cryptocurrency landscape.</p>
<p>This commitment to supporting innovative coins positions LBank as a frontrunner in the market, ready to deepen its presence and partnership with innovative project teams in the industry.</p>
<p>He emphasizes that LBank will continue to be a pioneer in this market, working closely with innovative projects to continually cultivate and advance the market. This holistic approach highlights LBank&#8217;s commitment to driving innovation and growth in the broader blockchain and crypto industry, demonstrating its role as more than just an exchange platform.</p>
<p>As we look to the future, the latest CMC H1 report underscores LBank&#8217;s continued growth and commitment to top-tier Centralized Exchange (CEX) services. By prioritizing MEME coins, LBank has shown a willingness to embrace risk, supporting innovation and engaging their community in the ever-evolving crypto market. As the industry landscape continues to evolve, LBank stands ready to contribute to its growth and diversification.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<hr />
<p><small><i>This is a press release. Readers should do their own due diligence before taking any actions related to the promoted company or any of its affiliates or services. Bitcoin.com is not responsible, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused or alleged to be caused by or in connection with the use of or reliance on any content, goods or services mentioned in the press release.</i></small></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/unnamed-2-760x428.png</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[Unpacking LBank's Success: A Strategic Approach to MEME Coins and the Crypto Market]]></bnmedia:barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Biggest Movers: SHIB Surges to 2-Week High on Friday, Whilst TRX Extends Gains</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/biggest-movers-shib-surges-to-2-week-high-on-friday-whilst-trx-extends-gains/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Eliman Dambell]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 15:37:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Meme Coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[shib]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[shiba inu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tron]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[trx]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=600110</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2058154703-1-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Biggest Movers: SHIB Surges to 2-Week High on Friday, Whilst TRX Extends Gains" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2058154703-1-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2058154703-1-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2058154703-1-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2058154703-1-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2058154703-1-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2058154703-1-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2058154703-1.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />Shiba inu was a notable gainer on Friday, climbing to a two-week high during today&#x2019;s session in the process. The move came as the meme coin rose by as much as 6%, despite the global crypto market cap mostly consolidating. Tron rose for a fourth straight session today. Shiba Inu (SHIB) Shiba inu (SHIB) rallied [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2058154703-1-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Biggest Movers: SHIB Surges to 2-Week High on Friday, Whilst TRX Extends Gains" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2058154703-1-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2058154703-1-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2058154703-1-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2058154703-1-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2058154703-1-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2058154703-1-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2058154703-1.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>Shiba inu was a notable gainer on Friday, climbing to a two-week high during today&#x2019;s session in the process. The move came as the meme coin rose by as much as 6%, despite the global crypto market cap mostly consolidating. Tron rose for a fourth straight session today. </strong></p>
<h2>Shiba Inu (SHIB)</h2>
<p>Shiba inu (SHIB) rallied to a two-week high on Friday, after breaking out of a key resistance level.</p>
<p>SHIB/USD surged to a peak of $0.000008217 earlier in today&#x2019;s session, following Thursday&#x2019;s low at $0.000007754.</p>
<p>Friday&#x2019;s move came as shiba inu broke out of a key resistance level at the $0.000008000 mark, hitting its highest point since June 15 in the process.</p>

<p>Another reason for today&#x2019;s action appears to be the relative strength index (RSI) moving above a ceiling at 55.00.</p>
<p>Currently, price strength is tracking at the 60.09 level, which is marginally below a ceiling at 61.00.</p>
<p>Should bulls manage to race past this point, there is a good chance the next target price will be $0.000008500.</p>

<h2>Tron (<a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/TRX" 312021  target="_blank">TRX</a>)</h2>
<p>Tron (<a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/TRX" 312021  target="_blank">TRX</a>) extended a recent bull run for a fourth day, with today&#x2019;s move taking the token to its highest point since last Sunday.</p>
<p>Following a low of $0.08221 on Thursday, <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/TRX" 312021  target="_blank">TRX</a>/USD climbed to an intraday high of $0.08417 earlier in today&#x2019;s session.</p>
<p>Tron bulls appear to be targeting a resistance level at $0.0860, which was last hit during last Saturday&#x2019;s peak of $0.0943.</p>

<p>Since hitting that 20-month high <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/TRX" 312021  target="_blank">TRX</a> has mostly consolidated, however bullish momentum seems to be gradually returning.</p>
<p>This comes after the relative strength index (RSI) moved beyond a ceiling of its own at 63.00, and is now tracking at 64.84.</p>
<p>If current sentiment remains, <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/TRX" 312021  target="_blank">TRX</a> could reach $0.0860 in the coming days.</p>
<p><em>Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:</em></p>
<p><em><strong>What is behind tron&#x2019;s recent bull run? Let us know your thoughts in the comments.</strong></em></p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2058154703-1-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[#SHIB snaps recent losing streak, climbing 6% higher during today's session.]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA[#SHIB races to 2-week high on Friday.]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>US House Financial Services Committee Passes Stablecoin Legislation &#8216;After a Few Fireworks&#8217;</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/us-house-financial-services-committee-passes-stablecoin-legislation-after-a-few-fireworks/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Terence Zimwara]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 14:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adrienne Harris]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clarity for Payment Stablecoins Act]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Council for Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[New York Department of Financial Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[patrick mchenry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sheila Warren]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US House Financial Services Committee]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=600002</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2041962920-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="US House Financial Services Committee Passes Stablecoin Legislation &#039;After a Few Fireworks&#039;" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2041962920-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2041962920-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2041962920-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2041962920-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2041962920-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2041962920-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2041962920.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />The U.S. House Financial Services Committee has passed Chairman Patrick McHenry&#8217;s Clarity for Payment Stablecoins Act with bipartisan support. McHenry said committee members, unlike the White House, understood the urgency and importance of providing clarity for payment stablecoins. Sheila Warren, the CEO of the Crypto Council for Innovation, described the bill&#8217;s passage as the &#8220;first [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2041962920-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="US House Financial Services Committee Passes Stablecoin Legislation &#039;After a Few Fireworks&#039;" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2041962920-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2041962920-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2041962920-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2041962920-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2041962920-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2041962920-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2041962920.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>The U.S. House Financial Services Committee has passed Chairman Patrick McHenry&#8217;s Clarity for Payment Stablecoins Act with bipartisan support. McHenry said committee members, unlike the White House, understood the urgency and importance of providing clarity for payment stablecoins. Sheila Warren, the CEO of the Crypto Council for Innovation, described the bill&#8217;s passage as the &#8220;first steps toward a legislative foundation for stablecoins in the U.S.&#8221;</strong></p>
<h2>Landmark Legislation Close to Becoming Law</h2>
<p>After holding negotiations for fifteen months, the U.S. House Financial Services Committee passed the Clarity for Payment Stablecoins Act on July 27 with bipartisan support. According to the committee’s chairperson, Patrick McHenry, the bill’s passage means &#8220;this landmark legislation is one step closer to becoming law.&#8221;</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/BREAKING?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#BREAKING</a>: Chairman <a href="https://twitter.com/PatrickMcHenry?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@PatrickMcHenry</a>&#39;s Clarity for Payment Stablecoins Act passes the Financial Services Committee with BIPARTISAN support.</p>
<p>After fifteen months of bipartisan collaboration, this landmark legislation is one step closer to becoming law. <a href="https://t.co/vCiyqjyAAf">pic.twitter.com/vCiyqjyAAf</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Financial Services GOP (@FinancialCmte) <a href="https://twitter.com/FinancialCmte/status/1684748577031999488?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 28, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Confirmation of the bill’s passage came after an eventful day which at one point saw McHenry blast the White House for frustrating the committee’s hopes of reaching a bipartisan agreement. McHenry, the U.S. Representative for North Carolina, claimed committee members — unlike the White House — understood the urgency and importance of providing clarity for payment stablecoins.</p>
<p>&#8220;A bipartisan deal was within reach—we were closer than we’ve ever been. A few small, but nonetheless important, provisions stood between us and a deal. It was the White House’s unwillingness to compromise that has once again brought negotiations to a halt,&#8221; McHenry <a href="https://financialservices.house.gov/news/documentsingle.aspx?DocumentID=408941">said</a>.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;"></p>
<p>The Republican also commended the New York Department of Financial Services superintendent Adrienne Harris for what he described as &#8220;her invaluable contributions.&#8221;</p>
<p>Following the bill’s passage, Sheila Warren, the CEO of the Crypto Council for Innovation, described this as the &#8220;first steps toward a legislative foundation for stablecoins in the U.S.&#8221; Warren, who acknowledged the &#8220;fireworks&#8221; which preceded the bill’s passage, said the step once again showed that the United States’ process of legislating is still difficult. However, she said the bill’s bipartisan support had proven to the world that &#8220;regulating crypto in the US is not a partisan issue.&#8221;</p>
<p>The CEO, like fellow crypto proponents who have been calling on the U.S. to take the lead in establishing clear rules for the industry, also highlighted how a regulatory regime can foster innovation and as well as &#8220;provide critical protections for consumers.&#8221;</p>
<p><em><strong>What are your thoughts on this story? Let us know what you think in the comments section below. </strong></em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2041962920-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[McHenry also commended the New York Department of Financial Services superintendent Adrienne Harris for what he described as "her invaluable contributions." #stablecoin #legislation]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA[Sheila Warren said the bill’s bipartisan support had proven to the world that "regulating #crypto in the US is not a partisan issue." #consumerprotection #innovation ]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin, Ethereum Technical Analysis: BTC Hangs on to $29,000 Level, Despite Increased Market Volatility </title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-ethereum-technical-analysis-btc-hangs-on-to-29000-level-despite-increased-market-volatility/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Eliman Dambell]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 12:51:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=600047</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1635530845-1-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Bitcoin, Ethereum Technical Analysis: BTC Manages Hangs on to $29,000 Level, Despite Increase Market Volatility " decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1635530845-1-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1635530845-1-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1635530845-1-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1635530845-1-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1635530845-1-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1635530845-1-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1635530845-1.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />Bitcoin remained above a key support point on Friday, despite bears attempting to push the price below $29,000. Today&#x2019;s session saw sentiment once again shift bearish, as U.S. consumer sentiment data looms. Ethereum was mostly unchanged in today&#x2019;s session. Bitcoin Bitcoin (BTC) continued to trade above the $29,000 mark on Friday, despite bearish pressure intensifying [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1635530845-1-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Bitcoin, Ethereum Technical Analysis: BTC Manages Hangs on to $29,000 Level, Despite Increase Market Volatility " decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1635530845-1-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1635530845-1-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1635530845-1-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1635530845-1-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1635530845-1-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1635530845-1-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1635530845-1.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>Bitcoin remained above a key support point on Friday, despite bears attempting to push the price below $29,000. Today&#x2019;s session saw sentiment once again shift bearish, as U.S. consumer sentiment data looms. Ethereum was mostly unchanged in today&#x2019;s session. </strong></p>
<h2>Bitcoin</h2>
<p>Bitcoin (<a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/BTC" 311996  target="_blank">BTC</a>) continued to trade above the $29,000 mark on Friday, despite bearish pressure intensifying in today&#x2019;s session.</p>
<p>After hitting a high of $29,520.71 on Thursday, <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/BTC" 311996  target="_blank">BTC</a>/USD dropped to an intraday low of $29,099.35 earlier in the day.</p>
<p>The move saw bitcoin briefly fall below a support point at $29,200, however prices have since climbed back above this point.</p>
<div class="tradingview-widget-container">
<div class="tradingview-widget-copyright"><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/?exchange=BITSTAMP" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span class="blue-text">Bitcoin chart</span></a> by TradingView</div>
<p><script type="text/javascript" src="https://s3.tradingview.com/tv.js"></script><script type="text/javascript">
  new TradingView.widget(
  {
  "width": "100%",
  "height": "400",
  "symbol": "BITSTAMP:BTCUSD",
  "interval": "D",
  "timezone": "Etc/UTC",
  "theme": "light",
  "style": "1",
  "locale": "en",
  "toolbar_bg": "#F1F3F6",
  "enable_publishing": false,
  "container_id": "tradingview_1247e"
}
  );
  </script></p>
</div>
<p><!-- TradingView Widget END --></p>
<p>This latest slippage comes as the 10-day (red) moving average continued its downward cross versus its 25-day (blue) counterpart.</p>
<p>In addition to this, the relative strength index (RSI) neared a breakout below a floor at 41.00, however it has so far avoided this.</p>
<p>Should this take place, the next possible destination for <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/BTC" 311996  target="_blank">BTC</a> could be $28,000.</p>

<h2>Ethereum</h2>
<p>Ethereum (<a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/ETH" target="_blank">ETH</a>) traded above its own support point at $1,850 on Friday, as the cryptocurrency continued consolidating.</p>
<p><a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/ETH" target="_blank">ETH</a>/USD dropped to a bottom at $1,855.32 earlier in today&#x2019;s session, a day after peaking at $1,878.43.</p>
<p>The price consolidation comes as the RSI failed to move above a current resistance level at 48.00.</p>
<div class="tradingview-widget-container">
<div class="tradingview-widget-copyright"><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ETHUSD/?exchange=BITSTAMP" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span class="blue-text">Ethereum chart</span></a> by TradingView</div>
<p><script type="text/javascript" src="https://s3.tradingview.com/tv.js"></script><script type="text/javascript">
  new TradingView.widget(
  {
  "width": "100%",
  "height": "400",
  "symbol": "BITSTAMP:ETHUSD",
  "interval": "D",
  "timezone": "Etc/UTC",
  "theme": "light",
  "style": "1",
  "locale": "en",
  "toolbar_bg": "#F1F3F6",
  "enable_publishing": false,
  "container_id": "tradingview_1247e"
}
  );
  </script></p>
</div>
<p><!-- TradingView Widget END --></p>
<p>As of writing, the index is on the cusp of crossing this line, however momentum is still relatively weak.</p>
<p>There could likely be a spark later in the day, depending on how traders react to the University of Michigan Consumer Sentiment report.</p>
<p><em>Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:</em></p>
<p><em><strong>Do you expect ethereum to drop below $1,800 this weekend? Leave your thoughts in the comments below.</strong></em></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1635530845-1-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[#BTC stays above $29,000, despite increasing bearish pressure.]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA[Despite pressure from bears, #BTC remains above $29,000 on Friday.]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Withdraws Its Crypto License Application in Germany</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/binance-withdraws-its-crypto-license-application-in-germany/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lubomir Tassev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 11:30:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchanges]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bafin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto custodian]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto license]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[german]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Germany]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[License]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[regulator]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[watchdog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[withdrawal application]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=599924</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="433" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2251111913-768x433.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Binance Withdraws Its Crypto License Application in Germany" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2251111913-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2251111913-1024x578.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2251111913-768x433.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2251111913-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2251111913-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2251111913-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2251111913.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />The world’s largest exchange for digital assets, Binance, has withdrawn its application for a German crypto custody license. The trading platform made it clear it’s not giving up on plans to eventually obtain authorization from the Federal Republic but wants its submission to better reflect the changing market and regulatory conditions. Crypto Exchange Binance to [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="433" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2251111913-768x433.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Binance Withdraws Its Crypto License Application in Germany" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2251111913-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2251111913-1024x578.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2251111913-768x433.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2251111913-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2251111913-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2251111913-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2251111913.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>The world’s largest exchange for digital assets, Binance, has withdrawn its application for a German crypto custody license. The trading platform made it clear it’s not giving up on plans to eventually obtain authorization from the Federal Republic but wants its submission to better reflect the changing market and regulatory conditions.</strong></p>
<h2>Crypto Exchange Binance to Reconsider Attempt at Getting German Regulatory Approval</h2>
<p>Binance, the leading cryptocurrency exchange by daily trading volume, has pulled out its application for a crypto license in Germany, Reuters reported, noting that the exchange is obviously rethinking its expansion plans in the current difficult regulatory environment.</p>
<p>The move comes after about a month ago the German financial news magazine Finance Forward <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/binance-reportedly-denied-crypto-license-in-germany/">revealed</a>, citing sources, that Germany’s Federal Financial Supervisory Authority (<a href="https://www.bafin.de/EN/Homepage/homepage_node.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bafin</a>) had informed Binance it would not be licensed as a crypto custodian in the country.</p>
<p>“Binance confirms it has proactively withdrawn its Bafin application. The situation, both in the global market and regulation, has changed significantly,” a spokesperson for the crypto giant explained on Wednesday. However, the company representative also said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Binance still intends to apply for appropriate licensing in Germany, but it is essential that our submission accurately reflects these changes.</p></blockquote>

<p>In the past months,  has been under increased pressure from regulators around the world. In the U.S., the exchange was <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/binance-cz-to-seek-dismissal-of-cftc-complaint/">sued</a> by both the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) for alleged violations of securities and derivatives laws.</p>
<p>In Europe, the major crypto exchange is facing challenges in several other jurisdictions. Authorities in Belgium <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/binance-ordered-to-cease-all-crypto-services-in-belgium/">ordered</a> the exchange to cease all crypto services while French prosecutors <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/french-investigation-targets-binance-allegations-of-money-laundering-and-regulatory-violations/">launched</a> an investigation based on money laundering allegations.</p>
<p>Besides the Bafin application withdrawal, first reported by Coindesk, Binance <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/binance-pulls-out-of-netherlands-seeks-to-deregister-cyprus-unit/">exited</a> the Dutch market in June after failing to register as a crypto service provider, applied for deregistration in Cyprus, <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/binance-unit-in-britain-cancels-uk-regulatory-authorization/">canceled</a> its U.K. authorization, and also withdrew its license application in Austria.</p>
<p><em><strong>Do you think Binance will resubmit its application for a German crypto license in the near future? Tell us in the comments section below. </strong></em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2251111913-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[#Binance withdraws its application for a #German #crypto #custody #license. ]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA[#Crypto #exchange #Binance to reconsider its attempt at getting regulatory approval in #Germany. ]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Canadian Regulator Proposes Changes to Its &#8216;Capital and Liquidity Approach to Crypto-Assets&#8217;</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/canadian-regulator-proposes-changes-to-its-capital-and-liquidity-approach-to-crypto-assets/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Terence Zimwara]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 10:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Basel Committee on Banking Supervision]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[capital treatment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto assets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto exposures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office of the Superintendent of Financial Institutions (OSFI)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Peter Routledge]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=599746</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1317562316-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Canadian Regulator Proposes Changes to Its &#039;Capital and Liquidity Approach to Crypto-Assets&#039;" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1317562316-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1317562316-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1317562316-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1317562316-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1317562316-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1317562316-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1317562316.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />The regulator of financial institutions in Canada said on July 26 that it had started the process of gathering the public’s view on proposals to change its &#8220;capital and liquidity approach to crypto-assets.&#8221; The draft guidelines are a response to the Basel Committee on Banking Supervision&#8217;s new banking standards for crypto-asset exposures. Staying Abreast With [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1317562316-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Canadian Regulator Proposes Changes to Its &#039;Capital and Liquidity Approach to Crypto-Assets&#039;" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1317562316-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1317562316-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1317562316-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1317562316-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1317562316-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1317562316-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1317562316.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>The regulator of financial institutions in Canada said on July 26 that it had started the process of gathering the public’s view on proposals to change its &#8220;capital and liquidity approach to crypto-assets.&#8221; The draft guidelines are a response to the Basel Committee on Banking Supervision&#8217;s new banking standards for crypto-asset exposures. </strong></p>
<h2>Staying Abreast With International Developments</h2>
<p>The Canadian regulator known as the Office of the Superintendent of Financial Institutions (OSFI) announced on July 26 that it is &#8220;proposing changes to its capital and liquidity approach to crypto-assets.&#8221; According to a statement, OSFI’s proposed new approach is intended &#8220;to reflect an evolving risk environment and international developments.&#8221;</p>
<p>As per the <a href="https://www.osfi-bsif.gc.ca/eng/osfi-bsif/med/Pages/crypto-bnk-ins-nr.aspx">statement</a>, the Canadian regulator kickstarted the process to gather the public’s view by unveiling two draft guidelines. One draft is focused on the regulatory capital treatment of crypto-asset exposures by regulated deposit-taking institutions, while the other draft is targeted at insurers.</p>
<p>The draft guidelines, which are now open for public consultation until September 20, 2023, are in response to new banking standards for crypto-asset exposures which were<a href="https://www.bis.org/bcbs/publ/d545.htm"> unveiled</a> in Dec. 2022 by the Basel Committee on Banking Supervision. OSFI also revealed in the statement that the new guidelines are expected to take effect in early 2025.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;"></p>
<h2>New Guidelines to Bring Clarity</h2>
<p>Meanwhile, in remarks accompanying the statement, Peter Routledge, the Superintendent of Financial Institutions, said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Deposit-taking institutions and insurers need clarity on how to treat crypto-asset exposures when it comes to capital and liquidity. We look forward to giving them this clarity through these new guidelines that reflect industry input and international standards.</p></blockquote>
<p>According to the statement, the new guidelines propose two approaches, a simplified and a more comprehensive one. The use of either approach will depend on the &#8220;extent of an institution’s exposure to crypto-assets.&#8221; The guidelines also detail the four classes of crypto assets and the respective capital treatment for each.</p>
<p>However, according to OSFI, the Aug. 2022 <a href="https://www.osfi-bsif.gc.ca/Eng/osfi-bsif/med/Pages/crypto22-nr.aspx">interim advisory</a> will remain in effect between now and when new guidelines become effective.</p>
<p><em><strong>What are your thoughts on this story? Let us know what you think in the comments section below. </strong></em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1317562316-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[One draft is focused on the regulatory capital treatment of #crypto-asset exposures by regulated #deposit-taking institutions, while the other is targeted at insurers. #regulation]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA[The new guidelines also detail the four classes of crypto assets and the respective capital treatment for each. #insurance #liquidity]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Roger Ver at Webx Asia: Reflections on Payments, Self-Custody, and the Role of Crypto Lawbreakers</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/roger-ver-at-webx-asia-reflections-on-payments-self-custody-and-the-role-of-crypto-lawbreakers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Graham Smith]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 08:00:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Featured]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[anarchy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin cash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blocksize Debate]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cannabis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto anarchy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet marketplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Freedom]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Libertarian]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marijuana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Payments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Roger Ver]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Silk Road]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Voluntaryism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web3]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Webx Asia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Webx Conference]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=599511</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/roger-768x432.png" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Roger Ver at Webx Asia: Reflections on Payments, Self-Custody, and the Role of Crypto Lawbreakers" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/roger-300x169.png 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/roger-1024x576.png 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/roger-768x432.png 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/roger-190x107.png 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/roger-380x214.png 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/roger-760x428.png 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/roger.png 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />When asked whether he&#x2019;d rather be called a &#x201C;bitcoin evangelist,&#x201D; or &#x201C;Bitcoin Jesus&#x201D; at the recent Webx seminar in Tokyo, Roger Ver responds: &#x201C;I prefer to be called Roger.&#x201D; The enthusiastic and outspoken figure in crypto, scattering sats around the world with unapologetic frankness about government, the bitcoin block size wars, and conflations of legality [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/roger-768x432.png" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Roger Ver at Webx Asia: Reflections on Payments, Self-Custody, and the Role of Crypto Lawbreakers" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/roger-300x169.png 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/roger-1024x576.png 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/roger-768x432.png 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/roger-190x107.png 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/roger-380x214.png 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/roger-760x428.png 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/roger.png 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>When asked whether he&#x2019;d rather be called a &#x201C;bitcoin evangelist,&#x201D; or &#x201C;Bitcoin Jesus&#x201D; at the recent Webx seminar in Tokyo, Roger Ver responds: &#x201C;I prefer to be called Roger.&#x201D; The enthusiastic and outspoken figure in crypto, scattering sats around the world with unapologetic frankness about government, the bitcoin block size wars, and conflations of legality with morality, Roger Ver has been somewhat quiet in recent months. That notwithstanding, the early bitcoin investor had much to say about the state of crypto in Tokyo this week, talking payments, altcoins, FTX, and the role of literal outlaws in changing the world for the better.</strong></p>
<h2>&#x2018;I Am Not Satoshi Nakamoto&#x2019;</h2>
<p>Taking the stage at the Tokyo International Forum on Tuesday, pioneering Bitcoin investor Roger Ver reassured journalist<a href="https://webx-asia.com/speaker/kazumoto-ohno/?"> Kazumoto Ohno</a> that he is indeed, not Bitcoin creator Satoshi Nakamoto. However, according to Ver, the Bank of Japan did contact him early on, around 2012 &#x2014; having heard he was promoting bitcoin in Japan &#x2014; asking to meet with the enigmatic bitcoin mastermind. &#x201C;I realized that they hadn&#x2019;t even done much research at all, at that point,&#x201D; Ver remarked.</p>
<p>When Ohno inquired whether crypto had evolved over the past 10 to 12 years as Ver expected it to, the Bitcoin.com founder noted that &#x201C;we&#x2019;ve made a huge amount of progress, but it didn&#x2019;t happen quite as quickly as I thought it was going to in the early days,&#x201D; further reflecting that &#x201C;the world changes very, very quickly, so make sure you enjoy the journey.&#x201D;</p>
<p>To Ver&#x2019;s thinking, which idea he credits to American computer scientist Ray Kurzweil: &#x201C;we always overestimate the amount of progress we&#x2019;re going to make in the short-term, but we underestimate the amount of progress we&#x2019;ll make in the long term &#x2014; and I think that&#x2019;s been true of my experience in crypto.&#x201D;</p>
<div>
<dl id="attachment_599798">
<dt>
<p></p></dt>
</dl>
</div>
<h2><a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/BTC" 311996  target="_blank">BTC</a>&#x2019;s Loss of Utility and the Critical Importance of Censorship Resistance</h2>
<p>Ver also weighed in on why he thinks what is now known as &#x201C;Bitcoin&#x201D; (<a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/BTC" 311996  target="_blank">BTC</a>) is heading in the wrong direction, and why &#x201C;Bitcoin Cash is the original Bitcoin,&#x201D; citing the unwieldy fees attendant to <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/BTC" 311996  target="_blank">BTC</a> transactions, and the <a href="https://www.bitcoin.com/bitcoin.pdf">Bitcoin white paper</a>. He emphasized:</p>
<blockquote><p>It&#x2019;s become a speculative asset &#x2026; whereas [as] we heard from other people on the previous panel: payments, payments, payments is the underlying utility that makes these cryptocurrencies so useful.</p></blockquote>
<p>Ver pointed to the asset&#x2019;s loss of market dominance and nodded to the fall of defunct social media platform Myspace when the user experience suffered, and consumers left for greener pastures. <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/BTC" 311996  target="_blank">BTC</a>, in other words, is still cruising largely on its &#x201C;brand recognition,&#x201D; as Ver puts it, and maximalist cliques even go so far as to mock people for wanting to make peer-to-peer payments with Satoshi&#x2019;s permissionless <a href="https://www.bitcoin.com/bitcoin.pdf">peer-to-peer payments protocol</a>.</p>
<div>
<dl id="attachment_599803">
<dt>
<p></p></dt>
</dl>
</div>
<p>Meanwhile, as Chainalysis Japan&#x2019;s<a href="https://webx-asia.com/speaker/hayato-shigekawa/?"> Hayato Shigekawa</a> warned of the dangers of darknet marketplaces (DNMs) and other &#x201C;illicit&#x201D; uses of crypto at the same <a href="https://webx-asia.com/webx/?">massive 2-day conference</a>, Ver credited <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/silk-road-advisor-sentenced-to-20-years-in-prison-while-a-rogue-double-agent-eludes-capture/">DNMs</a> with bringing the utility of bitcoin payments to the masses in the beginning, noting that &#x201C;If you look at what brought bitcoin to the world in the first place, it was these darknet markets that were using it for illegal commerce &#x2026; today almost none of them use bitcoin, they&#x2019;re using things like monero or other coins, and that&#x2019;s a sign that bitcoin isn&#x2019;t as useful for payments as it used to be.&#x201D; Ver emphasized:</p>
<blockquote><p>Whether it&#x2019;s monero, or bitcoin cash, or ethereum or whatever else, there&#x2019;s a huge, giant wide world out there and people having more choices is a good thing &#x2026; and if people want to speculate on <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/BTC" 311996  target="_blank">BTC</a>, have at it. If you want to speculate on something else, more power to you &#x2026; We have a decentralized set of currencies, and you can choose which one of those cryptocurrencies or protocols you want to use, and that&#x2019;s a good thing.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Thoughts on FTX and the Importance of Rule-Breakers for Human Progress</h2>
<p>Ohno broached the topic of FTX toward the end of the fireside chat, asking Ver: &#x201C;How would you see the impact of the FTX debacle on those who were about to invest in cryptocurrency? Did it scare them away?&#x201D; Ver replied that it did scare some away, but pointed out that the<a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/ftx-sues-sbf-former-execs-to-recover-over-1-billion/"> collapse of FTX</a> is really nothing new, citing Mt Gox, Celsius, and other previous collapses, and pointing out that the same thing happens in traditional finance.</p>
<p>&#x201C;It happens in traditional finance, it happened to crypto finance, but that&#x2019;s why self-custody, or at least having the ability to hold the cryptocurrency yourself is so incredibly important,&#x201D; Ver said, elaborating: &#x201C;and that&#x2019;s one more example why chains that are very scalable with low fees make it easier for people to hold the crypto themselves.&#x201D;</p>

<p>Bitcoin.com CEO Dennis Jarvis would echo this sentiment the next day on another stage at the Tokyo International Forum, declaring that &#x201C;Really the ethos of bitcoin and crypto is self-custody of funds,&#x201D; and stating that while centralized exchanges can fulfill a role, the goal is to make it so that crypto holders &#x201C;are not stuck in Web2.0 crypto&#x201D; with their funds constantly at risk due to lack of custody.</p>
<p>Emphasizing that a real-life physical wallet allows one to control their own paper money directly, Roger Ver cautioned against confusing true crypto wallets with mere &#x201C;accounts&#x201D; such as those on centralized exchanges and at traditional banks. &#x201C;The moment I take the money out of this wallet, and I give it to UFJ Mitsubishi [bank], now they have my money and I am at their mercy &#x2026; You&#x2019;re completely out of control as soon as you turn over your money to somebody else.&#x201D;</p>
<p>Ver ended the fireside echoing a point he had made earlier on in the interview, when he noted:</p>
<blockquote><p>So, the world we live in you have to play by all the regulations, because if you don&#x2019;t men with guns will send you to jail &#x2026; but that doesn&#x2019;t mean that you have a moral obligation to obey those rules and regulations.</p></blockquote>
<p>Explaining that when bitcoin came along &#x201C;it was too exciting to stay quiet politically any longer,&#x201D; Ver called on the audience &#x2014; peopled with those present to hear talks from politicians and startups on government regulation of crypto &#x2014; to stand up for what they believe in:</p>
<blockquote><p>I want to point out to everybody, that just because politicians get together and they write down words on a piece of paper and call it a law, it doesn&#x2019;t change morality. Right is right and wrong is wrong regardless of what the politicians say. And if you see something that&#x2019;s wrong, stand up there and say &#x2018;no, this is wrong, this is not okay, we should not do that.&#x2019;</p></blockquote>
<p>In doing this, Ver said that maybe others who felt the same but were too afraid to speak out would be encouraged to do so. Connecting regulations on economic freedom to other laws viewed as unjust, Roger Ver reflected on his time in federal prison in the United States, when he was incarcerated with several other <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/a-brief-introduction-to-voluntaryism-for-crypto-neophytes/">non-violent human beings</a>, some of whom were placed behind bars for cannabis, a simple plant.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/img_20230725_133736_932-1024x768.jpg?X-Amz-Content-Sha256=UNSIGNED-PAYLOAD&X-Amz-Algorithm=AWS4-HMAC-SHA256&X-Amz-Credential=AKIAYIWLWC3GPQWL5SMB%2F20230727%2Fus-east-1%2Fs3%2Faws4_request&X-Amz-Date=20230727T135629Z&X-Amz-SignedHeaders=host&X-Amz-Expires=600&X-Amz-Signature=bfb246c3e1a932f630a05aca10b21e4742e582d948d4782b3b90fac1e2636fbc" alt="" width="1024" height="768"></p>
<p>&#x201C;Thats how all human society moves forward &#x2014; it&#x2019;s by the lawbreakers and the people who are willing to disobey bad laws, that the laws get changed,&#x201D; he noted. Ver interrupted the event&#x2019;s emcee after the official finish of the talk to add one more point:</p>
<blockquote><p>It&#x2019;s still early days in the worldwide adoption of cryptocurrency &#x2026; tell your friends, tell your family, show them how cryptocurrencies work &#x2026; explain to them why cryptocurrencies are better than government-issued currencies and why competition leads to better quality products that more people around the world get to use. So it&#x2019;s up to all of us, to go out there and continue to push this forward to the world, so that the world becomes a better place, sooner rather than later.</p></blockquote>
<p><em><strong>What are your thoughts on Roger Ver&#x2019;s talk at Webx Asia? Be sure to let us know in the comments section below.</strong></em></p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/roger-760x428.png</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[Taking the stage at the #Tokyo International Forum on Tuesday, pioneering #Bitcoin investor #RogerVer assured journalist Kazumoto Ohno that he is not Bitcoin creator Satoshi #Nakamoto.]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA["Thats how all human #society moves forward — it's by the lawbreakers and the people who are willing to disobey bad #laws, that the laws get changed," Ver emphasized. #cryptocurrency #regulations]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bolivian Central Bank Using Chinese Yuan for International Settlements</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/bolivian-central-bank-using-chinese-yuan-for-international-settlements/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sergio Goschenko]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 06:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bolivia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chinese Yuan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dedollarization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Luis Arce]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marcelo montenegro]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=599751</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1294420726-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Bolivian Central Bank Using Chinese Yuan for International Settlements" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1294420726-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1294420726-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1294420726-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1294420726-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1294420726-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1294420726-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1294420726.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />Economy Minister Marcelo Montenegro acknowledged that the Bolivian Central Bank is harnessing the Chinese yuan in its commercial settlements. The switch to using the Chinese currency has to do with the dollar scarcity that the country is facing, having to approve a law to sell part of its gold reserves for U.S. dollars. Bolivian Central [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1294420726-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Bolivian Central Bank Using Chinese Yuan for International Settlements" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1294420726-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1294420726-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1294420726-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1294420726-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1294420726-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1294420726-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1294420726.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>Economy Minister Marcelo Montenegro acknowledged that the Bolivian Central Bank is harnessing the Chinese yuan in its commercial settlements. The switch to using the Chinese currency has to do with the dollar scarcity that the country is facing, having to approve a law to sell part of its gold reserves for U.S. dollars.</strong></p>
<h2>Bolivian Central Bank Settling International Transactions Using the Chinese Yuan</h2>
<p>The Bolivian Central Bank is carrying out settlements using the Chinese yuan in some of its international transactions. In a recent press conference, Economy Minister Marcelo Montenegro stated that the bank was already transacting using yuan, even without having Chinese banks in Bolivia.</p>
<p>However, Montenegro also explained that having a branch of a Chinese bank in the country would accelerate the adoption process of the currency in such transactions. He <a href="https://unitel.bo/portada/noticias/el-banco-estatal-ya-realiza-operaciones-con-yuanes-confirma-el-ministro-montenegro-AC8664534" target="_blank" rel="noopener">stated</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>It is clear that sometimes it is not necessary to have a bank to carry out operations, but obviously having a Chinese bank or one close to the region can also facilitate operations much more smoothly.</p></blockquote>
<p>The two governments of China and Bolivia are working to bring Chinese banks to Bolivia to act as intermediaries to ease the completion of transactions, according to statements from China&#8217;s Ambassador to Bolivia, Huang Yazhong.</p>

<h2>Bolivia&#8217;s De-Dollarization Process</h2>
<p>The president of Bolivia, Luis Alberto Arce, has called openly to de-dollarize Latam and support the introduction of new partners in the region, including BRICS countries like China. After assisting at the Common South Market Summit, he <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bolivias-president-calls-on-south-american-countries-to-ditch-us-dollar-bolster-alliances-with-china-and-brics/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">declared</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>Our region is seriously affected by the restrictions imposed by the northern financial system, which limits financing options, making it necessary to reduce dependence on the U.S. dollar and diversify our economic relations.</p></blockquote>
<p>Bolivia is facing a dollar crunch that affected the exchange rate of the U.S. dollar. In May, the government <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/latam-insights-bolivia-sells-gold-for-dollars-argentina-bans-fintech-crypto-fitch-upgrades-el-salvadors-credit-rating/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">approved</a> a law that allows it to sell up to half of its gold reserves for dollars on international markets to avoid a similar liquidity crunch.</p>
<p>The country is following in the footsteps of Argentina and Brazil, which have also shown signs of adopting the Chinese yuan in their financial systems. In March, Brazil <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/china-makes-advances-in-ditching-the-us-dollar-for-settlements-inks-deal-with-brazil-and-completes-first-yuan-lng-purchase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">inked</a> a deal with China to conduct bilateral trade transactions using national currencies. Argentina also <a href="https://www.argentina.gob.ar/noticias/argentina-deja-de-pagar-importaciones-en-dolares-y-pasa-yuanes" target="_blank" rel="noopener">integrated</a> the Chinese yuan into its system, allowing importers to settle transactions with China with the fiat currency.</p>
<p><em><strong>What do you think about Bolivia&#8217;s advancement in using the Chinese yuan for commercial settlements? Tell us in the comments section below.</strong></em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1294420726-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[Economy Minister Marcelo Montenegro stated that the #Bolivian Central Bank was already transacting using yuan, even without having #Chinese banks in #Bolivia.]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA[#Bolivian Economy Minister Marcelo Montenegro stated that "having a #Chinese bank or one close to the region can also facilitate operations much more smoothly."]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple and Palau Announce CBDC Stablecoin Pilot Program</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/ripple-and-palau-announce-cbdc-stablecoin-pilot-program/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sergio Goschenko]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 04:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jay Hunter Anson]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[palau]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[palau stablecoin (PSC)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Surangel S. Whipps]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=599418</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2283620141-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Ripple and Palau Announce CBDC Stablecoin Pilot Program" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2283620141-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2283620141-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2283620141-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2283620141-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2283620141-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2283620141-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2283620141.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />Palau, an insular nation in the Philippines Sea, has partnered with Ripple, announcing a limited pilot for its own U.S. dollar-pegged stablecoin issued using XRP technology. According to Jay Hunter Anson, a member of the board of directors of Palau&#x2019;s Ministry of Finance, the test started about three weeks ago to validate the design of [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2283620141-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Ripple and Palau Announce CBDC Stablecoin Pilot Program" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2283620141-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2283620141-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2283620141-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2283620141-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2283620141-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2283620141-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2283620141.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>Palau, an insular nation in the Philippines Sea, has partnered with Ripple, announcing a limited pilot for its own U.S. dollar-pegged stablecoin issued using <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/XRP" 311999  target="_blank">XRP</a> technology. According to Jay Hunter Anson, a member of the board of directors of Palau&#x2019;s Ministry of Finance, the test started about three weeks ago to validate the design of the stablecoin system.</strong></p>&#13;
<h2>Palau and Ripple Announce Test Pilot of U.S. Dollar-Pegged Stablecoin</h2>&#13;
<p>Palau, a country comprising more than 300 individual islands, is testing a U.S. dollar-pegged stablecoin on top of the Ripple network. Jay Hunter Anson, a member of the board of directors of Palau&#x2019;s Ministry of Finance, <a href="https://twitter.com/JHX_1138/status/1684165312348844032?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener">stated</a> that the pilot started in March and that the project has been distributing Palau&#x2019;s Stablecoin (PSC) for three weeks.</p>&#13;
<p>Hunter Anson was the first to make a <a href="https://twitter.com/JHX_1138/status/1681337599590383621?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener">purchase</a> using PSC, dubbed the &#x201C;kluk,&#x201D; purchasing a Micronesian breakfast at a collaborating vendor on July 13. He <a href="https://twitter.com/JHX_1138/status/1681135189236301824?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener">explained</a> that PSC was &#x201C;a prototype digitization of the U.S. dollar under development in partnership with Ripple using the <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/developers-propose-cross-chain-bridge-for-xrpl-network-to-enhance-blockchain-interoperability/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">XRPL</a> blockchain.&#x201D; If successful, this pilot could ostensibly revolutionize how inhabitants of Palau pay for goods and services.</p>&#13;
<p>The pilot has since expanded, adding more pilot volunteers to test the digital currency in the three enrolled vendors. On July 23, Hunter Anson <a href="https://twitter.com/JHX_1138/status/1683206451706068994?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener">announced</a> that the second batch of PSC was distributed to 35 more volunteer users.</p>&#13;
&#13;
<h2>Pilot Definitions</h2>&#13;
<p>In a <a href="https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20230726969255/en/Republic-of-Palau-Launches-US-Dollar-backed-Palau-Stablecoin-in-the-Next-Phase-of-Collaboration-with-Ripple-on-the-XRP-Ledger" target="_blank" rel="noopener">press release</a> on Wednesday, Ripple gave more details about this pilot program, stating that it would only allow 200 of Palau&#x2019;s government employees to use PSC with the enrolled local vendors in its first phase. Also, PSC will be issued using the Ripple central bank digital currency (CBDC) platform, allowing Palau&#x2019;s Ministry of Finance to mint, distribute, redeem, and destroy the digital token.</p>&#13;
<p>Furthermore, Palau&#x2019;s Finance Ministry will guarantee the reserve to redeem PSC for U.S. dollars at a 1:1 ratio. The <a href="https://twitter.com/JHX_1138/status/1684237779289485321?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener">objective</a> that Palau&#x2019;s government seeks to reach with this pilot is to &#x201C;reduce service charges for transaction costs like cash transfer, credit card payment fees&#x201D; and include more of its citizens in its financial services programs through digital means.</p>&#13;
<p>On this, the President of the Republic of Palau, Surangel S. Whipps, Jr., stated:</p>&#13;
<blockquote>&#13;
<p>By digitizing our currency, we hope to mobilize our economy and government processes to improve financial transactions and empower our citizens. As a smaller country, Palau has the advantage to be innovative and nimble in releasing our stablecoin.</p>&#13;
</blockquote>&#13;
<p><em><strong>What do you think about Palau&#x2019;s U.S. dollar-pegged stablecoin pilot test? Tell us in the comments section below.</strong></em></p>&#13;

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2283620141-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[#Palau stablecoin #PSC is "a prototype digitization of the #US dollar under development in partnership with #Ripple using the #XRPL blockchain."]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA[President of the Republic of #Palau, Surangel S. Whipps, Jr., stated: "By digitizing our currency, we hope to mobilize our economy and government processes to improve financial transactions." #Ripple]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
