<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:bnmedia="https://news.bitcoin.com/">

<channel>
	<title>Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/</link>
	<description>Daily Bitcoin News</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 02:20:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Web3 Revolution: &#8216;Low Latency Is King&#8217; Says Fleek Network Lead Researcher</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/web3-revolution-low-latency-is-king-says-fleek-network-lead-researcher/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Terence Zimwara]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 09:30:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Interview]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Decentralization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fleek network]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[low latency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web3]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=598175</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2176491409-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Web3 Revolution: &#039;Low Latency Is King&#039; Says Fleek Network Lead Researcher" decoding="async" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2176491409-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2176491409-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2176491409-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2176491409-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2176491409-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2176491409-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2176491409.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />According to Parsa Ghadimi, the lead researcher at the Web3 infrastructure platform Fleek Network, many developers of decentralized apps (dapps) continue to shun Web3 infrastructure because it has low latency. Ghadimi asserts that developers and users are more concerned with performance than the novelty of Web3 applications. Web3 Regulation a &#8216;Certainty&#8217; While this may explain [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2176491409-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Web3 Revolution: &#039;Low Latency Is King&#039; Says Fleek Network Lead Researcher" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2176491409-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2176491409-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2176491409-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2176491409-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2176491409-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2176491409-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2176491409.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>According to Parsa Ghadimi, the lead researcher at the Web3 infrastructure platform Fleek Network, many developers of decentralized apps (dapps) continue to shun Web3 infrastructure because it has low latency. Ghadimi asserts that developers and users are more concerned with performance than the novelty of Web3 applications.</strong></p>
<h2>Web3 Regulation a &#8216;Certainty&#8217;</h2>
<p>While this may explain developers&#8217; use of or preference for Web2 infrastructure, according to Ghadimi, participants in the Web3 ecosystem can reverse this trend by &#8220;matching the performance and latency of Web2.&#8221;</p>
<p>Meanwhile, when asked about reports of the United States&#8217; attempt to regulate the decentralized finance (defi) ecosystem, Ghadimi told Bitcoin.com News that he remains optimistic regulators will not go after projects which adhere to rules. Although the eventual regulation of Web3 is now widely seen as a &#8220;certainty,&#8221; the researcher nevertheless said he is &#8220;increasingly optimistic&#8221; that this will be done in a &#8220;sensible&#8221; way.</p>
<p>In his written answers sent to Bitcoin.com News via Telegram, Ghadimi also shared his thoughts on why the web infrastructure needs Web3. He also offered his thoughts about the future of centralized entities in Web3.</p>
<p>Below are all of Ghadimi&#8217;s responses to the questions sent.</p>
<p><strong>Bitcoin.com News (BCN): What does the decentralization of the Web3 infrastructure mean and what’s the need for moving infrastructure to a decentralized layer?</strong></p>
<p><strong>Parsa Ghadimi (PG):</strong> Decentralizing web infrastructure is the shift from using corporate-controlled web infrastructure and cloud platforms to permissionless, uncensorable, decentralized platforms. You are only as strong as your weakest link, and so if even one part of your stack is centralized, you are vulnerable to censorship, de-platforming, hacks, service failures, etc. That’s the main reason for needing to move internet infrastructure and software off corporate-controlled cloud platforms and onto decentralized networks. Web3 only becomes a reality if the entire stack is decentralized.</p>
<p><strong>BCN: Many developers building decentralized applications are aware of the critical principles of Web3 yet they still go on to build dapps on Web2 infrastructure. Why do you think they still do this and what needs to happen to encourage them to switch to a decentralized base layer?</strong></p>
<p><strong>PG:</strong> Performance/low latency is king. No one will care if your product is decentralized if it loads slowly. And so most developers are currently forced to use Web2 infra to get Web3 performance to meet developer/user demands. What needs to happen to encourage them to switch to decentralized infra is that there needs to be decentralized infra that can match the performance and latency of Web2. And that’s exactly what we are aiming to do with Fleek Network and building a decentralized edge network.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"></p>
<p><strong>BCN: Can you tell us about your platform — Fleek Network — and its approach to bringing developers a decentralized edge layer?</strong></p>
<p><strong>PG:</strong> Fleek Network is a decentralized edge network. It’s optimized to facilitate the deployment and running of performant web and edge services (CDN, serverless functions, etc.). It brings centralized web-like performance to Web3 without sacrificing Web3 values. It will lower the barrier of entry and speed up time to market for developers building Web3 infra/middleware by allowing them to offload a portion of their stack to a decentralized edge, similar to how the modern web works today. And it can replace a lot of the current parts of their stack that they still need Web2 infra for (ex. Cloudflare).</p>
<p><strong>BCN: Over the past few months, we have seen regulators (particularly in the U.S.) become increasingly aggressive in their actions against crypto giants like Coinbase, Binance, and the crypto ecosystem in general. Do you foresee this happening to decentralized entities and do you believe that regulators have a role in an ecosystem that’s designed to be self-regulated?</strong></p>
<p><strong>PG:</strong> It seems like the U.S. is attempting to establish a framework for what ‘sufficient decentralization’ means. So I hope they won’t go after the projects that adhere to that criteria. Regulation seems like a certainty at this point whether we like it or not, I just hope it’s sensible. But I’m becoming increasingly optimistic that it will be.</p>
<p><strong>BCN: Do you foresee more centralized entities in the Web3 space in the coming years?</strong></p>
<p><strong>PG:</strong> In absolute terms yes, just given the growth of Web3 that we will experience this decade. But I would expect to see the growth of decentralized entities match or exceed that over the same time period.</p>
<p><em><strong>What are your thoughts about this interview? Let us know what you think in the comments section below. </strong></em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2176491409-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[According to Parsa Ghadimi, developers can only move on to Web3 if it matches the performance and latency of Web2. #web3 #defi ]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA["#Regulation seems like a certainty at this point whether we like it or not, I just hope it’s sensible. But I’m becoming increasingly optimistic that it will be," said Parsa Ghadimi. #decentralized]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Latam Insights — Argentina&#8217;s Reserves Bleed, Central Bank of Brazil Would Be Able to Manipulate Digital Real in CBDC Pilot</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/latam-insights-argentinas-reserves-bleed-central-bank-of-brazil-would-be-able-to-manipulate-digital-real-in-cbdc-pilot/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sergio Goschenko]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 07:30:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Argentina]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brazil]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[central bank digital currency (CBDC)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chinese swap]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chinese Yuan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital real]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Futures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[latam insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[reserves]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=598144</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="696" height="392" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1827932012-1-1.webp" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Latam Insights — Argentina&#039;s Reserves Bleed, Central Bank of Brazil Would Be Able to Manipulate Digital Real In CBDC Pilot" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" />Welcome to Latam Insights, a compendium of Latin America&#8217;s most relevant crypto and economic news during the last week. In this issue, the Argentine central bank sheds yuan for dollars as its reserves bleed, the Central Bank of Brazil would be able to manipulate balances and block digital real accounts, and the first bitcoin futures [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="696" height="392" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1827932012-1-1.webp" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Latam Insights — Argentina&#039;s Reserves Bleed, Central Bank of Brazil Would Be Able to Manipulate Digital Real In CBDC Pilot" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" /><p><strong>Welcome to Latam Insights, a compendium of Latin America&#8217;s most relevant crypto and economic news during the last week. In this issue, the Argentine central bank sheds yuan for dollars as its reserves bleed, the Central Bank of Brazil would be able to manipulate balances and block digital real accounts, and the first bitcoin futures contract goes live in Argentina.</strong></p>
<h2>Argentine Central Bank Sheds Chinese Yuan as Its Reserves Bleed</h2>
<p>The Central Bank of Argentina is <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/central-bank-of-argentina-accelerates-yuan-sales-and-dollar-purchases-as-reserves-dwindle/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">leveraging</a> its Chinese yuan stash to purchase dollars and manage its internal operations as its reserve level dwindles. The bank is making payments to importers using part of the Chinese swap line that government officials <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/argentina-to-expand-de-dollarization-efforts-seeks-extension-of-yuan-based-swap-line-with-china/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">extended</a> to $10 billion in June.</p>
<p>Local newspaper La Nacion reported that the bank lost $170 million on July 10 and July 11 due to the payments the republic had to disburse to importers and the purchase of dollars. The gross reserves of the central bank bled out $580 million last week, reaching $26 billion. Aurum Valores, a financial group, estimated that the central bank lost $100 million per day.</p>
<p>On this, analysts from the local group Portfolio Personal Inversiones stated:</p>
<blockquote>
<p>A level of reserves is being tested that has never been observed since at least the late 1980s.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Half the available amount of the Chinese swap line ($5 billion) is said to have been used already, leaving the country trying to organize a new deal to accelerate disbursements from the International Monetary Fund (IMF).</p>
<h2>Central Bank of Brazil Would Be Able to Manipulate and Freeze Digital Real Accounts in CBDC Pilot</h2>
<p>The Central Bank of Brazil will reportedly be able to manipulate the numbers of specific accounts during the upcoming pilot test of the digital real, the Brazilian central bank digital currency (CBDC).</p>
<p><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/posts/pemagalhaes_github-ioralabsrealdigitalsmartcontracts-activity-7082009809549484032-Beqi?utm_source=share&amp;utm_medium=member_desktop" target="_blank" rel="noopener">According</a> to Pedro Magalhaes, a developer that claims to have discovered the solidity code of the digital real pilot using reverse engineering, the functions associated with the Brazilian CBDC smart contract let its issuer freeze the funds in a wallet, block the functionality of transferring tokens for a specific account, and issue tokens directly to a digital wallet.</p>

<h2>First Bitcoin Futures Contract Goes Live in Argentina</h2>
<p>The first bitcoin futures product in Argentina went live on Thursday, issued by <a href="https://www.matbarofex.com.ar/documentos/investigacion/guia-de-futuros-de-bitcoin" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Matba Rofex</a>, a regulated domestic stock exchange. The futures contract uses the Matba Rofex <a href="https://www.matbarofex.com.ar/Indice-btc-mtr/metodologia" target="_blank" rel="noopener">index</a>, allowing qualified investors to put their funds behind bitcoin in local currency without worrying about the custody of the underlying asset.</p>
<p>The issuance of this contract was <a href="https://www.argentina.gob.ar/noticias/la-cnv-aprobo-futuros-basados-en-indice-bitcoin" target="_blank" rel="noopener">approved</a> in April by the Argentine securities regulator. At that time, it stated this approval intended &#8220;to adapt to the regulatory challenges imposed by new technologies for the provision of financial products&#8221; and &#8220;promote the development of new and innovative products.&#8221;</p>
<p><em>To follow all the latest developments in crypto and the economy in Latin America, sign up for our Latam newsletter below.</em></p>

<p><em><strong>What do you think about this week&#8217;s Latam Insights report? Tell us in the comment section below.</strong></em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1827932012-1-1.webp</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[In this issue: #Argentine central bank sheds #yuan for dollars as its reserves bleed, Central Bank of #Brazil would be able to manipulate balances and block digital real accounts.]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA[In this issue: #Argentine central bank sheds #yuan for dollars as its reserves bleed, Central Bank of #Brazil would be able to manipulate balances and block digital real accounts.]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Venezuelan Crypto Ecosystem Still in Shambles 4 Months After Sunacrip Intervention</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/venezuelan-crypto-ecosystem-still-in-shambles-4-months-after-sunacrip-intervention/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sergio Goschenko]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 05:30:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corpoelec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Joselit Ramirez]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nicolas Maduro]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PDVSA Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Petro]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[restructuring]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sunacrip]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Venezuela]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=598047</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1778799026-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Venezuelan Crypto Ecosystem Situation Still Uncertain After 4 Months After Crypto Watchdog Sunacrip Intervention" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1778799026-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1778799026-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1778799026-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1778799026-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1778799026-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1778799026-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1778799026.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />The Venezuelan cryptocurrency ecosystem remains on shaky ground four months after the intervention of national crypto watchdog Sunacrip, and the arrest of its head, Joselit Ramirez, due to alleged participation in a $20 billion corruption scandal involving the undeclared sale of crude oil for crypto. There have been no official updates from Sunacrip&#8217;s restructuring board, [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1778799026-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Venezuelan Crypto Ecosystem Situation Still Uncertain After 4 Months After Crypto Watchdog Sunacrip Intervention" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1778799026-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1778799026-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1778799026-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1778799026-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1778799026-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1778799026-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1778799026.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>The Venezuelan cryptocurrency ecosystem remains on shaky ground four months after the intervention of national crypto watchdog Sunacrip, and the arrest of its head, Joselit Ramirez, due to alleged participation in a $20 billion corruption scandal involving the undeclared sale of crude oil for crypto. There have been no official updates from Sunacrip&#8217;s restructuring board, but Bitcoin mining activities are still halted per local sources&#8217; reports.</strong></p>
<h2>Venezuelan Crypto Ecosystem Still Affected After Sunacrip Intervention</h2>
<p>The situation of the Venezuelan cryptocurrency ecosystem and the current status of its official cryptocurrency asset, the petro, are yet uncertain after four months of the intervention of Sunacrip, the Venezuelan cryptocurrency watchdog. The restructuring board has made no official statements on the processes it is developing, and it is currently not known if the regulatory institution will even survive.</p>
<p>The government of Nicolas Maduro issued an executive order to intervene in the superintendence on March 17 after the <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/head-of-venezuelan-crypto-watchdog-sunacrip-arrested-on-alleged-corruption-charges-institution-to-face-restructuring/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">arrest</a> of its head Joselit Ramirez, who was accused of intermediating payments for $3 billion in undeclared crude sales to third parties. The financial hole in the case, which is commonly known as the PDVSA-Crypto scheme, was later expanded to represent a potential <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/how-crypto-ended-up-at-the-center-of-a-potential-20-billion-internal-corruption-scandal-in-venezuela-bitcoin-mining-shutdown-results/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">$20 billion loss</a> for the nation after more undeclared and unpaid sales linked to cryptocurrency payments were uncovered by Reuters.</p>
<p>The intervention of Sunacrip was followed by other measures that were not officially corroborated but were reported by local Bitcoin miners and media sources, like the operation&#8217;s <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/national-exchanges-reportedly-pause-operations-in-venezuela-as-attorney-general-confirms-crypto-watchdog-sunacrip-involvement-in-oil-sale-schemes/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">pause</a> in local exchanges. Also, miners from the registered cryptocurrency farms in the country were disconnected from the power grid by the state power company Corpoelec in mid-March.</p>
<p>This brought heavy losses for Bitcoin miners based in the country, with some <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/latam-insights-volcano-energy-bitcoin-mining-project-rises-in-el-salvador-venezuelan-miners-leaving-amidst-crypto-corruption-probe/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">mulling</a> moving to more crypto-friendly nations, such as Paraguay or El Salvador.</p>

<h2>Mass Layoffs and Petro Debacle</h2>
<p>Subsequently, there were <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/latam-insights-inflation-skyrockets-in-argentina-el-salvador-processes-digital-assets-licenses-venezuelan-crypto-corruption-probe-continues/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reports</a> of mass layoffs within Sunacrip, which had a payroll of approximately 600 employees, 400 being fired by April 26. But still, there were no official statements on the issue. Even after the Petro blockchain stopped its block production twice in May, with users <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/venezuelan-petro-blockchain-faces-operational-difficulties-hundreds-of-wallets-allegedly-blocked/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reporting</a> the blockage of hundreds of wallets, the institution has been radio silent.</p>
<p>Then, last month, sources linked to Sunacrip <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/reports-indicate-venezuela-is-preparing-to-liquidate-the-petro/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a> that the decision to end the petro and its operations was already taken, and it would be made effective after liquidating big holders of the currency at a still unknown market price.</p>
<p>On the possible effects of this situation, Juan Blanco Bracamonte, a Venezuelan Bitcoin miner, <a href="https://twitter.com/JblancoB/status/1680585147874246657?t=GkVV7Q-lZULd5nDsNlFSzQ&amp;s=19" target="_blank" rel="noopener">stated</a>:</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Starting from scratch will cost a lot of money and some investors are not willing to invest in the midst of the legal uncertainty that has been unleashed since March 2023.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The Sunacrip intervention measure will be effective until September 17 but can possibly be extended by six months more.</p>
<p><em><strong>What do you think about the situation of the cryptocurrency ecosystem in Venezuela? Tell us in the comments section below.</strong></em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1778799026-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[The situation of the #Venezuelan #cryptocurrency ecosystem and the current status of its official cryptocurrency asset, the #petro, are uncertain after four months of Sunacrip intervention.]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA[Last month, sources linked to #Sunacrip reported that the decision to end the #petro and its operations was already taken, and it would be made effective after liquidating holders of the currency.]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nobel Laureate Paul Krugman Says US Dollar Dominance Won&#8217;t Last Forever but Doubts Chinese Yuan Can Replace USD</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/nobel-laureate-paul-krugman-says-us-dollar-dominance-wont-last-forever-but-doubts-chinese-yuan-can-replace-usd/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Kevin Helms]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 03:30:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nobel Laureate]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nobel prize winner]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Paul Krugman BRICS]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Paul Krugman BRICS currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Paul Krugman China]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Paul Krugman Chinese yuan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Paul Krugman dollar reserve currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Paul Krugman US dollar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Paul Krugman US dollar dominance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US dollar dominance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=598291&#038;preview=true&#038;preview_id=598291</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/paul-krugman-us-dollar-768x432.png" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Nobel Laureate Paul Krugman Says US Dollar Dominance Won&#039;t Last Forever but Doubts Chinese Yuan Can Replace USD as Dominant Currency" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/paul-krugman-us-dollar-300x169.png 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/paul-krugman-us-dollar-1024x576.png 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/paul-krugman-us-dollar-768x432.png 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/paul-krugman-us-dollar-190x107.png 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/paul-krugman-us-dollar-380x214.png 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/paul-krugman-us-dollar-760x428.png 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/paul-krugman-us-dollar.png 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />Nobel Prize-winning economist Paul Krugman says the U.S. dollar&#8217;s dominance &#8220;won&#8217;t last forever.&#8221; While recognizing the global de-dollarization trend, he expressed skepticism about the Chinese yuan&#8217;s ability to replace the U.S. dollar as the world&#8217;s dominant currency. Economist Paul Krugman on U.S. Dollar Dominance and Chinese Yuan Nobel laureate Paul Krugman discussed the U.S. dollar&#8217;s [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/paul-krugman-us-dollar-768x432.png" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Nobel Laureate Paul Krugman Says US Dollar Dominance Won&#039;t Last Forever but Doubts Chinese Yuan Can Replace USD as Dominant Currency" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/paul-krugman-us-dollar-300x169.png 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/paul-krugman-us-dollar-1024x576.png 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/paul-krugman-us-dollar-768x432.png 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/paul-krugman-us-dollar-190x107.png 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/paul-krugman-us-dollar-380x214.png 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/paul-krugman-us-dollar-760x428.png 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/paul-krugman-us-dollar.png 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>Nobel Prize-winning economist Paul Krugman says the U.S. dollar&#8217;s dominance &#8220;won&#8217;t last forever.&#8221; While recognizing the global de-dollarization trend, he expressed skepticism about the Chinese yuan&#8217;s ability to replace the U.S. dollar as the world&#8217;s dominant currency.</strong></p>
<h2>Economist Paul Krugman on U.S. Dollar Dominance and Chinese Yuan</h2>
<p>Nobel laureate Paul Krugman discussed the U.S. dollar&#8217;s dominance and the potential for the Chinese yuan to replace the USD in an opinion piece published in The New York Times earlier this month. Krugman won the Sveriges Riksbank Prize in Economic Sciences in Memory of Alfred Nobel in 2008 for his analysis of trade patterns and location of economic activity.</p>
<p>Krugman acknowledged the growing de-dollarization trend worldwide and the potential decline of the U.S. dollar&#8217;s role in international trade, as more countries seek to de-dollarize. However, citing a Federal Reserve report that analyzed various indicators of dollar dominance, he stressed that the U.S. dollar&#8217;s dominance has remained steady over the past two decades, adding that “diminution of the dollar’s status seems unlikely in the near term.”</p>
<p>Regarding the decline of the U.S. dollar&#8217;s share in central bank reserves, which dropped from 71% in 2000 to 58% in 2022, the Nobel laureate explained: &#8220;This decline mainly reflects diversification into smaller currencies such as the Canadian and Australian dollars, rather than a move to serious dollar rivals.&#8221;</p>
<p>Noting that many people hold the view that the U.S. is weaponizing its currency through financial sanctions, Krugman further cited the Fed paper, stating:</p>
<blockquote><p>Just about all prominent reserve currencies are issued by close U.S. allies, who have also participated in sanctions against Russia. As a result, geopolitical adversaries do not have many attractive alternatives to the U.S. dollar.</p></blockquote>
<p>Krugman also discussed the possibility of the Chinese yuan displacing the U.S. dollar as the world’s dominant currency. While admitting that China is a major economic power, he questioned whether Mandarin will become the dominant language of international commerce or if the yuan will become a major international currency. The Nobel Prize-winning economist believes that it is unlikely that either will become dominant in international commerce in the near future, pointing to factors such as the limited use of Mandarin as a second language and China&#8217;s capital controls.</p>
<p>In conclusion, Krugman opined:</p>
<blockquote><p>The greenback’s dominance won’t last forever, because nothing does. But the hype about de-dollarization is much ado about almost nothing. For now, the dollar dominates because there just aren’t any good alternatives.</p></blockquote>
<p>Multiple people have warned about the end of the U.S. dollar dominance, including Rich Dad Poor Dad author <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/robert-kiyosakis-warnings-giant-crash-incoming-end-of-us-dollar-approaching/">Robert Kiyosaki</a>, S&amp;P Global economist <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/economist-predicts-end-of-us-dollar-dominance-as-more-countries-de-dollarize/">Paul Gruenwald</a>, and veteran trader <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/renowned-investor-jim-rogers-warns-us-dollars-time-coming-to-an-end-as-countries-seek-alternatives/">Jim Rogers</a>.</p>
<p>One currency that many expect to replace the U.S. dollar is the <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/brics-bank-official-discusses-common-currency-as-reports-of-gold-backed-brics-currency-gain-attention/">proposed BRICS currency</a> which could be backed by gold. U.S. Treasury Secretary <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/treasury-secretary-yellen-brics-currency-wont-threaten-us-dollar-dominance/">Janet Yellen</a>, however, doesn&#8217;t see the proposed BRICS recurrency as a threat to the USD.</p>
<p><em><strong>Do you agree with Nobel laureate Paul Krugman about the U.S. dollar dominance and the Chinese yuan? Let us know in the comments section below.</strong></em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/paul-krugman-us-dollar-760x428.png</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[Nobel laureate Paul Krugman says the U.S. #dollar's dominance "won't last forever," but he doesn't expect the Chinese #yuan to replace the $USD. #dedollarization]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA["Geopolitical adversaries do not have many attractive alternatives to the U.S. #dollar," said Nobel laureate Paul Krugman. #dedollarization #yuan]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>SEC &#8216;Disappointed&#8217; With XRP Ruling on Retail Investors — Chair Gensler Hints at More Crypto Industry Enforcement</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/sec-disappointed-with-xrp-ruling-on-retail-investors-chair-gensler-hints-at-more-crypto-industry-enforcement/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Kevin Helms]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 01:30:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gary Gensler Ripple ruling]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gary Gensler SEC appeal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gary Gensler XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple case]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple ruling]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC chairman XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC v Ripple ruling]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp security]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=598285&#038;preview=true&#038;preview_id=598285</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/gensler-ripple-xrp-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="SEC Chair Gary Gensler &#039;Disappointed&#039; With XRP Ruling on Retail Investors — Hints at More Crypto Industry Enforcement" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/gensler-ripple-xrp-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/gensler-ripple-xrp-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/gensler-ripple-xrp-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/gensler-ripple-xrp-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/gensler-ripple-xrp-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/gensler-ripple-xrp-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/gensler-ripple-xrp.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission Chairman Gary Gensler has stated that the regulator is &#x201C;disappointed&#x201D; with the SEC v. Ripple ruling on XRP regarding retail investors. &#x201C;We are still looking at it and assessing that opinion,&#x201D; he affirmed. Gensler also reiterated the SEC&#x2019;s commitment to enforcing regulations on the crypto industry and ensuring compliance among [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/gensler-ripple-xrp-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="SEC Chair Gary Gensler &#039;Disappointed&#039; With XRP Ruling on Retail Investors — Hints at More Crypto Industry Enforcement" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/gensler-ripple-xrp-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/gensler-ripple-xrp-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/gensler-ripple-xrp-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/gensler-ripple-xrp-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/gensler-ripple-xrp-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/gensler-ripple-xrp-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/gensler-ripple-xrp.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission Chairman Gary Gensler has stated that the regulator is &#x201C;disappointed&#x201D; with the SEC v. Ripple ruling on <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/XRP" 311999  target="_blank">XRP</a> regarding retail investors. &#x201C;We are still looking at it and assessing that opinion,&#x201D; he affirmed. Gensler also reiterated the SEC&#x2019;s commitment to enforcing regulations on the crypto industry and ensuring compliance among crypto firms.</strong>&#13;</p>
<h2>Gensler Says SEC Is &#x2018;Assessing&#x2019; the Ripple Ruling on <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/XRP" 311999  target="_blank">XRP</a></h2>
<p>&#13;<br />
The chairman of the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), Gary Gensler, commented on the <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/us-judge-rules-xrp-not-necessarily-a-security-on-its-face-sending-xrp-supporters-into-celebration/">ruling</a> in the SEC v. Ripple case during his remarks at the National Press Club luncheon Monday.&#13;<br />
&#13;<br />
The court ruled last Thursday, as <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/ripples-chief-legal-officer-breaks-down-ruling-in-sec-lawsuit-says-as-a-matter-of-law-xrp-is-not-a-security/">described</a> by Ripple&#x2019;s chief legal officer, that &#x201C;<a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/XRP" 311999  target="_blank">XRP</a> is not a security &#x2026; sales on exchanges are not securities. Sales by executives are not securities. Other <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/XRP" 311999  target="_blank">XRP</a> distributions &#x2014; to developers, to charities, to employees are not securities.&#x201D; The Ripple legal counsel noted: &#x201C;The only thing the court found constitutes an investment contract is past direct <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/XRP" 311999  target="_blank">XRP</a> sales to institutional clients.&#x201D;&#13;<br />
&#13;<br />
Gensler was asked: &#x201C;How does the federal court ruling last week in the Ripple case impact your stance towards digital asset regulation? Does it inject urgency in the need for federal legislation to clarify regulatory oversight of this industry?&#x201D;&#13;<br />
&#13;<br />
The SEC chief replied: &#x201C;We are pleased from that decision recognizing the importance of protecting institutional investors and the court&#x2019;s movement with regard to &#x2018;fair notice.'&#x201D; He continued:&#13;</p>
<blockquote><p>While disappointed on what they said about retail investors, we are still looking at it and assessing that opinion.</p></blockquote>
<p>&#13;<br />
While the crypto community celebrated the Ripple-<a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/XRP" 311999  target="_blank">XRP</a> ruling, there were cautionary voices. Former SEC internet enforcement chief <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/former-sec-official-warns-of-reversal-in-sec-v-ripple-ruling-on-xrp-says-the-decision-resides-on-shaky-ground/">John Reed Stark</a> and lawyer <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/legal-expert-warns-victory-may-be-short-lived-for-ripple-and-xrp-says-judge-got-the-law-wrong/">Bryan Jacoutot</a> believe that the ruling rests on shaky ground, warning that the decision could be overturned.&#13;<br />
&#13;<br />
&#13;<br />
&#13;<br />
Gensler was also asked: &#x201C;What&#x2019;s the next frontier for the SEC crypto enforcement push?&#x201D; The SEC chair replied: &#x201C;Our role at the SEC is again protecting the markets, the investing public, [and] the capital formation &#x2014; and ensuring compliance with the laws in the books as Congress passed them. That&#x2019;s what we are doing.&#x201D; He continued:&#13;</p>
<blockquote><p>So what&#x2019;s next? We are going to continue to try to bring firms that may not be in compliance into compliance without prejudging any one of them and try to ensure that we protect the investing public.</p></blockquote>
<p>&#13;<br />
Following the ruling on the Ripple case, several U.S. lawmakers have urged <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/us-lawmakers-call-on-congress-to-pass-crypto-law-following-sec-v-ripple-ruling-on-xrp/">Congress to pass legislation</a> to regulate the crypto industry and uphold the judge&#x2019;s ruling on the SEC v. Ripple case.&#13;<br />
&#13;<br />
<em><strong>What do you think about the statements by SEC Chairman Gary Gensler regarding the ruling on the SEC v. Ripple case over <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/XRP" 311999  target="_blank">XRP</a>? Let us know in the comments section below.</strong></em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/gensler-ripple-xrp-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[The #SEC is “disappointed” with the court's ruling on the #Ripple case regarding $XRP for retail investors, says SEC Chair Gary Gensler. #crypto]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA["So what's next? We are going to continue to try to bring firms that may not be in compliance into compliance," says #SEC Chairman Gary Gensler. #Ripple $XRP #crypto]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Decentralized Finance Sector Consolidates as $44B TVL Fails to Break $50B Barrier</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/decentralized-finance-sector-consolidates-as-44b-tvl-fails-to-break-50b-barrier/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jamie Redman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 00:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Defi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Aave]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Consolidation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[decentralized finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi sector]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Defi TVL]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Justlend]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lido Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[makerdao]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[market fluctuations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Smart Contract Tokens]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[total value locked]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TVL]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[uniswap]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=598293</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/def78ss9-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Decentralized Finance Sector Consolidates as $44B TVL Fails to Break $50B Barrier" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/def78ss9-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/def78ss9-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/def78ss9-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/def78ss9-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/def78ss9-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/def78ss9-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/def78ss9.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />As of July 17, 2023, the decentralized finance (defi) sector has been witnessing a great deal of consolidation with total value locked (TVL) figures standing at $44.19 billion. Throughout most of the year in 2023, except for a brief period of seven days in April, the TVL in defi has consistently remained below the $50 [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/def78ss9-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Decentralized Finance Sector Consolidates as $44B TVL Fails to Break $50B Barrier" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/def78ss9-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/def78ss9-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/def78ss9-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/def78ss9-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/def78ss9-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/def78ss9-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/def78ss9.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>As of July 17, 2023, the decentralized finance (defi) sector has been witnessing a great deal of consolidation with total value locked (TVL) figures standing at $44.19 billion. Throughout most of the year in 2023, except for a brief period of seven days in April, the TVL in defi has consistently remained below the $50 billion range. </strong>&#13;</p>
<h2>Value Locked in Defi in 2023 Remains Above $40B but Stagnates Below $50B</h2>
<p>&#13;<br />
Throughout the first half of 2023, the decentralized finance (defi) landscape has exhibited a lackluster performance, with the value locked in the sector remaining relatively stagnant. Specifically, on Monday, July 17, 2023, the total value locked (TVL) stands at $44.19 billion, according to defillama.com <a href="https://defillama.com">metrics</a>.&#13;<br />
&#13;<br />
&#13;<br />
&#13;<br />
Within this sum, <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/liquid-staking-derivatives-in-ethereum-swell-by-1-5-million-eth-in-2-months/">Lido Finance</a> commands a significant portion, securing $14.78 billion, which accounts for 33.45% of the aggregate TVL. Following Lido, prominent players in the defi realm include <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/aave-launches-gho-stablecoin-on-ethereum-network/">Aave</a> ($5.88B), <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/makerdao-issues-emergency-proposal-to-address-3-1b-in-usdc-collateral-after-stablecoin-depegging-incident/">Makerdao</a> ($5.47B), Uniswap ($3.78B), and Justlend ($3.69B).&#13;<br />
&#13;<br />
With the exception of a notable period from April 12th to the 19th, the TVL in the defi sector has consistently hovered below the $50 billion range throughout the year. In the middle of June, the TVL hit its lowest point in 2023, standing at $40.9 billion. However, it has managed to remain above the $40 billion threshold this year.&#13;<br />
&#13;<br />
Following the recent <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/us-judge-rules-xrp-not-necessarily-a-security-on-its-face-sending-xrp-supporters-into-celebration/">Ripple ruling</a>, which led to <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/xrps-rise-causes-ripple-of-gains-in-crypto-economy/">substantial gains</a> in the cryptocurrency markets and smart contract tokens, the TVL in the defi sector approached the $46 billion threshold. However, the <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/categories/smart-contract-platform">top smart contract token economy</a> has since relinquished most of those gains, experiencing a 2.4% decline to reach approximately $351 billion in the past 24 hours.&#13;<br />
&#13;<br />
&#13;<br />
&#13;<br />
Despite the overall retracement, <a href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/SOL/">solana (SOL)</a> has managed to sustain a 21.5% increase against the U.S. dollar over the past seven days. <a href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/ADA/">Cardano (ADA)</a> has also made notable strides, rising by 6.4% throughout the week.&#13;<br />
&#13;<br />
&#13;<br />
&#13;<br />
Additionally, <a href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/MATIC/">polygon (MATIC)</a> has defied the broader crypto market downturn, surging by 3.7% in the same period. Amid the broader market fluctuations, <a href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/ETH/">ethereum (ETH)</a> experienced a minor setback of 0.5%, while <a href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/BNB/">binance coin (BNB)</a> witnessed a decline of 1.4% over the course of this week.&#13;<br />
&#13;<br />
Notably, out of the total value locked (TVL) recorded during this period, Ethereum-based defi protocols accounted for a substantial <a href="https://defillama.com/chains">58.47%</a>, surpassing the $25 billion mark. Trailing behind Ethereum, Tron holds the second-largest blockchain in terms of TVLs, commanding 12.83% or $5.65 billion.&#13;<br />
&#13;<br />
<em><strong>What do you think about the rangebound statistics the TVL in defi has seen for most of 2023? Share your thoughts and opinions about this subject in the comments section below.</strong></em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/def78ss9-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[Throughout most of 2023, except for a brief period in April, the TVL in #DeFi has consistently remained below the $50 billion range.]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA[Throughout most of 2023, except for a brief period in April, the TVL in #DeFi has consistently remained below the $50 billion range.]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>G20&#8217;s FSB Pushes for Global Crypto Regulations and Standards Aiming to Curb Crypto ‘Spillover’ Risks</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/g20s-fsb-pushes-for-global-crypto-regulations-and-standards-aiming-to-curb-crypto-spillover-risks/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jamie Redman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 21:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto assets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[economic roles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[financial stability]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[financial stability board]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fsb]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[G20]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[G20 FSB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[global regulatory structure]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[interlinkages]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jurisdictional financial authorities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Recommendations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[responsible innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sector-specific issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[standard-setting bodies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terra's stablecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[traditional financial system]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=598256</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/g2089-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="G20&#039;s FSB Pushes for Global Crypto Regulations and Standards Aiming to Curb Crypto ‘Spillover’ Risks" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/g2089-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/g2089-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/g2089-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/g2089-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/g2089-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/g2089-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/g2089.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />On Monday, the Financial Stability Board (FSB), a product of the G20 organization, unveiled its proposed guidelines for a global regulatory structure overseeing the operations of crypto assets. The international entity emphasizes that nations should confront the risks cryptocurrencies pose to global financial stability. The FSB contends that occurrences within the preceding year have underscored [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/g2089-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="G20&#039;s FSB Pushes for Global Crypto Regulations and Standards Aiming to Curb Crypto ‘Spillover’ Risks" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/g2089-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/g2089-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/g2089-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/g2089-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/g2089-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/g2089-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/g2089.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>On Monday, the Financial Stability Board (FSB), a product of the G20 organization, unveiled its proposed guidelines for a global regulatory structure overseeing the operations of crypto assets. The international entity emphasizes that nations should confront the risks cryptocurrencies pose to global financial stability. The FSB contends that occurrences within the preceding year have underscored the “structural vulnerabilities of crypto assets and related players.”</strong></p>
<h2>G20’s Financial Stability Board Provides 9 Crypto Industry-Centric Recommendations for Countries and Standard-Setting Bodies</h2>
<p>As stated in a newly published <a href="https://www.fsb.org/wp-content/uploads/P170723-1.pdf">report</a>, the G20’s Financial Stability Board (FSB) wants to rein in the crypto industry with tighter regulations and standardized frameworks. The FSB&#8217;s strategy for governing crypto asset operations hinges on encouraging collaboration between jurisdictional financial authorities and standard-setting bodies (SSBs). This cooperation aims to guarantee that such activities are governed by sturdy regulation and oversight matching the financial stability risks they pose, all while fostering responsible innovation.</p>
<p>The FSB has identified several notable failures within the crypto industry over the previous year, including the <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/a-dark-day-for-crypto-a-deep-dive-into-the-obliterated-terra-token-ecosystem-and-damaged-apps/">depegging event</a> of Terra&#8217;s stablecoin and the <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/from-a-32-billion-valuation-to-financial-troubles-an-in-depth-look-at-the-rise-and-fall-of-ftx/">implosion of FTX</a>. “These events demonstrate interlinkages between crypto asset markets and the traditional financial system,” the authors of the FSB report outline. Nevertheless, the regulatory authority concedes that the impact on conventional finance was &#8220;limited&#8221; amid these two distinct incidents. Still, “interlinkages and possible spillovers between the crypto asset and traditional financial systems could markedly increase,” the FSB report explains.</p>
<p>The FSB further states:</p>
<blockquote><p>These events have further highlighted that many crypto asset activities involve economic functions similar to those in traditional finance and should be comprehensively regulated and/or brought into compliance with new or existing rules as appropriate.</p></blockquote>
<p>The FSB’s nine outlined recommendations stress that regulatory structures must also mandate that any crypto asset activities aiming to execute a similar economic role as those in the conventional financial system, are subject to identical or equivalent regulation. This should hold true regardless of how these crypto asset activities are carried out or the manner in which they are promoted, the report emphasizes. The FSB is of the opinion that the recommendations provide sufficient latitude for SSBs to formulate detailed standards tackling crypto sector-specific issues within their individual jurisdictions.</p>
<p>The FSB says the main concern is to “safeguard client assets,” remove “conflicts of interest,” from the sector, and establish “cross-border cooperation.” The FSB and the International Monetary Fund (IMF) &#8220;will deliver a joint report to the G20 in September 2023, which will synthesise the policy findings from IMF work on macroeconomic and monetary issues,” the FSB report concludes.</p>
<p><em><strong>What do you think about the G20&#8217;s Financial Stability Board recommendations for the crypto industry? Share your thoughts and opinions about this subject in the comments section below.</strong></em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/g2089-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[The G20’s Financial Stability Board (FSB) wants to rein in the #crypto industry with tighter regulations and standardized frameworks.]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA[The G20’s Financial Stability Board (FSB) wants to rein in the #crypto industry with tighter regulations and standardized frameworks.]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Aave Launches GHO Stablecoin on Ethereum Network</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/aave-launches-gho-stablecoin-on-ethereum-network/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jamie Redman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 19:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Aave]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AAVE token]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[borrowing rates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[circulating supply]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinmarketcap.com]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[decentralized finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dollar-pegged coins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum Network]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[GHO]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Global Trade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Goerli testnet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Governance proposal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[interest earning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[lending protocol]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[smart contract audits]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Transaction volume]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=598140</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/aave-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Aave Launches GHO Stablecoin on Ethereum Network" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/aave-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/aave-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/aave-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/aave-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/aave-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/aave-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/aave.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />Aave, a prominent lending protocol within the decentralized finance (defi) sphere, has unveiled GHO, a new stablecoin, which is now live on the Ethereum network. Aave users can now mint the stablecoin asset by leveraging Aave version three (v3). Aave&#8217;s Dollar-Pegged GHO Token Goes Live on Ethereum This week, on July 14, 2023, Aave&#8217;s community [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/aave-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Aave Launches GHO Stablecoin on Ethereum Network" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/aave-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/aave-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/aave-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/aave-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/aave-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/aave-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/aave.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>Aave, a prominent lending protocol within the decentralized finance (defi) sphere, has unveiled GHO, a new stablecoin, which is now live on the Ethereum network. Aave users can now mint the stablecoin asset by leveraging Aave version three (v3).</strong></p>
<h2>Aave&#8217;s Dollar-Pegged GHO Token Goes Live on Ethereum</h2>
<p>This week, on July 14, 2023, Aave&#8217;s community approved a <a href="https://app.aave.com/governance/proposal/?proposalId=268">governance proposal</a>, swiftly followed by the much-awaited launch of the stablecoin GHO on the Ethereum network. GHO, initially <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/aave-dao-approves-the-launch-of-a-collateral-backed-stablecoin-called-gho/">announced</a> in July 2022, had a <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/aave-launches-stablecoin-gho-on-ethereum-goerli-testnet-with-open-source-codebase-and-audits/">test run</a> on Ethereum&#8217;s Goerli testnet in February 2023. In line with the information from the Github repository, the newly debuted stablecoin, and its affiliated smart contract underwent <a href="https://github.com/aave/gho-core/tree/main/audits">multiple audits</a>.</p>
<p>Currently, GHO is relatively insignificant when compared with the top ten heavyweights of the stablecoin world, especially when considering circulating dollar-pegged coins. The circulating supply of GHO stands around <a href="https://archive.ph/gh5xm">2,510,269 tokens</a>, representing a meager 0.0016% of the overall $127 billion stablecoin economy. At 12:20 p.m. Eastern Time on Sunday, GHO hit a trough at $0.9813, yet so far, it has generally maintained its peg to the dollar.</p>
<p>Emulating numerous stablecoin assets, individuals can gather interest with Aave&#8217;s freshly debuted GHO stablecoin. Users who stake the AAVE token are also rewarded with an extra 30% discount on current GHO borrowing rates. Thus far, there are approximately 234 GHO holders, and since the mainnet inception, a total of 893 transactions have been logged. <a href="https://archive.ph/D8OZG">Data</a> sourced from coinmarketcap.com reveals that GHO has seen roughly $1,437,756 in worldwide trading volume over the past 24 hours.</p>
<p><em><strong>What do you think about the new Aave GHO stablecoin? Share your thoughts and opinions about this subject in the comments section below.</strong></em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/aave-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[The decentralized finance lending protocol Aave has announced that GHO, a new stablecoin, is now live on the #Ethereum network. ]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA[The decentralized finance lending protocol Aave has announced that GHO, a new stablecoin, is now live on the #Ethereum network. ]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Litecoin on the Brink of Third Halving: Record Hashrate and Profitable Mining Despite 17% Value Dip</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/litecoin-on-the-brink-of-third-halving-record-hashrate-and-profitable-mining-despite-17-value-dip/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jamie Redman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 17:32:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Antpool]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ASIC mining devices]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[block interval]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[daily profit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[F2Pool]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Halving]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hashrate]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[market fluctuation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miners]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mining Pools]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mining Rig]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Poolin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[reward reduction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[value depreciation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[value gain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ViaBTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=598195</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/halvin-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Litecoin on the Brink of Third Halving: Record Hashrate and Profitable Mining Despite 17% Value Dip" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/halvin-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/halvin-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/halvin-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/halvin-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/halvin-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/halvin-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/halvin.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />In a mere fortnight, the Litecoin network is poised for its third reward halving event, a seismic shift that will slash the LTC miners&#x2019; block rewards from 12.5 LTC per block down to 6.25 LTC. Data illustrates an intensified dedication of hashrate to the Litecoin blockchain as the critical halving deadline draws near.&#13; Litecoin Reward [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/halvin-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Litecoin on the Brink of Third Halving: Record Hashrate and Profitable Mining Despite 17% Value Dip" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/halvin-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/halvin-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/halvin-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/halvin-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/halvin-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/halvin-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/halvin.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>In a mere fortnight, the Litecoin network is poised for its third reward halving event, a seismic shift that will slash the <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/LTC" 312004  target="_blank">LTC</a> miners&#x2019; block rewards from 12.5 <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/LTC" 312004  target="_blank">LTC</a> per block down to 6.25 <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/LTC" 312004  target="_blank">LTC</a>. Data illustrates an intensified dedication of hashrate to the Litecoin blockchain as the critical halving deadline draws near.</strong>&#13;</p>
<h2>Litecoin Reward Halving Draws Near</h2>
<p>&#13;<br />
Over the last two weeks, <a href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/LTC/">litecoin (LTC)</a> has seen a notable descent, depreciating approximately 17% in value against the U.S. dollar. However, casting the gaze back a full month reveals a contrasting picture, with <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/LTC" 312004  target="_blank">LTC</a> capturing a gain of roughly 18%. In just 15 days, the Litecoin network stands on the precipice of its third halving.&#13;<br />
&#13;<br />
History shows us a pattern with the first two reward reductions taking place on August 25, 2015, and August 5, 2019, respectively. This forthcoming third halving is set to shrink the miners&#x2019; rewards from a substantial 12.5 <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/LTC" 312004  target="_blank">LTC</a> per block to a more modest 6.25 <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/LTC" 312004  target="_blank">LTC</a>. In contrast to Bitcoin&#x2019;s average block interval, which aims to clock in at ten minutes per block, Litecoin operates at a swifter pace, producing a new block every 2.5 minutes.&#13;<br />
&#13;<br />
At the time of writing, factoring in current <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/LTC" 312004  target="_blank">LTC</a> exchange rates, a single block rewards miners with $1,161 derived from the freshly minted 12.5 <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/LTC" 312004  target="_blank">LTC</a>. If the <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/LTC" 312004  target="_blank">LTC</a>&#x2019;s price manages to maintain the same exchange rate, a block mined post-August 2, 2023, can anticipate a value of around $580. The price upswing of <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/LTC" 312004  target="_blank">LTC</a> over the recent 30-day span has sparked substantial interest, luring an abundance of Scrypt hashrate.&#13;<br />
&#13;<br />
&#13;<br />
&#13;<br />
Litecoin&#x2019;s hashrate dramatically peaked on July 4, 2023, reaching a record high of 1.03 petahash per second (PH/s) at block height 2,503,485. This indicates an unprecedented level of activity on the network. At present, <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/LTC" 312004  target="_blank">LTC</a>&#x2019;s total hashrate is coasting along at <a href="https://www.coinwarz.com/mining/litecoin/hashrate-chart">804</a> terahash per second (TH/s).&#13;</p>
<p class="p1">
<p>&#13;<br />
In the mining industry, Litecoin&#x2019;s application-specific integrated circuit (ASIC) mining devices are currently staking a claim as some of the market&#x2019;s most profitable machinery. For instance, a mining rig delivering 8.8 gigahash per second (GH/s) can amass an estimated daily profit of $7.83. Moreover, a machine operating at 9.5 GH/s could garner a slightly higher daily earning of $9.24.&#13;<br />
&#13;<br />
As of July 16, Viabtc reigns supreme as Litecoin&#x2019;s leading mining pool, dedicating a formidable 268.63 TH/s of hashrate to the <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/LTC" 312004  target="_blank">LTC</a> chain. Approximately 27 dedicated mining pools are channeling their hashrate toward the <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/LTC" 312004  target="_blank">LTC</a> chain. Viabtc is followed by F2pool, contributing 136.87 TH/s, trailed by Antpool with 117 TH/s. Meanwhile, Litecoinpool adds 90.84 TH/s, Btc.com contributes 42.95 TH/s, and Poolin rounds out the field with a contribution of 30.49 TH/s.&#13;<br />
&#13;<br />
<em><strong>What do you think about the upcoming Litecoin halving? Share your thoughts and opinions about this subject in the comments section below.</strong></em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/halvin-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[Data illustrates an intensified dedication of hashrate to the #Litecoin blockchain as the critical #halving deadline draws near.]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA[Data illustrates an intensified dedication of hashrate to the #Litecoin blockchain as the critical #halving deadline draws near.]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance US Records Massive Discrepancies as USD Exchange Rates Plummet by 16% in July</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/binance-us-records-massive-discrepancies-as-usd-exchange-rates-plummet-by-16-in-july/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jamie Redman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 15:30:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[16%]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[16% wide]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2%]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[5]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[astonishing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance US greenbacks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance US USD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance.us]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[concerning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[discrepancies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[downturn]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange rates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Global Average]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mid-July]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rise]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sharply]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[soared]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USD pair]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[valuation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[worldwide average]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=598221</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/bus-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Binance US Records Massive Discrepancies as USD Exchange Rates Plummet by 16% in July" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/bus-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/bus-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/bus-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/bus-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/bus-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/bus-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/bus.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />As of July 17, 2023, fresh data indicates a concerning rise in discrepancies between Binance US&#x2019; exchange rates and the global average. Initially, at a mere 2% to 5% in late June, the disparity sharply soared to an astonishing 16% by mid-July. Even though bitcoin lingered just above $30,000 on Monday, its valuation on Binance [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/bus-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Binance US Records Massive Discrepancies as USD Exchange Rates Plummet by 16% in July" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/bus-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/bus-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/bus-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/bus-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/bus-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/bus-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/bus.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>As of July 17, 2023, fresh data indicates a concerning rise in discrepancies between Binance US&#x2019; exchange rates and the global average. Initially, at a mere 2% to 5% in late June, the disparity sharply soared to an astonishing 16% by mid-July. Even though bitcoin lingered just above $30,000 on Monday, its valuation on Binance US is roughly $5,000 lower than the worldwide average in relation to the USD pair.</strong>&#13;</p>
<h2>USD Trading Pairs on Binance US Show Significant Disparities</h2>
<p>&#13;<br />
At the week&#x2019;s start, the digital economy suffered a downturn with a 1.22% drop in value, reducing it to $1.2 trillion. Bitcoin (<a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/BTC" 311996  target="_blank">BTC</a>) maintains a trading value of around <a href="https://web.archive.org/web/20230717124934/https://coinmarketcap.com/">$30,180</a> per unit, while ethereum (<a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/ETH" target="_blank">ETH</a>) is roughly <a href="https://web.archive.org/web/20230717124934/https://coinmarketcap.com/">$1,911</a> per coin. However, the price divergence across <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/BTC" 311996  target="_blank">BTC</a>, <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/ETH" target="_blank">ETH</a>, and select other coins exclusively paired with the U.S. dollar on Binance US &#x2014; a prominent crypto exchange &#x2014; continues to expand.&#13;<br />
&#13;<br />
As per <a href="https://archive.ph/glZLe#selection-1517.0-1517.4">July 17 data</a>, <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/BTC" 311996  target="_blank">BTC</a>/USD trading illustrates <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/BTC" 311996  target="_blank">BTC</a> transactions at a starkly lower rate of $25,073 &#x2014; a staggering 16.92% below the global mean exchange rate for <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/BTC" 311996  target="_blank">BTC</a>. Similar inconsistencies in Binance US&#x2019; exchange rates are apparent for the majority of cryptocurrency assets and stablecoins when matched with the U.S. dollar. For instance, ether, now trading above $1,900 per unit, remarkably drops to around $1,595 on Binance US when paired with the greenback.&#13;<br />
&#13;<br />
&#13;<br />
&#13;<br />
Concurrently, <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/USDT" target="_blank">USDT</a>/USD pairs exhibit a rate of $0.76 per tether on this platform &#x2014; significantly lower than its anticipated dollar-pegged value. Likewise, binance coin (<a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/BNB" target="_blank">BNB</a>), despite its market value of $242 per coin, exchanges for a mere $200 when compared against the dollar on Binance US. Over the past fortnight, disparities within Binance US have further deepened; by the end of June, exchange rate variances spanned between <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-06-28/crypto-discounts-worsen-on-binance-us-as-sec-investigation-s-impact-takes-hold?leadSource=uverify%20wall">2% and 5%</a>.&#13;<br />
&#13;<br />
&#13;<br />
&#13;<br />
As July commenced, the gap between U.S. dollar matches and global exchange rates <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/binance-us-arbitrage-social-media-users-say-btc-discount-not-indication-of-an-opportunity/">widened considerably</a>. The cause behind Binance US&#x2019; current pricing discrepancies stems from the platform&#x2019;s suspension of USD deposits, resulting in customers being unable to top up their accounts with fresh dollars. The residual dollars on the exchange, since Binance US halted deposits, triggered the pricing irregularities, as traders sell coins at broad discounts. The duration and extent to which these disparities will persist remain uncertain.&#13;<br />
&#13;<br />
<em><strong>What do you think about the price discrepancies on Binance US compared to the global average? Share your thoughts and opinions about this subject in the comments section below.</strong></em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/bus-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[#Bitcoin’s valuation on Binance US is roughly $5,000 lower than the worldwide average in relation to the USD pair.]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA[#Bitcoin’s valuation on Binance US is roughly $5,000 lower than the worldwide average in relation to the USD pair.]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
