<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:bnmedia="https://news.bitcoin.com/">

<channel>
	<title>Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/</link>
	<description>Daily Bitcoin News</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 23:08:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>BRICS to Strengthen Economic Cooperation — Sherpa Calls for Increased Trade in National Currencies</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/brics-to-strengthen-economic-cooperation-sherpa-calls-for-increased-trade-in-national-currencies/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Kevin Helms]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 01:30:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BRICS currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BRICS leaders summit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BRICS membership discussion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BRICS national currencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sherpas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[South Africa]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=588462&#038;preview=true&#038;preview_id=588462</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/brics-sherpa-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="BRICS to Strengthen Economic Cooperation — Sherpa Calls for Increased Trade in National Currencies" decoding="async" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/brics-sherpa-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/brics-sherpa-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/brics-sherpa-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/brics-sherpa-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/brics-sherpa-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/brics-sherpa-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/brics-sherpa.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />South Africa’s BRICS Sherpa says one of the priorities at the upcoming BRICS summit is “to strengthen economic cooperation.” He added: “We need a stable global financial architecture, a global financial arena. That is why we say that we need to trade in our own currencies.” He also believes that the recession forecasts by the [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/brics-sherpa-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="BRICS to Strengthen Economic Cooperation — Sherpa Calls for Increased Trade in National Currencies" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/brics-sherpa-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/brics-sherpa-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/brics-sherpa-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/brics-sherpa-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/brics-sherpa-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/brics-sherpa-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/brics-sherpa.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>South Africa’s BRICS Sherpa says one of the priorities at the upcoming BRICS summit is “to strengthen economic cooperation.” He added: “We need a stable global financial architecture, a global financial arena. That is why we say that we need to trade in our own currencies.” He also believes that the recession forecasts by the International Monetary Fund (IMF) and the World Bank will not affect the BRICS nations.</strong></p>
<h2>BRICS Sherpa Discusses Summit Priorities</h2>
<p>South Africa’s BRICS Sherpa, Anil Sooklal, delved into the agendas and priorities of the upcoming BRICS summit under South Africa&#8217;s presidency in an <a href="https://tvbrics.com/en/news/anil-sooklal-one-of-the-objectives-of-the-brics-summit-is-to-strengthen-economic-cooperation/">interview</a> with BRICS TV, published Wednesday. Sooklal previously taught at the University of KwaZulu-Natal and the University of South Africa. He also served as Deputy Director General of the Asia and Middle East Department of International Relations and Cooperation until January 2022. From 2006 to 2012, he served as South Africa’s Ambassador to the European Union, Belgium, and Luxembourg.</p>
<p>The BRICS summit will be held in Johannesburg from Aug. 22 to 24. All leaders of the five member nations (Brazil, Russia, India, China, and South Africa) have been invited to attend. “This will be the first face-to-face summit in four years, Sooklal noted.</p>
<p>“BRICS as a global association is based on three pillars — political security, economic and financial development, and social interaction among the member countries. All three pillars are critical important for the creation of a global political architecture that is equitable and just, which is a stable safe environment for all,” the South African Sherpa explained, adding that on the economic and financial side:</p>
<blockquote><p>We need a stable global financial architecture, a global financial arena. That is why we say that we need to trade in our own currencies.</p></blockquote>
<p>The BRICS economic bloc is exploring the launch of a common currency which is expected to be <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/brics-leaders-set-to-discuss-common-currency-to-challenge-us-dollar-dominance-in-upcoming-summit/">discussed</a> by the BRICS leaders at the August summit. As the trend to de-dollarize grows worldwide, many people expect a BRICS currency to erode the U.S. dollar’s dominance.</p>
<p>Regarding the goals of the upcoming BRICS summit, he detailed, “One of the priorities is to strengthen economic cooperation.” Sooklal added that the group has adopted the second version of the BRICS Economic Partnership Strategy. &#8220;The document sets out the main areas for BRICS cooperation until 2025 in the following areas: trade, investment and finance, the digital economy, and sustainable development,” he stated.</p>

<p>Noting that the World Bank and the International Monetary Fund (IMF) “have agreed that about a third of the world economy will be in recession this year,” he opined:</p>
<blockquote><p>I do not think this forecast will affect the BRICS countries. We are going to see positive dynamics. Some of the fastest growing economies are India and China. They are helping to stimulate not only the BRICS economies, but the global economy as a whole.</p></blockquote>
<p>Discussing the growing interest in joining the BRICS group, Sooklal disclosed that during the Beijing summit last year, &#8220;the BRICS leaders asked us to consider the expansion of the association and to develop the guidelines for the admission of new members.&#8221; He recently revealed that <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/brics-getting-applications-to-join-every-day-attracts-19-requests-before-summit/">19 countries</a> have either applied to join or expressed interest in joining BRICS. &#8220;This is positive news for the bloc, as it demonstrates the confidence of the Global South in the leadership of our association,&#8221; he emphasized.</p>
<p><em><strong>What do you think about the BRICS expansion? Let us know in the comments section below.</strong></em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/brics-sherpa-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[#BRICS countries to strengthen economic cooperation, said South Africa’s BRICS Sherpa. #dedollarization]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA["We need to trade in our own currencies," said the South African #BRICS Sherpa. #dedollarization]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>146 Top Executives Urge Biden to Prevent US Default — Warns of &#8216;Disastrous Consequences&#8217;</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/146-top-executives-urge-biden-to-prevent-us-default-warns-of-disastrous-consequences/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Kevin Helms]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 23:30:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CEOs US default]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[executives US default]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Janet Yellen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US default]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US defaulting on debt obligations]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=588604&#038;preview=true&#038;preview_id=588604</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ceos-letter-to-biden-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ceos-letter-to-biden-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ceos-letter-to-biden-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ceos-letter-to-biden-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ceos-letter-to-biden-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ceos-letter-to-biden-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ceos-letter-to-biden-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ceos-letter-to-biden.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />Top executives from 146 major companies in the U.S. — including Morgan Stanley, Goldman Sachs, Nasdaq, and Pfizer — have urged President Joe Biden and congressional leaders to act swiftly to prevent the U.S. from defaulting on its debt, which could occur as early as June 1. They warned of “potentially disastrous consequences” if the [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ceos-letter-to-biden-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ceos-letter-to-biden-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ceos-letter-to-biden-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ceos-letter-to-biden-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ceos-letter-to-biden-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ceos-letter-to-biden-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ceos-letter-to-biden-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ceos-letter-to-biden.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>Top executives from 146 major companies in the U.S. — including Morgan Stanley, Goldman Sachs, Nasdaq, and Pfizer — have urged President Joe Biden and congressional leaders to act swiftly to prevent the U.S. from defaulting on its debt, which could occur as early as June 1. They warned of “potentially disastrous consequences” if the U.S. defaults on its debt obligations.</strong></p>
<h2>Executives Warn of ‘Disastrous Consequences’ From US Default</h2>
<p>A total of 146 executives from major companies in the U.S. have jointly written an open letter to President Joe Biden and congressional leaders urging them to take swift action to save the U.S. from defaulting on its debt obligations.</p>
<p>Among the letter signers are Goldman Sachs CEO David Solomon, Morgan Stanley CEO James Gorman, Nasdaq CEO Adena Friedman, Guggenheim Partners Executive Chairman Alan Schwartz, and Pfizer CEO Albert Bourla.</p>
<p>Addressing President Biden, Senate Majority Leader Chuck Schumer, Senate Minority Leader Mitch McConnell, House Speaker Kevin McCarthy, and House Minority Leader Hakeem Jeffries, the executives wrote:</p>
<blockquote><p>We write to emphasize the potentially disastrous consequences of a failure by the federal government to meet its obligations. Absent a resolution, the government is likely to run out of money as soon as June 1. Action to end the pending debt crisis is necessary now.</p></blockquote>
<p>“Failure to resolve the current impasse could easily have more negative consequences,” they continued. “Although the American economy is generally strong, high inflation has created stresses in our financial system, including several recent bank failures.”</p>
<p>The executives added: “Much worse will occur if the nation defaults on our debt obligations, which would weaken our position in the world financial system. Large amounts of our $31 trillion debt are held by pension funds, individuals, and other governments.” They noted:</p>
<blockquote><p>The inability to incur new debt would also threaten the government’s ability to pay its other bills, potentially including some payments to Social Security or Medicare recipients. This cannot be allowed to happen.</p></blockquote>
<p>“We strongly urge that an accord be reached quickly so that the country can avert this potentially devasting scenario,” they concluded.</p>

<p>U.S. Treasury Janet Yellen has warned that the Treasury may not be able to pay all of the government’s bills as early as <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/treasury-secretary-yellen-warns-us-could-default-on-its-debt-by-june-1/">June 1</a>. The <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/us-government-faces-significant-risk-of-default-in-june-congressional-budget-office-warns/">Congressional Budget Office</a> similarly estimated that the U.S. could default on its debt obligations in the first two weeks of June.</p>
<p>However, President Biden is &#8220;confident&#8221; that he can reach a deal with Republicans on the debt ceiling. Meanwhile, a group of Senate Democrats is reportedly <a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/2023/05/17/debt-ceiling-democrats-discharge-petition/">circulating a letter</a> urging him to prepare to invoke the 14th amendment to unilaterally resolve the debt ceiling standoff.</p>
<p>“I’m confident we’ll get the agreement on the budget and America will not default &#8230; We’re going to come together because there’s no alternative way to do the right thing for the country. We have to move on,” Biden said Wednesday. Former President and 2024 presidential candidate <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/donald-trump-urges-republicans-to-let-us-default-on-debt-if-democrats-dont-agree-to-spending-cuts/">Donald Trump</a> recently urged Republican lawmakers to let the U.S. default on its debt if the Democrats do not agree to spending cuts.</p>
<p><em><strong>What do you think about 146 executives urging President Joe Biden and congressional leaders to act swiftly to prevent the U.S. from having to default on its debt obligations? Let us know in the comments section below.</strong></em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ceos-letter-to-biden-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[146 top executives of major companies, including #MorganStanley and #GoldmanSachs, have urged President Joe Biden and congressional leaders to act swiftly to prevent a U.S. #default. #debtceiling]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA["We write to emphasize the potentially disastrous consequences of a failure by the federal government to meet its obligations," said the letter to Biden from 146 top executives. #debtceiling #default]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Axie Infinity Origins Breaks Through Apple&#8217;s App Store Barrier, Now Accessible to Select iOS Users</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/axie-infinity-origins-breaks-through-apples-app-store-barrier-now-accessible-to-select-ios-users/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jamie Redman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 21:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Apple's app store]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Axie Infinity marketplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Axie Infinity Origins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain-based game]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[google play store]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[iOS users]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFT platforms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Non-fungible Token]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[P2E]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[phased release]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[play to earn]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sky Mavis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=588395</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/axie-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/axie-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/axie-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/axie-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/axie-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/axie-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/axie-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/axie.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />Axie Infinity Origins, the blockchain-based, play-to-earn (P2E) game, has successfully cleared Apple&#8217;s rigorous App Store review process and the game’s app is now available for Apple iOS users. Sky Mavis, the creator behind Axie Infinity, has adopted a strategic approach by rolling out the game&#8217;s app in stages, with targeted release plans for various Latin [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/axie-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/axie-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/axie-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/axie-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/axie-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/axie-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/axie-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/axie.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p dir="ltr"><strong>Axie Infinity Origins, the blockchain-based, play-to-earn (P2E) game, has successfully cleared Apple&#8217;s rigorous App Store review process and the game’s app is now available for Apple iOS users. Sky Mavis, the creator behind Axie Infinity, has adopted a strategic approach by rolling out the game&#8217;s app in stages, with targeted release plans for various Latin American and Asian countries.</strong></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Blockchain Game Axie Infinity Origins Clears Apple&#8217;s Review</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Following the phased release on the Google Play Store, Axie Infinity Origins is now available for Apple iOS users in select countries. The game&#8217;s developer, Sky Mavis, <a href="https://twitter.com/AxieInfinity/status/1658778494875181058?s=20">announced</a> the launch of the iOS version on Wednesday. “Origins has passed review with Apple and is now available on the App Store,” Sky Mavis said. “We believe this is the first time that Apple has agreed to make an externally-purchased NFT usable on the App Store,” the team added.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The blockchain-based game that leverages non-fungible token (NFT) assets, Axie Infinity, was launched by the Vietnamese game studio in 2018. To date, the Axie Infinity marketplace has recorded $4.27 billion in total NFT sales. Initially, Sky Mavis announced that the Origins application was made available to Android users via the Google Play Store in Malaysia. The Apple iOS release will also be available in select countries.</p>
<p dir="ltr">“If you live in Argentina, Colombia, Peru, Mexico, Venezuela, Indonesia, Malaysia, or Vietnam, download Origins for iOS from the App Store,” Sky Mavis disclosed on Wednesday.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Apple&#8217;s App Store guidelines are stricter compared to Google&#8217;s rules. In recent years, Apple has restricted several blockchain-based apps, specifically targeting NFT platforms. For example, Daily Apps released an NFT application called Sticky, which initially remained on the App Store. However, the app, along with several others, was later removed from the store.</p>
<p dir="ltr"></p>
<p dir="ltr">Other NFT applications, such as Opensea&#8217;s App, are permitted to display NFTs to users, but trading functionality is disabled. Some believe these restrictions on NFT apps are linked to Apple&#8217;s requirement for a 30% share in all App Store sales. Regarding the Axie Infinity Origins app, Sky Mavis clarified that certain reward features in the game will only be accessible through the desktop or Android APK versions.</p>
<p dir="ltr">“Players will continue to earn SLP through gameplay, but will not be able to claim these rewards in-app,” Sky Mavis explained regarding the recent Apple release.</p>
<p><em><strong>What are your thoughts on the expansion of Axie Infinity Origins to Apple&#8217;s App Store? Share your thoughts in the comments section below. </strong></em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/axie-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[“#AxieInfinity Origins has passed review with Apple and is now available on the App Store,” Sky Mavis said. #Blockchain #P2E]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA[“#AxieInfinity Origins has passed review with Apple and is now available on the App Store,” Sky Mavis said. #Blockchain #P2E]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>DRC20 Tokens Take Dogecoin Community by Storm, Driving Record-Breaking Daily Transactions on the Network</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/drc20-tokens-take-dogecoin-community-by-storm-driving-record-breaking-daily-transactions-on-the-network/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jamie Redman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 19:30:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BRC20 token economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[daily transactions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin community]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Doginals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DRC20]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DRC20 token standard]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[emerging token type]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[excitement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fungible token supplies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[infrastructure backing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Capitalization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[over-the-counter trades]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[surge of activity]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=588557</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/drc20-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/drc20-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/drc20-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/drc20-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/drc20-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/drc20-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/drc20-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/drc20.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />With the BRC20 token economy maintaining a market capitalization of nearly $500 million, the introduction of the DRC20 token standard has sparked a flurry of excitement within the Dogecoin community. The emerging token type has ignited a surge of activity, leading to a substantial increase in daily transactions on the Dogecoin blockchain. Specifically, on Wednesday, [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/drc20-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/drc20-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/drc20-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/drc20-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/drc20-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/drc20-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/drc20-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/drc20.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>With the BRC20 token economy maintaining a market capitalization of nearly $500 million, the introduction of the DRC20 token standard has sparked a flurry of excitement within the Dogecoin community. The emerging token type has ignited a surge of activity, leading to a substantial increase in daily transactions on the Dogecoin blockchain. Specifically, on Wednesday, May 17, 2023, the network recorded a tally of over 820,000 confirmed transactions so far.</strong></p>
<h2>Dogecoin&#8217;s DRC20 Token Standard Sparks Surge in Daily Transactions</h2>
<p>After witnessing the success of the Ordinal inscription and BRC20 trend on the Bitcoin blockchain, the Dogecoin network now has its very own <a href="https://github.com/dogecoinw/cardinals/blob/main/bip.mediawiki">DRC20 token standard</a>. This development enables users to create fungible token supplies on the Dogecoin network in a decentralized manner, with the mere cost of a single DOGE.</p>
<p>Taking inspiration from the actions of Litecoin developers after the Ordinals on Bitcoin, DRC20s have implemented a similar technology, allowing arbitrary content to be etched onto elons, the smallest unit of DOGE.</p>
<p>Dubbed &#8220;Doginals&#8221; by certain members of the DOGE community, the DRC20 tokens are garnering infrastructure backing from a couple of projects, albeit at a gradual pace. A prime example of this support is the integration of DRC20 token minting into the <a href="https://dpalwallet.io/">Dpalwallet</a> software, which allows users to create their own Doginals.</p>
<p>Nonetheless, it&#8217;s important to note that DRC20s are still in their infancy, and the exact total supply of DRC20 tokens remains unknown. Furthermore, the absence of dedicated DRC20 marketplaces necessitates users to resort to over-the-counter (OTC) trades when buying or selling Doginals.</p>

<p>While the exact quantity of Doginal inscriptions minted on the Dogecoin network remains unknown, the network has been buzzing with a remarkable influx of daily transactions. <a href="https://blockchair.com/dogecoin/charts/transaction-count">Blockchair&#8217;s data</a> reveals that on May 17 alone, over 820,000 transactions have been confirmed so far, marking a new record for the meme coin network&#8217;s daily transaction volume. The surge in activity gained its initial momentum on May 10, and within a span of three days, daily DOGE transactions soared beyond the 600,000 and 700,000 marks.</p>

<p>The future of Doginal inscriptions, much like their Bitcoin Ordinal counterparts, remains to be seen in terms of sustained demand. However, the trend has shown remarkable resilience over the past week, reaching its peak. DRC20s, are a <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=DRC20&amp;src=typed_query&amp;f=top">hot topic</a> and have garnered significant attention on social media platforms like Twitter. The coming weeks will shed further light on whether this DRC20 token phenomenon can maintain its momentum.</p>
<p><em><strong>What are your thoughts on the rise of Doginals and the increasing daily transactions on the Dogecoin network? Share your insights and opinions about this subject in the comments section below. </strong></em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/drc20-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[#Dogecoin's DRC20 token standard has sparked a surge in daily transactions on the meme coin’s network. #DRC20 #DOGE]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA[#Dogecoin's DRC20 token standard has sparked a surge in daily transactions on the meme coin’s network. #DRC20 #DOGE]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stablecoin Issuer Tether Reveals Plan to Allocate Profits Into Bitcoin</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/stablecoin-issuer-tether-reveals-plan-to-allocate-profits-into-bitcoin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jamie Redman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 17:30:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[allocation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[attestation report]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[growth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[investment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Capitalization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[profits]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[reserves]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=588445</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ddddddc-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ddddddc-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ddddddc-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ddddddc-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ddddddc-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ddddddc-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ddddddc-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ddddddc.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />Tether, the stablecoin enterprise, has revealed its intention to devote 15% of its profits to bitcoin. The firm&#x2019;s announcement comes on the heels of Tether&#x2019;s recent attestation report, which emphasized the company&#x2019;s possession of bitcoin reserves worth $1.5 billion. Tether&#x2019;s Strategic Shift: Profits to Fuel Bitcoin Acquisition Tether, the company behind the crypto economy&#x2019;s largest [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ddddddc-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ddddddc-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ddddddc-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ddddddc-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ddddddc-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ddddddc-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ddddddc-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ddddddc.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>Tether, the stablecoin enterprise, has revealed its intention to devote 15% of its profits to bitcoin. The firm&#x2019;s announcement comes on the heels of Tether&#x2019;s recent attestation report, which emphasized the company&#x2019;s possession of bitcoin reserves worth $1.5 billion.</strong></p>
<h2>Tether&#x2019;s Strategic Shift: Profits to Fuel Bitcoin Acquisition</h2>
<p>Tether, the company behind the crypto economy&#x2019;s largest stablecoin asset, has unveiled its strategic vision to acquire bitcoin (<a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/BTC" 311996  target="_blank">BTC</a>) using its profits. &#x201C;Starting this month, Tether will regularly allocate up to 15% of its net realized operating profits towards purchasing bitcoin (<a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/BTC" 311996  target="_blank">BTC</a>),&#x201D; the firm detailed in a <a href="https://tether.to/en/tether-to-further-strengthen-reserves-through-purchase-of-bitcoin-with-realized-net-operating-profits/">blog post</a>. &#x201C;Tether anticipates that the current and future <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/BTC" 311996  target="_blank">BTC</a> holdings in its reserves will not exceed the Shareholder Capital Cushion and will further strengthen and diversify the reserves,&#x201D; the stablecoin issuer added.</p>
<p>Prior to the announcement, the company&#x2019;s latest <a href="https://tether.to/en/tethers-latest-q1-2023-assurance-report-shows-reserves-surplus-at-all-time-high-of-244b-up-148b-in-net-profit-new-categories-for-additional-transparency-reveals-bitcoin-and-gold-allocations/">attestation report</a> showcased its possession of $1.5 billion in bitcoin reserves. Notably, the report also indicated that a significant portion of Tether&#x2019;s reserves, amounting to $3.39 billion, is invested in precious metals. The company&#x2019;s announcement on Wednesday said that the investment underscores its confidence in bitcoin as a robust store of value. &#x201C;The decision to invest in bitcoin, the world&#x2019;s first and largest cryptocurrency, is underpinned by its strength and potential as an investment asset,&#x201D; Paolo Ardoino, Tether&#x2019;s CTO, said.</p>
<p>The Tether executive added:</p>
<blockquote><p>Bitcoin has continually proven its resilience and has emerged as a long-term store of value with substantial growth potential. Its limited supply, decentralized nature, and widespread adoption have positioned bitcoin as a favored choice among institutional and retail investors alike.</p></blockquote>

<p>Tether&#x2019;s announcement comes at a time when its stablecoin asset <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/USDT" target="_blank">USDT</a> is scaling toward <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/USDT" target="_blank">USDT</a>&#x2019;s peak market capitalization. On May 8, 2022, <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/USDT" target="_blank">USDT</a> achieved an all-time high (ATH) market cap of $83.279 billion. Presently, it stands awfully close to that ATH, valued at $82.67 billion. In a bid to sustain the growth trajectory of the stablecoin issuer, the company said its integration of bitcoin stands as a pivotal maneuver.</p>
<p>&#x201C;By incorporating Bitcoin into its investment strategy, Tether aims to capitalize on the digital asset&#x2019;s potential growth, while leveraging its position as a trusted and reliable financial infrastructure provider,&#x201D; Tether concluded on Wednesday.</p>
<p><em><strong>What are your thoughts on Tether&#x2019;s decision to allocate profits to Bitcoin and its potential impact on the stability of the crypto market? Share your insights and opinions in the comments section below. </strong></em></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ddddddc-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA["Its limited supply, decentralized nature, and widespread adoption have positioned #bitcoin as a favored choice," Paolo Ardoino, Tether’s CTO, said.]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA["Its limited supply, decentralized nature, and widespread adoption have positioned #bitcoin as a favored choice," Paolo Ardoino, Tether’s CTO, said.]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Harvard Business Review: Alchemy Pay, Crypto Payment Ecosystem Pioneer</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/harvard-business-review-alchemy-pay-crypto-payment-ecosystem-pioneer/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Media]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 15:45:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sponsored]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=587277&#038;preview=true&#038;preview_id=587277</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/06a637b6-9e89-46d5-80a4-0b3984ceb458-768x432.jpeg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/06a637b6-9e89-46d5-80a4-0b3984ceb458-300x169.jpeg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/06a637b6-9e89-46d5-80a4-0b3984ceb458-1024x576.jpeg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/06a637b6-9e89-46d5-80a4-0b3984ceb458-768x432.jpeg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/06a637b6-9e89-46d5-80a4-0b3984ceb458-190x107.jpeg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/06a637b6-9e89-46d5-80a4-0b3984ceb458-380x214.jpeg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/06a637b6-9e89-46d5-80a4-0b3984ceb458-760x428.jpeg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/06a637b6-9e89-46d5-80a4-0b3984ceb458.jpeg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />Introduction. When we discuss the future of the digital economy and real life in the next generation of the Internet, we are inevitably talking about Web 3.0. The future is unknown, but we have seen some tech companies already exploring and deepening on their tracks, such as Alchemy Pay, mentioned in this article. We will [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/06a637b6-9e89-46d5-80a4-0b3984ceb458-768x432.jpeg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/06a637b6-9e89-46d5-80a4-0b3984ceb458-300x169.jpeg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/06a637b6-9e89-46d5-80a4-0b3984ceb458-1024x576.jpeg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/06a637b6-9e89-46d5-80a4-0b3984ceb458-768x432.jpeg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/06a637b6-9e89-46d5-80a4-0b3984ceb458-190x107.jpeg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/06a637b6-9e89-46d5-80a4-0b3984ceb458-380x214.jpeg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/06a637b6-9e89-46d5-80a4-0b3984ceb458-760x428.jpeg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/06a637b6-9e89-46d5-80a4-0b3984ceb458.jpeg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><b>Introduction. </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">When we discuss the future of the digital economy and real life in the next generation of the Internet, we are inevitably talking about Web 3.0. The future is unknown, but we have seen some tech companies already exploring and deepening on their tracks, such as Alchemy Pay, mentioned in this article.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">We will analyze the targeted strategies and measures it has taken in the crypto payment space, taking into account the company&#x2019;s sustainable long-term goals while building a rich crypto payment ecosystem that is prepared for the Web 3.0 vision with its mission of bridging fiat and crypto global economies. These measures are very informative and should be considered by other company leaders.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Once seen by mainstream zeitgeist as a fringe technology destined to die out in society, cryptocurrency is now becoming a target of investment for countless fintech industry leaders since the powerful financial future it portrays. The proliferation of crypto payment platforms and users is driving the entire ecosystem closer to mainstream adoption. As more and more large financial companies enter the crypto payment space, the competition in this field is becoming increasingly fierce. Alchemy Pay, an industry veteran with extensive industry experience and solid product technology, is performing exceptionally well in this track on all fronts. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Founded in Singapore in 2017, the payment gateway that seamlessly connects cryptocurrencies and global fiat currencies for businesses, developers and users has walked a long way. It took less than 5 years to become the number one project with payment concept in the DeFi space and the leading crypto payment solution and technology provider in the Asia Pacific region. Alchemy Pay currently supports payments from 173 countries, including using Visa, Mastercard, Discover, Diners Club, Google Pay, Apple Pay, popular regional mobile wallets, and domestic bank transfers to purchase crypto, providing a fast, secure and convenient solution for over 2 million online and offline merchants with aggregated cryptocurrency and fiat payment technology. In 2021, ACH, Alchemy Pay&#x2019;s token issued on Ethereum and <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/BNB" 312009  target="_blank">BNB</a> Chain, listed on Coinbase, the world&#x2019;s largest compliant trading platform, continued to rise with an initial bottom of $0.001762 and rose over 13620.8% in the week after listing. How did Alchemy Pay achieve such an impressive performance in such a short period of time? </span></p>
<p><b>Layout in Advance to Gain Differentiated and Competitive Advantages</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Shawn Shi, co-founder of Alchemy Pay, has a keen eye for capturing industry trends and assessing business potential. He saw the trend in the crypto payment field, found a head start in it, and boldly took the lead. The series of milestone decisions taken by Alchemy Pay are not only unique, but have built differentiated and competitive advantages that have kept it at the forefront of the competition. These milestone decisions are focused on three main areas:  </span></p>
<p><b>Internationalization.</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> Strategic placement has a direct impact on the survival and growth of a business. While competitors were still working on their local strategies and businesses, Alchemy Pay has recognized the importance of competing on an international strategy and thoughtfully chose a different set of approaches from its competitors. In its second year of establishment, Alchemy Pay incorporated an international strategy into its development plan to create a unique value. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Alchemy Pay was founded at a time when mobile payments were at their best, but the entire payment network was almost monopolized by VISA and Mastercard, which deprived traditional merchants of many options. Therefore, Alchemy Pay decided to create a payment system that would connect the entire network and develop the most adaptable digital currency solution that would seamlessly integrate crypto payments with fiat payments, providing payment services and derivative financial solutions to global merchants and users in the crypto ecosystem.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In this context, Alchemy Pay has been building a global team since its foundation and has established a advisory board management system in line with the company&#x2019;s needs, implementing the corporate management philosophy of &#x201C;leaving the professional to the professionals&#x201D; and working together with experts worldwide from various industries to contribute to the global development of Alchemy Pay. David Plouffe, the former White House Senior Advisor and Obama&#x2019;s campaign manager, has recently joined the Alchemy Pay team, serving as a committee member of management and advisory board, and as Global Strategic Advisor to support strategy, compliance and government relations.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In addition to the European and American markets, Alchemy Pay also explored and developed the payment market in South East Asia and Latin America based on market demand research, achieving the highest market share in the industry. Alchemy Pay is built as a payment gateway that seamlessly converts the assets of both parties to a transaction, regardless of whether the user is paying in fiat or crypto currency. Its product experience on the user side was simple and smooth, and its professionalism was way ahead of its Asian competitors at the time.</span></p>
<p><a href="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/unnamed-91.png?X-Amz-Content-Sha256=UNSIGNED-PAYLOAD&X-Amz-Algorithm=AWS4-HMAC-SHA256&X-Amz-Credential=AKIAYIWLWC3GPQWL5SMB%2F20230517%2Fus-east-1%2Fs3%2Faws4_request&X-Amz-Date=20230517T123626Z&X-Amz-SignedHeaders=host&X-Amz-Expires=600&X-Amz-Signature=fa906373a572a5fae2996fbf25a124995f5a185c876887052580bec070852f20"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium_large wp-image-588386" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/unnamed-91-768x334.png" alt="" width="768" height="334" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/unnamed-91-300x130.png 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/unnamed-91-1024x445.png 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/unnamed-91-768x334.png 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/unnamed-91-1536x667.png 1536w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/unnamed-91.png 1600w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px"></a></p>
<p><b>Compliance.</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> While advancing its global market strategy, Alchemy Pay has recognized the importance of localized payments before its competitors. By continuously integrating localized payment methods such as e-wallets, Alchemy Pay is now able to support over 300 localized payment methods to meet the payment habits of local users and make it quicker for users to purchase crypto and Web 3.0 services using fiat currency. In the localization process, any actions involving financial and securities transactions and services are subject to local financial and securities laws and regulations. Although many countries allow cryptocurrency investment and trading, the related industries face stricter regulations.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">While competitors try to avoid compliance constraints to reduce costs, Alchemy Pay believes that the only way to be sustainable is to adhere to the bottom line of compliance. With more and more countries introducing laws and regulations on data security protection and raising new requirements for the globalization of payment systems, greater data security and privacy protection is becoming a global trend.  Alchemy Pay has been practicing the local compliance requirements in different countries and regions according to the specific situation, actively applying for licenses and landing business.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In addition to regulatory factors, the entry of companies and financial institutions has placed higher demands on cryptocurrency security and compliance, so licensed platforms have a distinct advantage in this regard. To date, less than 1% of web3 companies in the crypto payment industry have a license, but Alchemy Pay already has a large number of compliant licenses and payment channels. Currently, Alchemy Pay has obtained the 1,4,9 financial services license from the Hong Kong Securities and Futures Commission, the license from the Central Bank of Indonesia to operate remittances and fund transfers, the MSB license in the US and Canada, and Lithuanian Cryptocurrency Exchange & Wallet License</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">, while Alchemy Pay is also applying for MSO in Hong Kong, MTL in the US, DPT in Singapore and EMI in the UK. Alchemy Pay is acutely aware of the need to expand the touchpoint to every market in terms of payments, not only to keep an eye on policy trends and changes from regulators, but also to work with local banks. This is a very slow process but is critical to creating a secure and compliant payment experience for users.</span></p>
<p><b>Cash flow. </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">As Alchemy Pay moves forward with compliance and license applications in different countries, it has found that the compliance standards in Europe and the US are relatively clear, while in most other countries the laws and regulations are less clear. In such a dynamic and uncertain environment, the development of crypto business is bound to encounter some barriers, from which it is a long-term process to find a path to compliance or to establish partnerships to unify mutual understanding.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">At the same time, the whole business operation and ecological construction will also take a lot of time and cost. Because fiat currencies and crypto currencies, which are the products of two financial systems, the conversion process is sometimes delayed, and a deposit of fiat and crypto funds is formed in between. To avoid users waiting, Alchemy Pay will complete the conversion by paying itself&#x2013;a process that involves the act of advancing different funds. For this reason, Alchemy Pay proposes to prepare the cash flow in advance. This move not only ensures compliance operations and smooth payment systems, but also prepares itself for weathering the bear market smoothly.</span></p>
<p><b>Thinking Backwards, Exploring New Needs and Innovations</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Co-founder Shawn Shi said the Alchemy Pay team tends to think backwards in its decision-making process, agreeing that it should not limit its thinking to the direction it would normally consider, but rather challenge inertia and look at the needs of marginal users or former non-users. In Alchemy Pay&#x2019;s view, the needs of this group of people are often ignored as noise and thus become a missed opportunity for companies to advance their business. The rage for cryptocurrencies is bound to push businesses into the next phase of the internet Web 3.0 &#x2013; an internet ecosystem built on blockchain, crypto wallets, non-homogenous tokens (NFT) and decentralized autonomous organizations (DAO) &#x2013; and Alchemy Pay is no exception.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">But unlike other companies that have entered the Web 3.0 space in full swing, Alchemy Pay felt the need to pause and think about how these technological developments might affect business and how to solve the payment challenges of people who have difficulty using conventional services, design innovative solutions for them and tap into the broader market. As a result, Alchemy Pay decided to go against the trend and go back to Web2 or Web2.5, identifying exactly those unmet needs and choosing financial institution partners that are more Web2-friendly, thus significantly broadening its reach.</span></p>
<p><a href="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/unnamed-92.png?X-Amz-Content-Sha256=UNSIGNED-PAYLOAD&X-Amz-Algorithm=AWS4-HMAC-SHA256&X-Amz-Credential=AKIAYIWLWC3GPQWL5SMB%2F20230517%2Fus-east-1%2Fs3%2Faws4_request&X-Amz-Date=20230517T123755Z&X-Amz-SignedHeaders=host&X-Amz-Expires=600&X-Amz-Signature=23bfdfb1b728d549a39e0626d73a7383b7b54ceb58d9ec7df9d25d74ffce16b0"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium_large wp-image-588387" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/unnamed-92-768x311.png" alt="" width="768" height="311" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/unnamed-92-300x122.png 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/unnamed-92-1024x415.png 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/unnamed-92-768x311.png 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/unnamed-92-1536x622.png 1536w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/unnamed-92.png 1600w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px"></a></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Alchemy Pay believes that in order to find out where the customers are, it is necessary to focus on demographic and market trends, as the payment business is determined by user needs. Based on a large user base and user needs, Alchemy Pay has created its unique advantage &#x201C;easy to use and highly adaptable&#x201D;, which is compatible with all major forms of payment (POS, APP, Web, etc.) and all major wallets, and is adaptable to all major scenarios of payment solutions ( Apple Pay, Google Pay, national e-mobile wallets, etc.). This means that Alchemy Pay already meets the majority of users&#x2019; habits and further breaks the barrier between traditional payment methods and cryptocurrencies.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Alchemy Pay also meets the needs of most offline retail, e-commerce, online entertainment, bulk trading, supply chain finance, cross-border trading and other merchants, and further reduces their cost of use and improves transaction efficiency (traditional methods usually settle on the next day and charge high fees). ACH token is a value hub in its payment ecosystem, and it acts as an intermediate reconciliation token in the consensus protocol of the blockchain payment network, and can also be used to offset fees and receive various priority benefits. In the future, ACH is also expected to be the primary DAO governance pass in Alchemy Pay.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Payments, in fact, were the function of the earliest cryptocurrencies, such as Bitcoin and Litecoin, which all aimed to create a peer-to-peer, decentralized, open, transparent and irreversible payment ecology. In this ecology, users can make peer-to-peer asset transfers, which are simultaneously packaged by nodes and agreed by the whole network, which is considered a successful transaction. Due to this feature, cryptocurrencies have a theoretical potential for payments. Unlike the traditional Internet fiat payment system, which is already well established, the crypto industry and its online payments space is still in its early days due to credibility and infrastructure issues. The emergence of Alchemy Pay has built a bridge between the fiat and crypto payment shafts, on the basis of which cryptocurrencies are beginning to be accepted by traditional financial institutions. Alchemy Pay&#x2019;s vision is to create a global cryptocurrency payment scenario, connecting fiat and cryptocurrencies globally, and aspires to be the next generation of payment infrastructure. The payment ecosystem and infrastructure it has built is expected to deeply integrate cryptocurrencies with traditional commerce. As the richness of the ecosystem increases and the integrity of the ecosystem matures, Alchemy Pay&#x2019;s growth in the future is unlimited.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Source: </span><a href="https://www.hbrchina.org/2023-05-16/9524.html"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Harvard Business Review</span></a></p>
<p>&#xA0;</p>
<p>&#xA0;</p>
<p>&#xA0;</p>
<h2 style="text-align: center;"></h2>
<hr>
<p><small><em>This is a sponsored post. Learn how to reach our audience <a href="https://www.bitcoin.com/advertise/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">here</a>. Read disclaimer below.</em></small></p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/06a637b6-9e89-46d5-80a4-0b3984ceb458-760x428.jpeg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[Harvard Business Review: Alchemy Pay, Crypto Payment Ecosystem Pioneer]]></bnmedia:barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Biggest Movers: DOGE, XRP Hit 1-Week Highs, Despite Wednesday’s Crypto Red Wave</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/biggest-movers-doge-xrp-hit-1-week-highs-despite-wednesdays-crypto-red-wave/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Eliman Dambell]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 15:42:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Doge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=588409</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/shutterstock_2101155841-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/shutterstock_2101155841-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/shutterstock_2101155841-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/shutterstock_2101155841-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/shutterstock_2101155841-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/shutterstock_2101155841-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/shutterstock_2101155841-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/shutterstock_2101155841.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />Dogecoin rose to a one-week high on Wednesday, despite cryptocurrency markets mostly moving lower. As of writing, the global crypto market cap is trading nearly 1% lower. Xrp also surged, climbing by over 6% in today&#x2019;s session. Dogecoin (DOGE) Dogecoin (DOGE) was able to climb to a one-week high in today&#x2019;s session, despite markets mostly [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/shutterstock_2101155841-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/shutterstock_2101155841-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/shutterstock_2101155841-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/shutterstock_2101155841-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/shutterstock_2101155841-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/shutterstock_2101155841-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/shutterstock_2101155841-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/shutterstock_2101155841.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>Dogecoin rose to a one-week high on Wednesday, despite cryptocurrency markets mostly moving lower. As of writing, the global crypto market cap is trading nearly 1% lower. Xrp also surged, climbing by over 6% in today&#x2019;s session.</strong></p>
<h2>Dogecoin (DOGE)</h2>
<p>Dogecoin (DOGE) was able to climb to a one-week high in today&#x2019;s session, despite markets mostly trending lower.</p>
<p>Following a low of $0.07177 on Tuesday, DOGE/USD raced to an intraday high of $0.07422 earlier in the day.</p>
<p>Today&#x2019;s rally saw dogecoin climb for a second straight session, which pushed the meme coin to its highest point since May 8.</p>

<p>As a result of the move, the 14-day relative strength index (RSI) collided with a key resistance level of 40.00.</p>
<p>Although the index has moved marginally above this point, and is currently tracking at 40.40, DOGE has lost slight momentum.</p>
<p>The meme coin is now trading at $0.073, which is relatively lower than today&#x2019;s earlier high.</p>

<h2><a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/XRP" 311999  target="_blank">XRP</a></h2>
<p>Another notable gainer on Wednesday was <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/XRP" 311999  target="_blank">XRP</a>, formerly ripple, which rose by as much as 6% today.</p>
<p><a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/XRP" 311999  target="_blank">XRP</a>/USD rose to a peak at $0.4596 earlier in the day, which follows on from a low of $0.4202 during yesterday&#x2019;s session.</p>
<p>This has resulted in the token climbing for a fourth consecutive day, reaching its strongest level since May 7.</p>

<p>Looking at the chart, and similar to DOGE, a collision has occurred on the RSI, with a failure to break a wall at 48.00.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, price strength is at the 47.33 mark, with the price now at $0.4457.</p>
<p>Should this point be broken, there is a good chance that <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/XRP" 311999  target="_blank">XRP</a> could be heading to a resistance of $0.48350.</p>
<p><em>Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:</em></p>
<p><em><strong>Do you expect xrp to climb higher this week? Let us know your thoughts in the comments.</strong></em></p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/shutterstock_2101155841-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[#DOGE jumps to 1-week high, #XRP up 6% on Wednesday.]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA[#DOGE jumps to 1-week high, #XRP up 6% on Wednesday.]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ledger Faces Backlash for Controversial Backup Tool as Crypto Community Expresses Discontent</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/ledger-faces-backlash-for-controversial-backup-tool-as-crypto-community-expresses-discontent/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jamie Redman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 14:23:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alternative solutions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[backlash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto community]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[discontent]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[encrypted key fragments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[frustration]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hardware Wallet Manufacturer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ledger]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[new feature]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[seed phrases]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social media platforms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[third-party firms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tool]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=588179</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/jo4od88f900e-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Ledger Faces Backlash for Controversial Backup Tool as Crypto Community Expresses Discontent" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/jo4od88f900e-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/jo4od88f900e-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/jo4od88f900e-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/jo4od88f900e-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/jo4od88f900e-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/jo4od88f900e-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/jo4od88f900e.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />Hardware wallet maker Ledger is facing significant backlash for its recent introduction of a tool enabling users to back up their seed phrases through the transmission of encrypted key fragments to third-party firms. The crypto community has not embraced this new feature, with numerous digital currency users venting their frustration on social media platforms. Ledger&#8217;s [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/jo4od88f900e-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Ledger Faces Backlash for Controversial Backup Tool as Crypto Community Expresses Discontent" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/jo4od88f900e-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/jo4od88f900e-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/jo4od88f900e-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/jo4od88f900e-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/jo4od88f900e-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/jo4od88f900e-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/jo4od88f900e.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>Hardware wallet maker Ledger is facing significant backlash for its recent introduction of a tool enabling users to back up their seed phrases through the transmission of encrypted key fragments to third-party firms. The crypto community has not embraced this new feature, with numerous digital currency users venting their frustration on social media platforms.</strong></p>
<h2>Ledger&#8217;s Backup Tool Sparks Outrage in Crypto Circles</h2>
<p>In a recent move, hardware wallet manufacturer Ledger unveiled their latest tool, Ledger Recover. Unfortunately, the reception within the crypto community has been far from positive.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-588188 size-full" title="Ledger Faces Backlash for Controversial Backup Tool as Crypto Community Expresses Discontent" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/cz.jpg" alt="Ledger Faces Backlash for Controversial Backup Tool as Crypto Community Expresses Discontent" width="1280" height="550" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/cz-300x129.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/cz-1024x440.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/cz-768x330.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/cz.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 1280px) 100vw, 1280px" /></p>
<p>“Ledger Recover is an optional subscription for users who want a backup of their Secret Recovery Phrase,” the company <a href="https://twitter.com/Ledger/status/1658458714771169282?s=20">stated</a> on May 16. “You don’t have to use it, and can continue managing your recovery phrase yourself if that’s why you bought a Ledger.”</p>
<p>By utilizing Ledger Recover, users have the option to divide their seed into three encrypted shards, each containing a portion of the private key. These encrypted fragments are subsequently entrusted to third-party companies for secure storage. The hardware wallet company <a href="https://twitter.com/Ledger/status/1658458726016204800?s=20">explains</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>Ledger Recover encrypts a version of your private key and splits it into three fragments (using Shamir Secret Sharing) &#8211; all of this happens on the Secure Element chip, so your Secret Recovery Phrase is not at risk. These encrypted fragments are stored by 3 different parties on cryptographically-secure Hardware Security Modules.</p></blockquote>
<p>The announcement sparked a significant wave of discontent among cryptocurrency users. “Epic Fail,” one user <a href="https://twitter.com/BitcoinBazis/status/1658488119023538181?s=20">responded</a> to Ledger’s announcement on Tuesday. Bitcoin proponent Alistair Milne <a href="https://twitter.com/alistairmilne/status/1658381708763209729?s=20">told</a> his 126,000 Twitter followers: “Sure, you *could* use Ledger&#8217;s new &#8216;Recover&#8217; service and give them your private keys controlling your assets as well as a copy of your ID and other personal information … but why bother with a hardware wallet in the first place?”</p>
<p>By 4:00 p.m. Eastern Time on Tuesday, the name &#8220;Ledger&#8221; had surged in popularity, garnering 224,000 tweets in the Business and Finance category on Twitter. Notably, Mudit Gupta, an executive at Polygon Labs, vehemently criticized the recovery tool service.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-588192 size-full" title="Ledger Faces Backlash for Controversial Backup Tool as Crypto Community Expresses Discontent" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ddssdddssddds.jpg" alt="Ledger Faces Backlash for Controversial Backup Tool as Crypto Community Expresses Discontent" width="1280" height="250" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ddssdddssddds-300x59.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ddssdddssddds-1024x200.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ddssdddssddds-768x150.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ddssdddssddds.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 1280px) 100vw, 1280px" /></p>
<p>“Ledger just released a new update for Nano X that allows social recovery of your seed phrase,” Gupta <a href="https://twitter.com/Mudit__Gupta/status/1658368265687556097?s=20">said</a>. “It encrypts your seed in 3 shards and sends it to different entities that can then reconstruct the seed for you post ID verification. It&#8217;s a horrendous idea, DON&#8217;T enable this feature.”</p>

<p>The Twitter user Foobar <a href="https://twitter.com/0xfoobar/status/1658460603831263232?s=20">told</a> his 131,000 Twitter followers to boycott Ledger products. “Stop using Ledger hardware wallets,” Foobar tweeted. “Migrate away from them immediately. They’ve shown nothing but gross incompetence and wild misunderstanding of their own purpose. And now they’ve publicly admitted to intentionally backdooring their own proprietary hardware. Stop using Ledger.”</p>
<p>Ledger was also <a href="https://twitter.com/Pledditor/status/1658524159721209898?s=20">accused</a> of deleting a tweet that it added to the announcement thread. “I have personally used Ledger hardware wallets for about 7 years. Today is the first day I&#8217;ve decided to look elsewhere,” the Youtuber Colin Talks Crypto <a href="https://twitter.com/ColinTCrypto/status/1658539290245095425?s=20">told</a> his Twitter followers on Tuesday.</p>
<p><em><strong>What are your thoughts on Ledger&#8217;s controversial backup tool? Do you believe there are better alternatives available, or do you see potential in this approach? Share your insights and opinions in the comments section below.</strong></em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/jo4od88f900e-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[Hardware wallet maker Ledger's announcement sparked a significant wave of discontent among #cryptocurrency users.]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA[Hardware wallet maker Ledger's announcement sparked a significant wave of discontent among #cryptocurrency users.]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin, Ethereum Technical Analysis: BTC Drops Below $27,000 as US Debt Ceiling Fears Grip Markets</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-ethereum-technical-analysis-btc-drops-below-27000-as-us-debt-ceiling-fears-grip-markets/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Eliman Dambell]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 12:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[debt ceiling]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technical Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=588359</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/shutterstock_1251778627-1-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/shutterstock_1251778627-1-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/shutterstock_1251778627-1-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/shutterstock_1251778627-1-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/shutterstock_1251778627-1-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/shutterstock_1251778627-1-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/shutterstock_1251778627-1-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/shutterstock_1251778627-1.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />Bitcoin fell below the $27,000 level on May 17, as market uncertainty remained high amidst the debt ceiling crisis in the United States. Congress continues to negotiate terms of a potential increase to the limit, before the U.S. government runs out of cash on June 1. Ethereum also dropped, breaking out of the $1,800 level. [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/shutterstock_1251778627-1-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/shutterstock_1251778627-1-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/shutterstock_1251778627-1-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/shutterstock_1251778627-1-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/shutterstock_1251778627-1-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/shutterstock_1251778627-1-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/shutterstock_1251778627-1-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/shutterstock_1251778627-1.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>Bitcoin fell below the $27,000 level on May 17, as market uncertainty remained high amidst the debt ceiling crisis in the United States. Congress continues to negotiate terms of a potential increase to the limit, before the U.S. government runs out of cash on June 1. Ethereum also dropped, breaking out of the $1,800 level.</strong></p>
<h2>Bitcoin</h2>
<p>Bitcoin (<a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/BTC" 311996  target="_blank">BTC</a>) moved below the $27,000 level on Wednesday, following yesterday&#x2019;s U.S. Retail Sales report.</p>
<p><a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/BTC" 311996  target="_blank">BTC</a>/USD moved to a low of $26,785.41 earlier in today&#x2019;s session, which was following Tuesday&#x2019;s peak at $27,223.07.</p>
<p>Today&#x2019;s sell-off comes as bitcoin was unable to move beyond its key price ceiling at the $27,300 mark, leading to a shift in bearish sentiment.</p>
<div class="tradingview-widget-container">
<div class="tradingview-widget-copyright"><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/?exchange=BITSTAMP" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span class="blue-text">Bitcoin chart</span></a> by TradingView</div>
<p><script type="text/javascript" src="https://s3.tradingview.com/tv.js"></script><script type="text/javascript">
  new TradingView.widget(
  {
  "width": "100%",
  "height": "400",
  "symbol": "BITSTAMP:BTCUSD",
  "interval": "D",
  "timezone": "Etc/UTC",
  "theme": "light",
  "style": "1",
  "locale": "en",
  "toolbar_bg": "#F1F3F6",
  "enable_publishing": false,
  "container_id": "tradingview_1247e"
}
  );
  </script></p>
</div>
<p><!-- TradingView Widget END --></p>
<p>Looking at the chart, the decline also coincided with the 14-day relative strength index (RSI) failing to break its point of resistance at 42.00.</p>
<p>As of writing, price strength is tracking at 38.08, and seems to be heading close to a support zone of 36.00.</p>
<p>Should this point be reached, then there is a strong possibility that <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/BTC" 311996  target="_blank">BTC</a> could slip below $26,000.</p>

<h2>Ethereum</h2>
<p>In addition to <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/BTC" 311996  target="_blank">BTC</a>, ethereum (<a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/ETH" target="_blank">ETH</a>) also trended lower, falling under the $1,800 level in today&#x2019;s session.</p>
<p>Following a high of $1,835.55 on Tuesday, <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/ETH" target="_blank">ETH</a>/USD plunged to an intraday low of $1,792.08 earlier in the day.</p>
<p>As a result of today&#x2019;s drop in price, ethereum neared a long-term floor of $1,790, which is where price has retreated to during the past week.</p>
<div class="tradingview-widget-container">
<div class="tradingview-widget-copyright"><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ETHUSD/?exchange=BITSTAMP" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span class="blue-text">Ethereum chart</span></a> by TradingView</div>
<p><script type="text/javascript" src="https://s3.tradingview.com/tv.js"></script><script type="text/javascript">
  new TradingView.widget(
  {
  "width": "100%",
  "height": "400",
  "symbol": "BITSTAMP:ETHUSD",
  "interval": "D",
  "timezone": "Etc/UTC",
  "theme": "light",
  "style": "1",
  "locale": "en",
  "toolbar_bg": "#F1F3F6",
  "enable_publishing": false,
  "container_id": "tradingview_1247e"
}
  );
  </script></p>
</div>
<p><!-- TradingView Widget END --></p>
<p>Similar to <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/BTC" 311996  target="_blank">BTC</a>, the RSI here is also edging closer to a floor of its own, which in this instance is at the 41.00 point.</p>
<p>Price strength, which is currently at the 41.97 level, was unable to breach a resistance zone of 47.00, leading to today&#x2019;s drop-off.</p>
<p>There is a good chance that <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/ETH" target="_blank">ETH</a> could change course in the upcoming days, providing the floor at 41.00 remains firm.</p>
<p><em>Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:</em></p>
<p><em><strong>What else is behind today&#x2019;s drop in crypto prices? Leave your thoughts in the comments below.</strong></em></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/shutterstock_1251778627-1-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[#BTC slips below $27,000 on Wednesday, as US debt ceiling uncertainty worries markets.]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA[#BTC slips below $27,000 on Wednesday, as US debt ceiling uncertainty worries markets.]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin.com Wallet Celebrates Major Milestone With 40 Million Crypto Wallets Created</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-com-wallet-celebrates-major-milestone-with-40-million-crypto-wallets-created/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bitcoin.com]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 10:35:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Promoted]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin.com Wallet]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=588216</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/40m-news-768x432.png" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/40m-news-300x169.png 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/40m-news-1024x576.png 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/40m-news-768x432.png 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/40m-news-1536x864.png 1536w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/40m-news-2048x1152.png 2048w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/40m-news-190x107.png 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/40m-news-380x214.png 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/40m-news-760x428.png 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/40m-news-1520x855.png 1520w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/40m-news-1280x720.png 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />Bitcoin.com is proud to announce that it has reached a significant milestone in its mission to increase the adoption of cryptocurrency worldwide: the creation of the 40 millionth crypto wallet in the multi-chain, DeFi-ready Bitcoin.com Wallet. Since its inception in June 2017, the Bitcoin.com Wallet has seen a rapid rise in user adoption, reflecting the [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/40m-news-768x432.png" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/40m-news-300x169.png 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/40m-news-1024x576.png 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/40m-news-768x432.png 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/40m-news-1536x864.png 1536w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/40m-news-2048x1152.png 2048w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/40m-news-190x107.png 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/40m-news-380x214.png 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/40m-news-760x428.png 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/40m-news-1520x855.png 1520w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/40m-news-1280x720.png 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Bitcoin.com is proud to announce that it has reached a significant milestone in its mission to increase the adoption of cryptocurrency worldwide: the creation of the 40 millionth crypto wallet in the multi-chain, DeFi-ready </span><a href="https://wallet.bitcoin.com"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Bitcoin.com Wallet</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Since its inception in June 2017, the Bitcoin.com Wallet has seen a rapid rise in user adoption, reflecting the increasing acceptance and adoption of cryptocurrency around the globe.</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
</span></p>
<p><a href="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/40m-chart-news.png?X-Amz-Content-Sha256=UNSIGNED-PAYLOAD&amp;X-Amz-Algorithm=AWS4-HMAC-SHA256&amp;X-Amz-Credential=AKIAYIWLWC3GPQWL5SMB%2F20230517%2Fus-east-1%2Fs3%2Faws4_request&amp;X-Amz-Date=20230517T084425Z&amp;X-Amz-SignedHeaders=host&amp;X-Amz-Expires=600&amp;X-Amz-Signature=e28fe2b71fda5248b90db671fdbb49d96740c8c5713a5e756fde1a109ae14430"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-588222" title="Bitcoin.com Wallet Celebrates Major Milestone With 40 Million Crypto Wallets Created" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/40m-chart-news.png" alt="Bitcoin.com Wallet Celebrates Major Milestone With 40 Million Crypto Wallets Created" width="2560" height="1440" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/40m-chart-news-300x169.png 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/40m-chart-news-1024x576.png 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/40m-chart-news-768x432.png 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/40m-chart-news-1536x864.png 1536w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/40m-chart-news-2048x1152.png 2048w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/40m-chart-news-190x107.png 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/40m-chart-news-380x214.png 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/40m-chart-news-760x428.png 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/40m-chart-news-1520x855.png 1520w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/40m-chart-news-1280x720.png 1280w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/40m-chart-news.png 2560w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It took nearly two years for Bitcoin.com to reach its first five million wallets. In contrast, the recent fifteen million wallets have been created in just a year and a half, reflecting a dramatic increase in the pace of adoption.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Bitcoin.com CEO Dennis Jarvis commented, &#8220;We are extremely proud of the progress we&#8217;ve made since the Wallet’s launch in 2017. The growth and adoption rate we&#8217;ve seen is a testament to the increasing acceptance of cryptocurrencies. It&#8217;s not just about the numbers – these 40 million wallets represent individuals and businesses who are embracing the freedom, inclusivity, and innovation that cryptocurrency offers.&#8221;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Bitcoin.com Wallet has been at the forefront of the crypto revolution, providing a secure, easy-to-use platform for users to buy, sell, trade, and manage a variety of crypto assets. The success of the platform is a result of the company&#8217;s unwavering commitment to making cryptocurrency accessible and user-friendly.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Bitcoin.com Head of Financial Services Corbin Fraser added, “As we look to the future, we remain committed to ensuring that the Bitcoin.com Wallet continues to be a trusted, accessible, and powerful tool for Bitcoin and crypto users worldwide. To that end, we’re excited to be integrating our rewards and utility token VERSE, which will supercharge crypto adoption by making it easier than ever for newcomers.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As Bitcoin.com celebrates this milestone, the company wants to express its deepest gratitude to all its users. Their belief in the potential of cryptocurrency and their trust in the Bitcoin.com Wallet have been instrumental in the platform&#8217;s success.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">To show appreciation and to further promote crypto adoption, Bitcoin.com is hosting a </span><a href="https://medium.com/bitcoin-com/stake-to-win-10-000-in-prizes-f9f206f92a52"><span style="font-weight: 400;">$10K giveaway</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> and invites everyone to join in and help onboard the world to crypto and DeFi.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/40m-news-760x428.png</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[Bitcoin․com Wallet Celebrates Major Milestone with 40 Million Crypto Wallets Created]]></bnmedia:barker_title>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
