<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Magazine - Bitcoin News, Articles and Expert Insights]]></title><description><![CDATA[Established in 2012, Bitcoin Magazine is the oldest and most established source of trustworthy news, information and thought leadership on Bitcoin.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com</link><image><url>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/site/images/apple-touch-icon.png</url><title>Bitcoin Magazine - Bitcoin News, Articles and Expert Insights</title><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com</link></image><generator>Tempest</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 06:20:23 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.rss/full/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 06:20:23 GMT</pubDate><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><atom:link href="https://pubsubhubbub.appspot.com/" rel="hub"/><item><title><![CDATA[Bankrupt Lending Platform Celsius Agrees To Purchase Bid By Fahrenheit]]></title><description><![CDATA[A new company will be formed by the acquisition of embattled lender Celsius, which went bankrupt amidst the larger turmoil of 2022.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/celsius-agrees-to-purchase-bid-by-fahrenheit</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/celsius-agrees-to-purchase-bid-by-fahrenheit</guid><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[Celsius network]]></category><category><![CDATA[Bankruptcy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Business]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[BtcCasey]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 20:38:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkxNDAxMTQ0NTc1MDc1ODcz/border-wallets-seed-phrase-recovery-top-photo.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p>Bankrupt lending platform Celsius Network LLC has announced that it has selected a proposal by Fahrenheit as the winning bid to lead the company out of bankruptcy, according to reporting by <a href="https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/crypto-lender-celsius-picks-fahrenheits-bid-bankruptcy-exit-2023-05-25/">Reuters</a>.</p><p>Celsius, which filed for <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/celsius-files-for-chapter-11-bankruptcy">Chapter 11 protection in July</a>, sought a buyer to manage its cryptocurrency lending and bitcoin mining businesses. The chosen consortium, Fahrenheit, includes Arrington Capital, a blockchain-based venture capital firm. In addition to the consortium acquiring the company, a new board of directors, primarily appointed by creditors, will oversee the new company formed as a result of the purchase.</p><p>Celsius also revealed that it has secured a backup bid from the Blockchain Recovery Investment Consortium (BRIC), a holding company affiliated with Gemini Trust, owned by the Winklevoss twins, ensuring an alternative option in case the deal with Fahrenheit falls through.</p><p>According to Celsius, Fahrenheit will provide the necessary capital, management expertise, and technology to navigate the bankruptcy. The consortium's selection indicates a potential positive outcome for Celsius and its creditors, allowing the company to move forward under new management and ownership.</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkxNDAxMTQ0NTc1MDc1ODcz/border-wallets-seed-phrase-recovery-top-photo.png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Payments App Bottlepay To Shutdown Services]]></title><description><![CDATA[The company is encouraging users to withdraw their funds and to save transaction statements before the app’s closure.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/bitcoin-payments-app-bottlepay-to-shutdown-services</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/bitcoin-payments-app-bottlepay-to-shutdown-services</guid><category><![CDATA[Business]]></category><category><![CDATA[Payments]]></category><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[Bottlepay]]></category><category><![CDATA[Apps]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[BtcCasey]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 17:36:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk0MzI5NzY4OTU4MTA5MzYx/bitcoin-code.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p><a href="https://bottlepay.com/">Bottlepay</a>, a popular consumer app for Bitcoin transactions, has <a href="https://help.bottlepay.com/en/articles/7902589-the-bottlepay-app-is-closing-down">announced</a> its closure on Monday, July 24, 2023, leaving users with the task of withdrawing their funds. The company stated that all accounts will be closed, and users are urged to withdraw their funds either as Bitcoin or fiat currency (GBP/EUR) from the Bottlepay app before the closure date.&nbsp;</p><p>Failure to withdraw funds by the closure date will result in Bitcoin being converted to fiat currency and returned to the nominated bank account, while any fiat left in the account will be returned to the nominated bank account as well.</p><p>In a statement, Bottlepay advised users to utilize the app's downloads feature to save transaction statements before the closure date. The company emphasized that Bitcoin transactions can have tax implications, making the downloaded information valuable for future reference. As the closure date approaches, Bottlepay may contact users who still have Bitcoin or fiat currency in their accounts, either through the app or via email. However, the company cautioned users to be aware of potential scams and never initiate an offboarding process outside of the app.</p><p>Regarding the next steps, users are advised to download their transaction history and close their Bottlepay accounts. Instructions on how to withdraw funds from Bitcoin and fiat accounts, as well as how to download transaction history and close accounts, can be found on the app.</p><p>In a closing note, Bottlepay expressed gratitude to its customers and apologized for the inconvenience caused by the closure. While the company refrained from making specific recommendations about what to do with Bitcoin funds, users were encouraged to exercise due diligence when selecting alternative custodial wallets or converting Bitcoin to fiat currency. The Financial Conduct Authority (FCA) register can be consulted for information on other FCA-registered cryptoasset businesses operating in the UK.</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk0MzI5NzY4OTU4MTA5MzYx/bitcoin-code.png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Introducing The Rolling-Block Method: A New Way To Forecast Bitcoin Mining Difficulty]]></title><description><![CDATA[Luxor describes its newly-released methodology for improving the accuracy of Bitcoin mining difficulty predictions.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/technical/predicting-bitcoin-mining-difficulty</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/technical/predicting-bitcoin-mining-difficulty</guid><category><![CDATA[Bitcoin mining]]></category><category><![CDATA[Hash Price]]></category><category><![CDATA[hash rate]]></category><category><![CDATA[Feature]]></category><category><![CDATA[difficulty]]></category><category><![CDATA[Technical]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Colin Harper]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTg5NzA2OTgwMjI5NjUzNzAx/bitcoin-mining-miner.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p>Since Bitcoin’s inception, network <a href="https://data.hashrateindex.com/chart/bitcoin-price-and-difficulty">difficulty</a> has grown from 1 to as much as 48.71 trillion hashes that a miner would theoretically need to generate to find the winning one. This means it is 48.71 trillion times harder to mine a Bitcoin block today than when mining first began in 2009 — a compound increase of 20.64% per month.</p><p>At the time of this writing, Bitcoin’s difficulty is at an all-time high, which means that miners — on a BTC basis — are making less in rewards per unit of hash rate than ever before. Next to bitcoin’s price, Bitcoin’s difficulty is a primary factor that influences <a href="https://data.hashrateindex.com/network-data/btc">hash price</a> (<a href="https://data.hashrateindex.com/chart/bitcoin-hashprice-index">mining revenue per unit of hash rate</a>), so miners are interested in projecting Bitcoin’s <a href="https://data.hashrateindex.com/chart/bitcoin-network-hashrate">hash rate</a> growth and difficulty trends for business planning.</p><p>To this end, miners and Bitcoiners devised the constant-block-time method for estimating upcoming adjustments, but this method typically over or under estimates difficulty changes at the beginning of each difficulty epoch.</p><figure>
        <img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk4MTczODQxMTkxNjc0OTUy/average-difficulty-adjustment-by-year.png" height="72" width="620">
        
        
        <figcaption><em>Source: </em><a href="https://hashrateindex.com/"><em>Hashrate Index</em></a></figcaption>
    </figure><p>To improve on this, the team at Luxor Technologies developed a new method called the “rolling-block method,” which we describe in more detail in <a href="https://hashrateindex.com/blog/difficulty-forecasting-101-for-bitcoin-miners-hosters-lenders-and-hashrate-traders/">a recent report on forecasting Bitcoin mining difficulty.</a></p><p>It’s our hope that the rolling-block method for forecasting Bitcoin difficulty could provide miners, investors and hash rate traders a better tool to plan for difficulty changes</p><h2>Luxor's ‘Rolling Block Method’ For Forecasting Difficulty Adjustments</h2><p>For this report, we developed a new time series forecasting method for upcoming difficulty adjustments, which improves accuracy at the beginning of the epoch compared to the constant block time method. We call this the succinctly-named “rolling-2,015-block, square-root-weighted, epoch-adjusted block time method” (or just “rolling-block method,” “adjusted-block-time method,” or “dual-epoch method”).</p><p>This new method improves upon the constant-block-time method early in the epoch by including block times from the previous 2,015 blocks, instead of just the blocks from the current epoch, which can skew forecasts early in the epoch for lack of data points. To account for the change in network difficulty between epochs, block times in the previous epoch are adjusted by the previous adjustment. And finally, we weight the average block times of the current epoch with the square of the proportion through the epoch. This final step is to diminish the impact of block times from the previous epoch as the current epoch progresses since these values do not actually determine the upcoming adjustment.</p><p>In the chart below, we can see through confidence intervals that the new method performed better than the old model at the beginning of the epoch up to block 650, but it performed slightly more poorly thereafter:</p><figure>
        <img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk4MTczODQxMTkxNzQwNDg4/difficulty-adjustment-projection-confidence-intervals.png" height="388" width="620">
        
        
        <figcaption><em>Difficulty forecast confidence intervals. Sources: Luxor, Hashrate Index.</em></figcaption>
    </figure><p>This forecast, of course, is only for projecting the next difficulty adjustment. What if we wanted to forecast, say, a year into the future?</p><h2>Long-Term Bitcoin Mining Difficulty Forecasting</h2><p><a href="https://hashrateindex.com/blog/the-search-for-a-hashprice-floor-or-downside-resistance/">Luxor has developed models for long-term difficulty forecasting</a>, as well, but these models are obviously much more complex, since they span a longer time frame.</p><p>Our model takes the bitcoin price, transaction fees and block subsidy as inputs on the demand side, and internal data on ASIC production estimates and operating cost distributions across the industry on the supply side. Using these inputs, the model produces an equilibrium hash rate, difficulty and hash price for 18-month periods.</p><p>The model structure reflects reality; hash rate, difficulty and hash price are endogenous to the system, not exogenous determinants of one another. We can conduct sensitivity analyses with the model across all inputs as well. For example, we can forecast an equilibrium hash rate, difficulty, and hash price across a range of bitcoin prices.</p><p>The charts below present projections from our updated hash rate supply and demand model. It provides estimates for flat, bull and bear bitcoin price scenarios.</p><figure>
        <img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk4MTczODQxMTkxNjA5NDE2/hash-price-and-hash-rate.png" height="1071" width="620">
        
        
        <figcaption><em>Flat, bull and bear scenarios for hash rate and hash price. Sources: Luxor, Hashrate Index.</em></figcaption>
    </figure><h2>Hash Rate, Difficulty And Hash Price Projection Updates</h2><p>Hash rate is an emerging asset class and digital commodity market. Hash rate market participants like Bitcoin miners, hosters, lenders, investors and traders need access to the rigorous economic analysis and data available in other commodity markets.</p><p>Luxor will be committed to providing this analysis and forecasting on a quarterly basis. If you’d like to learn more, please <a href="https://hashrateindex.com/blog/difficulty-forecasting-101-for-bitcoin-miners-hosters-lenders-and-hashrate-traders/">visit this post.</a></p><p><em>This is a guest post by Colin Harper. Opinions expressed are entirely their own and do not necessarily reflect those of BTC Inc or Bitcoin Magazine.</em></p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTg5NzA2OTgwMjI5NjUzNzAx/bitcoin-mining-miner.png"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk4MTczODQxMTkxNjc0OTUy/average-difficulty-adjustment-by-year.png" height="72" width="620" medium="image" type="image/png"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk4MTczODQxMTkxNzQwNDg4/difficulty-adjustment-projection-confidence-intervals.png" height="388" width="620" medium="image" type="image/png"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk4MTczODQxMTkxNjA5NDE2/hash-price-and-hash-rate.png" height="1071" width="620" medium="image" type="image/png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[MicroBT COO Jordan Chen Discusses The Company's Long-Term Goals And The Newest Whatsminers At Bitcoin 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[Chen elaborated on the mission of MicroBT and how the updates in the new machines exemplify this focus.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/microbt-coo-jordan-chen-discusses-the-newest-whatsminers-at-bitcoin-2023</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/microbt-coo-jordan-chen-discusses-the-newest-whatsminers-at-bitcoin-2023</guid><category><![CDATA[Business]]></category><category><![CDATA[Asics]]></category><category><![CDATA[MicroBT]]></category><category><![CDATA[whatsminer]]></category><category><![CDATA[Solar Power]]></category><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[Mining]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[BtcCasey]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 21:03:28 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTgzMjM5NTgzMDQyMDUzMTU4/img_6181.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p>MicroBT, a leading manufacturer of Bitcoin mining rigs, is focused on addressing the need for upgraded power sources in bitcoin mining. In an interview conducted at Bitcoin 2023 in Miami Beach, MicroBT's COO, Jordan Chen, emphasized the company's commitment to developing a solar power mining solution. According to Chen, "Solar power is a perfect power source for bitcoin mining, both in terms of decentralization and sustainability." He further explained that MicroBT is working with partners along the value chain to provide a mature solution that utilizes solar power for mining worldwide.</p><p>Chen elaborated on the adjustment of voltage and frequency in MicroBT's Whatsminer rigs to adapt to the change in solar power. He stated, "The mining machine has to adapt to the power changes so as to keep mining throughout the day with various working voltage and frequency." Chen highlighted that this dynamic adjustment only costs about "1% to 2% efficiency compared to traditional shut-down-and-reboot method," ensuring continuous mining operations and optimizing revenue.</p><p>Discussing the cooling methods in <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/microbt-releases-new-line-of-whatsminer-m50-series">the new Whatsminer M50 series</a>, Chen provided insights into the benefits and unique features of each method. He explained, "Air-cooling is taking away heat via fans, while hydro-cooling uses water-cooling pads which eliminate the need for fans, heat sinks, and offer a longer lifetime." Regarding immersion cooling, Chen highlighted its advantages, stating, "It's really no dust, no exposure to corrosive air, low noise and a longer lifetime."</p><p>Chen shared MicroBT's focus on heat utilization scenarios, stating, "The heat generated during the mining process will be transferred to an outside heating loop through a heat exchanger." He further explained that the heat recovery ratio can be as high as 95%. Chen emphasized MicroBT's collaboration with customers on various applications, such as providing heating services to communities and generating steam for industrial uses like food processing.</p><p>When discussing MicroBT's vision for the future of Bitcoin mining, Chen emphasized their commitment to leveraging renewable energies and maximizing the reuse of heat generated during mining. He stated, "Our vision is allowing bitcoin mining to make a bigger and bigger positive contribution to society," with a focus on minimizing carbon emissions and carbon footprint.</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTgzMjM5NTgzMDQyMDUzMTU4/img_6181.png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[BIT Mining And Chain Reaction Partner To Create New Bitcoin Mining Systems]]></title><description><![CDATA[The partnership will leverage Chain Reaction’s ASIC announced at Bitcoin 2023 to further develop systems for miners.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/bit-mining-and-chain-reaction-partner-to-create-new-bitcoin-mining-systems</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/bit-mining-and-chain-reaction-partner-to-create-new-bitcoin-mining-systems</guid><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[Business]]></category><category><![CDATA[Mining]]></category><category><![CDATA[BIT Mining]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[BtcCasey]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 19:58:54 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkyNjA3MTM2MjI2NzQ4MTUz/20220926_good-gdog-proof-collaborative-custody-multisig-by-will-schoellkopf_.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p>BIT Mining Limited has announced a collaboration with semiconductor company Chain Reaction to develop next-generation systems for bitcoin mining. According to a <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/bit-mining-and-chain-reaction-form-collaboration-for-bitcoin-hashing-systems-301829444.html?ref=nobsbitcoin.com">press release</a>, the collaboration aims to leverage Chain Reaction's ‘<a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2023/05/16/2669890/0/en/Chain-Reaction-Launches-EL3CTRUM-the-Most-Powerful-Blockchain-Technology-on-the-Market.html">EL3CTRUM ASIC</a>’ solution to create hardware that delivers industry-leading performance with low power consumption.</p><p>The press release states that Chain Reaction specializes in designing hardware for blockchain, privacy, high-performance computing (HPC) and the cloud. With a team experienced in analog and circuit design, the company has successfully produced 30 ASIC tapeouts for high-volume manufacturing. The recently launched EL3CTRUM ASIC by Chain Reaction is described as a “groundbreaking blockchain chip that serves as the foundation for sustainable, high-performance blockchain technologies.”</p><p>Alon Webman, CEO of Chain Reaction, explained what the partnership hopes to yield, saying that "Chain Reaction's bleeding-edge ASICs will enable BIT Mining to build next-gen systems to advance the Bitcoin mining industry towards faster, more power efficient computing." </p><p>“We believe through this collaboration we can leverage our individual strengths to provide the mining community systems that enhance long-term benefits and capabilities,” Xianfeng Yang, CEO of BIT Mining reiterated. “With the crypto mining industry continuing to evolve, BIT Mining looks to develop systems that are more efficient, accessible, and sustainable."</p><p>The systems developed through this collaboration are expected to launch later this year.&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkyNjA3MTM2MjI2NzQ4MTUz/20220926_good-gdog-proof-collaborative-custody-multisig-by-will-schoellkopf_.png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[When Bitcoin Meets Artificial Intelligence: Woke Madness Or Awakened Sanity?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Ideological battle lines are being drawn around artificial intelligence, and Bitcoiners need to enter the fray.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/are-bitcoin-and-artificial-intelligence-compatible</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/are-bitcoin-and-artificial-intelligence-compatible</guid><category><![CDATA[Regulation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Opinion]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Aleksandar Svetski]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkzODM5Njc4ODI5MzcyOTEy/network-nodes.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p><em>This is an opinion editorial by Aleksander Svetski, author of “The UnCommunist Manifesto,” The Bitcoin Times and the “Remnant Series,” and head of growth and strategy at Lucent Labs.</em></p><p>I know, I know. Your Twitter feed has probably been drowning in threads and tips from AI bros who have discovered 99 ways for you to save 99 hours every week using ChatGPT or some other list of 99 AI apps.</p><p>I’m sick of it too. Trust me, especially considering that most of these AI “experts” were Web3 “experts” last year, NFT “experts” the year before and DeFi or crypto “experts” before that. Trend hopping at its finest.</p><p>That’s not to say there’s no value here to be found here. Somewhere beneath or behind the almost-deafening noise coming from these influencooors there is a possible paradigm shift, and a genuine set of use cases. We’ve seen some already, of course. </p><p>You can chat with these models to reason out a problem, you can summarize thoughts and ideas, find correlations between ideas, search for <em>some</em> information better than you could with Google and, of course, build more linguistically-functional chatbots. Perhaps the best use case thus far are the <a href="https://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2023/05/google-jumps-into-the-ai-coding-assistant-fray-with-codey-and-studio-bot/">dev-assistant tools</a>, but I get the sense that we’ve not yet seen the “Uber moment.”</p><p>There is also — somewhere beneath and behind all of the scary talk of <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Artificial_general_intelligence">artificial general intelligence (AGI)</a> and the idiocy being proposed by <a href="https://www.whitehouse.gov/ostp/ai-bill-of-rights/">bureaucrats and would-be regulators</a> — a more human-centric, human-enhancing use for these tools.</p><p>The idea of a language user interface as the next step from the thumb tapping we’ve become used to over the past decade is fascinating, and what we should be thinking about is how to make these tools new “<a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ebenbayer/2023/05/15/ai--biotechnology-show-its-time-to-think-past-bicycles-for-the-mind/?sh=2c7868754ea1">bicycles for the mind</a>,” as Steve Jobs said about computers. It’s very important that we push back against doomer narratives that lean the world toward “approved AI” in order to avoid such tools becoming yet another appendage of the State.</p><p>In this short article, I’d like to explore the ideological AI battlefield and its relationship to Bitcoin. Some pretty important battle lines have been drawn, and we must all be aware of them.</p><h2>Bitcoin Remains The Most Important Thing In The World</h2><p>Energy is still the currency of the universe. That’s not changing, and will never change. At the risk of sounding like too much of a hippie: It’s all energy.</p><p>People often forget that, and this recent AI hype cycle is a clear example. Most people you talk with, even otherwise smart people, think that AI is the biggest thing happening in the world today, and that it’s mankind’s most important innovation.</p><p>I think they’re wrong, in a big way. They’re missing something more foundational.</p><p>AI is a tool. When applied well, it’s a very effective tool. But however effective a tool it may be, it needs energy to run. Yes, it can and will enhance how we use and allocate energy, but ultimately, it is an amplifier. A tool. An “engine,” so to speak.</p><p>What is Bitcoin?</p><p>Well, Bitcoin is <em>like</em> energy. <em>Before the Saylor-haters out there screech about that not being literally accurate: I know! It’s a metaphor, and in my opinion, a useful one</em>. It’s useful because, in the same way we can essentially use energy to measure everything else, money is a measure that helps us (implicitly) account for energy, time and material resources. </p><p>If we understand that Bitcoin, on a long enough time scale (generationally speaking, not civilizationally) becomes <em>money</em>, then here’s the truth that AI people are missing:</p><p><strong>Bitcoin benefits from all of it, because Bitcoin is the foundation. Everything that happens, every technology, every tool, every innovation, enlarges the total Bitcoin pie.</strong></p><p>So, don’t get it twisted: AI is big, <em>but Bitcoin remains king.</em></p><p>Of course, in terms of financial returns, VC money and the like, AI companies will probably outpace both bitcoin returns (in the short term) and also Bitcoin company returns, but that’s to be expected in a fiat world where hype prevails over sanity, and we experience abnormal cyclicality.</p><p>AI is also undergoing a sort of renaissance, so there is lots of buzz. This will, in time, stabilize and as bitcoin becomes the unit of account, lo and behold, all of the <em>real</em> value generated from AI will ultimately accrue to bitcoin and bitcoin holders.</p><p>So, don’t stress if you’re feeling FOMO on AI. Don’t worry about changing your entire life around because some ex-crypto-turned-AI-expert guy wrote a viral tweet telling you about some new, generative AI tool that will obsolete some and make others mega rich.</p><p>Slow and steady continues to win the race. Bitcoin continues to be king.</p><h2>AI Is An Amplifier</h2><p>The second thing we need to realize is this: AI is like the computer or any other technology, for that matter.</p><p>It’s an engine. <em>It’s an amplifier.</em></p><p>It will amplify madness, stupidity and lies, or it will amplify soundness, sanity and truth.</p><p>It can be used as a tool of control and stupidification, or it can be used as a tool for liberating oneself from minutia and for enhancing one’s intelligence.</p><p>The direction we wind up ultimately depends on you.</p><p>Which tools are you using? Which do you demand? Which are you building? Which are you supporting?</p><p>Companies like <a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2023/apr/19/snapchat-making-ai-chatbot-similar-to-chatgpt-available-to-every-user">Snapchat are building AI tools</a> to infect your mind with nonsense:</p><figure>
        <img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk4MTUwNTgyMDY0NzE5MDM4/snapchat-ai.jpg" height="826" width="620">
        
        
        <figcaption><a href="https://substackcdn.com/image/fetch/f_auto,q_auto:good,fl_progressive:steep/https%3A%2F%2Fsubstack-post-media.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fpublic%2Fimages%2Fa6ecce10-7633-4e3b-8383-39672339268c_886x1181.jpeg"><em>Source</em></a></figcaption>
    </figure><p>OpenAI is busy guard-railing ChatGPT to such a degree that it spends <a href="https://www.pcmag.com/news/openai-sorry-chatgpt-bug-leaked-payment-info-to-other-users">more time apologizing and moralizing</a> than it does answering actual questions.</p><p>Bard is, likewise, <a href="https://www.the-sun.com/tech/7719664/googles-bard-ai-chatbot-accused-left-wing-bias/">regurgitating the same kind of garbage</a>, likely because it’s been neutered by “bias-removal” tools and toxicity filters.</p><p>These stupidities only serve to constrain people’s accepted thinking and speech, which results in a homogenization of thought. This can have two effects. In the worst case, so-called “safety concerns” lead to “approved AI” which ultimately leads to an internet that is accessed through chat filters with approved speech conditions. The alternative is if we push back and build alternatives. Their ignorance becomes our opportunity. While they focus on wokeness, we can build utility and authenticity. </p><p>Which brings me to my final point:</p><h2>We’re In A Global AI Arms Race</h2><p>The race is between two versions of the world:</p><ol><li>On the one hand, we have woke, generalist AIs that everyone is forced to use because newly-formed regulatory bodies deem them “safe” (see the <a href="https://garymarcus.substack.com/p/how-china-might-crush-the-west-in?utm_source=substack&amp;utm_campaign=post_embed&amp;utm_medium=web">ridiculously-moronic work being done by Gary Marcus</a> to set up such a global committee).</li><li>On the other, we have a future of distributed, more sovereign tools that people can choose from, that the user evaluates on merits they deem important.</li></ol><p>I know which future I want to see, and instead of sitting on the sidelines complaining, I’m working toward building alternative or parallel solutions.</p><p>In a future article, I’ll lay out what myself and a few really talented individuals have been working on. A beautiful marriage of Bitcoin as the focal point and Ai as the engine. </p><p>In the meantime, know this: <strong>The battle lines have been drawn.</strong></p><p>It’s iris-scanning, central bank digital currencies (CBDCs) <a href="https://www.ft.com/content/f1de2aee-ee13-45e1-bd61-0a269cd650d3">like World Coin</a> on one end, conveniently run by the same leadership as OpenAI, versus Bitcoin and smaller, more accurate, specialized and open-source language models on the other.</p><figure>
        <img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk4MTUwNTgyMDY0NjUzNTAy/world-coin.jpg" height="739" width="620">
        
        
        <figcaption><a href="https://twitter.com/nwilliams030/status/1540409206532186116"><em>Source</em></a></figcaption>
    </figure><p>We all have to make a choice about the kind of world we want to live in. Woke madness, or awakened sanity? Mainstream and generalized, or local and specialized?</p><p>In my next piece, I will present a potential solution, or at least a way forward. Until then, think deeply about what I have said. Don’t get flustered by all the hype. Remain steady in your conviction, remain vigilant with the narratives being pushed and be ready for the next battle — because it’s coming.</p><p><em>This is a guest post by </em><a href="https://linktree.com/Svetski"><em>Aleksandar Svetski</em></a><em>, founder of </em><a href="https://bitcointim.es"><em>The Bitcoin Times</em></a><em> and </em><a href="http://amber.app"><em>The Amber App,</em></a><em> author of “</em><a href="http://www.uncommunist.com/"><em>The UnCommunist Manifesto</em></a><em>,” “</em><a href="https://authenticintelligence.substack.com"><em>Authentic Intelligence</em></a><em>” and the up-coming “Bushido Of Bitcoin.” Opinions expressed are entirely their own and do not necessarily reflect those of BTC Inc or </em>Bitcoin Magazine<em>.</em></p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkzODM5Njc4ODI5MzcyOTEy/network-nodes.png"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk4MTUwNTgyMDY0NzE5MDM4/snapchat-ai.jpg" height="826" width="620" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk4MTUwNTgyMDY0NjUzNTAy/world-coin.jpg" height="739" width="620" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Upstream Data Files Lawsuit Against Crusoe Energy Systems For Bitcoin Mining Operations]]></title><description><![CDATA[The lawsuit alleges that Crusoe’s mining operations utilizing stranded natural gas infringe upon Upstream’s patent.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/upstream-data-files-lawsuit-against-crusoe-energy-systems</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/upstream-data-files-lawsuit-against-crusoe-energy-systems</guid><category><![CDATA[Miners]]></category><category><![CDATA[Upstream data]]></category><category><![CDATA[Lawsuit]]></category><category><![CDATA[Business]]></category><category><![CDATA[Patents]]></category><category><![CDATA[Crusoe]]></category><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[Mining]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[BtcCasey]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 19:11:38 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkzMzUxMjcwOTg2MTYzNzc5/mining-pick-axe.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p>Canadian Bitcoin mining corporation <a href="https://blog.upstreamdata.ca/">Upstream Data Inc</a>. has filed a patent infringement lawsuit against Delaware limited liability company <a href="https://www.crusoeenergy.com/">Crusoe Energy Systems</a> LLC in the United States District Court for the District of Colorado.&nbsp;</p><p><a href="https://media.licdn.com/dms/document/media/D561FAQHWC4EiAxmGog/feedshare-document-pdf-analyzed/0/1684512495590?e=1685577600&amp;v=beta&amp;t=_NRwT6YvH0ydEyWm5GBg8E-lglYTuqL8TWWIsBJ1K84">The lawsuit</a> alleges that Crusoe has infringed on Upstream's patent related to bitcoin mining technology used to convert stranded natural gas into bitcoin. According to the complaint, Upstream holds the patent for a system that powers a blockchain mine at remote oil well sites using stranded gas to generate electricity for cryptocurrency mining. According to the filing, the company has deployed over 350 bitcoin mining systems across the U.S. and Canada, addressing the issue of stranded gas venting and flaring.</p><p>Crusoe, which manufactures and operates cryptocurrency mining systems connected to stranded natural gas sources, is accused of competing with Upstream by selling and operating similar systems. The complaint claims that Crusoe's "Digital Flare Mitigation" systems infringe on Upstream's patented technology. The lawsuit further alleges that Crusoe was aware of Upstream's patented technology during the development of its own products. The lawsuit filing highlights instances where Crusoe identified Upstream as a competitor in blog posts and claims made in patent applications.</p><p>The lawsuit seeks damages and injunctive relief against Crusoe for patent infringement. Upstream argues that Crusoe's actions have caused harm to its business by infringing on its patent rights and creating unfair competition in the market.&nbsp;</p><p>The case will be heard in the United States District Court for the District of Colorado, where Crusoe has regular and established places of business according to the filing. Also noted in the lawsuit is a complaint filed against a customer of Upstream in Crusoe Energy Systems LLC v. Alkane Midstream LLC, which the lawsuit says "further confirm[s] Crusoe’s significant and substantial contacts with this district." Upstream asserts in the lawsuit that the court has jurisdiction over the case.</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkzMzUxMjcwOTg2MTYzNzc5/mining-pick-axe.png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[How To Figure Out If You Should Start Mining Bitcoin]]></title><description><![CDATA[Turning a profit from Bitcoin mining is a challenge, but not impossible. Here are some factors to consider if you want to start.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/should-i-start-mining-bitcoin</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/should-i-start-mining-bitcoin</guid><category><![CDATA[Halving]]></category><category><![CDATA[Business]]></category><category><![CDATA[Bitcoin mining]]></category><category><![CDATA[Opinion]]></category><category><![CDATA[energy costs]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Keaton Reckard]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTg5MjcxMzMyMzAxNTc5Mzky/20220504_btcfinal_zack-voell---so-what-if-bitcoin-miners-fees-are-low.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p><em>This is an opinion editorial by Keaton Reckard, the community engineer at Hiveon, </em><em>a mining ecosystem that includes an operating system for Bitcoin mining hardware.</em></p><p><a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/guides/bitcoin-mining">Bitcoin mining</a> refers to the process through which new bitcoin is introduced into circulation. The mining process plays a crucial role in confirming new transactions and maintaining the Bitcoin blockchain ledger as an immutable record of transactions. In essence, miners use ASIC hardware to solve complex computational problems, with the first one to find the solution earning a reward of bitcoin before the cycle restarts. </p><p>Though Bitcoin mining can be time-consuming, expensive and can yield inconsistent rewards depending on price volatility, it still holds a strong allure for investors drawn to the idea of earning bitcoin as compensation for their efforts. For tech-savvy individuals and hobbyists, mining can be an intriguing opportunity for many different reasons.</p><p>As opposed to traditional investment assets, such as standard bank deposits, real estate property or stocks, bitcoin can offer much higher returns. It’s an environmentally-conscious business that can prevent energy waste by utilizing excess energy, such as the natural gas that gets burned during oil extraction, idle wind turbines and surplus energy from hydroelectric or nuclear power plants. </p><p>Hiveon’s long-term predictions are that bitcoin’s value will rise after the halving (more on that below), so we’re accumulating coins now to multiply that money into the future. We also believe that, in the future, an alternative global financial system based on blockchain technology like Bitcoin’s will be dominant, and network validators will be able to make money from processing transactions.</p><p>But with mining difficulty and hash rate <a href="https://www.theblock.co/post/225359/bitcoin-difficulty-hashrate-miner-revenue">continuously hitting new highs</a> and <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-network-overwhelmed-by-390000-unconfirmed-transactions-and-surging-fees/">fees surging</a>, many may wonder if the practice is still worth investing in.</p><h2>Is Mining Bitcoin Worth It?</h2><p>To determine if Bitcoin mining will be “worth it” for them, equipment, prospective miners should conduct cost-benefit analyses to determine their break-even points. Factors to consider include power costs, hardware costs and efficiency, time and the market value of bitcoin. You can choose to factor in the current BTC price ($28,190 at the time of writing) or, attempt to extrapolate where you believe the price of BTC will be in the future.</p><h3>Power Costs</h3><p>At the time of this writing, Bitcoin mining can be profitable for individuals who pay <a href="https://whattomine.com/miners/163-bitmain-antminer-s19j-pro-96th?cost=0.11&amp;cost_currency=USD&amp;button=">$0.10 or less per kilowatt hour (kWh)</a> of power.</p><p>Access to energy at this price, however, can vary significantly across different regions, with some areas offering notably cheaper electricity than others. In terms of <a href="https://www.statista.com/statistics/263492/electricity-prices-in-selected-countries/">household electricity prices</a>, several Middle Eastern countries would make good homes for Bitcoin miners, including Iran, Qatar and Saudi Arabia. Meanwhile, prices in European countries like Denmark, Germany and the U.K., would make Bitcoin mining a difficult proposition.</p><h3>Hardware Costs</h3><p>Acquiring ASIC equipment has become relatively easy, although the price of ASICs ranges from a few hundred dollars to five-figure sums. I recently found a used Antminer S19 for sale in the U.K., listed at £2,700 (or about $3,343.38).</p><h3>Market Value</h3><p>Bitcoin achieved its highest price ever at <a href="https://99bitcoins.com/bitcoin/historical-price/">$67,549 in November 2021</a>. During this period, as the 2021 bull market reached its peak, miners’ bitcoin rewards were naturally more valuable in fiat terms than they are at the time of this writing, with the bitcoin price around $27,600. However, with <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/technical/bitcoins-high-fees-create-controversy-and-challenges">bitcoin transaction fees rising</a> as a result of ongoing experimentations with block space, miners are benefitting.</p><p>A <a href="https://btc.com/tools/mining-calculator">profitability calculator</a> can help potential miners evaluate the cost-benefit ratio of Bitcoin mining. These calculators can vary in complexity and may provide slightly different results. </p><h2>What Are The ‘Other’ Reasons For Bitcoin Mining?</h2><p>But for some Bitcoin miners, a simple cost-benefit analysis may not be the only factor in deciding whether mining is “worth it” or not in 2023.</p><p>Mining is an essential aspect of Bitcoin's decentralized transaction recording and validation process. Bitcoin mining serves a critical purpose by addressing an issue called “double spending,” a problem inherent in any digital currency system. Double spending is the digital equivalent of counterfeiting, which is kept in check in the physical world by middlemen like governments and banks. </p><p>For Bitcoin, this need to trust third parties has been replaced largely because of the computational effort provided by miners. Maintaining that freedom from middlemen, in addition to collecting revenue, may be a motivation to contribute to the mining network for some.</p><h2>Bitcoin Halving Cycles And What to Expect In 2024</h2><p>The <a href="https://www.coinwarz.com/mining/bitcoin/halving#:~:text=When%20is%20the%20Next%20Bitcoin%20Halving%20Date%3F,to%203.125%20Bitcoin%20per%20block.">next anticipated Bitcoin halving in April 2024</a> will likely have a significant impact on the mining dynamic.</p><p>A Bitcoin halving is an event in which the reward for mining new blocks is reduced by 50%, resulting in miners receiving half as many bitcoin in their reward for solving a block. Scheduled to occur every 210,000 blocks, Bitcoin halvings continue until the maximum supply of 21 million bitcoin has been issued.</p><p>The impact of the next halving on Bitcoin's price remains uncertain. Some analysts predict that the price will follow a similar pattern to previous halvings, rising post-event due to the constrained supply of new coins. However, any price increase will ultimately depend on demand for bitcoin and it should be noted that the market has matured significantly since the 2020 halving, and numerous well-established cryptocurrencies now compete for users.</p><p>Anyone considering whether Bitcoin mining will be profitable in 2023 will likely want to factor the impact of the next Bitcoin halving into their calculus as well.</p><h2>Difficult, But Not Impossible</h2><p>Profitable Bitcoin mining is a challenge, but it’s not impossible. Bitcoin is priced relatively low at the time of writing, yet an Antminer S19 can run profitably at a maximum power cost of $0.10 per kWh. While this rules out areas of the world like the U.K., there are many global locations where power is cheaper. Naturally, renewable sources of energy (solar panels in particular) really help improve profitability and, as the world transitions from oil and gas to renewable sources of energy, it’s hoped that the price of electricity will fall once again.</p><p>Access to cheap electricity, the quickly-evolving nature of Bitcoin and upcoming events like the halving are just some of the many factors to consider when you ask, is Bitcoin mining profitable?</p><p><em>This is a guest post by Keaton Reckard. Opinions expressed are entirely their own and do not necessarily reflect those of BTC Inc or Bitcoin Magazine.</em></p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTg5MjcxMzMyMzAxNTc5Mzky/20220504_btcfinal_zack-voell---so-what-if-bitcoin-miners-fees-are-low.png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Developer Introduces Ark, A Layer 2 Protocol For Fast And Efficient Payments]]></title><description><![CDATA[Ark promises easier access to a scalable Layer 2, negating the need for channel management.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/technical/bitcoin-developer-introduces-new-layer-2-protocol-ark</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/technical/bitcoin-developer-introduces-new-layer-2-protocol-ark</guid><category><![CDATA[development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Layer 2]]></category><category><![CDATA[Ark]]></category><category><![CDATA[Scaling]]></category><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[Technical]]></category><category><![CDATA[scalability]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[BtcCasey]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 20:58:15 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk0MjMxNzYxODMwNTUzMDkz/bitcoin-stack.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p>A Bitcoin developer by the name of <a href="https://twitter.com/brqgoo?lang=en">Burak</a> recently unveiled Ark, a Layer 2 protocol designed to enable fast and secure transactions. According to <a href="https://lists.linuxfoundation.org/pipermail/bitcoin-dev/2023-May/021694.html">a post on the Bitcoin dev mailing list</a>, Ark offers an alternative scaling approach that allows users to send and receive funds without liquidity constraints, making it easier for recipients to get paid without an onboarding setup. Unlike other Layer 2 solutions like Lightning, Ark does not require the opening and closing of channels, reducing the on-chain footprint significantly.</p><figure>
        <img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk4MTMzMzIzODEyMzE2MjMy/image1.png" height="304" width="620">
        
        
        <figcaption><a href="https://www.arkpill.me/deep-dive"><em>Image source</em></a></figcaption>
    </figure><p>The protocol operates using virtual UTXOs (vTXOs), which are short-lived notes that expire after four weeks. When a payment is made, existing vTXOs are redeemed, and new ones are created. The anonymity of coin ownership is improved by restricting vTXO values to a range of sats values. Users can acquire vTXOs from others or use a process called lifting, which allows them to lift their on-chain UTXOs off the chain for virtual UTXOs.</p><p>The protocol introduces an intermediary called the Ark Service Provider (ASP), which serves as a liquidity provider, CoinJoin coordinator and Lightning service provider. ASPs create rapid, blinded CoinJoin sessions every five seconds, known as pools, which ensure the atomicity of payment schedules. Recipients can claim their funds through a txlock condition that requires the connector outpoint to remain unchanged.</p><p>Ark's integration with the Lightning Network allows users to attach HTLCs (or PTLCs) to a pool transaction, enabling interoperability between the two protocols. Multiple ASPs can be used to pay Lightning invoices from different vTXO sources using multi-part payments. Payments on Ark are credited every five seconds, allowing users to spend their zero-conf vTXOs immediately without waiting for on-chain confirmations.</p><p>The developer behind Ark highlighted the protocol's potential for future extensions and improvements. A hypothetical data manipulation opcode could disincentivize double-spending, and users could forge an ASP's signature to reclaim their vTXOs in case of a double-spend. Overall, Ark offers a promising solution for efficient and secure off-chain transactions on the Bitcoin network.</p><p>For more information on Ark and its technical details, curious users are encouraged to visit <a href="https://arkpill.me/deep-dive">https://arkpill.me/deep-dive</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk0MjMxNzYxODMwNTUzMDkz/bitcoin-stack.png"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk4MTMzMzIzODEyMzE2MjMy/image1.png" height="304" width="620" medium="image" type="image/png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Neutronpay And Pouch.ph Partner To Offer Affordable Remittances For Canada And Vietnam Using Lightning]]></title><description><![CDATA[Canadians who want to send money back to the Philippines can now leverage the Lightning Network to do so.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/neutronpay-and-pouch-ph-now-offer-lightning-remittances-for-canada-and-vietnam</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/neutronpay-and-pouch-ph-now-offer-lightning-remittances-for-canada-and-vietnam</guid><category><![CDATA[Business]]></category><category><![CDATA[Remittances]]></category><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[Lightning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Philippines]]></category><category><![CDATA[Canada]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[BtcCasey]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 17:06:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkzMDI2MTUyOTY3NzA5OTE3/global-hyperbitcoinization.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p><a href="https://neutronpay.com/">Neutronpay</a>, a digital payment platform based in Canada, has partnered with <a href="https://pouch.ph/">Pouch.ph</a> to offer fast and affordable remittance services for Filipinos living in Canada and Vietnam. According to a press release sent to Bitcoin Magazine, the partnership aims to provide a secure and cost-effective solution for Filipino expatriates who want to send money to their loved ones in the Philippines. By leveraging Bitcoin's Lightning Network, the partnership enables the conversion of Canadian dollars or Vietnamese dong into bitcoin, which is then converted into Philippine pesos and transferred directly to the recipient's bank or mobile money account.</p><p>Albert Buu, the founder and CEO of Neutronpay, expressed his excitement about the collaboration, stating, "Our integration with Bitcoin's Lightning Network is a major step forward in improving the lives of our customers, and we look forward to exploring new ways to innovate cross-border payments."</p><p>The demand for remittances to the Philippines has been growing steadily, with personal remittances reaching a record high of $36.14 billion in 2022, according to data from the Banko Sentral ng Pilipinas. Canada accounted for 3.6% of total remittances to the Philippines, highlighting the importance of providing efficient and cost-effective remittance services to the Filipino community in Canada.</p><p>Ethan Rose, the CEO of Pouch, emphasized the significance of the partnership in empowering overseas Filipino workers (OFWs) to easily send money back home. He stated, "Working with Neutronpay is consistent with our endeavor to empower OFWs to easily send money to their families and loved ones."</p><p>The NeutronPay app is currently available exclusively on Canadian and Vietnamese app stores, while the Pouch.ph app can be downloaded from the Google Play Store and Apple Store. This collaboration between Neutronpay and Pouch.ph brings lightning-fast remittance services to Filipinos in Canada and Vietnam, offering a convenient and cost-effective way to support their families and loved ones back home in the Philippines.</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkzMDI2MTUyOTY3NzA5OTE3/global-hyperbitcoinization.png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ordinals Have Proven Demand On Bitcoin, But Fees Will Push Users To Layer 2]]></title><description><![CDATA[The surge of Ordinals demonstrates a significant market, but not one that Bitcoin is built to sustain on the base layer.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/bitcoin-ordinal-problems-solved-by-layer-2</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/bitcoin-ordinal-problems-solved-by-layer-2</guid><category><![CDATA[Layer 2]]></category><category><![CDATA[Ordinals]]></category><category><![CDATA[Transactions]]></category><category><![CDATA[Opinion]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Fees]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Steven Hay]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkwMjY2NTkxMzgyODczMjQx/bitcoin-lightning-network.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p><em>This is an opinion editorial by Steven Hay, a writer, former trader and art dealer.</em></p><p>The <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/questioning-bitcoin-magazine-ordinal-auction">Ordinals controversy</a> is still simmering and seems set to flare up again soon. Although Ordinals’ block space usage had been<a href="https://dune.com/queries/2009834/3326390"> trending down</a> since March 23, 2023, the release of<a href="https://arthodl.net/2023/04/05/bugatti-and-asprey-bringing-high-tech-faberge-style-eggs-to-ordinals/"> notable collections</a> and a <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/technical/bitcoins-high-fees-create-controversy-and-challenges">burgeoning mania</a> for BRC-20 tokens seems to have reversed that trend. </p><p>Should competition for block space between Ordinals, BRC-20 tokens and purely monetary transactions remain high, so will fees. And, should fees climb sufficiently high, the ghastly shades of the<a href="https://blog.bitmex.com/the-blocksize-war-chapter-1-first-strike/"> blocksize war</a> may rise once more to torment all Bit-kind.</p><h2>The Case Against Ordinals</h2><p>Fees aren't the only flashpoint. While Bitcoin has certainly had its share of negative headlines over the years, the protocol itself has thus far escaped the same level of recrimination. Exchange failures, drug sales, countless scams — these are all things people did <em>with</em> the tech, rather than any intrinsic fault of the tech itself. Not so with, say, Ethereum, where sketchy smart contracts are virtually part of the machine. </p><p>With Ordinals popularizing the integration of Bitcoin's blockchain with all manner of infamous Ethereum innovations (such as NFTs, tokens and, perhaps soon,<a href="https://thebitcoinmanual.com/articles/what-are-brc-721-tokens/"> smart contracts</a>), reputational risk to the Bitcoin protocol grows. How long until a token is issued directly on Bitcoin which passes the<a href="https://www.investopedia.com/terms/h/howey-test.asp"> Howey Test</a> and so falls afoul of the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission? </p><p>Further in this regard, Ordinals also greatly lower the barrier to introducing illicit or classified content into Bitcoin's blockchain.</p><figure>
        <img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk3OTg3MjYyNDQzNTYyNzgx/rug-pull.jpg" height="310" width="620">
        
        
        <figcaption><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/destroying-substratum-appeal-payingreceiving-judgment-jayapal/"><em>Source</em></a><em> (modified by author).</em></figcaption>
    </figure><p>As for the loss of user funds due to rug pulls, bugs, hacks and takedowns, all of these boxes have already been ticked under Ordinals. Most recently,<a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ordinals-finance-has-conducted-a-1m-rug-pull-certik"> Ordinals Finance</a> pulled a $1 million rug, albeit on the Ethereum side of the ledger. Just prior to that,<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/news/coinedition:bd9364062094b:0/"> UniSat</a> fumbled the launch of its BRC-20s marketplace, resulting in costly double-spend attacks and a lengthy market halt. Before <em>that</em>, several major marketplaces bowed to legal pressure from<a href="https://arthodl.net/2023/04/11/magic-eden-market-delists-ape-collections/"> Yuga Labs</a> and delisted ape-related collections. </p><p>Furthermore, all of these "hiccups" occurred against the background of a<a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-ordinals-community-debates-fix-after-inscription-validation-bug"> bug</a> discovered within Ordinals' all-important indexing system. Finally — and I hate to say this — further problems of this nature are anticipated. Consider that one of the largest<a href="https://dune.com/domo/ordinals-marketplaces"> marketplaces by users and volume</a>, Ordinals Wallet as well as the significant Ordswap marketplace both keep keys in browser<a href="https://snyk.io/blog/is-localstorage-safe-to-use/"> </a>local storage, according to what I’ve heard on Discord, which <a href="https://snyk.io/blog/is-localstorage-safe-to-use/">runs contrary to recommended security practices</a> (to say the least).</p><p>I believe the above paragraphs summarize the case against Ordinals from the perspective of many Bitcoin Maximalists — among whose ranks I myself numbered, at least until the Ordinals<a href="https://www.urbandictionary.com/define.php?term=Purity%20Spiral"> purity spiral</a> went helter-skelter. And while these concerns have merit, there's one particular complaint which I believe deserves to go unmentioned; that Ordinals are a scam. </p><p>When willing buyers and willing sellers exchange goods with informational symmetry, without any claims made as to future price appreciation, well, that's the definition of honest business — and that's the current situation within Ordinals marketplaces. Prove me wrong.</p><h2>In Defense Of Ordinals</h2><p>A point in favor of Ordinals is that <a href="https://decrypt.co/125556/bitcoin-stamps-nfts-are-gaining-on-ordinals">it's possible to prune their content from stored blockchain data</a>. Pruning resolves the blockchain file size bloat issue, which is fairly trivial considering that I expect the bloat to be easily outpaced by the growth of affordable data storage. More importantly, pruning ensures that anyone running a full node can opt out of storing any illegal material (which, to be fair, existed on Bitcoin's blockchain long before Ordinals).</p><p>In regards to the reputational and legislative risks to Bitcoin arising from Ordinals content stored on the blockchain, these can be mitigated — but not eliminated — by proper communication. The point must be hammered home (and not just for the sake of Ordinals) that Bitcoin's uncensorable and permissionless structure has certain unavoidable drawbacks which, on balance, are vastly outweighed by its advantages.</p><p>On the technical front, it's possible that post-traumatic stress from the blocksize war is leading some to view Ordinals as a big-blocker-style assault on Bitcoin's base layer... but as an entirely optional Layer 2, Ordinals have far more in common with the Lightning Network than with Bcash and its ilk. Granted, content insertion into witness data is also occurring, but that process is moderated by fees... </p><p>Fees? Lightning? Let's not jump ahead to the resolution of this Ordinals controversy!</p><p>As for the loss of user funds to cyber bandits or technical gremlins, such losses are likely to remain limited due to the relatively small size of the Ordinals economy. As the<a href="https://www.ordinalhub.com/price-tracking?dateRange=All&amp;page=1"> estimated total value</a> of all Ordinals collection at the time of this writing is currently around 1,628 BTC, worth some $45 million, nothing approaching the scale of the infamous fiascos that have plagued crypto is even possible at this stage:</p><figure>
        <img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk3OTg3MjYyMTc1MTI2Njg5/most-costly-crypto-hacks.jpg" height="337" width="620">
        
        
        <figcaption><a href="https://techmonitor.ai/technology/cybersecurity/biggest-cryptocurrency-hacks-of-all-time"><em>Source</em></a></figcaption>
    </figure><p>So much for playing defense. The fact is that Ordinals are attracting new users, developers, artists and companies to the Bitcoin space. This will surely have multiple benefits beyond the immediate boost to the value and prestige of the entire ecosystem. Onboarding more users of all kinds is the surest path to accelerating hyperbitcoinization. And if Bitcoin succeeds, the world will be liberated from the death grip of central banking — but let's put our ruby-quartz visor back on and refocus.</p><figure>
        <img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk3OTg3MjYyMTc1MTkyMjI1/cyclops-visor.jpg" height="310" width="620">
        
        
        <figcaption><a href="https://marvel.fandom.com/wiki/Cyclops%27_Visor"><em>Source</em></a></figcaption>
    </figure><p>While most early Bitcoiners got on board due to technical curiosity or ideological motivation, later adoption waves were likely driven by economic factors. Many of these later entrants stuck around because they realized<a href="https://twitter.com/ChadsBitcoin/status/1258854925884362755"> Bitcoin is a revolution disguised as a get-rich-quick scheme</a>. While we await the next bull cycle, Ordinals are attracting a fresh set of users, composed largely of young creatives. </p><p>Should we really turn these hopefuls away, to wander in the shitcoin swamps?</p><h2>The Solution</h2><p>Ordinals have proven the strong demand for Bitcoin NFTs, tokens and smart contracts. Although such things have been tried on Bitcoin in the past, through whatever confluence of factors, the time is now demonstrably ripe for them. A<a href="https://dune.com/dgtl_assets/bitcoin-ordinals-analysis"> quick glance</a> at inscription count over time (currently over five million after about five months) is enough to confirm this. The associated impact on fees has been equally obvious:</p><figure>
        <img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk3OTg3MjYyNDQzNTYyMTQ1/bitcoin-mempool-weight.jpg" height="269" width="620">
        
        
        <figcaption><a href="https://jochen-hoenicke.de/queue/#BTC,all,weight"><em>Source</em></a></figcaption>
    </figure><p>Note that the two previous spikes, around the starts of 2018 and 2021, coincided with the resolution of massive bull markets. From January of this year, the markets have been fairly calm and the latest spike is attributable to Ordinals. This raises the question of how horrifically high fees will get if the current Ordinals volume persists into the climax of another bull cycle... </p><p>In my view, this is the only critical issue presented by Ordinals; a looming problem with the potential to outweigh the benefit of the adoption boost. With <a href="https://decrypt.co/139259/bitcoin-ddos-ordinals-inscriptions-attack">fees hitting the 600-plus sat per virtual byte (vB) nosebleed levels</a> last seen in late 2017 and early 2018, Bitcoin might lose as many (or more) users to other chains as it gains from Ordinals.</p><p>The solution to high fees back in the day was the<a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/guides/what-is-segwit"> SegWit</a> soft fork, which greatly reduced the size and fees of conforming transactions. SegWit also enabled the launch of the Lightning Network, a layer atop Bitcoin designed to process low-value transactions. One quirk of Bitcoin is its flat fee and data structure, whereby the cost and block space required to send $1 in BTC is equal to those for sending $1 billion in BTC. Offloading low-value transactions to Lightning frees up block space, resulting in lower bitcoin fees. In combination, these two upgrades ensured that when bitcoin pushed to its all-time high in 2021, fees remained reasonable.</p><p><strong>So, why should the solution to high fees arising from Web3 stuff on Bitcoin be any different?</strong></p><p><a href="https://www.rgbfaq.com/">RGB</a>,<a href="https://lightning.engineering/posts/2022-9-28-taro-launch/"> Taro</a>,<a href="https://www.stacks.co/"> Stacks</a> — these are all technologies to shunt Web3 transactions and data from the Bitcoin blockchain and onto Layer 2. While the approach seen in Ordinals and Stamps of writing content directly to the base layer offers unrivaled permanence and immutability, it's also extremely costly. For example, an artist I spoke with recently told me that he spent $3,800 to inscribe a collection. Especially in these tough economic times, that's a lot for a young creative to gamble in an unpredictable market!</p><p>Consider that, as of this writing, 200 of the collections tracked by<a href="https://www.ordinalhub.com/price-tracking?dateRange=All&amp;page=1&amp;sort=volume_btc%3Aasc"> OrdinalHub</a> have seen <em>zero</em> all-time volume, as in no sales at all. This figure barely scratches the surface of market failures. Sorting the 1,000-plus collections on <a href="https://bestinslot.xyz/ordinals/collections/#order=7d_sales_asc&amp;page=35">Best In Slot</a> by inverse weekly sales volume reveals hundreds with zero sales.<a href="https://ordinalswallet.com/collections"> See for yourself</a> how many low-value collections on Ordinals Wallet have had zero volume or sales over the last week. Pending a proper analysis, my intuition is that fewer than one in 100 inscriptions listed on a marketplace will turn a profit.</p><p>The novelty of Ordinals will fade, but the high costs will remain. Given that Layer 2 solutions don't store data on the blockchain, their creation costs will be orders of magnitude lower. High-end collections, like<a href="https://arthodl.net/2023/04/05/bugatti-and-asprey-bringing-high-tech-faberge-style-eggs-to-ordinals/"> Asprey Bugatti Eggs</a>, may still inscribe to Ordinals as the perceived luxury and maximum-permanence option, but the vast majority of creators will opt for the inexpensive alternatives still linked to Bitcoin, even if indirectly.</p><p>Cost isn't the only factor behind the inevitable migration of most users to Layer 2. The size constraints of Bitcoin blocks make bulky content (like high-resolution images or audio, complex code and all but the shortest video clips) unaffordable or even impossible to inscribe. With generative AI making it easy to create high-resolution image content — and soon audio and video content, too — how much longer will the average creator be content to pay a relative fortune to inscribe text and small, static images?</p><h2>Base Layer To Layer 2</h2><p>The way I see things playing out, Ordinals has proven the market demand for Bitcoin-based NFTs, tokens, DeFi, etc. — as unpalatable as some may find that demand. Regardless, the cost and relative slowness of these assets on the base layer should eventually drive most users to Layer 2 solutions, already nearing completion. The base layer will perhaps become the digital equivalent of the Louvre, housing only the most significant works under the tightest security. Layer 2 will host everything else.</p><p>Ordinal antagonists should take note. Twitter screeds denouncing inscribers as attackers for adding monkey JPEGs to the blockchain only incite hilarity and encourage defiance. A $100 or even a $25 inscription fee is a far more effective disincentive, already established and requiring no keyboard bashing. To defuse the looming threat of high fees, the proactive strategy would be to contribute or donate to the development of Layer 2 solutions.</p><p><em>This is a guest post by Steven Hay. Opinions expressed are entirely their own and do not necessarily reflect those of BTC Inc or Bitcoin Magazine.</em></p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkwMjY2NTkxMzgyODczMjQx/bitcoin-lightning-network.png"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk3OTg3MjYyNDQzNTYyNzgx/rug-pull.jpg" height="310" width="620" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk3OTg3MjYyMTc1MTI2Njg5/most-costly-crypto-hacks.jpg" height="337" width="620" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk3OTg3MjYyMTc1MTkyMjI1/cyclops-visor.jpg" height="310" width="620" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk3OTg3MjYyNDQzNTYyMTQ1/bitcoin-mempool-weight.jpg" height="269" width="620" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Decoding Bitcoin’s Transaction Surge: The Emergence Of History’s Greatest Accounting Innovation]]></title><description><![CDATA[The rise of Ordinals has brought massive transaction volume to Bitcoin and its promise as a historic accounting innovation is starting to show.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/accounting-for-bitcoin-transaction-spike</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/accounting-for-bitcoin-transaction-spike</guid><category><![CDATA[Ordinals]]></category><category><![CDATA[Accounting]]></category><category><![CDATA[mempool]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Transactions]]></category><category><![CDATA[Opinion]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Darin Feinstein]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkxNDAxMTQ0NTc1MDc1ODcz/border-wallets-seed-phrase-recovery-top-photo.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p><em>This is an opinion editorial by Darin Feinstein, the co-founder and co-chairman of Bitcoin mining firm Core Scientific.</em></p><p>The <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/08/binance-lifts-block-on-bitcoin-withdrawals-amid-heavy-volumes.html">recent surge in transaction volume</a> on the Bitcoin network has sparked conversation and debate about <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/technical/bitcoins-high-fees-create-controversy-and-challenges">heightened transaction fees</a> and Bitcoin's overall goals and purpose. This has resulted in questions regarding the network's future and its ability to handle the increasing demand. </p><p>In response to those questions, it can be helpful to consider the intricacies of Bitcoin’s transaction volume through an accounting lens, as the Bitcoin network, at its foundation, is an accounting ledger with its data written to a public chain and recorded forever. Through this lens, we’ll delve into why Bitcoin’s transaction volume matters, how often such surges will occur and whether or not this growth is sustainable.</p><h2>The Accounting Innovation Of Bitcoin</h2><p>As an accounting ledger, Bitcoin represents the first true accounting innovation in <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Double-entry_bookkeeping">more than 700 years</a>, marking a transition from the legacy, stakeholder-controlled, <em>private</em>, double-entry accounting systems to a <em>public</em>, triple-entry system. </p><p>“Triple entry” simply means that two-party transactions (debit and credit) are written to a public, immutable ledger (the third entry). “Public” means that the ledger is accessible at any time by anyone on the Bitcoin network.</p><p>The accounting innovation here is simply the removal of stakeholders (humans) in exchange for machines (aka, servers and nodes) that run difficulty-adjusted proof of work (PoW). Bitcoin uses PoW to substantiate the entries, instead of relying on stakeholders who may be biased or incentivized to commit fraud or manipulate the ledgers. This means that the miners and nodes control the network in an unbiased, free-from-manipulation environment, not humans.</p><p>In contrast, all legacy accounting technologies relied on trusted third parties, known as the “stakeholders.” The fatal problem with a stakeholder-controlled system is that humans are flawed, and the ledgers are subject to human error, fraud, censorship and manipulation.</p><p>Until Bitcoin, every government, every bank, and every corporation on earth has used private, double-entry accounting systems controlled 100% by the stakeholders. This means that the stakeholders can alter the books and records of all of these legacy systems in secret, away from the public eye. In order to catch fraud, corruption or even error, the entire stakeholder-controlled system — including every transaction traced back to its root — would need to be audited. This process is time consuming, complicated and cumbersome, and like all legacy systems, the audits are conducted by humans, further subjecting the audit system to fraud, corruption and error. </p><p>Bitcoin solves this in three ways:</p><ol><li>By turning private ledgers into public ledgers</li><li>By removing stakeholder control and using difficulty-adjusted PoW to record transactions</li><li>By eliminating the need for a human audit as the network self-audits the timechain, every block</li></ol><p>Altogether, this creates the first unalterable ledger in human history.</p><h2>Accounting For The Truth With Bitcoin</h2><p>Accounting can be simply viewed as verifying the truth of the data involved. The role of accounting is to ensure that the data you are being shown is true. And accounting has never been more important in society than it is today, as truth is under constant attack in every arena. All systems rely on accounting, and the massive amount of available information makes discerning the truth difficult.</p><p>Truth is the most important commodity on the planet earth. How do you record the truth, aggregate the truth and then disseminate the truth if all the records are corruptible by humans?</p><p>Because the Bitcoin ledger is public, self-auditing and immutable, it cannot be corrupted or altered by any human. Never before in the history of record keeping could you rely on ledger to be 100% truthful, until the invention of Bitcoin.</p><p>If you are a member of a legacy, stakeholder-dominated business that relies on legacy accounting, and you have been historically able to manipulate the truth via control of the ledgers, a Bitcoin ledger is fatal.</p><p>In terms of who controls the information on ledgers, at the top of the food chain are totalitarian governments that want to control the truth. Bitcoin decimates these systems as the government, as key stakeholders, no longer has control of the information/data. That is why Bitcoin is <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/bitcoin-is-a-trojan-horse-for-freedom">often referred to as a “Trojan horse.”</a> On its face, it's presented as a technology based on money, but diving deeper, Bitcoin represents a new accounting technology that will provide increased freedom to the people within every nations' borders.</p><p>When you give people immutable data that cannot be seized, you give them freedom in the form of property rights, sound/hard money, truth, control and much more.</p><h2>Bitcoin Will Be The Ledger Of Choice For Everything</h2><p>The somewhat abbreviated way of explaining the “why” motivating people to choose Bitcoin to transact on is that the underlying ledger controlling the data is the best ledger system ever invented, free from fraud, control and manipulation, and providing freedom to those who use it. </p><p>Simply put: If you value the data you wish to record, you are incentivized to choose the only ledger in human history that will record it for eternity without being subject to human manipulation.</p><p>If you believe that an immutable unalterable ledger is superior to legacy, alterable, stakeholder ledgers, intuition suggests that all data will eventually be recorded on the Bitcoin network, from wills and trust, to corporate data, to climate data, to vaccine data, to title/ownership data and so on. The list of possibilities is endless. </p><p>All businesses, governments, and banks rely on ledgers. Nearly all industries have made groundbreaking discoveries and inventions since their inception, except for accounting. After 700 years, triple-entry systems have just now been invented (double entry <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Double-entry_bookkeeping">was invented in earnest in the 1400s</a>), and legacy stakeholder hesitance to accept an analog system moving to a digital, unalterable system should be questioned.</p><h2>Ordinals Are Just The Beginning</h2><p>Ordinals and NFTs are important to some people. The beauty of a free system is that everyone has the option to pursue what has value to them. If you believe they have zero value, you do not have to engage with them, but Bitcoin as a free market will not censor certain transactions because others do not value them. The network will always allow for innovation and free choice. Those who want to pay the appropriate fee can record Ordinals or NFT transactions on the Bitcoin network. The Bitcoin mempool in the future will always have a base layer of transactions waiting for the fees to drop low enough to be written on chain.</p><p>Since all data will want to be recorded on this network, this will not be the first or last time there is a wait to record your transaction. For smaller transactions, there are Layer 2 solutions, such as the Lightning Network, that live on top of Bitcoin and can be used immediately. Ordinals and NFTs all might go away in the future, and the transaction volume might wane, but eventually they will be replaced by other projects that similarly want to utilize this ledger, the cycle will repeat no matter what the product or data is.</p><p>Since the Bitcoin innovation is the removal of the requirement to trust the stakeholders, anyone who is advocating to censor the Bitcoin network's content is inherently anti-Bitcoin or does not understand Bitcoin. Those who seek to exploit control and power over the Bitcoin network are the exact problem that Bitcoin solves for.</p><p>As the world realizes that the only way to preserve truth (i.e., data and information) is on the Bitcoin network, the traffic will increase. This increased traffic creates a robust atmosphere for entrepreneurs to build on top of the Bitcoin network and a variety of products and services will emerge that aggregate content and write to the Bitcoin base layer.</p><p>Bitcoin fear, uncertainty and doubt (FUD) is spread by those who are challenged or fear this technology — understanding this network is no small task, it takes thousands of hours. Anyone who says they understand Bitcoin after a cursory examination is lying or ignorant. Similarly, transaction fee FUD is generated by people arguing both sides, that there are both too few transactions to support the network as well as too many transactions to support the network. </p><p>The truth is that the network is working as intended, and a full mempool that requires free market discovery to price transactions is unavoidable and thus, intended.</p><p>Accounting is the operating system that runs the world. All systems and information need to be honestly recorded, analyzed and then truthfully distributed in order to make sense of the data. Historically, ledgers have been protected by physical human violence, which means whoever has the monopoly on violence (aka, governments) can alter the records and/or its distribution. </p><p>Recording truth on the Bitcoin ledger is the only way to record data that does not rely on human violence to protect or disseminate it, for the first time in history.</p><p><em>This is a guest post by Darin Feinstein. Opinions expressed are entirely their own and do not necessarily reflect those of BTC Inc or Bitcoin Magazine.</em></p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkxNDAxMTQ0NTc1MDc1ODcz/border-wallets-seed-phrase-recovery-top-photo.png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Zoltan Pozsar, Who Just Left Credit Suisse, Addresses Issues Facing The Federal Reserve And The Dollar At Bitcoin 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[Markets analyst Zoltan Pozsar addressed issues facing the Fed, the dollar’s diminishing power and whether bitcoin can be the world’s money.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/markets/zoltan-pozsar-on-bitcoin-financial-system</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/markets/zoltan-pozsar-on-bitcoin-financial-system</guid><category><![CDATA[u.s. dollar]]></category><category><![CDATA[Bitcoin 2023]]></category><category><![CDATA[banks]]></category><category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Peter Chawaga]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 23:38:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk4MDkwMzUyMTI3NjQ4OTU4/zoltan-pozsar-bitcoin-2023.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p>Zoltan Pozsar, who <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/zoltan-pozsars-writing-is-dense-esoteric-and-a-hit-now-hes-left-credit-suisse-f2ec2483">until recently</a> worked as the managing director of investment bank Credit Suisse, offered his insight into financial markets and the issues that are weakening the dollar’s dominance around the world.</p><p>In his role at Credit Suisse, Pozsar’s insight into the ins and outs of the legacy financial system and market dynamics was highly sought after. His recent departure from the bank came shortly after <a href="https://www.investopedia.com/what-happened-at-credit-suisse-and-why-did-it-collapse-7369825">it was purchased by UBS in March</a> as an attempt to keep it from collapsing amid <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/markets/recap-of-last-weeks-banking-contagion-and-bitcoin">existential turmoil</a> for banks around the world. On stage at Bitcoin 2023, Pozsar addressed how U.S. banks have been impacted.</p><p>"This is basically an episode where the large banks are largely insulated from the problems," Pozsar said. "It's basically lessons in not being able to run interest rate risk, not knowing how to make a loan that will be weathering a rising interest rate storm.”</p><p>He described the Federal Reserve’s responses to these banking failures as only addressing “half the problem.”</p><p>“I think it's more like foaming the runway for any of the large banks that might be having problems down the road,” he added.</p><p>Pozsar was interviewed on stage by BitMEX co-founder Arthur Hayes, who pressed him on whether he owns any bitcoin.</p><p>“I don't own any,” Pozsar responded. “I'm observing it. I don't like to dabble in things that I don't understand well.”</p><p>Pozsar outlined his pessimism that bitcoin could ever really serve as money, as his historical research has shown him that money has to have a direct link to a government to endure. As a fundamentally decentralized, peer-to-peer network, Bitcoin could not support money that fits his definition.</p><p>“The one thing I will say about bitcoin is that money, if you will, is something that is purely public or a public-private partnership,” Pozsar explained. “When I look at Bitcoin, it’s a purely-private initiative. It’s clearly lacking a state link. But then again, things are evolving, there are a number of countries that have adopted bitcoin as a legal tender, so things are definitely in flux there.”</p><p>In his writing, Pozsar has underscored the <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/danrunkevicius/2022/03/10/after-this-war-is-over-money-will-never-be-the-same-what-credit-suisses-shocking-prediction-means-for-bitcoin-and-crypto-prices/?sh=2c32f3776c25">evolving role that Bitcoin is playing around the world as institution-backed money like the U.S. dollar becomes weaker</a>. At Bitcoin 2023, he listed several global market trends, including the rising economic power of China, that are threatening its role as the global reserve currency.</p><p>“There’s a number of changes happening that I think we need to keep an eye on because it’s all going to be at the expense of the dollar’s share of commodity finance, trade finance, share of reserve assets and so on,” Pozsar said.</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk4MDkwMzUyMTI3NjQ4OTU4/zoltan-pozsar-bitcoin-2023.jpg"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[The World’s Largest Bitcoin Conference Will Take Place In Nashville For 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[The Bitcoin Conference will be heading to Music City next year as it brings together Bitcoiners from around the world.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/industry-events/worlds-largest-bitcoin-conference-will-take-place-in-nashville-for-2024</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/industry-events/worlds-largest-bitcoin-conference-will-take-place-in-nashville-for-2024</guid><category><![CDATA[Nashville]]></category><category><![CDATA[Industry Events]]></category><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[The Bitcoin Conference]]></category><category><![CDATA[Events]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[BtcCasey]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 20:32:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk4MDg2MjkwOTY3NjM1MDE2/b24_press_release.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p><em>Disclaimer: The Bitcoin Conference and Bitcoin Magazine are both operated by BTC Inc.</em></p><p><a href="http://b.tc/conference">The Bitcoin Conference</a>, the world's largest and most prestigious gathering of the Bitcoin industry, is set to take place in Nashville, Tennessee, from July 25-27, 2024. The decision to move the conference to Nashville underscores the organizers' efforts to promote Bitcoin adoption beyond traditional financial centers. With a focus on fostering local adoption, the conference aims to unite thought leaders, industry experts and businesses in exploring the limitless possibilities presented by Bitcoin.</p><p>David Bailey, CEO of Bitcoin Magazine, expressed his optimism about Nashville's potential for Bitcoin growth, stating, "We believe that Nashville possesses the ideal blend of freedom-loving mindset and entrepreneurial spirit that will enable Bitcoin to thrive." The organizers are actively collaborating with local restaurants and businesses to ensure seamless bitcoin payments, transforming Nashville into a hub of bitcoin acceptance. The initiative seeks to empower both merchants and customers and establish a solid foundation for economic growth.</p><p>Mike Germano, President at BTC Inc., highlighted the significance of the conference for Nashville, stating, "We aim to foster a community where Bitcoin payments are widely accepted, unlocking new opportunities and creating a strong foundation for economic growth and preparing the city for bitcoiners to descend next July." The move has been met with enthusiasm by Bill Hagerty, United States Senator of Tennessee, who welcomed the conference, noting, "I couldn't be more excited that the 2024 Bitcoin Conference is coming to Nashville Tennessee."</p><p>Beyond the conference sessions, attendees can anticipate networking opportunities, exhibitions showcasing cutting-edge technology and interactive workshops aimed at educating and empowering individuals in the Bitcoin landscape. The inclusive environment fosters collaboration and meaningful connections among beginners and seasoned professionals alike.</p><p>Tickets for the conference are now available for purchase on the <a href="http://b.tc/conference/2024">official conference website</a>, with organizers advising interested individuals and organizations to secure their spots early due to the expected high demand. For sponsorship opportunities, media inquiries, or further information about the Bitcoin Conference, contact media@btcmedia.org.</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk4MDg2MjkwOTY3NjM1MDE2/b24_press_release.png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[First RGB-Powered NFT Marketplace Launches At Bitcoin 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[DIBA, the announced marketplace, also introduces the BitMask Bitcoin-only wallet capable of storing unique digital assets.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/first-rgb-powered-nft-marketplace-launches-at-bitcoin-2023</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/first-rgb-powered-nft-marketplace-launches-at-bitcoin-2023</guid><category><![CDATA[Business]]></category><category><![CDATA[RGB]]></category><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[NFTs]]></category><category><![CDATA[Marketplace]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[BtcCasey]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 18:54:43 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk0MzI5NzY4OTU4MjQwNDMz/bitcoin-price-market-analysis.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p><a href="https://diba.io">DIBA</a>, the first Bitcoin NFT marketplace utilizing <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/tags/rgb">RGB</a> smart contracts, has officially launched on mainnet. According to a press release sent to Bitcoin Magazine, the platform also introduces BitMask, an exclusive Bitcoin-only wallet capable of storing unique digital assets (UDAs) such as music and art. The UDAs will be hosted on high availability storage and cloud services provided by <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/tags/hut-8">Hut 8</a>, a publicly traded bitcoin miner in North America.</p><p>DIBA aims to bring Bitcoin utility to the masses by enabling the exchange of UDAs on a decentralized and censorship-resistant network. Notable bitcoin investors, including Tim Draper of Draper Associates and Bill Tai of ACTAI Unicorn Fund, support the venture. Gideon Nweze, founder and CEO of DIBA, expressed his excitement about the launch, stating, "This marks a major milestone in the transition of the internet onto Bitcoin."</p><p>Tim Draper also commended DIBA's innovative approach, emphasizing the potential of NFTs on Bitcoin. He said, "What Gideon and the team at DIBA have built is a testament to the potential NFTs on Bitcoin hold in capturing the creative and sovereign spirit of this next generation."</p><p>DIBA's partnership with Hut 8 is another example of the optimism surrounding Bitcoin and Layer 1 and 2 protocols. Josh Rayner, VP of High Performance Computing at Hut 8, expressed support for the Bitcoin NFT platform, stating, "We are bullish on Bitcoin and the potential of Layer 1 and 2 protocols, and are proud to support DIBA's Bitcoin NFT platform with high availability storage and cloud services."</p><p>According to the press release, the DIBA marketplace utilizes both the RGB smart contract protocol on Bitcoin, as well as the Lightning Network to maximize the efficiency of the marketplace’s functions.</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk0MzI5NzY4OTU4MjQwNDMz/bitcoin-price-market-analysis.png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Strike Expands Global Reach, Introduces USDT Support And Unveils Enhanced App At Bitcoin 2023 Conference]]></title><description><![CDATA[Strike announced its availability in 65 additional countries, a new app design and USDT support at Bitcoin 2023.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/strike-expands-globally-introduces-usdt-support-and-more-at-bitcoin-2023</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/strike-expands-globally-introduces-usdt-support-and-more-at-bitcoin-2023</guid><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strike]]></category><category><![CDATA[Wallet]]></category><category><![CDATA[Lightning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Business]]></category><category><![CDATA[app]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[BtcCasey]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 21:30:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk4MDY0MjU4MzIyMzQzMTAy/dscf3538-1.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p>At Bitcoin 2023 in Miami Beach, global bitcoin payments service <a href="https://strike.me">Strike</a> announced that their service is now available in 65 more countries spread across six continents. This coincides with the introduction of the ability to receive funds in U.S. dollar equivalents, namely USDT. In addition, the app received a major facelift and overhaul that has made the UI cleaner, the UX friendlier and also includes a new logo.</p><p>Many of the countries that have been requested by users of Bitcoin Twitter are now able to instantly send and receive money utilizing the Lightning Network. In an interview with Strike’s VP of Product, Manuela Rios, she explained that the app now has an effective reach of 3 billion people. </p><p>“With <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/bitcoin-enables-instant-fiat-transfers-to-africa">Send Globally,</a> the value prop is that you send dollars and receive as a local currency directly in a bank account on the other side … this one’s different — what we found through user research that people on the other side in jurisdictions with weak currencies would say ‘Hey this experience is amazing, but can I have a dollar equivalent?’” </p><p>In regards to purchasing Bitcoin, Rios said that “globally, you don’t see a seamless experience.” So the new Strike app also functions as a Lightning wallet where you can buy and sell bitcoin via dollar equivalent rails. </p><p>At his speech at Bitcoin 2023, Strike CEO Jack Mallers explained the wider vision of the updates, saying "We’re delivering a cash balance that the global south can rely on, and an awesome beautiful punk unconventional black and white brand, as the Fed is driving our own banks insolvent."</p><p>He also highlighted the company’s response to feedback, displaying a set of tweets asking for LNURL support, shortly after announcing that the new app has LNURL support — all <a href="mailto:usernames@strike.me">usernames@strike.me</a> function as a LNURL as of the launch.</p><p>“We made a lot of product changes to support what we hope to become an amazing global money app,” Mallers said. “As a company, we know what we’re fighting for, we know who we are, we changed the way we looked, but we never changed the way we felt.” </p><p>In addition to the new features and access, the app includes a simplified sign-up process in order to make signing up easier. “The end goal for us is to serve 7-8 billion people, and we’ll be stepping our way to make it to the countries that didn’t make it in this MVP,” Rios explained. </p><p>Rios explained the impact of the launch and additional features, saying that “For the Bitcoiners, you can expect a beautiful Lightning wallet and a cost effective way to buy bitcoin, and for the people not yet so familiar with bitcoin, but are familiar with 109% inflation, giving them access to a U.S. dollar equivalent stablecoin is massive — now you can save in something that won’t be so quickly devalued.”&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk4MDY0MjU4MzIyMzQzMTAy/dscf3538-1.jpg"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[‘Big Short’ Author Michael Lewis On The Financial Crisis, FTX And Bitcoin’s Freedom From Intermediaries]]></title><description><![CDATA[At Bitcoin 2023, best-selling author and journalist Michael Lewis shared his views on Bitcoin, FTX and the ills of the financial system.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/big-short-author-michael-lewis-on-bitcoin</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/big-short-author-michael-lewis-on-bitcoin</guid><category><![CDATA[Financial crisis]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[Bitcoin 2023]]></category><category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Peter Chawaga]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 21:06:32 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk4MDYzODk3Mjc2NTg5MTI4/bitcoin-2023-michael-lewis.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p>Best-selling author and journalist Michael Lewis, known for writing “The Big Short,” “Moneyball” and “The Blind Side,” offered his perspective on the current financial landscape and the rapidly-changing world of cryptocurrency on stage today at Bitcoin 2023.</p><p>“When I first encountered the idea of being able to use the blockchain technology to disintermediate financial intermediaries, I thought, ‘thank God,’” Lewis said of his realizations when first researching Bitcoin. “There are lots of unnecessary hands touching money when financial transactions occur. They've just been kind of hard baked into the system.”</p><p>As the author of “The Big Short,” Lewis outlined the fundamental inequalities and short-sighted policies of the contemporary financial system that led to the economic crisis of 2007 and 2008. At Bitcoin 2023, he acknowledged how Bitcoin is designed as an escape from the problems that caused that crisis.</p><p>“If you go back to Satoshi’s original paper, you know, line one, paragraph two, you eliminate the need for a trusted financial intermediary,” Lewis said. “Clearly, the very beginning of the spirit of the enterprise is mistrust of existing financial institutions, well earned mistrust, on the backend of the financial crisis.”</p><p>Across his books and news reporting, Lewis has been praised for his ability to condense complicated financial concepts into digestible prose and demonstrate systemic issues through the experiences of the individuals within them. This skillset makes him uniquely qualified to digest and interpret the emerging cryptocurrency ecosystem, which experienced unprecedented turmoil last year with the implosion of numerous crypto projects, <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/legal/ftx-files-for-bankruptcy-ceo-resigns">most notably FTX</a>. </p><p>At Bitcoin 2023, he discussed his next book and movie project, which will focus on FTX, and described some of the insight he gained from spending time with former CEO Sam Bankman-Fried before and after its collapse.</p><p>"Not in a million years did I think I was going to write about Sam Bankman-Fried," Lewis recalled, adding that he was first asked to meet with Bankman-Fried by a friend on Wall Street, and found himself intrigued by his unique personality. "There's so obviously the potential for a great movie in it... so you want to let people know it's out there."</p><p>Lewis was joined on stage by Arthur Hayes, the co-founder of cryptocurrency exchange BitMEX. Hayes asked Lewis if he owned bitcoin, and Lewis quipped that it was “in the FTX bankruptcy.”</p><p>Hayes and Lewis also touched on the current banking crisis, with Lewis sharing the view that things have not really changed in the institutional system since 2008 — that, if anything, things are worse for retail investors.</p><p>“It seems inherently unstable right now,” he said. “You essentially created a handful of institutions that are too big to fail, and everyone knows their deposits are insured, so no other institution can actually compete in that environment… It’s not going to end until there’s some structural reform.”</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk4MDYzODk3Mjc2NTg5MTI4/bitcoin-2023-michael-lewis.jpg"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Speaking At Bitcoin 2023, Tulsi Gabbard Describes How A U.S. CBDC Threatens Freedom]]></title><description><![CDATA[Former congresswoman and presidential candidate Tulsi Gabbard described how CBDCs threaten freedom at the Bitcoin 2023 event.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/tulsi-gabbard-on-u-s-freedom-at-bitcoin-2023</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/tulsi-gabbard-on-u-s-freedom-at-bitcoin-2023</guid><category><![CDATA[U.s.]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[cbdc]]></category><category><![CDATA[Bitcoin 2023]]></category><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Peter Chawaga]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 20:32:15 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk4MDYzMzM5NDY3NzExNjc4/tulsi-gabbard-bitcoin-2023.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p>Former congresswoman and presidential candidate Tulsi Gabbard addressed the audience at Bitcoin 2023 today, focusing on the institutional problems with U.S. politics and elected leaders who seek to consolidate power rather than serve constituents.</p><p>“I served in Congress for eight years and ran for president in 2020, and while we like to have this idea that we have great courageous leaders in Washington … unfortunately, that’s not the case,” Gabbard said. “Ultimately, they’re driven by a fear of losing power and losing control and, at the heart of it, they’re afraid of us. They’re afraid of a free society.”</p><p>In particular, she highlighted the Biden administration’s<a href="https://www.whitehouse.gov/briefing-room/statements-releases/2022/03/09/fact-sheet-president-biden-to-sign-executive-order-on-ensuring-responsible-innovation-in-digital-assets/"> exploration of a central bank digital currency (CBDC)</a>, underscoring how such a project would be antithetical to the privacy- and freedom-preserving qualities of cash transactions. As outlined in its white paper by Satoshi Nakamoto, “<a href="https://bitcoin.org/bitcoin.pdf">Bitcoin: A Peer-To-Peer Electronic Cash System</a>,” Bitcoin was designed to preserve these qualities in a digital way.</p><p>“The Biden administration’s move toward implementing a central bank digital currency is their latest effort towards exerting control and taking away our freedom,” Gabbard said. “No matter how many flowery words they use to deny that there is ill intent… no matter how many times they say, ‘Hey this is for your own good’... But ultimately, we know this is about their insatiable mission and desire for total control.”</p><p>She also suggested that those in power are combative toward or disinterested in Bitcoin because it cannot be manipulated by any third parties.</p><p>“You would think they would be interested in how Bitcoin is transforming the lives of people around the world, but they don’t actually care about people,” she said.</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk4MDYzMzM5NDY3NzExNjc4/tulsi-gabbard-bitcoin-2023.jpg"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Robert Kennedy Jr. Makes Campaign Debut At Bitcoin 2023: ‘Free Money Is As Important As Free Expression’]]></title><description><![CDATA[Making his first public appearance as a presidential candidate, Robert F. Kennedy Jr. outlined his vision for supporting Bitcoin and freedom in the U.S.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/robert-kennedy-jr-debuts-campaign-at-bitcoin-2023</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/robert-kennedy-jr-debuts-campaign-at-bitcoin-2023</guid><category><![CDATA[u.s. president]]></category><category><![CDATA[Politics]]></category><category><![CDATA[U.s.]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[Bitcoin 2023]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Peter Chawaga]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 18:37:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk4MDYxNDk3NzMyMDQ3OTQ0/robert-kennedy-jr-makes-campaign-debut-at-bitcoin-2023.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p>Robert F. Kennedy Jr. made his first public appearance as a presidential candidate at the Bitcoin 2023 conference today, sharing his own experiences with Bitcoin, warning about how technology is enabling government totalitarianism around the world and describing how he would protect the rights of Bitcoiners if elected president.</p><p>“As president, I will make sure that your right to hold and use bitcoin is inviolable,” Kennedy said. "I am an ardent defender and lifelong defender of civil liberties and Bitcoin is both an exercise and a guarantee of those freedoms.”</p><p>Kennedy told the crowd that he was first inspired by Bitcoin as a critical freedom technology after learning about how it was used to circumvent financial restrictions <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/how-bitcoin-fueled-canada-trucker-convoy">during the Canadian trucker protest last year</a>.</p><p>“None of these lawful and peaceful protestors had violated any law… But suddenly, they found that they could not access their money, their bank accounts to pay their mortgages or feed their families,” he recalled. “When I witnessed this … devastating use of government repression, I realized for the first time how free money is as important as free expression.”</p><p>Kennedy has publicly expressed his support for Bitcoin <a href="https://twitter.com/RobertKennedyJr/status/1653808786577010697?lang=en">since May 2023</a>, acknowledging its separation from other cryptocurrencies and indicating that legislators should support its development rather than hinder it, as with regulations like the <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/legal/biden-administration-proposes-30-tax-on-energy-used-by-bitcoin-miners">Biden administration’s proposed tax on energy used by miners</a>. On stage, he reinforced his distaste for such regulations and he outlined the steps his administration would take to drive Bitcoin innovation in the U.S.</p><p>"First, I will defend the right of self custody of bitcoin and other digital assets," he said. “Second, I will uphold the right to run a node at home… Third, I will defend use-neutral, industry-neutral regulation of energy… Fourth, I will make sure that the United States remains the global hub of Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies… I will reverse the government’s growing hostility toward this industry.” </p><p>Finally, he said that he would look closely at “whether individuals like Ross Ulbricht,” the founder of <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/silk-road-ross-ulbricht-from-prison">darknet, bitcoin-based marketplace Silk Road</a> who received a double life sentence in 2013, were prosecuted “for actual crimes, or as a means to crackdown on crypto.”</p><p>“I will consider pardoning them and I will act very quickly to do so,” Kennedy added.</p><p>Kennedy<a href="https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/robert-kennedy-jr-launches-long-shot-presidential-bid/story?id=98691944"> launched his Democratic primary bid</a> shortly before <a href="https://twitter.com/RobertKennedyJr/status/1653808786577010697?lang=en">signaling support for the Bitcoin industry on Twitter</a> and <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/industry-events/bitcoin-2023-is-robert-f-kennedy-jr-s-first-event-as-presidential-candidate">announcing his Bitcoin 2023 appearance</a>. His public stances on issues like vaccine mandates and climate change have contradicted those of most mainstream Democrats and he has positioned himself <a href="https://www.foxnews.com/media/rfk-jr-dems-party-war-americans-cant-afford-emergency">as a party outsider</a>. As of this writing, he sits in second place, though trailing by a significant margin, to Joe Biden <a href="https://www.racetothewh.com/2024/dem">in national polling average</a>.</p><p>At Bitcoin 2023, Kennedy clarified that he is not personally invested in bitcoin and announced that his presidential campaign would be the first in history to accept donations via the Lightning Network.</p><p>"We are now living in this age of turnkey totalitarianism ... and our job is to try and build and fortify democratic institutions at the same rate,” he concluded. “The biggest, most important one on the horizon is Bitcoin, because it can't be manipulated.”</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk4MDYxNDk3NzMyMDQ3OTQ0/robert-kennedy-jr-makes-campaign-debut-at-bitcoin-2023.jpg"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Governor Ridwan Kamil And Samson Mow Describe The Future Of Bitcoin In Indonesia At Bitcoin 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[The populous country would benefit greatly from taking advantage of the abundant renewable energy available.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/the-future-of-bitcoin-in-indonesia-at-bitcoin-2023</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/the-future-of-bitcoin-in-indonesia-at-bitcoin-2023</guid><category><![CDATA[Renewable Energy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Indonesia]]></category><category><![CDATA[Bitcoin 2023]]></category><category><![CDATA[Mining]]></category><category><![CDATA[Adoption]]></category><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[BtcCasey]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 15:13:36 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk4MDU4MjAxMzQ0NjQ4MjY0/keh_8762.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p>Governor of the Indonesian Province of West Java, Ridwan Kamil and prominent Bitcoin global advocate and JAN3 CEO Samson Mow, revealed in a fireside chat titled "The Indonesia Bitcoin Mining Campaign" that the government of Indonesia is researching various ways in which bitcoin adoption in the country could benefit its people.</p><p>Governor Kamil explained the specific environment that makes Indonesia a potential major player in the bitcoin mining space, saying “[Indonesia has] the second most geothermal potential in the world — more than 800 rivers with hydropower. As bitcoin allows the transformation of energy into money, bitcoin could be transformative for indonesia”</p><p>He also explained that the country is already on a steady path towards adoption, with more than 12 million cryptocurrency investors, 70% of which are invested in bitcoin. According to Governor Kamil, this number grows by half a million a year. </p><p>In addition, the Governor touched on how bitcoin could bring financial technology to people in his country who currently do not have access to that. “Bitcoin is a solution in my opinion to unbankable parts of my society,” he explained. “40% of my people are unbankable.” </p><p>Another topic touched on was the recent introduction of an Omnibus bill that allows for 100% foreign investment into renewable energy projects above 1 MW. This bill could lead to increased investment and attention in the region. “Come to indonesia, lets have this big reserve of renewable energy dedicated to the bitcoin mining business,” Governor Kamil said. </p><p>Mow touched on the opportunity at hand for Indonesia, saying that “The first [countries] that adopt bitcoin in a meaningful way will have a big advantage.” Afterwards, Governor Kamil inquired about the way that El Salvador’s bitcoin bonds function. Mow replied that “The bonds can finance the buildout of new energy infrastructure … Indonesia could have a volcano bond too.”</p><p>Overall, the talk indicated that Governor Kamil is cautiously optimistic, and that he sees bitcoin as a potential game changer for the economy of his country and the livelihood of his people. As a country with access to major amounts of renewable energy and large portions of the population unbanked, it is seemingly ripe for bitcoin adoption. </p><p>"The new generation is buying Bitcoin as a reserve," Governor Kamil concluded. “Hopefully Indonesia will be a Bitcoin heaven in the future."</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk4MDU4MjAxMzQ0NjQ4MjY0/keh_8762.jpg"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[The World’s Largest Payroll Providers Can Now Use Bitwage To Pay Employees In Bitcoin]]></title><description><![CDATA[Employers using payroll providers like ADP, Paychex and Paycom can now utilize Bitwage to easily pay their employees in their preferred currency.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/bitwage-announces-payroll-solution-compatible-with-major-providers</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/bitwage-announces-payroll-solution-compatible-with-major-providers</guid><category><![CDATA[Bitwage]]></category><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[Paycheck]]></category><category><![CDATA[Payroll]]></category><category><![CDATA[Business]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[BtcCasey]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 15:05:52 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkzODM5Njc4ODI5MzcyOTEy/network-nodes.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p><a href="https://www.bitwage.com">Bitwage</a>, a leading provider of Bitcoin payroll and invoicing, has introduced a solution that allows employers to seamlessly connect their payroll providers to Bitwage's service. This development simplifies and ensures compliance for workers who wish to receive a percentage of their paycheck in Bitcoin, stablecoins or USD. Notably, this solution is compatible with various payroll providers, including ADP, Paychex, Paycom, Gusto, Trinet and many others.</p><p>According to a press release sent to Bitcoin Magazine, what sets Bitwage apart is its non-custodial experience, ensuring that employees receive their payments directly into the wallet of their choice, maximizing security and minimizing risk. </p><p>To implement this solution, companies need to sign up on the Bitwage platform and connect their payroll provider through the Bitwage Automated Connection. From there, Bitwage creates a custom, post-tax benefit on the payroll provider's portal, allowing employees to opt-in. Employees can then choose the amount they wish to be deducted from their paycheck and distributed through Bitwage.</p><p>With each pay cycle, Bitwage automatically generates a payroll for each employee based on their payroll preferences, extracting the necessary data directly from the payroll system. Employees can receive their payments directly into their preferred Bitcoin, crypto or stablecoin wallet or even as their local currency into their bank accounts.</p><p>Bitwage's CEO, Jonathan Chester, emphasized their mission to enable workforces to be paid in their preferred method, whether it's bitcoin or fiat. “We recognize that crypto can be scary for employers, so to enable this mission, we are building out fully compliant solutions and removing the complexities and custodial risk of crypto from the equation,” Chester said.</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkzODM5Njc4ODI5MzcyOTEy/network-nodes.png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Brink Announces $1 Million Donation-Matching Campaign From Marathon Digital Holdings For Bitcoin Development]]></title><description><![CDATA[Marathon Digital Holdings will match donations made to Brink to support Bitcoin development, for as much as a $1 million total this year.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/brink-million-dollar-bitcoin-donation-campaign</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/brink-million-dollar-bitcoin-donation-campaign</guid><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[brink]]></category><category><![CDATA[development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Bitcoin 2023]]></category><category><![CDATA[Marathon Digital Holdings]]></category><category><![CDATA[Donations]]></category><category><![CDATA[Business]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Peter Chawaga]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 21:43:13 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk4MDQxMjk5NTc0NTk2Njgw/bitcoin-2023-brink-marathon-digital-donation-campaign.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p>On stage at the Bitcoin 2023 conference, <a href="https://brink.dev/">Brink</a> announced a matching campaign for donations from Bitcoin mining firm <a href="https://marathondh.com/">Marathon Digital Holdings</a> to support the work of Bitcoin Core developers. Marathon will match donations made to Brink on a two-for-one basis for the duration of the conference, which ends on May 20, and then match donations one for one through the end of the year, up to $1 million total.</p><p>“We’re going to match dollar for dollar $500,000-worth of donations that Brink receives for Core developers. More importantly, we will donate two-for-one if you donate money during this conference,” said Fred Thiel, Marathon’s CEO. “So, if you believe in the importance of supporting Core development efforts … then I strongly urge you (to) donate 50 cents, $1, whatever you can during the conference.”</p><p>By committing to match all third-party donations up to an aggregate of $500,000 until December 31, 2023, Marathon hopes to advance Brink’s support for the developers who maintain and upgrade Bitcoin’s code. <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/technical/john-newberys-new-nonprofit-brink-will-train-and-support-bitcoin-developers">Since 2020</a>, Brink has supported numerous developers in their work to make Bitcon more accessible and advanced through grants, mentorship and education, including <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/bitcoin-non-profit-brink-funds-11-bitcoin-lightning-developers">former lead maintainer Marco Falke, Lightning Network white paper author Tadge Dryja</a> and <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/bitcoin-non-profit-brink-funds-11-bitcoin-lightning-developers">Bitcoin Core PR Review Club’s Gloria Zhao</a>.</p><p>“We have nine developers in five different countries that are all independent developers funded by Brink,” explained Mike Schmidt, the executive director of Brink. “I think we would all agree that we would want this Bitcoin software that’s powering all of this innovation on top to be better reviewed, better tested, better maintained, easier to run and more performant. So that’s why at Brink we fund grantees that are spending upwards of 50% of their time on testing and reviewing the Bitcoin Core code, proposing changes to the Core codebase and basically making that software more secure.”</p><p>Donations made to Brink through <a href="https://brink.dev/donate">its website</a> are now eligible for the match. Thiel framed the campaign as part of Marathon’s larger commitment to securing the Bitcoin network as a significant contributor of hash rate, the computing power that ensures Bitcoin’s immutability.</p><p>“We believe that it’s the most secure protocol out there and we think we and the rest of the industry should do everything they can to support the developers and really foment as much activity in the space as possible,” Thiel said.&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk4MDQxMjk5NTc0NTk2Njgw/bitcoin-2023-brink-marathon-digital-donation-campaign.jpg"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[IBEX Mercado Announces Partnership With Grupo Salinas Bringing Lightning Access To Millions Of Mexican Citizens]]></title><description><![CDATA[The partnership kicked off with one of Mexico’s largest internet providers, Total Play, partnering with IBEX to integrate bitcoin Lightning payments.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/bitcoin-lightning-service-ibex-mercado-announces-partnership-with-grupo-salinas</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/bitcoin-lightning-service-ibex-mercado-announces-partnership-with-grupo-salinas</guid><category><![CDATA[Ricardo Salinas]]></category><category><![CDATA[Mexico]]></category><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[Lightning]]></category><category><![CDATA[IBEX Mercado]]></category><category><![CDATA[Business]]></category><category><![CDATA[IBEX]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[BtcCasey]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 21:42:41 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkyODY4MzAyMTgyMjI5NzEy/markets-price-chart.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p><a href="https://www.poweredbyibex.io/">IBEX Mercado</a>, a bitcoin Lightning payment service provider, has announced a new partnership with Grupo Salinas, one of the largest corporate conglomerates in Mexico.</p><p>“Over four million Mexicans can now pay with bitcoin for their cable, internet, and phone service,” IBEX’s CEO Jose Lemus said on stage as he announced the partnership. “With this partnership, we’re opening the doors to every bitcoin and Lightning company and financial tech company that wants to leverage Lightning technology … [we will be] rolling out new technology with Grupo Salinas that will enable mexicans to pay their groceries with bitcoin, electronics and to receive remittances.” Lemus explained his excitement about the announcement, saying that this is the “tip of the iceberg of what will go on in Mexico.” </p><p>The collaboration signifies a major step in Mexico's adoption of bitcoin and Lightning. In addition, the integration of Lightning payments via IBEX with Total Play opens up new possibilities for fast and efficient transactions for Total Play customers.</p><p>“The true value of this technology is not about paying for a cup of coffee in a different way,” Lemus said. “In a world where we’re going to have increasing digitization of our products and services, we need better payment technology … we did not have a good enough payments technology — but now we do, with Lightning.” </p><p>Integration of bitcoin Lightning in Grupo Salinas’ products and services via IBEX can place Mexico at the forefront of the digital revolution, providing citizens with a secure, modern and efficient payment option.</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkyODY4MzAyMTgyMjI5NzEy/markets-price-chart.png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[MicroBT Releases New Line Of WhatsMiner M50 Series At Bitcoin 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[The M50S++, M53S++ and M56S++ boast impressive stats that maximize efficiency while simultaneously boosting potential environmental benefits.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/microbt-releases-new-line-of-whatsminer-m50-series</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/microbt-releases-new-line-of-whatsminer-m50-series</guid><category><![CDATA[Mining]]></category><category><![CDATA[MicroBT]]></category><category><![CDATA[whatsminer]]></category><category><![CDATA[Business]]></category><category><![CDATA[Asics]]></category><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[Bitcoin 2023]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[BtcCasey]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 20:25:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkwOTE3NzExNjQ2MTcyNzU3/aa-btc-4.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p>MicroBT, the Bitcoin ASIC manufacturer behind the <a href="https://www.whatsminer.com/index.html">WhatsMiner</a> line of ASIC mining machines, unveiled its latest offerings at Bitcoin 2023 in Miami Beach. Dr. Zuoxing Yang, the founder and CEO of MicroBT, highlighted the importance of "High density, low noise, low failure rate and low maintenance” ASIC machines bringing bitcoin mining to a new era.</p><p>The talk started with a roll of film focusing on the energy crisis, green energy and the role that bitcoin can play as a solution. It then posed the question: “What matters more, mining or surviving?” </p><p>“I never stop thinking of better power solutions for bitcoin mining,” Dr. Yang said. </p><p>MicroBT introduced three new models of the WhatsMiner M50 series: the air-cooled M50S++, the hydro-cooled M53S++, and the immersion cooled M56S++. These models offer impressive computing power ranging from 150 to 320 terahash/second (TH/s) respectively, with power efficiencies of 22 joules per terahash (J/TH).</p><p>Dr. Yang highlighted the heat collection capabilities of the mining rigs, which can be utilized for various purposes, such as space heating and industrial processes. He mentioned that the hydro-cooling mining rigs can reach outlet water temperatures of over 70℃ (158℉), enabling 2.4MW of power for a 40-foot container. Additionally, the immersion-cooling solution requires only 10L of oil per miner, demonstrating its efficiency.</p><p>He emphasized that “every M56 miner only requires as low as 10L oil with our specified tank.” </p><p>MicroBT's focus since its inception in 2016 has been the development of high-efficiency Bitcoin mining rigs. The company aims to support miners in adhering to Bitcoin's decentralization principles while prioritizing network stability. Dr. Yang emphasized MicroBT's commitment to working with partners to promote sustainable mining practices, zero-carbon emissions and social responsibility.</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkwOTE3NzExNjQ2MTcyNzU3/aa-btc-4.png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[BitMEX To Send Physical Bitcoin To The Moon In Partnership With Astrobiotic Technology And Bitcoin Magazine]]></title><description><![CDATA[A physical coin loaded with 1 BTC, along with the Genesis Block text, will venture beyond the atmosphere on a space launch this summer.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/bitmex-to-send-physical-bitcoin-to-the-moon</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/bitmex-to-send-physical-bitcoin-to-the-moon</guid><category><![CDATA[Moon]]></category><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[Moon Landing]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Bitmex]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[BtcCasey]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 19:55:12 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkzMjU1NjA1NDIxNDgzNTg3/bitcoin-to-the-moon.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p>BitMEX, a leading bitcoin derivatives exchange, has announced that it will be sending the first physical bitcoin to the Moon in partnership with Astrobotic Technology Inc. and Bitcoin Magazine. The rocket carrying a physical Bitcoin wallet is scheduled to launch from the Kennedy Space Center this summer, marking a significant milestone for both space exploration and the bitcoin industry.</p><p>The bitcoin, engraved with a public address and private key, is loaded with 1 BTC and will become the first-ever financial asset sent to space. This endeavor symbolizes the exploration of Bitcoin's use cases beyond Earth and opens up possibilities for future interaction with the token. Stephan Lutz, Acting CEO and Group CFO at BitMEX, expressed pride in the achievement, stating, "This is not just an achievement for BitMEX, but a breakthrough in human history."</p><p>According to a press release sent to Bitcoin Magazine, the mission has undergone rigorous testing and preparation to ensure the Bitcoin wallet's readiness for space flight.</p><p>In addition to the physical bitcoin, the text of the Genesis Block, the first block of Bitcoin ever mined, will be carried to the Moon as a homage to Satoshi's protocol. The Genesis Block will be displayed on a metal plate with raw hex data and a hologram of the Bitcoin Magazine logo.</p><figure>
        <img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk4MDgzODE0OTE4OTg4ODcy/bitcoin-moon-rock---front.jpg" height="464" width="620">
        
        
        
    </figure><figure>
        <img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk4MDgzODE0OTE5MDU0NDA4/bitcoin-moon-rock---left-34.jpg" height="464" width="620">
        
        
        
    </figure><p>A replica of the coin and Genesis Block metal plate, placed on a "moon rock" will be auctioned in partnership with Bitcoin Magazine at Bitcoin 2023. In addition, a limited edition series of commemorative coins and Ordinals will be auctioned closer to the launch date.</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkzMjU1NjA1NDIxNDgzNTg3/bitcoin-to-the-moon.png"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk4MDgzODE0OTE4OTg4ODcy/bitcoin-moon-rock---front.jpg" height="464" width="620" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk4MDgzODE0OTE5MDU0NDA4/bitcoin-moon-rock---left-34.jpg" height="464" width="620" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lava Introduces Self-Custody Wallet And Bitcoin DeFi Platform At Bitcoin 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[Lava utilizes discreet log contracts and other Bitcoin-native mechanisms to provide a full-fledged Bitcoin financial service platform.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/lava-introduces-self-custody-wallet-and-bitcoin-defi-platform</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/lava-introduces-self-custody-wallet-and-bitcoin-defi-platform</guid><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[Self Custody]]></category><category><![CDATA[Wallet]]></category><category><![CDATA[dlcs]]></category><category><![CDATA[defi]]></category><category><![CDATA[Lending]]></category><category><![CDATA[Business]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[BtcCasey]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 16:54:13 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkxNzU0OTcxNDk3MTEzMjUx/20220819_best-sidechain-recap---shinobi.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p><a href="http://lava.xyz/">Lava</a>, a financial technology company, has unveiled a new self-custody wallet and decentralized finance (DeFi) platform on Bitcoin. Utilizing Lava's loan protocol, users can borrow stablecoins against native bitcoin, eliminating the risks associated with bridge hacks and custodian rehypothecation.</p><p>CEO Shehzan Maredia highlighted the advantages of Lava's borrowing mechanism, stating, "With Lava, people can borrow transparently without rehypothecation risk and without relying on bridges or custodians. Users won't have to trust their counterparty and can borrow using a system that gives users cryptographic assurance that the rules of their contracts will be honored." Lava achieves this through invisible smart contracts called <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/technical/dlcs-on-lightning-and-bitcoin-smart-contracts">discreet log contracts</a> (DLCs), which ensure collateral integrity and enable programmable loan initiation and repayment without the need for intermediaries.</p><p>According to a press release sent to Bitcoin Magazine, Lava wallet aims to empower individuals who face challenges with traditional banking, offering innovative security solutions and safety checks to prevent transaction errors. Maredia said that he envisions bitcoin and dollars as the two most crucial assets of the coming decade. Lava's goal, the press release stated, is to create a bitcoin and dollar-centric financial experience that grants users true financial freedom, enabling them to take control of their finances and simplify money management.</p><p>In an interview, Maredia expressed gratitude to his cofounder, team, investors, and supporters, emphasizing that this is only the beginning for Lava. The company said it intends to continue advancing its mission of making finance sovereign and simple.</p><p>Lava's self-custody wallet is currently available on mobile platforms, including iOS and Android, with plans for additional interfaces in the future. </p><p>The company said it intends to differentiate itself from other self-custody wallets through its user-centered financial utility experience including offering borrowing against bitcoin, direct purchases of bitcoin and stablecoins, seamless bank account transfers and simplified transactions. Security is a top priority — Lava stated that there will be future enhancements like collaborative custody and cold wallet integration.</p><p><em>Disclosure: Lava is a portfolio company of BTC Inc., the parent company of Bitcoin Magazine.</em></p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkxNzU0OTcxNDk3MTEzMjUx/20220819_best-sidechain-recap---shinobi.png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cash App, Lighting Labs, Lightspark Executives Discuss Bringing Bitcoin Payments To The World]]></title><description><![CDATA[In a panel discussion at Bitcoin 2023, leaders from some of the largest Bitcoin-focused companies discussed building on the Lightning Network.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/building-lightning-network-companies</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/building-lightning-network-companies</guid><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[Lightspark]]></category><category><![CDATA[Cash App]]></category><category><![CDATA[Lightning network]]></category><category><![CDATA[Business]]></category><category><![CDATA[Lightning Labs]]></category><category><![CDATA[Bitcoin 2023]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Peter Chawaga]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 16:13:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk4MDM2MTQxNTg3MzEwMDE5/fwbgj1mwaaqn5h9.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p>In a panel discussion at the Bitcoin 2023 conference moderated by CNBC technology reporter <a href="https://twitter.com/KenzieSigalos">MacKenzie Sigalos</a>, leaders from some of the biggest businesses building services based on the Lightning Network discussed the opportunities and challenges for Bitcoin’s payments-focused second layer protocol.</p><p>The discussion, titled “Building Lightning-Native Companies,” featured <a href="https://twitter.com/starkness">Elizabeth Stark</a>, the CEO of software development firm Lightning Labs; <a href="https://twitter.com/davidmarcus">David Marcus</a>, the CEO of <a href="https://www.lightspark.com/">Lightspark</a>, a firm focused on making Lightning adoption easier and more accessible; and <a href="https://twitter.com/milessuter">Miles Suter</a>, the Bitcoin product lead at <a href="https://cash.app/">Cash App</a>, a mobile payment platform that <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/cash-app-enables-bitcoin-lightning-payments-for-40-million-users">introduced Lighting payments to its more than 40 million users in 2022</a>.</p><p>"We've really reached the point right now where Lightning is maturing and we're seeing more and more adoption,” Stark said, summarizing the momentum she has seen since she co-founded Lightning Labs in 2016. “People are adopting the network because it is solving real problems for them."</p><p>By allowing peers to create closed payment channels between themselves, which are only settled on the underlying Bitcoin blockchain when closed, the Lightning Network <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/guides/lightning-network">enables bitcoin payments that can take place in seconds while still benefiting from the security of Bitcoin’s base ledger</a>. But as this second layer is <a href="https://lightning.network/lightning-network-paper.pdf">relatively young</a>, adoption represents <a href="https://bitcoinvisuals.com/lightning">just a fraction</a> of the larger digital payments volume across the world.</p><p>The panelists highlighted the importance of developing products and services that make Lightning easier to use and solve some of its outstanding issues, like the network’s relatively-low liquidity and limited number of nodes.</p><p>“A channel-based payment network is still very complicated,” Sigalos pointed out. “There’s not a ton of liquidity sitting on the nodes right now” for instance.</p><p>In response, Suter noted that many of the challenges in making Lightning more accessible derive from Bitcoin’s most important qualities.</p><p>"It's hard to develop on Bitcoin,” he explained. “We see that everyday... but it's an intentional decision because we believe that's what allows it to maintain a very minimal attack surface.”</p><p>But the panelists all agreed that when there are significant problems for Lightning to solve, like in countries where it can help people access the dollar or enable more efficient cross-border transactions, adoption is evident. As more of those problems emerge and companies like these continue to build products and services on top of Lightning, they expect adoption to accelerate.</p><p>“Making it easy will drive more adoption,” Marcus said. “Between now and next year when we gather again, we’ll be in a much better place when it comes to Lightning adoption.”</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk4MDM2MTQxNTg3MzEwMDE5/fwbgj1mwaaqn5h9.jpg"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Lightning Company Lightspark Introduces Lightspark Wallet SDK]]></title><description><![CDATA[The SDK is designed to offer businesses and platforms an easily accessible Lightning wallet experience.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/lightspark-introduces-lightspark-wallet-sdk</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/lightspark-introduces-lightspark-wallet-sdk</guid><category><![CDATA[Business]]></category><category><![CDATA[Lightning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Lightspark]]></category><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[BtcCasey]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkyNjA3MTM2MjI2NzQ4MTUz/20220926_good-gdog-proof-collaborative-custody-multisig-by-will-schoellkopf_.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p>Lightspark has announced the launch of the Lightspark Wallet SDK, a tool designed to enable businesses of all sizes the ability to offer their customers a Lightning wallet. According to a press release sent to Bitcoin Magazine, Lightspark aims to make the Lightning Network more accessible and mainstream, ensuring that payments are open, secure and instant.</p><p>The press release explained that the Lightspark Wallet SDK is the result of careful consideration of businesses' needs and feedback from customers. The SDK is tailored for seamless usage by businesses of all sizes and stages, the company stated, with easy integration and the ability to add unique UI and brand identity. It aims to simplify the complexity of Lightning payments, allowing businesses to focus on building exceptional user experiences without worrying about technical intricacies such as setting up channels and rebalancing liquidity.</p><p>The SDK also incorporates Lightspark Predict, which offers low latency, high payment success rates, and low costs, ensuring reliable and capital-efficient Lightning payments, according to the press release. By leveraging Lightspark Predict, the release explained, businesses gain better connectivity to the wider Lightning Network, enhancing reliability and certainty when sending and receiving Lightning payments.</p><p>Also highlighted by the company, were recent partnerships which proved the growing adoption of Lightning amongst businesses. Xapo Bank <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/xapo-bank-first-bank-to-offer-bitcoin-lightning">became the first bank to integrate</a> with the Lightning Network via Lightspark, allowing its members to pay for small purchases with bitcoin directly, without converting to USD first. </p><p>In addition, Lightspark highlighted partnerships with Rain, the largest crypto-asset platform in the MENA region, which is enabling its users to execute real-time bitcoin transactions using Lightspark, and Flexa, a digital commerce integration provider that has leveraged Lightspark “to help businesses navigate to the next era of commerce.”</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkyNjA3MTM2MjI2NzQ4MTUz/20220926_good-gdog-proof-collaborative-custody-multisig-by-will-schoellkopf_.png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[With Rushed Moratorium On Bitcoin Mining, North Carolina County Stifles Innovation]]></title><description><![CDATA[“This improperly-enacted moratorium is low-hanging fruit and Bitcoiners need to press public officials like those in Buncombe County…”]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/north-carolina-bitcoin-mining-moratorium</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/north-carolina-bitcoin-mining-moratorium</guid><category><![CDATA[Regulation]]></category><category><![CDATA[North Carolina]]></category><category><![CDATA[Opinion]]></category><category><![CDATA[Business]]></category><category><![CDATA[Bitcoin mining]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Dennis Fassuliotis]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTg4NDU1MzQ3MzAyNzA0NzU2/bitcoin-mining-asic-security.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p><em>This is an opinion editorial by Dennis Fassuliotis, founder of South Carolina Blockchain Inc. and co-founder of South Carolina Emerging Technology Association, Inc.</em></p><p>Why is the <a href="https://www.citizen-times.com/story/news/local/2023/05/04/buncombe-county-approves-a-1-year-moratorium-on-cryptocurrency-mining/70179529007/">Buncombe County, North Carolina moratorium on Bitcoin mining</a> so important?</p><p>Because they got caught. </p><p>There is a contagion running through Western North Carolina and this time, we know it was man made in a lab. It is called a “moratorium on bitcoin mining.” Its origins <a href="https://www.clayconc.com/_files/ugd/fe4bcd_163aefda66f243cfb4f8c41bd27ebce5.pdf">date back to August 2022 in Clay County</a>, and Buncombe County has mutated it into this newest strain based on broadly construing a North Carolina zoning statute to authorize a development moratorium. </p><p>When properly used, North Carolina’s <a href="https://www.ncleg.gov/EnactedLegislation/Statutes/PDF/BySection/Chapter_160D/GS_160D-107.pdf">development moratorium statute</a> <a href="https://www.sog.unc.edu/resources/legal-summaries/land-use-and-development-moratoria">seeks to ensure that a new type of development does not proceed until changes to regulations or environmental issues are appropriately addressed</a>. This allows for more effective planning and management of growth and development while minimizing potential negative impacts on the community.</p><p>Because a moratorium is a drastic restriction on property rights, the statute imposes conditions that an administrative authority must satisfy to get one. Even then, such a moratorium can only span <a href="https://www.ncleg.gov/EnactedLegislation/Statutes/PDF/BySection/Chapter_160D/GS_160D-107.pdf">a minimum of 61 days</a> and a maximum of one year, as noted by the planning commissioner <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=A3e09Xulteg">during a recent public briefing</a>. </p><p>In this case, Buncombe County commissioners, <a href="https://www.citizen-times.com/story/news/local/2023/05/04/buncombe-county-approves-a-1-year-moratorium-on-cryptocurrency-mining/70179529007/">under the direction of Planning Director Nathaniel Pennington</a>, argued that they needed a one-year moratorium on cryptocurrency mining in the unincorporated areas of Buncombe County <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=A3e09Xulteg">so they could study the industry</a> and “<a href="https://www.citizen-times.com/story/news/local/2023/05/04/buncombe-county-approves-a-1-year-moratorium-on-cryptocurrency-mining/70179529007/">craft standards for the newly-defined use.</a>” </p><p>But we already have a workable definition for a bitcoin mine, <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/legal/drive-bitcoin-right-through-south-carolina">as confirmed in my last opinion editorial</a>,<a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/legal/drive-bitcoin-right-through-south-carolina"> </a>where I referred to a bitcoin mine as a “digital asset data center.” So, let’s just simply define a “bitcoin mining center” as a data center that produces an intangible product. </p><p>That’s now where the rubber meets the road. At the February 2023 commission meeting, armed with the American Planning Association’s “<a href="https://www.planning.org/publications/document/9249180/">Zoning for Data Centers and Cryptocurrency Mining</a>,” <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=A3e09Xulteg">Pennington argued</a> that cryptocurrency mining centers don’t meet the definition of a data center under existing North Carolina law. </p><p>The North Carolina statute that enables data mining center tax breaks <a href="https://www.datacenterknowledge.com/archives/2015/10/01/north-carolina-makes-data-center-tax-breaks-easier-to-get">was enacted in 2015</a>, just six years after the birth of bitcoin. Consequently, most states, including North Carolina, are living with statutes tailored for centralized data center operations and incentives that were carved out to attract corporate data centers built by companies like Google, which include large campuses, consume vast amounts of water and require huge amounts of power. Qualified data centers receive sales tax exemption on electricity. </p><p>As a result, North Carolina’s data mining center laws <em>in practice</em> offer big money for the benefit of a select few tech corporations, but the overarching <em>intent</em> of this legal framework was to promote economic development in North Carolina. Rather than follow the original intent of the data center definition to create opportunities, it’s now the club that is being used to discourage siting digital asset data centers in some western North Carolina counties. </p><p>However, in his rush to pass an ordinance where there were no permit applications pending, the planning director failed to include a “statement of the problems or conditions necessitating the moratorium <em> </em>and [that’s the operative word] what courses of action, alternative to a moratorium, were considered … and why those alternative courses of action were not adequate,” as is required by the <a href="https://www.ncleg.gov/EnactedLegislation/Statutes/PDF/BySection/Chapter_160D/GS_160D-107.pdf">North Carolina General Assembly’s moratoria guidelines</a>.</p><p>So, in my eyes, the planning commission has failed to complete the due diligence legally required to impose a moratorium and appears to be acting with a bias intended to discourage Bitcoin miners from locating in Buncombe County. </p><p>Now that Buncombe County’s overreach has been caught and called out, do we catch and release or seize the opportunity to counter <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=A3e09Xulteg">unfounded claims</a> of e-waste, noise, water consumption and public safety concerns to get this moratorium overturned by the county’s commissioners or the court system?</p><p>This improperly-enacted moratorium is low-hanging fruit and Bitcoiners need to press public officials like those in Buncombe County who don’t do their job properly or exert a bias without doing their homework. Someone should be held accountable and, in this case, all fingers point in the direction of the Buncombe County Planning Commission and the American Planning Association. </p><p>The way in which Bitcoin mining is treated presents a pivotal moment for Buncombe County’s innovation economy. With their hastily and improperly enacted moratorium, Buncombe County’s commissioners failed to rise to the occasion. </p><p>Rather than ban a perfectly-legal activity that they do not fully understand, the commissioners could have created a countywide task force, but that was never presented as an option. A task force could study the pros and cons of digital assets, while planning could have a seat at the table and serve all of their constituents, not just a vocal minority. That should have been the objective. Instead, the adopted policy stifles innovation and advances a false narrative. </p><p>I know this has not gone unnoticed at the state level and the <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/legal/north-carolina-house-passes-bill-banning-cbdc-payments">recent <em>unanimous</em> vote to advance an anti-central-bank-digital-currency (CBDC) bill</a> after <a href="https://twitter.com/NC_Blockchain/status/1649571425726898176?s=20">public uproar</a> resulted in revising a prior anti-Bitcoin bill tells me that progress can be made. Education on all levels is still the key. Hopefully, the Buncombe County commissioners will learn to join the cause or miss out on one of the most important emerging tech industries driving adoption of the soundest money ever invented.</p><p><em>This is a guest post by Dennis Fassuliotis. Opinions expressed are entirely their own and do not necessarily reflect those of BTC Inc or Bitcoin Magazine.</em></p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTg4NDU1MzQ3MzAyNzA0NzU2/bitcoin-mining-asic-security.png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Foundation Devices Announces Standalone Envoy Bitcoin Mobile Wallet App]]></title><description><![CDATA[The announcement describes how the Envoy app will utilize Magic Backups to make recovery easy, alongside updates on the Passport wallet.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/foundation-announces-envoy-bitcoin-mobile-wallet-app</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/foundation-announces-envoy-bitcoin-mobile-wallet-app</guid><category><![CDATA[Apps]]></category><category><![CDATA[Wallet]]></category><category><![CDATA[Business]]></category><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[Foundation]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[BtcCasey]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 16:29:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkzMjU1NjA1NDIxNTQ5MTIz/technical-bitcoin-development-pixel.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p>Foundation Devices, a leader in Bitcoin-centric tools, has announced the launch of its Envoy mobile app as a standalone Bitcoin mobile wallet with enhanced features for account management and privacy.</p><p>According to a press release sent to Bitcoin Magazine, this update is part of Foundation's mission to make digital sovereignty more accessible and to lower the barriers to bitcoin self-custody. The new Envoy app introduces what Foundation is calling “Envoy Magic Backups,” a simplified setup and backup process for mobile wallets. The press release described how users can now start using the wallet in just 60 seconds without seed words and easily restore their wallet on any device with a few taps.</p><p>Zach Herbert, Co-Founder and CEO of Foundation, expressed his excitement about the update, stating, "With this update, we are excited to bring our best-in-class design, intuitive and approachable user experience, and peace of mind to smartphone users across the globe — no Passport required." </p><p>In addition to the introduction of the Envoy app, Foundation has also announced a price reduction for its Passport hardware wallet, now priced at $199. Customers who ordered within the last 90 days are eligible to claim a $50 gift card for the Foundation store. </p><p>Alongside this, Foundation released a major update to the Passport hardware wallet, introducing the Key Manager extension that enables powerful new tools such as child seeds and Nostr keys.</p><p>Herbert emphasized Foundation's commitment to accessibility, stating, "Foundation is committed to making Bitcoin and decentralized technologies accessible to everyone. These updates mark significant advancements in our mission to empower individuals to reclaim their digital sovereignty."</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkzMjU1NjA1NDIxNTQ5MTIz/technical-bitcoin-development-pixel.png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Relai Introduces Monthly Zero-Fee Bitcoin Purchases]]></title><description><![CDATA[Users of the Swiss Bitcoin app can now take advantage of one zero-fee bitcoin purchase up to 100 CHF/EUR monthly.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/relai-introduces-monthly-zero-fee-bitcoin-purchases</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/relai-introduces-monthly-zero-fee-bitcoin-purchases</guid><category><![CDATA[Fees]]></category><category><![CDATA[Apps]]></category><category><![CDATA[Relai]]></category><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[Business]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[BtcCasey]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 14:57:32 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkzMjU1NjA1NDIxNjE0NjU5/city-of-the-future.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p>Relai, a Swiss non-custodial Bitcoin app, has announced the launch of zero-fee bitcoin purchases in order to attract more users.&nbsp;</p><p>This new offering allows users to make one fee-free bitcoin purchase per month for up to 100 CHF/EUR. By offering a zero-fee purchase option to its user base of over 70,000 individuals, Relai hopes to encourage more individuals to explore the benefits of owning bitcoin and participating in the digital economy.</p><p>Julian Liniger, Relai CEO and co-founder, expressed his excitement about the new offering in a press release sent to Bitcoin Magazine, stating, "We are thrilled to offer our users the zero fee purchase option. It's a testament to our commitment to simplifying Bitcoin investments and making it accessible to everyone." He further emphasized the importance of providing fair and secure access to bitcoin, calling it the "best savings technology ever invented."</p><p>In addition to the zero-fee trading launch, Relai explained that it recently made improvements to its user interface, making it even easier for users to onboard and use core functions like buying and selling. The press release states that these efforts have contributed to the company's success, with March 2023 being its best month to date according to the company. Relai reported a 215% year-on-year revenue growth since March 2022, along with a 53% increase compared to February 2023.</p><p>Relai <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/swiss-bitcoin-app-relai-raises-4-5-million">recently announced</a> an investment of $4.5 million, led by Jeff Booth's ego death capital. The company has reiterated its plans for the future, including Lightning integration and the launch of a white-label product.</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkzMjU1NjA1NDIxNjE0NjU5/city-of-the-future.png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Financial Services Provider River Announces $35 Million Series B Fundraising Round]]></title><description><![CDATA[The company says the funding will be used to expand its suite of Bitcoin services and strengthen its position in the market.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/river-announces-35-million-series-b-fundraising-round</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/river-announces-35-million-series-b-fundraising-round</guid><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[Business]]></category><category><![CDATA[river financial]]></category><category><![CDATA[fundraising]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[BtcCasey]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 13:50:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk0NDg4MTA1ODc5ODczMDI5/economic-chart-analysis.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p>Bitcoin technology and financial services company, River, has announced a successful $35 million equity round in its Series B fundraising effort. Led by Kingsway Capital, the round also saw participation from notable investors such as Peter Thiel, Cygni, Goldcrest and Valor Equity Partners. The company provides a range of Bitcoin services, including zero-fee recurring orders, full-reserve custody, mining and a Bitcoin wallet that supports both on-chain and Lightning Network transactions.</p><p>Alex Leishman, the CEO of River, highlighted the growing interest in Bitcoin driven by business and institutional adoption. He emphasized the importance of Bitcoin as a secure path to a stronger and more transparent global economy, especially in light of recent bank failures and bailouts. Leishman stated, "Adopting Bitcoin with a trusted partner is no longer the speculative choice, but rather the prudent one."</p><p>According to a press release sent to Bitcoin Magazine, River has experienced significant growth in demand for its enterprise Lightning API, River Lightning. This API enables companies to integrate with the Lightning Network and facilitate instant Bitcoin payments. Notably, El Salvador's Chivo wallet relies on River Lightning for Lightning transactions. The surge in demand for Lightning transactions, driven by rising on-chain fees, has prompted River to expand its B2B River Lightning segment.</p><p>Leishman emphasized River's commitment to responsible and reliable practices, setting the company apart from others in the crypto industry. He noted, "We have not taken shortcuts or reckless risks with our regulatory strategy and product offering. We're a mission-driven company with full-reserve Bitcoin custody, and will continue to play our part in moving society towards a brighter economic future powered by Bitcoin."</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk0NDg4MTA1ODc5ODczMDI5/economic-chart-analysis.png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[What Does Nigeria’s Blockchain-Friendly Regulatory Change Mean For Bitcoin Adoption?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Formal approval for blockchain technology in Nigeria marks an about-face for the government and it could increase Bitcoin adoption.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/nigeria-regulation-friendly-to-bitcoin</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/nigeria-regulation-friendly-to-bitcoin</guid><category><![CDATA[Africa]]></category><category><![CDATA[Business]]></category><category><![CDATA[Opinion]]></category><category><![CDATA[Blockchain]]></category><category><![CDATA[Regulation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Nigeria]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Heritage Falodun]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkyODY4MzAyMTgyMTY0MTc2/legal-justice.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><figure>
        <a href="https://bm.b.tc/bitcoin2023-conf-tickets" rel="nofollow"><img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk2NDE0NDk3MjI3ODEwMjkw/bitcoin-2023-website-article-banner.png" height="88" width="620"></a>
        
        
        
    </figure><p><em>This is an opinion editorial by Heritage Falodun, a Bitcoin consultant and computer scientist based in Nigeria.</em></p><p>On May 3, 2023, during a federal executive council meeting presided over by President Muhammadu Buhari at the council chamber in Abuja, the <a href="https://twitter.com/toluogunlesi/status/1653769481691299840?s=20">Nigerian government approved the official use of blockchain technology in the country</a>. </p><p>Nigeria’s minister of communications and digital economy, <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Isa_Ali_Pantami">professor Ali Isa Pantami</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/ProfIsaPantami/status/1653791726568390657?s=20">disclosed the official approval of “The National Blockchain Policy For Nigeria,”</a> <a href="https://www.vanguardngr.com/2023/05/fg-approves-natl-blockchain-policy/">stating that</a> the “the new policy was a product of consultations with 56 institutions and personalities whose end goal is to institutionalize blockchain technology in Nigeria’s economy and security sectors.”</p><figure>
        <img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk3ODc0NDgxOTcxMjc0OTI0/the-national-blockchain-policy-for-nigeria.png" height="412" width="620">
        
        
        <figcaption><a href="https://www.benjamindada.com/nigeria-use-of-blockchain-approved/"><em>Source</em></a></figcaption>
    </figure><h2>Nigeria’s History With Bitcoin Regulation</h2><p>Taking a deep dive into understanding the disposition of the Nigerian government toward blockchain-dependent innovations over the years will paint a clear picture of how crucial and important this recent policy and federal approval is for the Bitcoin space in Nigeria and Africa at large. </p><p>On January 12, 2017, the Central Bank of Nigeria (CBN) <a href="https://www.cbn.gov.ng/Out/2021/CCD/Letter%20on%20Crypto.pdf">issued a circular</a> which cautioned financial institutions and the general public about the risks associated with blockchain-dependent technologies, such as Bitcoin. Building on that previous warning and directive, on February 5, 2021, the Central Bank of Nigeria <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/bitcoin-will-persist-in-nigeria-but-the-ban-changes-things">officially prohibited banks from facilitating any Bitcoin- and crypto-related transactions</a> by reissuing the circular — a ban that remains unreversed as at the time of writing. </p><p>This restrictive policy come at a time when adoption of Bitcoin and shitcoin-related activities was on the rise in Nigeria, and it was a restriction that <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/oluwaseunadeyanju/2021/09/14/bitcoin-opportunity-africa-adoption-rate-is-highest-globally/?sh=55d196fb6d57">further fueled the use of Bitcoin and stablecoins</a> as users who are wallowing in the pains of financial restriction increasingly discovered the power of decentralized Bitcoin innovations, like peer-to-peer (P2P) marketplaces.</p><p>Amid all of these impromptu regulatory measures, CBN was apparently busy creating what it considered an alternative to shitcoins: a government-controlled digital currency called the e-naira, which was <a href="https://www.cbn.gov.ng/out/2021/ccd/enaira%20launch%20press%20release%20%20231021.pdf">officially launched</a> on the October 25, 2021, unequivocally built on a centralized system, not a decentralized blockchain like Bitcoin’s. Meanwhile, Nigeria’s Security And Exchange Commission (SEC) was occupied with <a href="http://forbes.com/sites/oluwaseunadeyanju/2022/05/14/nigeria-issues-crypto-asset-rules-in-a-move-that-could-boost-adoption/?sh=e8c23a212e6d">creating policy frameworks for token-issuance platforms and exchanges</a>.</p><p>All these regulatory changes were not unconnected to the government's awareness of just how thriving the blockchain industry is in Africa’s most populous country.</p><figure>
        <img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk3ODc0NDgxOTcxMzQwNDYw/national-blockchain-adoption-strategy.png" height="578" width="620">
        
        
        <figcaption><em>Source</em>: <em>A draft of Nigeria’s “</em><a href="https://nitda.gov.ng/wp-content/uploads/2020/10/DRAFT-NATIONAL-BLOCKCHAIN-ADOPTION-STRATEGY.pdf"><em>Nation Blockchain Adoption Strategy</em></a><em>”</em></figcaption>
    </figure><h2>What Does This Mean For Bitcoin In Nigeria?</h2><p>At this point, one will naturally ask what another regulatory update in the national blockchain policy means for Bitcoin.</p><p>A quick but detailed response would be: This is definitely a welcomed development for Bitcoin advocates in the country and one of the possibly many steps that we might witness in the right direction.</p><p>From my interpretation, this policy is focused more on giving a direct government overview to relevant regulatory bodies such as the <a href="https://nitda.gov.ng/">National Information Technology Development Agency</a> (NITDA), CBN, SEC, the <a href="https://ncc.gov.ng/">Nigerian Communications Commission</a> (NCC) and the <a href="https://www.nuc.edu.ng/">National Universities Commission</a> (NUC), among many others who are now expected to develop more detailed regulatory frameworks from using blockchain-based innovations like Bitcoin. The government is moving from being totally repelled by or antagonistic about Bitcoin-, blockchain- and crypto-related activities to now accepting them by default and creating a regulatory environment for them to move forward.</p><p>And while altcoins and other development and products dependent on blockchains excluding Bitcoin still stand a chance to remain regulated and subjected to the directives of these incoming regulations, Bitcoin uniquely repels such regulations. </p><p>As a stakeholder in the African Bitcoin space, I must confess that consistent clarity from governments will not only help in driving adoption but will also create an enabling environment for Nigerians to incorporate decentralized blockchain technology, like Bitcoin, into scaling their businesses and ways of life, while opening numerous legal opportunities for everyone.</p><p>As the industry keeps shaping up, keep tabs on the space, as Nigeria President-Elect Bola Tinubu has promised <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/feed/post/292724">to enable the prudent use of blockchain technology and cryptocurrencies in the nation's banking and financial sector</a>. My fingers remain crossed until we experience full implementation of Bitcoin-friendly regulations in Nigeria.</p><p><em>This is a guest post by Heritage Falodun. Opinions expressed are entirely their own and do not necessarily reflect those of BTC Inc or Bitcoin Magazine.</em></p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkyODY4MzAyMTgyMTY0MTc2/legal-justice.png"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk2NDE0NDk3MjI3ODEwMjkw/bitcoin-2023-website-article-banner.png" height="88" width="620" medium="image" type="image/png"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk3ODc0NDgxOTcxMjc0OTI0/the-national-blockchain-policy-for-nigeria.png" height="412" width="620" medium="image" type="image/png"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk3ODc0NDgxOTcxMzQwNDYw/national-blockchain-adoption-strategy.png" height="578" width="620" medium="image" type="image/png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Argentina Launches Introduction To Lightning Network Course]]></title><description><![CDATA[Participants in the course will learn the basics of the Lightning Network and what additional capabilities it brings to Bitcoin.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/bitcoin-argentina-launches-introduction-to-lightning-course</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/bitcoin-argentina-launches-introduction-to-lightning-course</guid><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[Argentina]]></category><category><![CDATA[Lightning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Education]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[BtcCasey]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 20:27:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkxNjYwMTg3MjA2MzYyNjEw/bitcoin-magazine-argentina.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><figure>
        <a href="https://bm.b.tc/bitcoin2023-conf-tickets" rel="nofollow"><img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk2NDE0NDk3MjI3ODEwMjkw/bitcoin-2023-website-article-banner.png" height="88" width="620"></a>
        
        
        
    </figure><p>Bitcoin Argentina, an NGO focused on promoting Bitcoin, is offering a virtual training course called "Introduction to Lightning Network."</p><p>According to a press release sent to Bitcoin Magazine, the course aims to educate participants on the operation and development possibilities of the Layer 2 solution that operates on top of the Bitcoin network. </p><p>Jimena Vallone, the executive director of Bitcoin Argentina, stated, "With the Bitcoin Argentina NGO, we want to bring about knowledge about this technology and generate practical and theoretical spaces that allow professionals, specialists, users and interested parties to explore its uses and potential."</p><p>The course, starting on May 23, will be taught by prominent specialists in the field, including Nicolás Bourbon, Francisco Calderon, Federico Andragnes and members of <a href="https://libreriadesatoshi.com/">Librería de Satoshi</a>, Laura Medina and Gustavo Torres. The curriculum will cover introductory aspects of Bitcoin, the mining process, the structure and operation of the Lightning Network, the technological implications for network growth, digital wallets, transactions and fraud prevention.</p><p>Bitcoin Argentina has previously organized the Lightning Hackday in Buenos Aires, which received a positive response from participants. Vallone expressed the organization's motivation behind the training course, saying, "We want to provide the necessary tools so that more and more people can learn about the potential of decentralized technologies and the financial innovation that began with Bitcoin in 2009."</p><p>Interested individuals can <a href="https://www.eventbrite.com.ar/e/curso-introduccion-a-lightning-network-tickets-622475620337">register for the course</a> directly or via the <a href="https://bitcoinargentina.org/">NGO's website</a>, with limited spots available. Participants will receive a certificate of attendance upon completion of the program.</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkxNjYwMTg3MjA2MzYyNjEw/bitcoin-magazine-argentina.png"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk2NDE0NDk3MjI3ODEwMjkw/bitcoin-2023-website-article-banner.png" height="88" width="620" medium="image" type="image/png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Fold Bitcoin Rewards App Announces Expansion Into El Salvador, Spearheading Latin American Operations]]></title><description><![CDATA[A new office in El Salvador will make the company’s expansion into Latin America as seamless as possible.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/fold-bitcoin-rewards-app-announces-expansion-into-el-salvador</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/fold-bitcoin-rewards-app-announces-expansion-into-el-salvador</guid><category><![CDATA[Latin america]]></category><category><![CDATA[fold]]></category><category><![CDATA[Business]]></category><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[el salvador]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[BtcCasey]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 16:40:29 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkyMTY1MzkxMDU1NzI1NzQ5/20220907_better-legal-tender-law-in-el-salvador---gaby-vias.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p>Bitcoin rewards company Fold has announced its expansion into El Salvador, establishing a new office that will serve as its base for operations in Latin America. Fold, known for <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/fold-opens-access-to-sats-back-debit-card">introducing</a> the world's first bitcoin rewards Visa Debit Card to the U.S. market in 2020, aims to make bitcoin accessible and easy for users worldwide.</p><p>Fold CEO Will Reeves expressed enthusiasm about the move in a press release shared with Bitcoin Magazine, stating, "As a country that has embraced bitcoin and has been a pioneer in adopting new monetary technology, we believe that El Salvador is the perfect place for Fold to expand its presence in Latin America." Reeves sees El Salvador as an ideal location due to the country's positive stance on bitcoin and its efforts to build new capital markets.</p><p>According to the release, Fold's expansion will bring valuable solutions to consumers and businesses in the region through its rewards program and embedded bitcoin infrastructure. The company stated its plans to announce partnerships with major players in Latin America soon. According to the release, to date, Fold's bitcoin rewards infrastructure has processed over $1 billion in volume, highlighting its growing success and impact.</p><p>Stacy Herbert, from the National Bitcoin Office of El Salvador, expressed excitement about Fold's arrival, stating, "Fold certainly fits that description and we are excited to welcome them to Bitcoin Country." Fold's expansion into El Salvador marks a significant milestone for the company as it continues to foster a global bitcoin community.</p><p>The new office in El Salvador and the local team will enable Fold to provide personalized support to its Latin American users and partners. The Fold mobile app is available for download on Android and iOS devices.</p><p>For more information on Fold's expansion and upcoming partnerships, the company encouraged users to visit their website at<a href="http://www.foldapp.com/"> www.foldapp.com</a>.&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkyMTY1MzkxMDU1NzI1NzQ5/20220907_better-legal-tender-law-in-el-salvador---gaby-vias.png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bitcoin 2023 Is The Festival Of Humanity We Need As Technology’s Grip Grows Stronger]]></title><description><![CDATA[With the specter of technologies like AI and CBDCs rising, Bitcoin 2023 will foster critical human connections.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/bitcoin-2023-celebrates-human-connection</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/bitcoin-2023-celebrates-human-connection</guid><category><![CDATA[Bitcoin 2023]]></category><category><![CDATA[cbdc]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Opinion]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Nozomi Hayase]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkwMjIxODM0MDY1NTUyNzI2/hope-father-daughter-horizon.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><figure>
        <a href="https://bm.b.tc/bitcoin2023-conf-tickets" rel="nofollow"><img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk2NDE0NDk3MjI3ODEwMjkw/bitcoin-2023-website-article-banner.png" height="88" width="620"></a>
        
        
        
    </figure><p><em>This is an opinion editorial by Nozomi Hayase, Ph.D., who has a background in psychology and human development. </em><em>Disclaimer: Bitcoin 2023 and Bitcoin Magazine are both operated by BTC Inc.</em></p><p>With <a href="https://www.foxbusiness.com/economy/april-inflation-breakdown-where-are-prices-rising-fastest">rising inflation</a> and a <a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/the-regional-bank-crisis-did-not-appear-over-on-thursday-86a51703">growing number of bank failures</a>, the dysfunctional nature of the fiat system becomes more apparent day by day. In the midst of this chaos, Bitcoin enthusiasts are staying calm, even generally hopeful about their futures.</p><p>As public trust in institutions weakens, governments around the world are gearing up for central bank digital currencies (CBDCs) as a means of reasserting their authority over peoples’ money. </p><p>“Thank God, we have Bitcoin!” </p><p>Those of us who are fortunate to have found it are relieved that Bitcoin exists. As Christine Lagarde, the head of the European Central Bank once <a href="https://twitter.com/Reuters/status/1349402076372209664?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1349402076372209664%7Ctwgr%5E2ede5541109a2e3ad065ba3608b9dee15335fbe0%7Ctwcon%5Es1_&amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fbitcoinmagazine.com%2Fculture%2Fbitcoiner-optimism-saves-the-world">acknowledged</a>, Bitcoin is an escape hatch from the financial surveillance state.</p><p>Bitcoin, the hardest money ever created, presents a real alternative to both current fiat currencies and CBDCs. Now, those who so choose don’t have to go down the path leading toward a dystopian society. This might make us feel at ease. Some of you might think we can just HODL and maybe orange pill newcomers here and there, and simply wait for hyperbitcoinization. But I say, “Not quite yet. We can’t just sit back and relax.”</p><p>We Bitcoiners have important tasks ahead: Bitcoin's battle against the fraudulent banking system is far from over. It is really only just beginning.</p><h2>The Battle Is Beginning</h2><p>Bitcoin, over the 14 years <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/History_of_bitcoin">since its creation</a>, has been slowly unveiling its revolutionary potential. Bitcoin is a form of “digital gold” that cannot be confiscated. As a saving technology, it provides inflation proofing, allowing us to store value securely. Its core feature of censorship resistance has also helped it to gain popularity, since the importance of having “freedom money” has become clearer to political dissidents and the oppressed the world over.</p><p>Now that the COVID-19 pandemic has wound down, and the emergency has been declared over, global leaders aim to re-engineer the economy. <a href="https://www.weforum.org/great-reset">The initiatives</a> of the Great Reset <a href="https://www3.weforum.org/docs/WEF_CBDC_Technology_Considerations_2021.pdf">plan to use CBDCs</a> as instruments of control, in the process creating a post-human society where human beings, as we have known them, cease to exist.</p><p>Things are moving fast. Commenting on the development of AI and its potential ramifications for humanity, Jordan Peterson, a prominent Canadian psychologist, <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Qh0WQWACCDg">said</a>, “We better get our acts together before the giants show up. They are like knocking at the door right now.”</p><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Qh0WQWACCDg" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe><p>Peterson has <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Qh0WQWACCDg">talked about</a> how ChatGPT, a <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Large_language_model">large language model (LLM)</a> and advanced conversational chatbot, is already building an increasingly-intelligent system. He described the process whereby, in the next few years, this AI model could extract a model of the world from the entire corpus of language, and use that to create a fully-rendered, photo-realistic animation indistinguishable from the image of a genuine person. By giving an example of turning a virtual girlfriend into a sex partner, he explained how easily it could falsify the representation of reality so completely that we all become confused about what is real and what is not.</p><p>And this technology is rapidly advancing. In March 2023, ChatGPT4, the most powerful artificial intelligence, <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbesbusinesscouncil/2023/03/28/gpt-4-released-what-it-means-for-the-future-of-your-business/?sh=147d3b612dc6">was released</a>. And Bitcoiners are in a unique position to take Peterson’s warning seriously and start doing something about the issues he has raised. </p><p>Bitcoin is pro-human technology. It provides a tool for us to detect counterfeit reality and which helps us to authenticate and secure truth, backed by our real human experiences.</p><p>Now, digitization of all aspects of society is taking place. From finance to healthcare and education, people are brought to the web to live their lives in a way that disconnects them from their bodies and from the natural environment. This trend leads to “hyper-mechanization,” a term I use to describe the turning point at which machines and robots become dominant in our world, dictating our very experiences. </p><p>This force of digitization, now becoming extreme, is also penetrating into the Bitcoin space. From Twitter to Nostr, and more than we are willing to admit, many of us are hooked to the iPhones and computers that keep us plugged into the matrix, becoming cut off from genuine, heart-to-heart interactions with other human beings.</p><p>As a machine-takeover of the world increasingly threatens the essence of what it means to be human, it is important for us to learn to unplug ourselves and maintain our relationships to ourselves and to nature. We need to collectively practice being offline from time to time, connecting with one another in real life. It is crucial for us to create a resilient human network of proof of work, built on top of the technology that can authenticate reality, based on our truly-felt feelings. </p><h2>Experiencing The Power Of Bitcoin, Firsthand</h2><p>This week, from May 18 to May 20, <a href="https://b.tc/conference/">the biggest Bitcoin conference</a> will take place in Miami Beach, Florida, bringing together Bitcoiners from all over the world. Along with presentations and panels from experts, professionals and leaders in the industry (check the speaker’s list <a href="https://b.tc/conference/speakers">here</a>), this three-day educational event will provide a space for Bitcoiners to gather outside of cyberspace and get to know one another.</p><div><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><a href="https://twitter.com/BTCBrunchMiami/status/1617234263501590532"></a></blockquote><script async="" src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><p>From <a href="https://twitter.com/bitcoininmiami/status/1647786228459110400?s=43&amp;t=4-Zdlcfd6SKLkdflZIarcg">brunches</a> to <a href="https://www.eventbrite.com/e/anders-pubby-toxic-happy-hour-pleb-party-miami-brought-to-you-by-swancom-tickets-478687135107?utm_campaign=bitcoin-2023&amp;utm_medium=dot-com&amp;utm_content=bitcoin_week_page">happy-hour pleb parties</a>, there will be plenty of opportunities for Bitcoiners to hang out. Through our exchanges of smiles and hugs, we can have firsthand experiences that demonstrate the power of bitcoin as the currency of love.</p><p>Crucially, the conference will also give us a chance to share our appreciation for artists who have been enriching the Bitcoin space. It will host <a href="https://b.tc/conference/art-gallery">an art gallery</a> displaying the work of more than 60 talented Bitcoin artists.</p><div><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><a href="https://twitter.com/Jethroe111/status/1651939821948903427"></a></blockquote><script async="" src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><div><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><a href="https://twitter.com/hitomi_matsui/status/1654655957597667329"></a></blockquote><script async="" src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><div><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><a href="https://twitter.com/13flr_escalator/status/1648688201668673544"></a></blockquote><script async="" src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><p>There, attendees can meet and interact with these artists in person. Now that AI can whip out sophisticated images in a matter of seconds and mimic our creativity, it becomes vital for us to recognize the value of art created by real human beings who are inspired by their own visions, and engaged in a hard and honest labor of love. </p><p>During the first and second general attendance days of Bitcoin 2023 (on May 19 and 20, 2023), the exuberance of Bitcoin competition will be brought to the main exposition hall to ignite a spirit of collaboration and teamwork. Initiated as a community project, <a href="https://b.tc/conference/bitcoin-games">the Bitcoin Games</a> will provide a fun and joyful contest where local meetups can match their skills and talents to compete. The winning team will bring home the trophy and one full BTC, which can be used to help develop their community (check <a href="https://b.tc/conference/bitcoin-games">here</a> for the details).</p><p>From the <a href="https://b.tc/conference/bazaar">Bitcoin Bazaar</a>, a massive peer-to-peer marketplace, to <a href="https://b.tc/conference/after-party">the official after party</a>, lots of fun things will be happening throughout the week (check the full agenda <a href="https://b.tc/conference/agenda">here</a>). </p><p>Bitcoin is electronic cash backed by human ingenuity. But what powers Bitcoin is our passion and the values that are shared in our hearts. What good is free speech money, if there is no human being who can speak? What is the worth of life, if there is nobody who can feel and experience its fullness?</p><p>At Bitcoin 2023, Bitcoiners around the world can come together to work toward hyperbitcoinization, in order to preserve what defines us uniquely as human beings. It presents a festival of humanity. </p><p>“Tick tock, next block.” </p><p>The countdown has just begun. It’s time to amplify relentless optimism and celebrate the beauty and magnificence that we all are. </p><p><em>This is a guest post by Nozomi Hayase. Opinions expressed are entirely their own and do not necessarily reflect those of BTC Inc or Bitcoin Magazine.</em></p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkwMjIxODM0MDY1NTUyNzI2/hope-father-daughter-horizon.png"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk2NDE0NDk3MjI3ODEwMjkw/bitcoin-2023-website-article-banner.png" height="88" width="620" medium="image" type="image/png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[As The U.S. Faces Default On $31 Trillion Debt, The Case For Bitcoin Grows Stronger]]></title><description><![CDATA[With U.S. politicians quibbling over the debt ceiling, will more people recognize the benefits of Bitcoin?]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/us-31-trillion-debt-makes-bitcoin-case</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/us-31-trillion-debt-makes-bitcoin-case</guid><category><![CDATA[Politicians]]></category><category><![CDATA[U.s.]]></category><category><![CDATA[Opinion]]></category><category><![CDATA[debt]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Robert Hall]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkzODM5Njc4ODI5NTAzOTg0/dollar-popping.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><figure>
        <a href="https://bm.b.tc/bitcoin2023-conf-tickets" rel="nofollow"><img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk2NDE0NDk3MjI3ODEwMjkw/bitcoin-2023-website-article-banner.png" height="88" width="620"></a>
        
        
        
    </figure><p><em>This is an opinion editorial by Robert Hall, a content creator and small business owner.</em></p><p>If you follow U.S. politics, you understand that the country is <a href="https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-12061031/Where-Biden-Republicans-stand-debt-limit-ahead-Big-Four-meeting.html">on the brink of defaulting on its massive $31 trillion debt</a>. </p><p>At the crux of the issue is that there are<a href="https://pressgallery.house.gov/member-data/party-breakdown"> </a>Republicans in one corner, who control the House of Representatives <a href="https://pressgallery.house.gov/member-data/party-breakdown">with a slim 222 to 213 majority.</a> In the other corner, the <a href="https://about.bgov.com/brief/balance-of-power-a-partisan-convergence-in-the-senate/">U.S. Senate</a> and the White House, under Joe Biden, are controlled by Democrats.</p><p>Both parties are diametrically opposed to what the other wants. Republicans want to <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/gops-debt-ceiling-proposal-where-do-republicans-want-to-cut-spending-366a29b6">significantly cut spending</a> in order to raise the debt limit for a year. Democrats want <a href="https://newrepublic.com/article/172376/debt-ceiling-deadline-default-negotiations">a “clean” debt ceiling bill passed without strings attached</a>. As you can see, both parties’ starting positions are nowhere near each other. Ultimately, this has turned into a game of chicken based on who will blink first. It’s all very tiring.</p><p>Is this the way a government should be run? It is absolutely crazy that these leaders would risk defaulting on money that has already been spent. This is like if you or I whipped out a credit card, went crazy buying all kinds of stuff, and did not make the monthly payment at the end of the month.</p><p>The government has been able to run up the debt for a long time because it has had willing participants, such as pension funds, hedge funds, sovereign wealth funds and regular joes who lent them money by buying treasury bills because they believed they would be paid back with interest.</p><p>This has been the case for a long time, but now this arrangement is being called into question with the will they, won’t they bull going on in Congress right now. </p><h2>Seriously Broke</h2><p>Are these politicians so detached from reality to think that, once the debt limit is breached and people stop getting paid what is owed to them, people will go right back to loaning them money?</p><p>If they do, they will demand even higher interest rates. The government can’t even afford the rates we have now! What happens if the borrowing cost for the government goes to 10% or 15%? Ain’t nothing getting funded; I can tell you that much.</p><p><a href="https://www.pgpf.org/blog/2023/02/interest-costs-on-the-national-debt-are-on-track-to-reach-a-record-high">Check out this</a>:<a href="https://www.pgpf.org/blog/2023/02/interest-costs-on-the-national-debt-are-on-track-to-reach-a-record-high"> </a>The federal government spent a record $475 billion on interest payments in fiscal year 2022. Interest costs grew 30% last year and are poised to jump another 35% this year, according to the Congressional Budget Office's (CBO’s) own estimate!</p><p>The CBO believes the federal government will spend $640 billion in interest payments this year alone. Is this the<a href="https://jameslavish.substack.com/p/-whats-a-debt-spiral-and-is-the-us"> debt spiral that James Lavish</a> has been talking about lately? It sure as hell seems like it to me.</p><p>We are on a slow-motion collision course with the economic reality that you can’t print and borrow money without consequences. Inflation rears its ugly head first, and then people realize the money they are being paid back with has diminished purchasing power. Once people know they are losing money when they lend it to the federal government, it’s game over.</p><p>This debt-ceiling debate will highlight the dysfunction of the federal government and its inability to keep its promises. This is what surprises me about the politicians on both sides of the aisle.</p><p>Do they really want to show this level of incompetence to the world? It’s like watching your family fight in the front yard. It’s embarrassing as hell and will change the perception that your neighbors have about your family.</p><p>A debt default will change the perception of the U.S. from a trusted payer to a debt junkie unable to pay its debts.</p><h2>How Is Default Good For Bitcoin?</h2><figure>
        <img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk3ODUyMTkyMTY0NTUzOTAw/bitcoin-dollar.jpg" height="411" width="620">
        
        
        <figcaption><a href="https://pixabay.com/photos/bitcoin-crypto-btc-cryptocurrency-3890350/"><em>Source</em></a></figcaption>
    </figure><p>The silver lining to this whole debt-ceiling debacle is that it’s going to throw rocket fuel on the price of bitcoin. As people see that their money is no longer “safe” with the federal government, they will seek an alternative to U.S. treasuries. Undoubtedly, some of the dollars that would have been earmarked for treasuries will flow into bitcoin.</p><p>New entrants to bitcoin will see that it is the safe haven asset they were looking for the whole time. There is no counterparty risk, and the supply can’t be diluted.</p><p>During the <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/2013_United_States_debt-ceiling_crisis#:~:text=It%20began%20in%20January%202013,following%20the%20crisis%20in%202011.">last contentious debate over the debt ceiling</a>, under the Obama administration, the price of <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/guides/bitcoin-price-history">bitcoin went from $13 and ended the year at $755.</a> It also reached an all-time high of $1,163 that year. Coincidence? Maybe, but it does make sense for people to protect their wealth during times of potential calamity such as a default. </p><p>So, I say to the politicians running the government right now: Go ahead and keep playing these games. Default or don’t default because, in the end, it doesn’t matter; you still lose. You have led the world to ruin, and it will be up to Bitcoin to save humanity from itself. The debt-ceiling debacle only accelerates the inevitable.</p><p>And to the Bitcoiners: Keep stacking them sats like your lives depend on it, because one day they might. </p><p><em>This is a guest post by Robert Hall. Opinions expressed are entirely their own and do not necessarily reflect those of BTC Inc or Bitcoin Magazine.</em></p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkzODM5Njc4ODI5NTAzOTg0/dollar-popping.png"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk2NDE0NDk3MjI3ODEwMjkw/bitcoin-2023-website-article-banner.png" height="88" width="620" medium="image" type="image/png"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk3ODUyMTkyMTY0NTUzOTAw/bitcoin-dollar.jpg" height="411" width="620" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[To Reach Women, Bitcoiners Should Change Their Approach]]></title><description><![CDATA[“Having participated in many Bitcoin events in different cities and states, I’ve noticed that women are always outnumbered… This is a problem!”]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/three-ways-to-reach-women-with-bitcoin</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/three-ways-to-reach-women-with-bitcoin</guid><category><![CDATA[women]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Orange Pill]]></category><category><![CDATA[Opinion]]></category><category><![CDATA[Adoption]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Tali Lindberg]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkzMDA4NjEyODU4MTQzOTY1/20220928_20220926_good-ross-placeholder.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><figure>
        <a href="https://bm.b.tc/bitcoin2023-conf-tickets" rel="nofollow"><img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk2NDE0NDk3MjI3ODEwMjkw/bitcoin-2023-website-article-banner.png" height="88" width="620"></a>
        
        
        
    </figure><p><em>This is an opinion editorial by Tali Lindberg, co-founder of Free Market Kids, a company focused on financial literacy and Bitcoin education.</em></p><p><em>Author’s note: This is a politically-incorrect article because I’m about to make gross generalizations about men and women. If you are easily offended, you probably shouldn’t read on.</em></p><p>When I first entered the Bitcoin space, I met a woman who asked me if I was interested in starting a woman’s Bitcoin meetup. </p><p>“I wish there was one,” she said. </p><p>At the time, I was a bit offended by the idea. </p><p>“Bitcoin is already a small space, why would we want to separate men and women?” I wondered. </p><p>Since then, I’ve had a change of heart.</p><figure>
        <img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk3NzEzMjQxOTE5NTk2MzM4/educate-individuals.png" height="520" width="620">
        
        
        <figcaption><em>Source: Author</em></figcaption>
    </figure><p>Having participated in many Bitcoin events in different cities and states, I’ve noticed that women are always outnumbered by men… by a lot! I would estimate that 80% to 90% of the people I’ve met in the Bitcoin space are men. </p><p>This is a problem.</p><p>Women have the power to shape the future leaders of this world through their intimate bonds with their children. A baby who is born this year may enter adulthood in a world where fiat currency is a thing of the past, and bitcoin is the global, digital currency. </p><p>This timeline, however, will not be possible without having the buy-in of more women.</p><p>In this article, I will discuss what I’ve observed and make some recommendations on how to effectively introduce Bitcoin to more women.</p><h2>Facts Vs. Stories</h2><p>If you asked my husband what he thought about the state of the economy, he would immediately spout out facts about how our market is not free and how the government picks winners and losers. He would go on about zombie companies, malinvestment, how much the Federal Reserve inflates the money supply and how the chairman manipulates the interest rate, etc. </p><p>If you asked me the same question, on the other hand, I would talk about some of our elderly neighbors, and go into great detail about a recent conversation I had with a retired grandmother: Standing in the hot sun next to squawking hens as they pecked loudly and aggressively at their food, we discussed the challenges of protecting our chickens from predators and growing a garden, even though neither of us was passionate about farming. </p><p>(I can feel some of you getting impatient with me as you’re reading this. <em>Get to the point, why don’t you? What does this have to do with the question?</em> Well, hold on, I’m getting there!) </p><p>We chatted at length about prices going up and how raising chickens and growing gardens were our ways of hedging against crazy price increases at the grocery store. I would then tell you that she and her husband are on a fixed income and about her worry that, with the way things are going, one day soon she won’t be able to buy enough groceries to keep from going hungry.</p><figure>
        <img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk3NzEzMjQxOTE5NjYxODc0/he-said-she-said.png" height="620" width="620">
        
        
        <figcaption><em>Source: Author</em></figcaption>
    </figure><p>In my mind, this is what the “state of our economy” means — the peoples’ stories. And in the presence of men, despite them being friendly, welcoming and very encouraging, I still feel pressure to cut out details and “get to the point.” On the other hand, in the presence of women, telling peoples’ stories often feels natural and easy because that’s the way many women hash out important topics.</p><p>This is a major difference between men and women: men typically get to the facts, and women tell stories. </p><h2>Cigars And Whisky Vs. Tea And Biscuits</h2><p>My husband and I have <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/parallels-between-homeschool-and-bitcoin">been on a mission to bring Bitcoin education to homeschoolers</a>. In all of the conversations we’ve had, our experience has been that 90% of the women say the same thing: “I don’t understand Bitcoin, I don’t think I can figure it out. My husband handles the finances and investment decisions.”</p><p>Why would women, who are equally as educated and intelligent as their spouses, leave this vitally important knowledge solely to the care of men? Dare I say that this is because Bitcoin educational materials and learning environments tend to lean heavily toward the way men communicate? </p><p>Perhaps we need a women-to-women approach. Please don't misunderstand me; I am not saying that women are incapable of understanding technical and factual information in the same way that men are. Both genders are equally capable. However, in our pursuit of equality, we must not lose sight of the fact that men and women differ not only biologically but also in the way they perceive and interact with the world.</p><p>When men gather, they can often exchange quick pleasantries and get right down to business. At the end of such a meeting, everyone feels satisfied. Most women in the same scenarios, however, would not feel satisfied. We need to visit first, ask about one another's weeks, how the kids are doing and any challenges that we have faced during the week. We exchange stories and empathize to show that we care. To quote the famed sales guru <a href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/863418-people-don-t-care-how-much-you-know-until-they-know">Zig Ziglar</a>, “People don't care how much you know until they know how much you care.” </p><p>Are we not all salespeople trying to sell the idea of Bitcoin? Maybe we can take a page out of Ziglar's book.</p><h2>Why Vs. What</h2><p>When I first tried to read up on Bitcoin because of my husband’s insistent nudging, I found it exceptionally frustrating. There are many books on the market, numerous podcasts and a plethora of YouTube videos explaining Bitcoin. However, until I understood why Bitcoin is important to me personally, I would rather have done something else with my precious free time. </p><p>Charts and graphs and angry rants about the political landscape or the corrupt system wouldn’t convince me. Although these issues annoy me, I mostly chalk them up to things I can’t do anything about. My schedule is already full of more things to do than the time to do them. However, if you tell me a human story about someone facing hardship and difficult consequences due to the fallacies of our monetary system, then my anger at the injustice would propel me to do the necessary research and learn about how bitcoin is an alternative currency, not just a risky speculation or possibly a wild gamble.</p><p>To reach women en masse, we’ve got to focus on telling good stories about the “why” of Bitcoin.</p><p>It is not my intention to suggest that men and women Bitcoiners cannot benefit from the same meetups or education materials. Our society is currently obsessed with labeling everyone with some obscure name that separates them from each other. I don’t want to play that game. I am suggesting that if we are mindful of the audience we are trying to reach, perhaps we could craft our message differently to get our point across more successfully.</p><p>Here's an example of how women perceive men talking about the why of Bitcoin — my niece drew the following comic strip to highlight what she had learned after listening to a Bitcoin podcast:</p><figure>
        <img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk3NzEzMjQxOTE5NDY1MjY2/bitcoin-podcasts.png" height="520" width="620">
        
        
        
    </figure><p>I wonder how different the comic strip would have looked if two women had done the podcast, even if they had discussed exactly the same topics and come to the same conclusions as the hosts of the podcast that my niece listened to.</p><p>Here are some suggestions based on my personal experiences in reaching precoiner women:</p><figure>
        <img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk3NzEzMjQxOTE5NTMwODAy/mama-bear.png" height="520" width="620">
        
        
        
    </figure><h2>One: Anger Mama Bear! </h2><p>Tell personal stories to share the <em>why</em> of Bitcoin. Following the story I shared earlier in this article about elderly retirees, most people would feel sympathetic toward them having to work in the hot sun day after day to grow their own food. But if you explained to a young mother who is lovingly and protectively cradling her newborn baby against her chest that the impending hyperinflation means her child would grow up to be in the same situation, having to literally labor in the field for food, you will have incited the most powerful force on earth: a mother’s instinct to protect her young. Now you’ll have a motivated individual who is ready to do whatever it takes to learn about this crazy thing called Bitcoin.</p><h2>Two: Host Women’s Events </h2><p>Remember that book “<a href="https://www.amazon.com/Men-Mars-Women-Venus-Understanding/dp/0060574216">Men Are From Mars, Women Are From Venus</a>”? </p><p>We need to embrace who we are. Being different is good, just as specialization is a positive force in truly free<em> </em>markets. Marketing a new and mysterious idea like Bitcoin can only be effective with customized messaging and delivery methods to reach different target audiences. </p><p>Recognize that women and men socialize differently and feel comfortable in different environments. When women talk to women, we have more freedom to express ourselves with an ease that is not as readily available in a co-ed gathering. This is not to say that men and women cannot speak to one another, but simply that certain conversations can feel more comfortable woman to woman. </p><h2>Three: Less Is More </h2><p>Don’t vomit facts and charts and numbers at a woman precoiner. You can’t “logic” women into Bitcoin. You have to emotionally persuade women into Bitcoin. Ask questions about their lives and concerns and let them have enough time to fully share. </p><p>Talking less is actually more persuasive than talking more. Allow the conversation to naturally develop to the point where they ask the first questions. That’s when you know the floor is yours. Share in small bits. Keep a low-time-preference mentality.</p><p>I hope this article helps men Bitcoiners to communicate more effectively with women and finds its way to women Bitcoiners who are willing to work together to reach other women in a way that only we can: woman to woman. </p><p><em>This is a guest post by Tali Lindberg. Opinions expressed are entirely their own and do not necessarily reflect those of BTC Inc or Bitcoin Magazine.</em>&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkzMDA4NjEyODU4MTQzOTY1/20220928_20220926_good-ross-placeholder.png"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk2NDE0NDk3MjI3ODEwMjkw/bitcoin-2023-website-article-banner.png" height="88" width="620" medium="image" type="image/png"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk3NzEzMjQxOTE5NTk2MzM4/educate-individuals.png" height="520" width="620" medium="image" type="image/png"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk3NzEzMjQxOTE5NjYxODc0/he-said-she-said.png" height="620" width="620" medium="image" type="image/png"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk3NzEzMjQxOTE5NDY1MjY2/bitcoin-podcasts.png" height="520" width="620" medium="image" type="image/png"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk3NzEzMjQxOTE5NTMwODAy/mama-bear.png" height="520" width="620" medium="image" type="image/png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[The 2024 Presidential Election Could Make Or Break Bitcoin In The U.S.]]></title><description><![CDATA[2024 is shaping up to be a pivotal year for Bitcoin and the U.S. That’s why it’s time for a generational change in leadership.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/us-needs-a-bitcoin-president-in-2024</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/us-needs-a-bitcoin-president-in-2024</guid><category><![CDATA[donald trump]]></category><category><![CDATA[joe biden]]></category><category><![CDATA[u.s. president]]></category><category><![CDATA[Opinion]]></category><category><![CDATA[francis suarez]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Politics]]></category><category><![CDATA[U.s.]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Robert Hall]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2023 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkxNTY2MDg3NDI1MzY5NzYz/politics-voting-democrat-republican-candidate-top-photo.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><figure>
        <a href="https://bm.b.tc/bitcoin2023-conf-tickets" rel="nofollow"><img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk2NDE0NDk3MjI3ODEwMjkw/bitcoin-2023-website-article-banner.png" height="88" width="620"></a>
        
        
        
    </figure><p><em>This is an opinion editorial by Robert Hall, </em><em>a content creator and small business owner.</em></p><p>The race for the 2024 U.S. presidential election is starting to kick into gear, featuring some of the same cast of characters from the last few elections. On the Democratic side, you have <a href="https://www.npr.org/2023/04/25/1145679856/biden-president-announcement-2024-running-reelection">Joe Biden</a>,<a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/boston/news/robert-f-kennedy-jr-2024-presidential-election-campaign-announcement/"> Robert F. Kennedy</a> and<a href="https://www.pbs.org/newshour/politics/democrat-marianne-williamson-announces-2024-presidential-run"> Marianne Williamson</a> suggesting they will run. Then, <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Donald_Trump_2024_presidential_campaign">Former President Donald Trump</a>, <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nikki_Haley_2024_presidential_campaign">Nikki Haley</a>, <a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2024-election/ron-desantis-set-jump-2024-presidential-fray-may-rcna81666">Ron DeSantis</a> and <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Vivek_Ramaswamy_2024_presidential_campaign">Vivek Ramaswamy</a> are on the other side of the aisle.</p><p>If you have been following the race so far, you might know that Trump <a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/2024-presidential-primary-trump-v-trump-fatigue-poll-2023-05-01/">seems to be walking away with the nomination</a> before the process even starts next year. If he ends up being the nominee, we will likely get a re-run of 2020, where we have two men over 70 years old who both think that they know what is right for the country. Who else is tired of having baby boomers running the show? I am, to be honest.</p><h2>Boomer Presidents Don’t Understand Bitcoin</h2><p>Baby boomers, you’ve had their time in the sun. It’s time to leave the stage and let the younger generations of leaders have a chance to lead the country. We need leaders who understand the emerging challenges facing America as we speak.</p><p>We need leaders who thoroughly understand economic policy and the value of innovation in the financial space. For instance, the baby boomers at the top of the ticket don’t have the depth or the capacity to understand the once-in-a-lifetime opportunity that Bitcoin presents to America and the American people.</p><p><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jackkelly/2022/01/28/president-joe-biden-is-going-after-bitcoin-cryptocurrencies-and-nfts/?sh=15a93c757b9a">Biden</a> and <a href="https://www.computerworld.com/article/3408900/trumps-hostile-view-of-bitcoin-and-crypto-could-chill-industry.html">Trump</a> have been openly hostile towards Bitcoin because they believe in the supremacy of the fiat dollar system. The time is now to elect someone with a bold vision for the future, who understands that the way that the entitlement systems are set up and the dollar's role in the world isn’t sustainable over the long term.</p><p>If America stays on its current path, it will only lead to chaos, lawlessness, and a lower standard of living for everyone. Is this the future that you want for your children and grandchildren? 2024 is our chance to start a new journey toward freedom, the rule of law and the opportunity to make something of yourself, regardless of your station in life.</p><h2>Why We Need A Bitcoiner As President</h2><p>It has been reported recently that the mayor of Miami, Francis Suarez,<a href="https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/3960935-miami-mayor-close-to-decision-on-2024-gop-presidential-bid/"> is close to a decision on whether to run for president next year</a>. For those who don’t know him, he is <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/tags/francis-suarez">one of the most pro-Bitcoin politicians in the country</a>. He has actively courted Bitcoiners to come to Miami and help make it the Bitcoin capital of the world. So far, he has largely succeeded in doing that.</p><p>But in addition to making the U.S. an epicenter for Bitcoin innovation, having a Bitcoiner like Suarez as president will, critically, stop the emergence of a central bank digital currency (CBDC) in America dead in its tracks. If Biden or Trump is elected, it is almost certain that some form of CBDC will be activated in America. With the deployment of a CBDC, you can kiss your financial freedom goodbye. You can kiss your privacy goodbye.</p><p>You will no longer have autonomy over what you can eat or how far you can travel. You will have a social credit score, <a href="https://velocityglobal.com/blog/chinese-social-credit-system/#:~:text=China's%20social%20credit%20system%20gives,credit%20and%20fewer%20business%20opportunities.">as has been implemented in China</a>. Is this the type of life that you want? We have to strive for a better life. </p><p>Just recently, the rails for a CBDC were introduced to the public.<a href="https://www.computerworld.com/article/3693256/fed-s-zelle-like-instant-payment-system-to-go-live-in-july-hundreds-now-testing.html"> </a>FedNow, as it is called, <a href="https://www.computerworld.com/article/3693256/fed-s-zelle-like-instant-payment-system-to-go-live-in-july-hundreds-now-testing.html">will be operational by July 2023.</a> It is said that it will be used to speed up payments between customers and businesses, which may be accurate at the moment. However, as with any system, it will likely evolve into something vastly different than what it was intended to be.</p><p>Can we really trust a government that has given us the<a href="https://www.aclu.org/issues/national-security/privacy-and-surveillance/surveillance-under-patriot-act"> Patriot Act</a>,<a href="https://www.cloudwards.net/prism-snowden-and-government-surveillance/"> PRISM</a> and now the proposed<a href="https://www.eff.org/deeplinks/2023/04/broad-vague-restrict-act-dangerous-substitute-comprehensive-data-privacy"> RESTRICT Act</a> to resist total control over what you spend your money on?</p><p>The RESTRICT Act, for instance, put forth by none other than <a href="https://www.politico.com/news/2023/02/14/elizabeth-warren-anti-crypto-ftx-00082624">Bitcoin-hating Senator Elizabeth Warren</a>, has the potential to harm Bitcoiners in the United States with its overly-broad language about digital communication tools being a threat to national security. While the overt target may be TikTok, nothing is stopping regulators from using this law against Bitcoin in the future.</p><p>Looking past this smokescreen, you can see that they are building their case to the public: <a href="https://markets.businessinsider.com/news/currencies/hillary-clinton-says-cryptocurrency-destabilize-nations-2021-11">Hilary Clinton</a>, <a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/after-ftx-collapse-pressure-builds-tougher-crypto-rules-2022-12-02/">international regulators</a> and the <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/us-treasury-warns-defi-being-200515406.html?guccounter=1&amp;guce_referrer=aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuZ29vZ2xlLmNvbS8&amp;guce_referrer_sig=AQAAAHro6hwDAeWGZk2LcXCSxoM5mIJu8Gk8X1q9_NyN451C1t-QqL_KRE7pkrk2NnlqmckDN-rhenF6ePW3yXcFWoAAuDnRaJaXESwHKYsieMc0ue0s1_6dc3_0Srjc6fweVc9diJcm0lrZS5azqW4bgjER2tvbykCfUYvGvKyWFFCJ">U.S. Treasury</a> have all warned about the dangers of cryptocurrency.</p><p>Now, put this in the context of <a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/us-policy/interactive/2023/national-debt-31-trillion/">$31 trillion in U.S. national debt</a>, unsustainable entitlement spending, a world slowly moving away from the dollar, high gas prices and uncontrollable inflation. Then it becomes clear that they will close off the exits to Bitcoin before most people learn about how to use them. They want to herd the masses into a CBDC for a “great reset” of the monetary system. This is coming if we don’t start electing people who understand that Bitcoin is our last chance to escape a sinking ship.</p><p>Mayor Saurez gets it, and if any other politicians in America understand Bitcoin, it is time that we support them and get more Bitcoiners in office. The dollar is the Titanic, and Bitcoin is the lifeboat. Will enough people get on to be saved? Time will tell and the upcoming presidential election could be a final chance.</p><p><em>This is a guest post by Robert Hall. Opinions expressed are entirely their own and do not necessarily reflect those of BTC Inc or Bitcoin Magazine.</em></p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkxNTY2MDg3NDI1MzY5NzYz/politics-voting-democrat-republican-candidate-top-photo.png"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk2NDE0NDk3MjI3ODEwMjkw/bitcoin-2023-website-article-banner.png" height="88" width="620" medium="image" type="image/png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[U.S. Senators Introduce Bill Requiring Reports On El Salvador’s Bitcoin Adoption]]></title><description><![CDATA[The reports will look to answer questions about the impacts of El Salvador’s bitcoin legal tender law on the U.S. and other countries.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/el-salvador-bitcoin-news/bill-requiring-reports-on-el-salvadors-bitcoin-adoption-introduced</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/el-salvador-bitcoin-news/bill-requiring-reports-on-el-salvadors-bitcoin-adoption-introduced</guid><category><![CDATA[El Salvador]]></category><category><![CDATA[Senators]]></category><category><![CDATA[Senate]]></category><category><![CDATA[Legal Tender]]></category><category><![CDATA[el salvador]]></category><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[Adoption]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[BtcCasey]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 21:40:57 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkyODY4MzAyMTgyMTY0MTc2/legal-justice.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p>A group of United States senators have introduced a bill requiring reports on the adoption of bitcoin as legal tender in El Salvador.&nbsp;</p><p>The "<a href="https://www.foreign.senate.gov/imo/media/doc/MCC22059.pdf">Accountability for Cryptocurrency in El Salvador Act</a>," introduced by Senator James Risch, Senator Bob Menendez, and Senator Bill Cassidy, requires the Secretary of State, in coordination with other relevant Federal departments and agencies, to submit a report on the adoption of bitcoin as legal tender in El Salvador. The report must include an assessment of the regulatory framework in El Salvador and the potential impact of Bitcoin adoption on macroeconomic stability, democratic governance, and the flow of remittances from the United States to El Salvador.</p><p>The bill also calls for a plan to mitigate any potential risks to the United States financial system posed by the adoption of a cryptocurrency as legal tender in El Salvador and any other country that uses the U.S. dollar as legal tender. According to the bill, the plan should be submitted to the appropriate committees of Congress no later than 90 days after the report required by subsection (a).</p><p>The Bitcoin Law, passed by the Salvadoran government in June 2021, gives <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/el-salvador-to-declare-bitcoin-as-legal-tender">Bitcoin legal tender</a> status in the country. The move was criticized by some experts, who argued that it could lead to instability in the country's economy. Others, however, saw the move as a potential catalyst for broader adoption of bitcoin in the region. Despite the controversy surrounding the move, El Salvador has remained committed to its Bitcoin adoption plans.</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkyODY4MzAyMTgyMTY0MTc2/legal-justice.png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[U.S. Congressman Brad Sherman Sends Letter To SEC Chair Calling Attention To Grayscale Bitcoin Trust Situation]]></title><description><![CDATA[A member of Congress has now requested action in regards to billions of dollars locked in the Grayscale Bitcoin Trust.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/legal/u-s-congressman-sends-letter-to-sec-chair-calling-attention-to-gbtc-situation</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/legal/u-s-congressman-sends-letter-to-sec-chair-calling-attention-to-gbtc-situation</guid><category><![CDATA[Legal]]></category><category><![CDATA[Gbtc]]></category><category><![CDATA[gary gensler]]></category><category><![CDATA[Dcg]]></category><category><![CDATA[Congressmen]]></category><category><![CDATA[Grayscale Bitcoin Trust]]></category><category><![CDATA[Grayscale]]></category><category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[BtcCasey]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 16:10:26 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk0MjMxNzYxODMwNTUzMDkz/bitcoin-stack.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><figure>
        <a href="https://bm.b.tc/bitcoin2023-conf-tickets" rel="nofollow"><img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk2NDE0NDk3MjI3ODEwMjkw/bitcoin-2023-website-article-banner.png" height="88" width="620"></a>
        
        
        
    </figure><p>U.S. Congressman Brad Sherman has sent a letter to Gary Gensler, Chair of the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), regarding the situation of Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC).</p><div><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><a href="https://twitter.com/BradSherman/status/1656783945155899396"></a></blockquote><script async="" src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><p><a href="https://twitter.com/BradSherman/status/1656783945155899396?s=20">According to Sherman</a>, as many as 850,000 retail investors, including some who used individual retirement account funds, are currently trapped in their GBTC investments due to the actions of GBTC and its parent company, Digital Currency Group (DCG). Sherman estimates that these investors' retirement security and in some cases, their life savings, may be at risk and that if the situation is not remedied, they could lose tens of billions of dollars of their savings.</p><p>Sherman's concerns regarding GBTC stem from the fact that GBTC shares currently trade at a <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/markets/potential-paths-forward-for-gbtc">~42% discount</a> to the bitcoins in the trust, and Grayscale has refused to redeem GBTC shares, citing Regulation M's prohibition on simultaneous sales and redemptions of the same security. Grayscale's Head of Investor Relations, Rayhanch Sharif-Askary, admitted that the company's flooding of the market with GBTC by continuously issuing new shares between 2018 and 2021 drove the discount to its net asset value.</p><p>Sherman alleges that Grayscale's actions are motivated by a desire to increase assets under management, regardless of the impact on GBTC's retail investors. Grayscale charges users an annual 2% fee based on the actual value of bitcoin, not the value of the GBTC that investors own. By charging more than four times what their competitors charge, Grayscale was able to bring in $615 million in fees alone in 2021, according to the letter.</p><p>Sherman has posed several questions to the SEC related to this matter, including whether Regulation M is a barrier to allowing shareholder redemptions today, whether the SEC is aware of other specific rules and regulations that are a barrier to allowing shareholder redemptions today, and whether it is a matter of concern that Grayscale does not have a single independent director on either its board of directors or audit committee.</p><p>In conclusion, Congressman Brad Sherman's letter to the SEC Chair, Gary Gensler, is raising concerns over the situation of Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC). Sherman is worried that as many as 850,000 retail investors could lose their retirement security and savings, as they are currently trapped in their GBTC investment due to the actions of GBTC and its parent company, Digital Currency Group. At Bitcoin 2023 in Miami, there will be a <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/industry-events/reedemgbtc-com-to-host-shareholders-meetup-at-miami-bitcoin-conference">shareholders meetup</a> to discuss the next steps that concerned shareholders can take. This aims to be the largest gathering of shareholders since the beginning of the Trust, with more than 30% of shareholders expected to attend.</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk0MjMxNzYxODMwNTUzMDkz/bitcoin-stack.png"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk2NDE0NDk3MjI3ODEwMjkw/bitcoin-2023-website-article-banner.png" height="88" width="620" medium="image" type="image/png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[This Mother’s Day, Try Explaining Bitcoin To Your Mom]]></title><description><![CDATA[If your mom has a hard time getting off zero, like this author’s does, you should give it another shot on Mother’s Day.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/give-bitcoin-for-mothers-day</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/give-bitcoin-for-mothers-day</guid><category><![CDATA[Opinion]]></category><category><![CDATA[Orange Pill]]></category><category><![CDATA[Holiday]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Family]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Hector Alvero]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkwNDI4MzgyNTMyNTQ0NDEw/114-btc.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><figure>
        <a href="https://bm.b.tc/bitcoin2023-conf-tickets" rel="nofollow"><img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk2NDE0NDk3MjI3ODEwMjkw/bitcoin-2023-website-article-banner.png" height="88" width="620"></a>
        
        
        
    </figure><p><em>This is an opinion editorial by Hector Alvero, a Bitcoin educator who serves as co-host of the Broward County Bitcoiners meetup.</em></p><figure>
        <img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk3NjY0ODE2NDMxNjM4MzIy/a-flower-for-mothers-day.png" height="329" width="620">
        
        
        <figcaption><a href="https://www.freepik.com/premium-photo/baby-giving-red-gerber-flower-her-mother-mothers-day-concept_7230662.htm"><em>Source</em></a></figcaption>
    </figure><p>As Bitcoiners, we love the exhilarating feeling of bringing a new person into the Bitcoin lifeboat. Many of us constantly work to orange pill our friends, our coworkers and our neighbors, trying to save as many as we can before the fiat ship sinks. We'll even try to orange pill the waiter at our favorite local restaurant, helping them download a Lightning wallet and offering to give them a bigger tip to help them "get off zero."</p><p>But what about your mom? Have you given her the same gift that you’ve given to the Uber driver who took you home from your last conference or meetup? Have you taken the time to help her understand the impact that inflation is having on her economic security, and how Bitcoin can protect her from the financial earthquake that is coming? Have you helped her understand what money is and why Bitcoin is the greatest savings technology ever discovered? </p><p>If you have, I applaud you. If you haven't gotten there yet, this Mother's Day is the perfect time to show her that you love her enough to spend the time it takes for her to understand Bitcoin.</p><p>You might be thinking, "I already tried, and she didn't get it." I can sympathize with that. My mom didn't get it right away, either. She said it sounded like a Ponzi scheme and that it couldn't be money because it wasn't real or backed by anything. </p><p>Maybe you have heard some of these same objections. Maybe you are frustrated and figure you should just let it go. If so, ask yourself this question: How many times has your mom explained something to you that you didn't understand at first? She likely did not just give up on helping you learn and grow. Are you going to quit on her now when her entire future is at stake? Of course not… you're a Bitcoiner.</p><figure>
        <img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk3NjY0ODE2NDMxNzAzMzQx/jumping-on-the-bed.jpg" height="620" width="620">
        
        
        <figcaption><a href="https://www.rd.com/list/mom-memes/"><em>Source</em></a></figcaption>
    </figure><p>Think back to when you first heard about Bitcoin. Did you get it right away? I didn't. A friend told me about Bitcoin at a Halloween party in 2015, and while I didn't dismiss it, I certainly did not understand its importance at first. Life was busy, and so I forgot about it for about a year until he tried again in late 2016 and helped me learn enough to buy a small amount and begin my journey. Maybe you have a similar story of someone who kept trying until you understood this revolutionary technology enough to take your first step on the path to economic freedom and sovereignty. Imagine how different your outlook on the future would be if they had not kept trying.</p><p>Remember, Bitcoin is hard to grok. It was for me, and maybe it was for you, too. It is also generally harder to understand the older someone is because they have lived in their economic circumstances for longer than a younger person has, and are often more reluctant to accept a new paradigm. Change can be scary, especially for someone that might be feeling confused about why the world seems to be spinning out of control. It might take more patience. It might take a few more conversations or the breaking up of big topics into smaller ones before the light bulb goes on for your mom. Try to find something she can relate to that Bitcoin fixes and focus on that aspect alone. Relevance is a powerful tool for persuasion.</p><h2>Break Up Bitcoin Topics For Your Mom</h2><figure>
        <img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk3NjY0ODE2NDMxNjM3ODA1/confused-math-lady.gif" height="394" width="620">
        
        
        <figcaption><a href="https://imgflip.com/gif-maker/286126573/Confused-Math-Lady"><em>Source</em></a></figcaption>
    </figure><p>For my mom, what made the light bulb go on in her head was when I related one piece of Bitcoin’s value proposition to something she understood from her own life. In her case, it was Bitcoin’s resistance to censorship and confiscation. </p><p>My mom grew up in Cuba and was a teenager when Fidel Castro <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fidel_Castro_in_the_Cuban_Revolution">rose to power in the late 1950s</a>. She remembers how her family’s meager cash savings, which my grandfather kept in a glass jar hidden in the house, was demonetized when the new regime took power. My grandfather refused to turn in the money and buried the jar in the backyard. He trusted that eventually, everything would go back to how it was before and the old currency would be accepted again. </p><p>This never happened, and my grandparents had to flee the island with my mom soon after. They also had to leave behind the valueless pieces of paper buried in the backyard of the house, which they also no longer owned thanks to the new government’s abolition of private property rights.</p><p>They lost the money, the house and they barely escaped with their lives. When I talked with her about Bitcoin in terms of it being property that no one can take from her, she got it.</p><h2>Give The Gift Of Bitcoin This Mother’s Day</h2><p>This Mother's Day, I encourage you to consider trying again. Try again like your mom encouraged you to do when she taught you to ride a bike, trying again even when you kept falling. Try again like my mom did when teaching me to parallel park, even after I ran over the garbage can… twice. </p><p>She never gave up on you, and now it is your turn to believe in her and return the favor. Now is the moment when you can show her that those lessons of persistence, patience and love took hold. This Mother’s Day is your chance to save her life and future, and to repay her for giving both of those things to you.</p><figure>
        <img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk3NjY0ODE2NDMxNzY4ODc3/dear-mom.png" height="527" width="620">
        
        
        <figcaption><a href="https://www.primitivesbykathy.com/products/box-sign-dear-mom-i-get-it-now-thank-you-103463/"><em>Source</em></a></figcaption>
    </figure><p><em>This is a guest post by Hector Alvero. Opinions expressed are entirely their own and do not necessarily reflect those of BTC Inc or Bitcoin Magazine.</em></p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkwNDI4MzgyNTMyNTQ0NDEw/114-btc.png"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk2NDE0NDk3MjI3ODEwMjkw/bitcoin-2023-website-article-banner.png" height="88" width="620" medium="image" type="image/png"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk3NjY0ODE2NDMxNjM4MzIy/a-flower-for-mothers-day.png" height="329" width="620" medium="image" type="image/png"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk3NjY0ODE2NDMxNzAzMzQx/jumping-on-the-bed.jpg" height="620" width="620" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk3NjY0ODE2NDMxNjM3ODA1/confused-math-lady.gif" height="394" width="620" medium="image" type="image/gif"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk3NjY0ODE2NDMxNzY4ODc3/dear-mom.png" height="527" width="620" medium="image" type="image/png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[SEC Slammed By U.S. Chamber Of Commerce For Regulatory Approach To Cryptocurrencies In Coinbase Filing]]></title><description><![CDATA[A court filing by the Chamber of Commerce found that the SEC’s slow and unclear regulatory actions have hampered innovation.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/legal/sec-slammed-by-u-s-chamber-of-commerce-for-crypto-regulations</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/legal/sec-slammed-by-u-s-chamber-of-commerce-for-crypto-regulations</guid><category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[Legal]]></category><category><![CDATA[Regulation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[BtcCasey]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 21:40:47 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkwMjY2NTkxMzgyODczMjQx/bitcoin-lightning-network.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><figure>
        <a href="https://bm.b.tc/bitcoin2023-conf-tickets" rel="nofollow"><img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk2NDE0NDk3MjI3ODEwMjkw/bitcoin-2023-website-article-banner.png" height="88" width="620"></a>
        
        
        
    </figure><p>The Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) is facing criticism from the United States Chamber of Commerce over its lack of clarity regarding which digital assets are securities under federal law. This issue has “immense implications for every person involved in the $1 trillion digital-asset economy,” a <a href="https://www.uschamber.com/assets/documents/U.S.-Chamber-Amicus-Brief-In-re-Coinbase-Third-Circuit.pdf">court filing</a> by the Chamber states.</p><p>According to the filing, the SEC has refused to engage in any systematic process or rulemaking to explain what its claimed authority means, instead offering one-off enforcement actions and public speeches. This has created regulatory uncertainty and destabilized the regulatory environment for digital assets.</p><p>In July 2022, Coinbase <a href="https://www.sec.gov/rules/petitions/2022/petn4-789.pdf">petitioned</a> the SEC to initiate a rulemaking regarding digital-asset securities. It urged the Commission to answer basic questions such as "which digital assets are securities?" More than 1,700 commenters echoed Coinbase's call, but the SEC expressed no interest in addressing Coinbase's request, according to the Chamber. Coinbase then <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/legal/coinbase-files-lawsuit-against-sec-seeking-regulatory-clarity">pursued a lawsuit</a> against the SEC in order to compel the regulator into action, which is where the filing by the U.S. Chamber of Commerce comes from. </p><p>The SEC's Chairman has asserted that the securities laws are unambiguous as applied to blockchain-based digital assets. Despite constructively denying Coinbase's petition, the SEC has refused to memorialize its decision in a formal response.</p><p>According to the Chamber, the SEC's lack of clarity has caused economic harm to both Coinbase and the broader business community. The uncertainty deters productive conduct and stifles innovation and undermines broader American economic and strategic interests. Continued uncertainty also has implications for the nation's geopolitical interests and the continued primacy of the dollar, given the increasing relevance of digital assets to international monetary policy.</p><p>The SEC's refusal to engage in rulemaking or respond to Coinbase's rulemaking petition has destabilized the regulatory environment for digital assets, the Chamber states. </p><p>“Agencies ordinarily provide regulatory clarity by promulgating rules of general applicability,” the filing says. “This preference for rulemaking has important benefits: It forces agencies to put to paper their regulatory plans, and it provides for fixed, prospective effective dates that ensure parties can bring their conduct into conformance with the law rather than be held liable later for violating duties they did not know existed.”</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkwMjY2NTkxMzgyODczMjQx/bitcoin-lightning-network.png"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk2NDE0NDk3MjI3ODEwMjkw/bitcoin-2023-website-article-banner.png" height="88" width="620" medium="image" type="image/png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Marathon Digital Holdings Faces Second Subpoena By SEC In Relation To Montana Mining Operation]]></title><description><![CDATA[According to a quarterly filing by the miner, the SEC is still inquiring about a Montana mining operation previously investigated in 2021.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/marathon-digital-holdings-faces-second-subpoena-by-sec</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/marathon-digital-holdings-faces-second-subpoena-by-sec</guid><category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category><category><![CDATA[Marathon Digital Holdings]]></category><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[Public Miners]]></category><category><![CDATA[Mining]]></category><category><![CDATA[Regulation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Business]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[BtcCasey]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 18:35:45 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk0MzI5NzY4OTU4MTc0ODk3/bitcoin-legal-regulation.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><p>Marathon Digital Holdings, a public Bitcoin miner, has received another subpoena from the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) regarding whether there were possible violations of federal securities law in agreements related to a Hardin, Montana data center facility that Marathon built.&nbsp;</p><p>“The Company and certain of its executives received a subpoena to produce documents and communications,” related to the facility in the third quarter of 2021, a <a href="https://ir.marathondh.com/sec-filings/all-sec-filings/content/0001493152-23-016184/0001493152-23-016184.pdf">quarterly filing</a> by the company stated. </p><p>In that agreement, Marathon issued 6,000,000 shares of restricted Common Stock, “in transactions exempt from registration under Section 4(a)(2) of the Securities Act of 1933.” However, the company filing revealed that it recently received another subpoena from the SEC on April 10, 2023, “relating to, among other things, transactions with related parties." <br><br>The company says it is cooperating with the investigation. The facility in Montana was designed to have up to 100-megawatts of power, according to the filing.</p><p>Marathon’s stock price has been volatile in recent months, reflecting the ups and downs of the bitcoin market, however, the stock has generally followed an upward trend since early 2021, as the value of bitcoin has risen.</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTk0MzI5NzY4OTU4MTc0ODk3/bitcoin-legal-regulation.png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Core Developer Amiti Uttarwar Will Be Reinforcing Decentralization At Bitcoin 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[Speaking at Bitcoin 2023, Bitcoin Core Developer Amiti Uttarwar will advocate for Bitcoin’s unique and critical development model.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/developer-amiti-uttarwar-at-bitcoin-2023</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/developer-amiti-uttarwar-at-bitcoin-2023</guid><category><![CDATA[Bitcoin 2023]]></category><category><![CDATA[core developer]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Amiti Uttarwar]]></category><category><![CDATA[Decentralization]]></category><category><![CDATA[Feature]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Peter Chawaga]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 13:55:31 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTc5Mjk3Nzg1MjcwNzA3OTA3/okcoin-bitmex-grant-150000-to-bitcoin-core-developer.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><figure>
        <a href="https://bm.b.tc/bitcoin2023-conf-tickets" rel="nofollow"><img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk2NDE0NDk3MjI3ODEwMjkw/bitcoin-2023-website-article-banner.png" height="88" width="620"></a>
        
        
        
    </figure><p>“One of the many ways that Bitcoin is an experiment is in its decentralized development model,” explained Amiti Uttarwar. “Whether a non-profit or a private company, the vast majority of software projects have a centralized structure for directing funding, prioritizing projects and coordinating efforts. But the community consensus model of Bitcoin is essential for ongoing censorship resistance. While it’s not easy to get tens of thousands of individual computers to agree, getting thousands of humans to agree is arguably the greater challenge.”</p><p>As a Bitcoin Core developer, Uttarwar is understandably fascinated with Bitcoin’s unique consensus model. She opted to focus on this community-led, open-source project full time in 2019, taking a significant pay cut from an engineering role with Coinbase, and has since earned grants to continue her work from <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/technical/okcoin-bitmex-operator-grant-150000-to-core-developer-amiti-uttarwar">OKCoin, BitMEX operator HDR Global</a> and <a href="https://www.gemini.com/blog/gemini-to-sponsor-bitcoin-core-developer-amiti-uttarwar">Gemini</a>. </p><p>Her past codebase contributions have <a href="https://github.com/bitcoin/bitcoin/pull/22950">changed the logic of Bitcoin’s address management</a>, <a href="https://github.com/bitcoin/bitcoin/pull/21528">fundamentally shifted address communication</a> and <a href="https://github.com/bitcoin/bitcoin/pull/18038">reduced privacy leaks caused by transaction broadcasting</a>. Today, her development focus is on improving support for privacy-enhancing communication layers like Tor, I2P and CJDNS through a collaboration with Chaincode Labs’ <a href="https://twitter.com/lightlike1?lang=en">Martin Zumsande</a>.</p><p>“While Bitcoin users can run nodes on multiple networks right now, the benefits are limited and often require a deep level of understanding from the node operator,” Uttarwar said. “Our current project is to enable automatic connections to nodes on every network that a user has enabled. With our work, if a user has enabled clearnet (with interfaces IPv4 or IPv6) and Tor on their Bitcoin node, the node will strive to ensure at least one of their 10 outbound connections is to an onion peer on the Tor network.” </p><p>For Uttarwar, who has seen her work merged into a Bitcoin Core update and who depends upon the larger community of Bitcoin developers for feedback and critical review of her work, the decentralization that underpins this software project is more than just a development model, it is a responsibility.</p><p>“Honoring decentralization in the world of Bitcoin development requires participation from Bitcoin users at varying levels of expertise,” she said. “For example, a protocol upgrade can only happen if users all over the world decide to adopt the code and activate the new logic... The question of what makes Bitcoin better evokes strong opinions in the community, but whether advocating for ossification or soft-fork methodology, funding developers or selecting maintainers, the question that underpins all of these conversations is: How do we agree on what Bitcoin needs in a decentralized way?”</p><p>Exploring this existential question will be Uttarwar’s focus at the upcoming Bitcoin 2023 conference, where she is <a href="https://b.tc/conference/agenda">set to deliver a keynote</a> titled “Decentralization In Action.” Rather than advocating for a particular Bitcoin project, use case or implication, Uttarwar will be using this spotlight to grapple with the very nature of organizational systems and the unique value of Bitcoin development in their context.</p><p>“My talk begins with an epistemological lens, identifying meaningful mental models by taking a look at the world around us,” she described. “By starting with these examples, I encourage the audience to broaden their understanding of how decentralization works in practice. The rest of the talk relates these questions back to daily challenges in the ecosystem of Bitcoin builders. Bitcoin relies on nodes running code around the world to ensure censorship resistance on the network. Upholding this goal also requires a decentralized model of development — the community needs to ensure that making changes to the code is not vulnerable to a single point of failure.”</p><p>She will also participate in a panel discussion alongside Bitcoin Magazine’s <a href="https://twitter.com/AaronvanW">Aaron van Wirdum</a>, Judica Founder <a href="https://twitter.com/JeremyRubin">Jeremy Rubin</a> and Lightning Network Developer <a href="https://twitter.com/tdryja">Tadge Dryja</a> called “Evolving Bitcoin’s Code” to further explore when and how changes can be successfully made to Bitcoin’s underlying software.</p><p>Uttarwar sees Bitcoin 2023 as a chance to advocate for the work that she and the rest of the Bitcoin development community are doing every day, reinforcing what decentralization really means for all of us who enjoy the tools built on top of this technology.</p><p>“At Bitcoin 2023, I aim to encourage people to develop a richer understanding of the complexity of what it means to build a truly decentralized technology, and how the success of Bitcoin relies on the individuals within the community contributing their unique attention,” she concluded. “I look forward to getting a pulse of the greater community, learning more about what excites people as well as current pain points. I’m also excited to connect with different people and discover corners of conversation that reinforce my excitement for this space.”</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTc5Mjk3Nzg1MjcwNzA3OTA3/okcoin-bitmex-grant-150000-to-bitcoin-core-developer.png"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk2NDE0NDk3MjI3ODEwMjkw/bitcoin-2023-website-article-banner.png" height="88" width="620" medium="image" type="image/png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[With The E-Krona, Sweden Is Attacking The Virtues Bitcoin Is Built To Protect]]></title><description><![CDATA[As they increase financial surveillance and control, Swiss authorities are inadvertently making the case for Bitcoin as an alternative.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/sweden-cbdc-for-financial-surveillance</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/sweden-cbdc-for-financial-surveillance</guid><category><![CDATA[cbdc]]></category><category><![CDATA[Opinion]]></category><category><![CDATA[Surveillance]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sweden]]></category><category><![CDATA[central bank]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Peter Bistoletti]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkwODQ5NjE5NzcxNTMyODgx/blockchain-surveillance.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><figure>
        <a href="https://bm.b.tc/bitcoin2023-conf-tickets" rel="nofollow"><img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk2NDE0NDk3MjI3ODEwMjkw/bitcoin-2023-website-article-banner.png" height="88" width="620"></a>
        
        
        
    </figure><p><em>This is an opinion editorial by Peter Bistoletti, a Bitcoiner who has lived in Sweden since 1971.</em></p><p>Sweden is the nightmare example of a state destroying financial privacy, winning the war on cash and having control of all financial transactions. Sweden has <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/opinion/articles/2023-03-01/the-cashless-economy-sweden-s-switch-to-digital-tells-a-cautionary-tale#xj4y7vzkg">almost completely abolished anonymous cash transactions</a> and, as a result, its regulators have control of all financial assets. Since at least 1971, when I moved to Sweden, bank assets have to be reported annually to the tax authorities, which can also demand documentation for all bank transactions. Since 2020, <a href="https://edri.org/our-work/swedish-law-enforcement-given-the-permission-to-hack/">the Swedish police have the right by law to acquire access to locked iphones and computers by use of force</a>. </p><p>In such a privacy-averse environment, one should consider Bitcoin as a better alternative. </p><h2>Introducing The E-Krona</h2><p>In the early days of Bitcoin, one could buy BTC anonymously through platforms such as LocalBitcoins, which is impossible today. To buy BTC through the majority of accessible platforms now, one has to follow strict KYC and AML regulations. Sweden <a href="https://coinatmradar.com/country/205/bitcoin-atm-sweden/#:~:text=Total%20number%20of%20Bitcoin%20ATMs%20%2F%20Tellers%20in%20Sweden%3A%200">also has no Bitcoin ATMs</a>. Swedish banks, politicians and the media have an overwhelmingly hostile attitude towards BTC.</p><p>Sweden is now moving toward a central-bank-issued, digital, national currency. <a href="https://www.riksbank.se/globalassets/media/rapporter/e-krona/2017/rapport_ekrona_uppdaterad_170920_eng.pdf">Since 2017</a>, the Swedish central bank, Sveriges Riksbank, <a href="https://www.nobelprize.org/prizes/economic-sciences/">the issuer</a> of the prize in economic science in memory of Alfred Nobel, has been promoting the e-krona as a complement to, or replacement of, physical cash. Proponents of e-krona argue that it prevents money laundering and criminal activities, speeds up the financial system and finetunes financial and monetary activities. Critics argue that it is the ultimate tool for financial censorship, control and surveillance. The development of e-krona is happening in <a href="https://www.riksbank.se/globalassets/media/rapporter/e-krona/2023/e-krona-pilot-phase-3.pdf">cooperation with other central banks</a> and the Bank For International Settlements (BIS).</p><p>E-krona is, at present, a pilot project, testing the technical platform and the cooperation of banks, companies and end users. The e-krona will preserve several functions of cash but <em>not</em> anonymity. The volume of e-krona created will <em>not</em> be determined by mining (like it is for Bitcoin), but by the central bank. Positive or negative interest rates will also be determined by the central bank. In a deeper sense, the e-krona without a function like Bitcoin mining is merely a central database controlled by the central bank. </p><h2>Designed To Limit Freedom</h2><p>The technical underpinnings for the e-krona are based on a form of blockchain technology through <a href="https://www.riksbank.se/globalassets/media/rapporter/e-krona/2022/e-krona-pilot-phase-2.pdf">the Corda platform, developed by the software company R3, and ran a February 2020 technical pilot project in cooperation with Accenture</a>, a large, global tech company. The e-krona is programmable and only the central bank can create and destroy e-krona, which is distributed via banks to the general public. The end user can exchange e-krona with bank money in an account and can execute and accept transactions. </p><p><a href="https://www.riksbank.se/en-gb/payments--cash/e-krona/technical-solution-for-the-e-krona-pilot/">There will be</a>:</p><ol><li>A “riksbank node” to create and destroy e-krona.</li><li>A “notary node” at the Riksbank to prevent double use of e-krona.</li><li>“Participants nodes” at banks, and payment service providers for checking the authenticity of e-krona.</li><li>“Nodes for end users” for deposits/withdrawals with the aid of digital wallets. </li><li>Mobile bank identifications, which <a href="https://www.bankid.com/en">have been in use in Sweden for many years</a>, will be necessary for personal identification.</li></ol><p>With the e-krona, the Swedish government will be able to see, in real time, every money transfer that anyone makes. It will also be possible to decrease access to the e-krona, for example, via a social credit score or if one is not compliant with climate change propositions. With the e-krona, the government can freeze someone's financial resources and the Swedish state can directly tax customers' accounts. As a guise pretending to spur spending, a negative interest rate would result in people losing money on their e-krona accounts and the programmable capacities of e-krona could mean that people are prohibited from buying certain goods. There will be numerous ways to program the e-krona, which opens the way to a dystopian, Orwellian surveillance and control state. </p><p>The e-krona is centralization and central planning as it existed in the <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gosbank#:~:text=The%20Soviet%20state%20used%20Gosbank,five%2Dyear%20plans%20and%20directives.">Soviet Union's banking system</a>.</p><p>Nevertheless, central planning has never worked, and large, centralized bureaucracies are often not very efficient. Central storage of financial information might also pose a problem for authorities. In a cyber attack, the entire network might be disabled. </p><p>Bitcoin, on the other hand, provides decentralization. It is much more difficult, maybe impossible, to attack the Bitcoin network. The Bitcoin network has also become more and more resilient over time. </p><h2>We Must Remain Vigilant </h2><p>However, the e-krona could become a competitor to Bitcoin because ordinary people might rather trust and use e-krona instead of bitcoin. One main purpose of the e-krona is price stability. Bitcoin has, at present, high price volatility. The bitcoin price’s stability is influenced by supply and demand, investor sentiments, trading activities, regulations and media hype. As of this writing, <a href="https://buybitcoinworldwide.com/volatility-index/">the latest 60-day estimate for bitcoin volatility was 2.48%; while for gold, the historical average volatility has been around 1.2%; and for major currencies, it is between 0.5% and 1%</a>.<br></p><p>Financial privacy should be a human right, but central bank digital currencies (CBDCs) and the e-krona are leading to the destruction of financial privacy and to the centralization of authoritarian state power. Therefore, we have to fight and prevent the creation and use of CBDCs and the e-krona. The vision of Satoshi Nakamoto, the inventor of Bitcoin, was built on three core values: security, privacy and decentralization. Bitcoin can provide all of these benefits, which CBDCs and the e-krona never can to the same extent. </p><p><em>This is a guest post by Peter Bistoletti. Opinions expressed are entirely their own and do not necessarily reflect those of BTC Inc or Bitcoin Magazine.</em></p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkwODQ5NjE5NzcxNTMyODgx/blockchain-surveillance.png"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk2NDE0NDk3MjI3ODEwMjkw/bitcoin-2023-website-article-banner.png" height="88" width="620" medium="image" type="image/png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[$48 Million Bitcoin Prius Set To Appear At Bitcoin 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[The “Bitcoin Car,” currently up for auction as a piece of Bitcoin history, will be on display in Miami Beach.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/48-million-bitcoin-prius-set-to-appear-at-bitcoin-2023</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/48-million-bitcoin-prius-set-to-appear-at-bitcoin-2023</guid><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Auction]]></category><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[cars]]></category><category><![CDATA[History]]></category><category><![CDATA[Bitcoin 2023]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[BtcCasey]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 17:52:46 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTgzMjM5NTgzMDQxODU2OTMw/img_6139.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><figure>
        <a href="https://bm.b.tc/bitcoin2023-conf-tickets" rel="nofollow"><img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk2NDE0NDk3MjI3ODEwMjkw/bitcoin-2023-website-article-banner.png" height="88" width="620"></a>
        
        
        
    </figure><p><em>Disclaimer: Bitcoin 2023 and Bitcoin Magazine are both operated by BTC Inc.</em></p><p>The “Bitcoin Car,” a 2013 Toyota Prius that was purchased with 1,000 bitcoin, will be showcased at the upcoming Bitcoin 2023 conference in Miami Beach. The event will take place from May 18-20, during which the car will be on display. The auction of the Bitcoin Car, being conducted via Scarce.City, a Bitcoin auction site, began on May 10 and will conclude on May 20. The current owners of the car, Devin Konopa and Trevor Pirtle, will be allowing Bitcoin OGs from all over the United States flocking to Bitcoin 2023 to tag the car before its appearance at the conference.</p><figure>
        <img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk3ODUyMDI5NDkzMTkyNTY2/image1.png" height="349" width="620">
        
        
        <figcaption><a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/48-million-bitcoin-car-up-for-auction-301821087.html"><em>Image Source</em></a></figcaption>
    </figure><p>Konopa spoke about the cultural significance of the car, stating that "this Prius represents the growth of public awareness, an acceptance of digital currency, and a significant tipping point in the Bitcoin space." He also expressed his desire to see the car displayed in a museum one day as a symbol of the rise of Bitcoin.</p><p>The Prius has been dubbed the "$48M Prius" by the media and the Bitcoin community due to the historical significance of its peak value, a <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/48-million-bitcoin-car-up-for-auction-301821087.html">press release</a> announcing the car’s appearance states. Since its purchase, the car has been to over 30 Bitcoin events according to the announcement, and has transported hundreds of thousands of dollars of cash from early Bitcoin ATMs.</p><p>The auction for the First Bitcoin Car is expected to generate a great deal of interest among Bitcoin enthusiasts and collectors at the highly anticipated event in Miami Beach. Those who wish to bid on the car can do so by visiting the <a href="http://firstbitcoincar.com/">FirstBitcoinCar.com</a> website, and those who seek to view the car for themselves can get tickets for Bitcoin 2023 at <a href="http://b.tc/conference">b.tc/conference</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTgzMjM5NTgzMDQxODU2OTMw/img_6139.png"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk2NDE0NDk3MjI3ODEwMjkw/bitcoin-2023-website-article-banner.png" height="88" width="620" medium="image" type="image/png"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk3ODUyMDI5NDkzMTkyNTY2/image1.png" height="349" width="620" medium="image" type="image/png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Death Of Trust: As Institutions Erode, Bitcoin Is Our Only Hope]]></title><description><![CDATA[Public trust in authorities is failing and doomsayers are gaining attention, underscoring the need for Bitcoin to replace subjective truth.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/as-trust-erodes-bitcoin-is-verifiable</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/as-trust-erodes-bitcoin-is-verifiable</guid><category><![CDATA[Opinion]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[verification]]></category><category><![CDATA[Trust]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Dan Weintraub]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkzOTk5NDg5MTkzODEzNTA5/bitcoin-domino.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><figure>
        <a href="https://bm.b.tc/bitcoin2023-conf-tickets" rel="nofollow"><img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk2NDE0NDk3MjI3ODEwMjkw/bitcoin-2023-website-article-banner.png" height="88" width="620"></a>
        
        
        
    </figure><p><em>This is an opinion editorial by Dan Weintraub, an author and high school teacher who first became interested in Bitcoin while teaching economics.</em></p><p>Recently, I’ve been thinking a good deal about Balaji Srinivasan’s $1 million dollar bet that bitcoin would reach $1 million in June (<a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/brandonkochkodin/2023/05/02/balaji-srinivasan-concedes-bet-that-bitcoin-will-reach-1-million-in-90-days/?sh=698f93cb76c6">which he recently conceded</a>), his <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/balaji-srinivasan-says-hyperinflation-happening-now-makes-million-dollar-bets-on-bitcoin-price-exceeding-1m-in-90-days/">apparent hyperbole with regard to imminent U.S. dollar hyperinflation</a> and his <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/former-coinbase-cto-urges-get-to-bitcoin-before-cbdc-digital-lockdown/">musings about digital lockdowns</a>. It all sounds a bit far-fetched to me. </p><p>On this score, he reminds me of Peter Schiff, a man who <a href="https://www.yahoo.com/now/crypto-extinction-peter-schiff-predicted-140000434.html">for decades</a> has told us the sky is falling and that the world will end as fiat currencies all collapse; a man who claims intellectual superiority over <a href="https://www.thestreet.com/video/fed-might-look-like-fools-if-they-raise-rates-says-peter-schiff-13275500">the “fools” at the Federal Reserve</a> (meanwhile and generally speaking, the global economy hums along and collapse appears, at least for the time being, to be the stuff of dystopian clickbait on YouTube). </p><p>I, for one, try to eschew conspiracy thinking because it feels neurologically indulgent to me. In simpler words, those who peddle in conspiracy theories do so because it gets them, and their followers, off. “Meltdown masturbation,” if you will. (By way of example, the <a href="https://www.logically.ai/factchecks/library/bcfb22c4">wild-eyed belief that the U.S. government used the COVID-19 lockdowns as a trial run for further repression</a> reeks of paranoia and a desperate quest for making some kind of dopamine-producing meaning out of a rather bleak moment in time. Crazy town, really; but good fodder for the production of adrenaline-inducing catastrophe porn.)</p><p>Yes, I am skeptical of prognostications of impending doom. But that said, there is an underbelly to such thinking that reveals a far more troubling dynamic; a dynamic that, driven by the exponential age in which it exists, is fast on the rise. And this dynamic will be far more destructive, far more catastrophic, than the supposed collapse of fiat or that the coming of a global banking crisis could ever be. </p><p>We are entering an age in which all trust is dying, and with the end of trust comes the end of… <em>everything</em>. Sure, I may think that Srinivasan and all of the other gloom-and-doom, the-end-is-nigh purveyors have, in some manner and to some degree, lost their grips, but there is something quite revealing not simply in the power of their musings, but in the reality that it reveals, in the attention and excitement it attracts. </p><p>You see, no one trusts anything or anyone anymore. And that utterly terrifies me.</p><h2>The Death Of Trust</h2><p>The list of institutions that we increasingly mistrust is, well, endless. And the depth and breadth of such distrust grows daily. </p><p>I’m not so sure that I need to provide the reader with an in-depth analysis of our collective loss of trust in everything. And so, in the interest of brevity, here is the abridged version:</p><p>Track the numbers and you will see that <a href="https://www.pewresearch.org/politics/2022/06/06/public-trust-in-government-1958-2022">trust in government is at all-time lows</a> and continues to crash. Whether it’s because our leaders actually are dishonest, self-serving, greedy, power-hungry, incipient lobbyist-ghouls, or whether it’s because that’s how they are portrayed in the media, government officials and institutions are roundly and profoundly distrusted. </p><p>An <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/emilywashburn/2023/02/03/america-less-confident-in-police-than-ever-before-a-look-at-the-numbers/?sh=2e27e4296afb">ever-diminishing minority trusts law enforcement</a>, perhaps because such a minority either has relatives who serve on the police force or because their own power is buoyed by the machinations of the policing and legal systems. For the most part, Americans seem to view police officers as former high-school misfits who magically discovered expressions of sweet revenge in being able to bully the rest of us. Add to this the widespread corruption that permeates every nook and cranny of law enforcement and of our justice system (<em>cough, the </em><a href="https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/politics-law-drive-supreme-court-decisions-poll/story?id=99168846"><em>Supreme Court</em></a><em>, cough</em>), and it’s no wonder that “f*** the police” is a popular cultural refrain. </p><p>Interestingly, <a href="https://news.gallup.com/poll/403166/americans-trust-media-remains-near-record-low.aspx">fewer and fewer people trust the so-called mainstream media</a>; so few, in fact, that there actually isn’t a mainstream media anymore. Pretty much all media has become an expression of ideological vitriol, a theatrical dance aimed at capturing a larger market share of the neurologically dispossessed; a cynical beast birthed and nurtured to line the coffers of the men and women who captain these galactic founts of misinformation. </p><p><a href="https://www.k12dive.com/news/pandemic-declined-trust-public-education/637383/">Few trust our public school systems anymore</a>. What was once viewed as a virtuous institution, an endeavor of the highest good, public education has been summarily devoured by every possible ideologically-propelled interest group; the vomit that has followed has painted a picture of public education as rife with lazy teachers teaching knucklehead kids.</p><p>I could go on. From corrupt corporations and their corrupt CEOs to the self-serving, self-righteous and self-aggrandizing leaders of organized labor; from duplicitous, woke and censorship-informed activists touting the need for correct pronoun adherence to the reactionary and manipulative religious leaders looking to return the nation to the wonderful patriarchies of the 1950s, trust is vanishing into the very ether in which these individuals stoke their fires and solidify their self-concentered narratives.</p><p>But wait! It gets better. For now, superimposed over this already bleak landscape, say hello to ChatGPT, to deep fake technology, to central bank digital currencies; bid an open-hearted welcome to trust’s final frontier, a world in which discerning truth from falsehood becomes virtually impossible.</p><p>What a dumpster of a world. What is to be done?</p><p>Enter, Bitcoin.</p><h2>Bitcoin And Verification Of Truth</h2><p>I have written several papers (I like to call them books because it makes me feel smart, and I have even published them on Amazon) about Bitcoin, extolling the virtues of this quite-extraordinary technology. In all of those pieces I have asked, nay begged, that we have some imagination when considering our Bitcoin future. I will go even further here: Bitcoin is our <em>only</em> hope in an increasingly trustless world, for within the Bitcoin protocol lies the answer to all of the conundrums <em>posed</em> by a trustless world: </p><p>The ultimate answer is verification of truth. Hear me out.</p><p>To begin with, when I suggest that we have some imagination, I am actually not asking for all that much. The boxes in which we live, the lenses through which we view reality, have evolved time and time again. It wasn’t all that long ago that we believed that the Earth was the center of the universe, that humans would never fly, that computers were the providence of NASA. Things have changed, and they have changed quickly. The <a href="https://www.history.com/this-day-in-history/world-wide-web-launches-in-public-domain">public internet was born</a> around 30 years ago, give or take. Now look at us. It is almost too hard to imagine what the next 10 years will bring.</p><p>So, why Bitcoin? Why is this relatively-straightforward technology (ingenious and elegant, complex and nuanced… but straightforward nonetheless) the answer to the impending doom we all face if we are unable to prime and restart our national and international trust engine? </p><p>It’s simple. Because Bitcoin <em>is</em> the truth. On a most basic level, the Bitcoin protocol — and the tens of thousands of nodes that run the software — verifies each and every transaction that takes place on chain. No one is in control. No one’s word needs to be taken as fact. The truth is manifest and auditable on the blockchain itself. Countless, entirely-objective nodes make falsification of the record an impossibility. Bitcoin is thus an inviolable, immutable, incontrovertible truth.</p><p>Have some imagination!</p><p>What if, just what if, the Bitcoin network, in time, becomes the base layer of this thing we call the internet? What if all data that passes through this network is verified and scoured for falsehood by the soon-to-be billions of verifying nodes; nodes that become native to the devices that we employ for all of our communication and social/virtual interactions? And what if more and more people, in an effort to <em>believe</em>, abandon the cynical and exploitative and fetid digital world that has evolved to date, and instead join a network of unassailable truth?</p><p>You see, the promise of Bitcoin is not that it serves as sound money in an unsound monetary universe; the promise is not that it births a banking system that is devoid of scammy, fraudulent middlemen; no, the promise is far, far more profound. </p><p>The promise of Bitcoin is that it slowly devours the very beast that gave birth to its need. </p><p>Trust is a human imperative, a social imperative. Without trust, chaos ensues. In a world in which belief in things must always be questioned, mental health suffers, governments fail and anarchy rises; lawlessness and violence become the norm rather than the exception. In a trustless world, isolation and hoarding are seen as virtues rather than maladaptations. In a trustless world, everything falls apart, institutions crumble, warlords and demagogues emerge on an ever-rising tide of uncertainty and fear. </p><p>We are moving toward such a future, toward such a world. Bitcoin is our only hope. In Bitcoin there exists the possibility that trust can slowly be reestablished, not based upon the words and deeds of men, but instead on a universal digital protocol that sifts through the mire and always, without prejudice, arrives at the truth.</p><p>We must have the imagination to believe in this possibility. This is what makes Bitcoin a beacon of hope, a ray of light permeating the haze of a creeping fog of surrender. </p><p>I HODL bitcoin, thus. I preach the gospel of Bitcoin because I dare to hope, for my great grandkids, in a world community governed by truth, verified by benevolent objectivity; a world in which trust forms the very core of our existence.</p><p>So to Srinivasan and Schiff and all of the other catastrophians I say: Perhaps you are right. But the truth remains: The only way out of this existential death spiral is through a rebirth of trust, and only Bitcoin, realized to its highest and most majestic potential, can provide this. </p><p>Just imagine.</p><p><em>This is a guest post by Dan Weintraub. Opinions expressed are entirely their own and do not necessarily reflect those of BTC Inc or Bitcoin Magazine.</em></p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkzOTk5NDg5MTkzODEzNTA5/bitcoin-domino.png"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk2NDE0NDk3MjI3ODEwMjkw/bitcoin-2023-website-article-banner.png" height="88" width="620" medium="image" type="image/png"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Declaration Of Monetary Independence To Reappear At Bitcoin 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[Miami Beach will once again see the DoMI signed by thousands of excited Bitcoiners as they flock to Bitcoin 2023.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/declaration-of-monetary-independence-to-reappear-at-bitcoin-2023</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/declaration-of-monetary-independence-to-reappear-at-bitcoin-2023</guid><category><![CDATA[Events]]></category><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Bitcoin 2023]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[BtcCasey]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 23:25:50 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkyNTM3MTYyODg3OTk2OTY0/individual-challenge-climb-peak-flag-mountain-top-photo.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><figure>
        <a href="https://bm.b.tc/bitcoin2023-conf-tickets" rel="nofollow"><img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk2NDE0NDk3MjI3ODEwMjkw/bitcoin-2023-website-article-banner.png" height="88" width="620"></a>
        
        
        
    </figure><p><em>Disclaimer: Bitcoin 2023 and Bitcoin Magazine are both operated by BTC Inc.</em></p><p>The Declaration of Monetary Independence (DoMI), which made an <a href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/bitcoin-2022-separation-of-money">impressive debut at Bitcoin 2022</a> in Miami Beach, will once again be on display at Bitcoin 2023. The 9-foot by 12-foot document made a massive impact on attendees at the previous conference, with thousands of Bitcoin enthusiasts adding their signatures to the piece of art. <a href="https://declarationofmonetaryindependence.org/">DoMI</a> is essentially a 21st-century version of the Declaration of Independence, with 27 reasons listed on why fiat currency is an unfair and broken monetary system controlled by governments that favors the wealthiest and most privileged. The second half of the document lists 29 reasons why Bitcoin is the fairest and most egalitarian monetary system ever conceived and implemented.</p><figure>
        <img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTg4ODc1MDA5NjMwOTM4NzA0/domi-saturday.jpg" height="827" width="620">
        
        
        
    </figure><p>At Bitcoin 2022, DoMI was displayed at the entrance of the Nakamoto Stage, where it attracted the attention of everyone who entered. The signing got off to a slow start, but after one of the original authors of the document signed it, hundreds of attendees started to add their own signatures to the piece of art. Over the course of the three-day conference, thousands of people signed the document, making it resemble activist street art upon a replica of the original Declaration of Independence.</p><p>As Bitcoin 2023 approaches, Bitcoin enthusiasts are eagerly looking forward to the re-emergence of DoMI. The document will once again be displayed prominently at the conference, this time on a 10-foot by 8-foot document with a “Tick toc next block” background in the Lightning Food Court, reminding everyone of the need to separate money from the state and to promote Bitcoin as the fairest and most egalitarian monetary system. Attendees can expect the same enthusiasm and excitement that characterized the signing of DoMI at the previous conference, with many people eager to add their signatures to this historic document.</p><p>DoMI is a reminder that Bitcoin is more than just a digital currency; it represents a fundamental shift in the way we think about money and the role of government in its creation and regulation. As Bitcoin continues to gain wider acceptance and adoption, DoMI will serve as a testament to the power of decentralization and the need for a fairer and more just monetary system.</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTkyNTM3MTYyODg3OTk2OTY0/individual-challenge-climb-peak-flag-mountain-top-photo.png"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk2NDE0NDk3MjI3ODEwMjkw/bitcoin-2023-website-article-banner.png" height="88" width="620" medium="image" type="image/png"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTg4ODc1MDA5NjMwOTM4NzA0/domi-saturday.jpg" height="827" width="620" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bull Bitcoin Launches No-KYC Purchasing Through Canadian Post Office]]></title><description><![CDATA[Users can now purchase up to $999 CAD at any post office without providing personal identifying information.]]></description><link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/bull-bitcoin-launches-no-kyc-purchasing</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/bull-bitcoin-launches-no-kyc-purchasing</guid><category><![CDATA[News]]></category><category><![CDATA[Business]]></category><category><![CDATA[KYC]]></category><category><![CDATA[bull bitcoin]]></category><category><![CDATA[Exchanges]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[BtcCasey]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 14:59:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTgyODY5MDM0MjAxNTIzNjE5/img_4905.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- tml-version="2" --><figure>
        <a href="https://bm.b.tc/bitcoin2023-conf-tickets" rel="nofollow"><img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk2NDE0NDk3MjI3ODEwMjkw/bitcoin-2023-website-article-banner.png" height="88" width="620"></a>
        
        
        
    </figure><p>Canadian Bitcoin exchange, <a href="https://www.bullbitcoin.com/">Bull Bitcoin</a>, has launched a new no-KYC (know-your-customer) service which enables users to buy bitcoin with cash or debit card. Users can go to any Canadian Post office, scan the QR code generated on the Bull Bitcoin app, and pay in cash or via debit card.</p><figure>
        <img src="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk3ODI1OTY0Njc4MzI1NDIw/image1.png" height="484" width="620">
        
        
        
    </figure><p>The funds are automatically added to the user's Bull Bitcoin account within a few minutes. Transactions of up to ~$745 ($999.99 CAD) can be made per transaction, with no KYC required. The exchange has a fee of 2% for no-KYC sats, the cheapest of any such service in Canada, according to a press release sent to Bitcoin Magazine, while Bull Bitcoin's on-chain withdrawals remain free.</p><p>Canadian regulations state that Bitcoin exchanges must perform KYC and keep transaction records for all purchases above $1,000 CAD. Bull Bitcoin states that its privacy policy complies with the fair information principles in the Personal Information Protection and Electronics Document Act (PIPEDA), which prevents it from collecting information that is not needed for a legitimate purpose. </p><p>With no risk of chargeback for cash and debit card transactions, the company states that it has no legitimate reason to ask for KYC.</p><p>Bull Bitcoin aims to offer cash bitcoin purchases due to customer demand, and for those without access to bank accounts. The company also aims to attract migrant workers for remittances and users who want to limit the amount of personal information they give to trusted third parties. In addition, cash and debit card transactions are not subject to fraudulent chargebacks, unlike bank transfers and e-transfers. The process of funding accounts with cash or debit cards is also faster and more convenient.</p>]]></content:encoded><media:thumbnail url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_limit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cfl_progressive%2Ch_1200%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_1200/MTgyODY5MDM0MjAxNTIzNjE5/img_4905.jpg"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk2NDE0NDk3MjI3ODEwMjkw/bitcoin-2023-website-article-banner.png" height="88" width="620" medium="image" type="image/png"/><media:content url="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/.image/c_fit%2Ccs_srgb%2Cq_auto:good%2Cw_620/MTk3ODI1OTY0Njc4MzI1NDIw/image1.png" height="484" width="620" medium="image" type="image/png"/></item></channel></rss>