<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:bnmedia="https://news.bitcoin.com/">

<channel>
	<title>Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/</link>
	<description>Daily Bitcoin News</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 06:43:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>LBank Exchange Will List DBear Coin (DBC) on July 31, 2023</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-dbear-coin-dbc-on-july-31-2023/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Media]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 11:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press release]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DBC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dbear Coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lbank]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LBank Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lbank Labs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=600283&#038;preview=true&#038;preview_id=600283</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/21323-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="" decoding="async" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/21323-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/21323-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/21323-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/21323-1536x864.jpg 1536w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/21323-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/21323-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/21323-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/21323-1520x855.jpg 1520w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/21323-1280x720.jpg 1280w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/21323.jpg 1600w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />PRESS RELEASE. Road Town, BVI, July 30, 2023 &#x2013; LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, will list DBear Coin (DBC) on July 31, 2023. For all users of LBank Exchange, the DBC/USDT trading pair will be officially available for trading at 6:00 UTC on July 31, 2023. DBear Coin (DBC) is a lifestyle [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/21323-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/21323-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/21323-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/21323-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/21323-1536x864.jpg 1536w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/21323-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/21323-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/21323-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/21323-1520x855.jpg 1520w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/21323-1280x720.jpg 1280w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/21323.jpg 1600w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>PRESS RELEASE. Road Town, BVI, July 30, 2023</strong> &#x2013; LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, will list DBear Coin (DBC) on July 31, 2023. For all users of LBank Exchange, the DBC/<a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/USDT" 312012  target="_blank">USDT</a> trading pair will be officially available for trading at 6:00 UTC on July 31, 2023.</p>
<p>DBear Coin (DBC) is a lifestyle Blockchain-Commerce for the MZ generation, characterized by Web3.0, Metaverse, and customized NFT. All DBC platforms are interconnected like a universe, enabling users to learn, play, and shop. Its native token, DBC, will be listed on LBank Exchange at 6:00 UTC on July 31, 2023, with the goal of expanding its global footprint and supporting the realization of its forward-thinking objectives.</p>
<p><b>Introducing DBear Coin</b></p>
<p>DBear Coin (DBC) is a lifestyle Blockchain-Commerce for the MZ generation, characterized by Web3.0, Metaverse, and customized NFT. All DBC platforms are interconnected like a universe, enabling users to learn, play, and shop. DBC serves as both a membership point and a medium of exchange within the D:Bear universe, facilitated through the DMNC NRT card, while also acting as a rewarding mechanism. Leading the BDC project is Man-won Chung, the former CEO of SK Telecom, a company with a market capitalization of $8 billion and the creator of the widely successful OKcashbag point system, which boasts 21 million users.</p>
<p>The Dbear Universe project aims to provide a comprehensive &#x201C;Character-Based Lifestyle Commerce&#x201D; experience for the MZ (Millennial and Gen Z) generation. By becoming a member of the Dbear Universe, individuals will receive a Dbear Member&#x2019;s NFT Card (DMNC), granting them access to various lifestyle platforms within the Dbear ecosystem. Holding the NFT card allows members to enjoy exclusive consumer rewards and benefits. B-Commerce (Blockchain Commerce) is at the core of the project, introducing an innovative consumer benefit NFT model. Dbear Universe stands out as the sole NFT commerce initiative in the rapidly growing global character market. Through attractive items and features, members can create their unique NFTs through the MCM (Members Creating & Minting) process, potentially increasing the value of their digital assets. Additionally, Dbear Universe offers access keys to BEARMANSION, a metaverse within the Dbear ecosystem.</p>
<p>The project envisions utilizing innovative technologies and ideas to improve the quality of life for humanity, fostering a richer and happier family life. Its mission is to suggest common interests and hobbies for parents and children to share and empathize with, while building a user-friendly and accessible system for everyone. Additionally, it aims to reduce financial stress in households through an effective reward system and integrate blockchain into daily life, creating an encompassing ecosystem. The project emphasizes practical liquidity, freedom of choice, and rational decision-making. It strives to establish a fair hierarchy based on levels of interest and participation and ensures sustainability through proactive system management and investment in development.</p>
<p><b>About DBC Token</b></p>
<p>The main mission of D-Bear Coin (DBC) is to establish a stable B-Commerce Economy within the D-Bear Universe ecosystem. The project team aims to implement inflation-deflation prevention policies to ensure the stable function of DBC as a currency and minimize significant price fluctuations. Through platform development, marketing, and supply policies, the project aims to increase the holding value of DBC progressively, providing enhanced lifestyle opportunities for members of the D-Bear Universe.</p>
<p>Based on ERC20, DBC has a total supply of 4 billion (i.e. 4,000,000,000). The token distribution consists of 15% for the team, 10% for marketing, 7.5% for promotion and others, 30% for Member Rewards, and 18.75% each for LMNC SWAP and Point SWAP. It will be listed on LBank Exchange at 6:00 UTC on July 31, 2023, investors who are interested in DBC can easily buy and sell it on LBank Exchange by then. The listing of DBC token on LBank Exchange will undoubtedly help it further expand its business and draw more attention in the market.</p>
<p><b>Learn More about DBC Token:</b></p>
<p>Official Website: <a href="https://www.dbear.io/">https://www.dbear.io/</a></p>
<p>Contract: <a href="https://etherscan.io/token/0xe1C6785660eB3C1b2744BfF7504dF5F6ad6276E3">https://etherscan.io/token/0xe1C6785660eB3C1b2744BfF7504dF5F6ad6276E3</a></p>
<p><b>About LBank</b></p>
<p>LBank is one of the top crypto exchanges, established in 2015. It offers specialized financial derivatives, expert asset management services, and safe crypto trading to its users. The platform holds over 9 million users from more than 210 regions across the world. LBank is a cutting-edge growing platform that ensures the integrity of users&#x2019; funds and aims to contribute to the global adoption of cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p><b>Start Trading Now: </b><a href="https://www.lbank.com/">lbank.com</a></p>
<p><b>Community & Social Media: </b></p>
<p>l <a href="https://t.me/LBank_en">Telegram</a></p>
<p>l <a href="https://twitter.com/LBank_Exchange">Twitter</a></p>
<p>l <a href="https://www.facebook.com/LBank.info">Facebook</a></p>
<p>l <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/lbank">LinkedIn</a></p>
<p>l <a href="https://www.instagram.com/lbank_exchange/">Instagram</a></p>
<p>l <a href="https://www.youtube.com/c/LBankExchange">YouTube</a></p>
<p><b>Press contact: </b></p>
<p><a href="mailto:press@lbank.info">press@lbank.info</a></p>
<p><b>Business Contact:</b></p>
<p>LBK Blockchain Co. Limited</p>
<p>LBank Exchange</p>
<p><a href="mailto:marketing@lbank.info">marketing@lbank.info</a></p>
<p><a href="mailto:business@lbank.info">business@lbank.info</a></p>
<p>&#xA0;</p>
<p>&#xA0;</p>
<hr>
<p><small><i>This is a press release. Readers should do their own due diligence before taking any actions related to the promoted company or any of its affiliates or services. Bitcoin.com is not responsible, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused or alleged to be caused by or in connection with the use of or reliance on any content, goods or services mentioned in the press release.</i></small></p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/21323-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[LBank Exchange Will List DBear Coin (DBC) on July 31, 2023]]></bnmedia:barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto․com Granted Registration Approval in the Netherlands</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/crypto%e2%80%a4com-granted-registration-approval-in-the-netherlands/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lubomir Tassev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 08:30:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchanges]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[approval]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Bank]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto.com]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[De Nederlandsche Bank]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DNB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dutch]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[EU]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Europe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Netherlands]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[registration]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[rules]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[U.K.]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=600236</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1940355673-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Crypto․com Granted Registration Approval in the Netherlands" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1940355673-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1940355673-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1940355673-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1940355673-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1940355673-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1940355673-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1940355673.jpg 1281w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />Digital asset exchange Crypto․com has been approved for registration as a crypto service provider in the Netherlands. The regulatory nod comes after a review of its business operations and compliance with the Dutch anti-money laundering legislation, the company pointed out. Trading Platform Crypto․com Adds Another Regulatory Approval in Europe Cryptocurrency exchange Crypto․com has secured an [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1940355673-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Crypto․com Granted Registration Approval in the Netherlands" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1940355673-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1940355673-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1940355673-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1940355673-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1940355673-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1940355673-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1940355673.jpg 1281w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>Digital asset exchange Crypto․com has been approved for registration as a crypto service provider in the Netherlands. The regulatory nod comes after a review of its business operations and compliance with the Dutch anti-money laundering legislation, the company pointed out. </strong></p>
<h2>Trading Platform Crypto․com Adds Another Regulatory Approval in Europe</h2>
<p>Cryptocurrency exchange Crypto․com has secured an approval for registration with the Dutch central bank as a provider of crypto services in the Netherlands. The confirmation follows a comprehensive review of its compliance with the country’s Money Laundering and Terrorist Financing (Prevention) Act, the company noted in a press release.</p>
<p>Crypto․com’s CEO Kris Marszalek described the registration approval from De Nederlandsche Bank (<a href="https://www.dnb.nl/en/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">DNB</a>) as a significant milestone for the company’s business and a testament to its commitment to compliance. He was also quoted as stating:</p>
<blockquote><p>Collaborating with regulators to responsibly advance the crypto and blockchain industry is of paramount importance to Crypto.com.</p></blockquote>
<p>Marszalek further emphasized that the exchange looks forward to continuing to work with the DNB and other regulators around the world. With the Dutch registration, the trading platform adds another approval from authorities in Europe amid increased regulatory uncertainty and scrutiny for the industry in many jurisdictions.</p>
<p>The Singapore-based crypto exchange has already obtained its license as a Major Payment Institution (MPI) for digital token payments, e-money issuance, account issuance, and cross-border and domestic money transfer services from the city-state’s monetary authority. It has registrations and authorizations in the U.S., Australia, Dubai, and South Korea.</p>

<p>On the Old Continent, Crypto․com has received registration as a Digital Asset Service Provider (DASP) from the Financial Markets Authority (AMF) of France and registration approval as a crypto asset business from the U.K.’s Financial Conduct Authority (FCA). The crypto firm is registered as a Virtual Asset Service Provider (VASP) in Spain as well and has registrations in Italy, Greece and Cyprus.</p>
<p>Crypto․com’s approval in the Netherlands comes after the decision of  to <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/binance-pulls-out-of-netherlands-seeks-to-deregister-cyprus-unit/">pull out</a> of the Dutch market after failing to obtain registration as a crypto service provider. Sayings it wants to focus on fewer regulated entities in Europe, the world’s largest exchange for digital assets also applied for deregistration in Cyprus, <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/binance-unit-in-britain-cancels-uk-regulatory-authorization/">canceled</a> its U.K. authorization, and <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/binance-withdraws-its-crypto-license-application-in-germany/">withdrew</a> its license applications in Germany and Austria. In the past months, Binance has been under increased pressure from regulators around the world.</p>
<p>The EU is yet to implement its package of comprehensive regulations for the sector, the Markets in Crypto Assets (MiCA) law. A provisional agreement on the legislation was <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/eu-makes-deal-on-mica-legislation-to-regulate-crypto-markets/">reached</a> in June 2022, EU lawmakers <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/eu-parliament-greenlights-markets-in-crypto-assets-law-tracing-rules/">voted</a> to approve it in April of this year and the EU Council <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/eu-council-adopts-new-rules-for-europes-crypto-markets/">adopted</a> the new rules in May. However, their Union-wide implementation is expected to take another 18 months.</p>
<p><em><strong>What future do you see for cryptocurrency exchanges operating in Europe? Share your thoughts on the subject in the comments section below. </strong></em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_1940355673-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[Crypto․com adds another #regulatory approval in #Europe. ]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA[Digital asset #exchange Crypto․com receives #registration approval in the #Netherlands. ]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Another US Bank Collapses: Heartland Tri-State Bank Closed by Regulator</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/another-us-bank-collapses-heartland-tri-state-bank-closed-by-regulator/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Kevin Helms]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 05:30:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bank failures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking Crisis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[failed banks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Heartland Tri-State Bank]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Heartland Tri-State Bank closed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Heartland Tri-State Bank failed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Heartland Tri-State Bank FDIC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Heartland Tri-State Bank Kansas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Heartland Tri-State Bank seized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[regional banks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=600245&#038;preview=true&#038;preview_id=600245</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/heartland-tri-state-bank-failure-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Another US Bank Collapses: Heartland Tri-State Bank Closed by Regulator" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/heartland-tri-state-bank-failure-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/heartland-tri-state-bank-failure-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/heartland-tri-state-bank-failure-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/heartland-tri-state-bank-failure-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/heartland-tri-state-bank-failure-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/heartland-tri-state-bank-failure-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/heartland-tri-state-bank-failure.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />Heartland Tri-State Bank has become the latest bank in the U.S. to fail. The Kansas banking regulator closed the bank and appointed the Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation (FDIC) as the receiver on Friday. Regulator Shuts Down Heartland Tri-State Bank A regional bank in the U.S., Heartland Tri-State Bank, was closed by the Kansas Office of [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/heartland-tri-state-bank-failure-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Another US Bank Collapses: Heartland Tri-State Bank Closed by Regulator" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/heartland-tri-state-bank-failure-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/heartland-tri-state-bank-failure-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/heartland-tri-state-bank-failure-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/heartland-tri-state-bank-failure-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/heartland-tri-state-bank-failure-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/heartland-tri-state-bank-failure-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/heartland-tri-state-bank-failure.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>Heartland Tri-State Bank has become the latest bank in the U.S. to fail. The Kansas banking regulator closed the bank and appointed the Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation (FDIC) as the receiver on Friday.</strong></p>
<h2>Regulator Shuts Down Heartland Tri-State Bank</h2>
<p>A regional bank in the U.S., Heartland Tri-State Bank, was closed by the Kansas Office of the State Bank Commissioner on Friday. The regulator subsequently named the Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation (FDIC) as the receiver. The FDIC announced:</p>
<blockquote><p>To protect depositors, the FDIC entered into a purchase and assumption agreement with Dream First Bank, National Association, of Syracuse, Kansas, to assume all of the deposits of Heartland Tri-State Bank.</p></blockquote>
<p>The FDIC explained that Heartland Tri-State Bank had approximately $139 million in total assets and $130 million in total deposits as of March 31. In addition to assuming all of the failed bank deposits, Dream First Bank, National Association, &#8220;agreed to purchase essentially all of the failed bank’s assets,&#8221; the FDIC detailed.</p>
<p>The regulator added that the four branches of Heartland Tri-State Bank will reopen as branches of Dream First Bank, National Association, on Monday, under normal business hours.</p>

<p>Several banks have failed in the U.S. this year. On March 10, <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/first-citizens-bank-acquires-silicon-valley-bank-costing-fdic-deposit-insurance-fund-an-estimated-20b/">Silicon Valley Bank</a> was closed by the California Department of Financial Protection &amp; Innovation. On March 12, <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/signature-bank-closure-has-nothing-to-do-with-crypto-says-regulator/">Signature Bank</a> was closed by the New York State Department of Financial Services. On May 1, <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/jpmorgan-chase-assumes-control-of-first-republic-bank-following-seizure-by-california-regulators/">First Republic Bank</a> was closed by the California Department of Financial Protection and Innovation. Moreover, <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/silvergate-bank-announces-voluntary-liquidation-as-crypto-industry-woes-persist/">Silvergate Bank</a> announced voluntary liquidation.</p>
<p>Multiple people have foreseen an increase in regional bank failures as the Federal Reserve persists with its interest rate hikes. This week, the Fed raised interest rates by <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/federal-reserve-raises-federal-funds-rate-by-25bps-amidst-moderate-economic-growth/">25 basis points</a>. Rich Dad Poor Dad author Robert Kiyosaki warned in April that regional banks are <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/robert-kiyosaki-says-regional-banks-are-being-wiped-out-calls-fed-criminal/">being wiped out</a> because of Fed policies. Economist Peter Schiff stated earlier this month that <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/economist-peter-schiff-warns-all-banks-will-fail-people-will-suffer-massive-losses-as-banking-crisis-unfolds/">all banks will fail</a> and people will suffer massive losses as the banking crisis unfolds.</p>
<p><em><strong>Do you think more banks will fail in the U.S. this year? Let us know in the comments section below.</strong></em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/heartland-tri-state-bank-failure-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[Heartland Tri-State Bank has become the latest bank in the U.S. to fail. #FDIC #bankingcrisis]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA[Heartland Tri-State Bank has become the latest bank to fail and closed by a banking regulator in the U.S. #FDIC #bankingcrisis]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>World’s Largest Web3 Event TOKEN2049 Singapore Hits 300 Sponsor Milestone,  Announces New Headline Speakers</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/worlds-largest-web3-event-token2049-singapore-hits-300-sponsor-milestone-announces-new-headline-speakers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Media]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 05:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=600022&#038;preview=true&#038;preview_id=600022</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/singapore-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/singapore-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/singapore-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/singapore-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/singapore-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/singapore-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/singapore-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/singapore.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />PRESS RELEASE. SINGAPORE — 30 July 2023 — TOKEN2049, Asia’s premier Web3 and crypto conference, announced a slate of prolific title sponsors and headline speakers for its upcoming Singapore edition. With just 50 days to go in the countdown, TOKEN2049 will take place from 13-14 September 2023 at Marina Bay Sands, ahead of the Formula [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/singapore-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/singapore-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/singapore-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/singapore-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/singapore-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/singapore-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/singapore-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/singapore.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>PRESS RELEASE. </strong><b>SINGAPORE — 30 July 2023 — </b><a href="https://www.asia.token2049.com/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">TOKEN2049</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, Asia’s premier Web3 and crypto conference, announced a slate of prolific title sponsors</span> <span style="font-weight: 400;">and headline speakers for its upcoming Singapore edition. With just 50 days to go in the countdown, TOKEN2049 will take place from 13-14 September 2023 at </span><a href="https://www.marinabaysands.com/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Marina Bay Sands</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, ahead of the </span><a href="https://www.formula1.com/en/racing/2023/Singapore.html"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Formula 1 Singapore Grand Prix 2023</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> race weekend. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Heralding a record-breaking repertoire of over 300 exhibitors, TOKEN2049 is set to welcome over 10,000 attendees with over 80 percent coming from overseas, making it the industry’s largest international gathering of the year. Congregating key business leaders from traditional finance and big tech to crypto-native entrepreneurs and builders as well as policy-makers, TOKEN2049 continues to cement its world-class status as the global premier Web3 event. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Panels, keynotes, and fireside chats at this year’s TOKEN2049 will address a myriad of topics including the changing global regulatory landscape, the convergence of crypto and AI, blockchain scaling, the intersection of Web3 gaming and the metaverse, the institutionalisation of digital assets, Web3 infrastructure, multi-chain network and protocol interoperability amongst many more critical themes. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Additional speakers at this year’s conference include amongst others Cameron and Tyler Winklevoss, Co-Founders of Gemini; Jeremy Allaire, Co-Founder and CEO of Circle; Jenny Johnson, CEO of Franklin Templeton; Daniel Alegre, CEO of Yuga Labs; Richard Teng, Head of Regional Markets at Binance; Daniel Ricciardo and Pierre Gasly, Formula One Drivers and Web3 enthusiasts from </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Scuderia AlphaTauri</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> and BWT Alpine Formula One respectively. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“The East/West Crypto Flippening is upon us and we are excited to be a part of TOKEN2049 as the conference brings together builders, leaders, and thinkers from across the crypto industry,” said </span><b>Cameron Winklevoss, Co-Founder of Gemini. </b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Commemorating the latest milestone, </span><b>Alex Fiskum, Co-Founder of TOKEN2049 </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">said: “We’re proud to present an ever-growing sensational speaker and sponsor line-up for this year’s edition of TOKEN2049, with broad international media coverage. The feedback has been unanimous – Asia is a driving force of innovation in crypto and Web3, and TOKEN2049 is the prime showcase where the global ecosystem will converge. Overall event traction has been tremendous with hundreds of side events expected throughout </span><a href="https://week.token2049.com"><span style="font-weight: 400;">TOKEN2049 Week</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">. We are also seeing that hotels across the city are already selling out as the anticipation for TOKEN2049 grows. We’re incredibly excited.” </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">TOKEN2049’s top-flight roster of title sponsors includes leading crypto exchange and Web3 technology company </span><b>OKX</b><span style="font-weight: 400;">; the gateway to ethics-first Shariah-compliant finance in the digital age, </span><b>Islamic Coin</b><span style="font-weight: 400;">;</span><b> TRON DAO</b><span style="font-weight: 400;">, empowering decentralized commerce and community for every human on the planet; </span><b>Polkadot</b><span style="font-weight: 400;">, the blockspace ecosystem for boundless innovation; DAO-led web3 ecosystem </span><b>Mantle</b><span style="font-weight: 400;">; world’s largest crypto copy trading platform </span><b>Bitget</b><span style="font-weight: 400;">; structured liquid staking and asset tracking protocol </span><b>Tranchess</b><span style="font-weight: 400;">; </span><b>Fireblocks, </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">an enterprise platform to manage digital asset operations and build innovative businesses on the blockchain; global financial technology firm </span><b>Circle Internet Financial (Circle)</b><span style="font-weight: 400;">; top cryptocurrency exchange platform </span><b>KuCoin</b><span style="font-weight: 400;">; global digital asset market maker and multi-stage Web3 investment firm</span><b> DWF Labs</b><span style="font-weight: 400;">; and high-performance public blockchain </span><b>Klaytn</b><span style="font-weight: 400;">.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">PR Newswire is a community partner of TOKEN2049 Singapore. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">For more information and continued updates on TOKEN2049 Singapore, please visit: </span><a href="https://www.asia.token2049.com/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.asia.token2049.com/</span></a></p>
<p><b>###</b></p>
<p><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Alex Fiskum, Co-Founder of TOKEN2049 is available for interview.</span></i></p>
<p><b>ABOUT TOKEN2049</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">TOKEN2049 is a premier Web3 event, organised annually in Singapore, where decision-makers in the global crypto ecosystem connect to exchange ideas, network, and shape the industry. TOKEN2049 is a global meeting place for entrepreneurs, institutions, industry insiders, investors, builders, and those with a strong interest in the crypto and blockchain industry.</span></p>
<p><b>Media Contact</b></p>
<p><a href="mailto:token2049sg@wachsman.com"><span style="font-weight: 400;">token2049sg@wachsman.com</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<hr />
<p><small><i>This is a press release. Readers should do their own due diligence before taking any actions related to the promoted company or any of its affiliates or services. Bitcoin.com is not responsible, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused or alleged to be caused by or in connection with the use of or reliance on any content, goods or services mentioned in the press release.</i></small></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/singapore-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[World’s Largest Web3 Event TOKEN2049 Singapore Hits 300 Sponsor Milestone,  Announces New Headline Speakers]]></bnmedia:barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Russian Official Says BRICS Currency Could Be Discussed at Upcoming Summit</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/russian-official-says-brics-currency-could-be-discussed-at-upcoming-summit/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Kevin Helms]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 03:30:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BRICS currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BRICS de-dollarization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BRICS Summit]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=600241&#038;preview=true&#038;preview_id=600241</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/russia-brics-currency-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Russian Official Says BRICS Currency Could Be Discussed at Upcoming Summit" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/russia-brics-currency-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/russia-brics-currency-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/russia-brics-currency-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/russia-brics-currency-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/russia-brics-currency-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/russia-brics-currency-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/russia-brics-currency.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />Russia’s deputy prime minister has stated that the topic of a common BRICS currency may still be on the table at the economic bloc&#8217;s upcoming leaders’ summit. A total of 69 leaders, including all African heads of state, have already been invited to the August summit where de-dollarization will be among the key topics discussed. [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/russia-brics-currency-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Russian Official Says BRICS Currency Could Be Discussed at Upcoming Summit" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/russia-brics-currency-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/russia-brics-currency-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/russia-brics-currency-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/russia-brics-currency-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/russia-brics-currency-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/russia-brics-currency-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/russia-brics-currency.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>Russia’s deputy prime minister has stated that the topic of a common BRICS currency may still be on the table at the economic bloc&#8217;s upcoming leaders’ summit. A total of 69 leaders, including all African heads of state, have already been invited to the August summit where de-dollarization will be among the key topics discussed.</strong></p>
<h2>Russian Official on BRICS Currency</h2>
<p>Russian Deputy Prime Minister Alexei Overchuk stated in an interview with Russian news outlet Tass on the sidelines of the second Russia-Africa summit this week that the issue of creating a basket of BRICS currencies may be raised at the economic bloc’s upcoming summit that will take place from Aug. 22-24. The BRICS nations comprise Brazil, Russia, India, China, and South Africa.</p>
<p>The Russian official was quoted as saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>The BRICS leaders will hold a meeting soon where they may touch upon the settlement system issue. Perhaps, the idea of creating a basket of currencies based on a certain payment unit will also be discussed.</p></blockquote>
<p>&#8220;Perhaps the leaders will decide to task the relevant expert bodies with looking into the matter,&#8221; Overchuk added, emphasizing: &#8220;Clearly, it’s a very difficult issue.&#8221;</p>
<p>While the Russian deputy prime minister believes that the topic of a common BRICS currency could be discussed at the summit, South Africa’s diplomat in charge of BRICS relations, Anil Sooklal, has stated: &#8220;There’s never been talk of a BRICS currency, <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/brics-currency-not-on-agenda-for-leaders-summit-nations-to-focus-on-de-dollarization/">it’s not on the agenda</a>.&#8221; South Africa is hosting the BRICS summit this year, and Sooklal is in charge of planning the agenda for the summit.</p>
<p>Moreover, Leslie Maasdorp, vice president and chief financial officer of the New Development Bank, also known as the BRICS Bank, recently clarified that the economic bloc has no immediate plan to launch a currency to compete with the U.S. dollar. Noting the distinction between de-dollarization efforts and the creation of a common BRICS currency, he <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/brics-bank-official-discusses-common-currency-as-reports-of-gold-backed-brics-currency-gain-attention/">stressed</a>: “The development of anything alternative is indeed a medium to long-term ambition.” Both Maasdorp and Sooklal have stressed that the BRICS bloc is focusing on de-dollarization and encouraging the use of national currencies for trade settlements.</p>

<p>Furthermore, rumors abound that the BRICS group might unveil a <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/brics-bank-official-discusses-common-currency-as-reports-of-gold-backed-brics-currency-gain-attention/">gold-backed currency</a> during the summit. Many people believe that a unified BRICS currency could erode the U.S. dollar&#8217;s status as the world&#8217;s dominant currency. Nevertheless, obstacles lie ahead. Russia&#8217;s central bank governor, for instance, has <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/russias-central-bank-brics-currency-requires-consent-of-many-parties-faces-implementation-challenges/">cautioned</a> that a BRICS currency will require the consent of numerous parties, and she foresees potential challenges in its implementation.</p>
<p>The BRICS has drawn interest from <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/brics-interest-soars-40-countries-seek-membership-as-de-dollarization-efforts-grow/">over 40 countries</a> seeking to join the group. According to Sooklal, 22 nations have already formally applied. Moreover, the diplomat has revealed that South Africa has <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/brics-invites-69-leaders-to-august-summit-western-countries-omitted/">invited 69 leaders</a> to the summit, including all of the African heads of state and the leaders of major Global South bodies. However, he affirmed that no Western countries have been invited.</p>
<p><em><strong>Do you think the subject of a common BRICS currency will be discussed at the economic bloc’s upcoming summit? Let us know in the comments section below.</strong></em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/russia-brics-currency-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[Russia’s deputy prime minister says the topic of a common #BRICScurrency may still be discussed at the bloc's upcoming leaders’ summit. #BRICS #dedollarization]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA["Perhaps, the idea of creating a basket of currencies based on a certain payment unit will also be discussed," the Russian official said. #dedollarization #BRICS]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>US House Committee Passes &#8216;Keep Your Coins Act&#8217; to Protect Right to Self-Custody Crypto</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/us-house-committee-passes-keep-your-coins-act-to-protect-right-to-self-custody-crypto/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Kevin Helms]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 01:30:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Congress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[congress passes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto bills]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto laws]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[House Committee on Financial Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Keep Your Coins Act 2023]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Keep Your Coins Act passes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=600234&#038;preview=true&#038;preview_id=600234</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/keep-your-coins-act-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="US House Committee Passes &#039;Keep Your Coins Act&#039; to Protect Right to Self-Custody Crypto" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/keep-your-coins-act-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/keep-your-coins-act-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/keep-your-coins-act-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/keep-your-coins-act-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/keep-your-coins-act-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/keep-your-coins-act-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/keep-your-coins-act.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />The U.S. House Committee on Financial Services has passed the Keep Your Coins Act of 2023 to protect the self-custody of crypto. “Those attacking self-custody oppose individual freedom. They want someone they control to control your assets,” said Congressman Warren Davidson who introduced the bill. Keep Your Coins Act of 2023 Advances The U.S. House [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/keep-your-coins-act-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="US House Committee Passes &#039;Keep Your Coins Act&#039; to Protect Right to Self-Custody Crypto" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/keep-your-coins-act-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/keep-your-coins-act-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/keep-your-coins-act-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/keep-your-coins-act-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/keep-your-coins-act-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/keep-your-coins-act-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/keep-your-coins-act.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>The U.S. House Committee on Financial Services has passed the Keep Your Coins Act of 2023 to protect the self-custody of crypto. “Those attacking self-custody oppose individual freedom. They want someone they control to control your assets,” said Congressman Warren Davidson who introduced the bill.</strong></p>
<h2>Keep Your Coins Act of 2023 Advances</h2>
<p>The U.S. House Committee on Financial Services passed the <a href="https://www.congress.gov/118/bills/hr4841/BILLS-118hr4841ih.xml">Keep Your Coins Act of 2023</a> (H.R. 4841) on Thursday. The bill, sponsored by Rep. Warren Davidson (R-OH), “would ensure that consumers are allowed to maintain custody of their digital assets in self-hosted wallets,” ⁦the committee described.</p>
<p>Congressman Davidson tweeted Friday:</p>
<blockquote><p>Last night, U.S. House Committee on Financial Services⁩ passed my bill to protect self-custody. Those attacking self-custody oppose individual freedom. They want someone they control to control your assets. Defend Freedom.</p></blockquote>
<p>Keep Your Coins Act of 2023 prohibits federal agencies &#8220;from restricting the use of convertible virtual currency by a person to purchase goods or services for the person&#8217;s own use, and for other purposes,&#8221; according to the text of the bill.</p>
<p>In addition, federal agencies may not prohibit, restrict, or otherwise impair a person&#8217;s ability to &#8220;self-custody digital assets using a self-hosted wallet or other means to conduct transactions for any lawful purpose,” the bill adds.</p>

<p>Many people took to Twitter to thank Congressman Davidson for protecting self-custody. Rep. Davidson &#8220;is America’s NUMBER ONE protector of self-custody and a person’s fundamental right to individual financial freedom,&#8221; lawyer John E. Deaton wrote.</p>
<p>&#8220;The debate on Rep. Warren Davidson’s self-custody bill was important. He speaks powerfully about foundational questions regarding the relationship of the individual &amp; the state &amp; why public policy shouldn’t begin with a presumption of surveillance. We are lucky to have his leadership,&#8221; Coinbase&#8217;s chief policy officer, Faryar Shirzad, opined.</p>
<p>Besides the Keep Your Coins Act of 2023, the U.S. House Committee on Financial Services also passed three other crypto-related bills this week. They are the <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/us-lawmakers-advance-fit-for-the-21st-century-act-to-establish-crypto-framework/">Financial Innovation and Technology (FIT) for the 21st Century Act</a>, the Blockchain Regulatory Certainty Act, and the <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/us-house-financial-services-committee-passes-stablecoin-legislation-after-a-few-fireworks/">Clarity for Payment Stablecoins Act</a>.</p>
<p><em><strong>What do you think about U.S. lawmakers advancing the Keep Your Coins Act of 2023? Let us know in the comments section below.</strong></em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/keep-your-coins-act-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA["Those attacking #selfcustody oppose individual #freedom. They want someone they control to control your assets," said the congressman. #cryptocurrency #crypto #KeepYourCoinsAct]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA[The U.S. House Committee on Financial Services has passed the #KeepYourCoinsAct of 2023 to protect the #selfcustody of #crypto. #cryptocurrency]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>SEC Chair Gary Gensler Says Crypto Is a Highly Speculative Field &#8216;Rife With Fraud&#8217;</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/sec-chair-gary-gensler-says-crypto-is-a-highly-speculative-field-rife-with-fraud/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Kevin Helms]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 23:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gary Gensler]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gary Gensler crypto fraud]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gary gensler crypto regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec crypto fraud]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec crypto regulation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=600231&#038;preview=true&#038;preview_id=600231</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/gensler-crypto-fraud-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="SEC Chair Gary Gensler Says Crypto Is a Highly Speculative Field &#039;Rife With Fraud&#039;" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/gensler-crypto-fraud-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/gensler-crypto-fraud-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/gensler-crypto-fraud-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/gensler-crypto-fraud-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/gensler-crypto-fraud-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/gensler-crypto-fraud-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/gensler-crypto-fraud.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) Chair Gary Gensler has called crypto &#8220;a highly speculative asset class&#8221; and a field that is &#8220;rife with fraud.&#8221; He stressed that there are far too many bad actors in crypto, noting that crypto platforms often commingle funds and trade against their customers. Gary Gensler Says Crypto Field Rife [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/gensler-crypto-fraud-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="SEC Chair Gary Gensler Says Crypto Is a Highly Speculative Field &#039;Rife With Fraud&#039;" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/gensler-crypto-fraud-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/gensler-crypto-fraud-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/gensler-crypto-fraud-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/gensler-crypto-fraud-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/gensler-crypto-fraud-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/gensler-crypto-fraud-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/gensler-crypto-fraud.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) Chair Gary Gensler has called crypto &#8220;a highly speculative asset class&#8221; and a field that is &#8220;</strong><strong>rife with fraud.&#8221; He stressed that there are far too many bad actors in crypto, noting that </strong><strong>crypto platforms often commingle funds and trade against their customers.</strong></p>
<h2>Gary Gensler Says Crypto Field Rife With Fraud</h2>
<p>The chairman of the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), Gary Gensler, slammed crypto in an interview with Bloomberg on Thursday.</p>
<p>“In this field of crypto investing, a lot of investors should be aware it&#8217;s not only a highly speculative asset class, it&#8217;s also one that they currently should not assume that they are getting the protections of the securities law, even though the securities laws apply to many of those tokens without prejudging anyone. But, you as investors are not getting the full, fair, and truthful disclosure,” the SEC chair cautioned.</p>
<p>Gensler added:</p>
<blockquote><p>The platforms, the intermediaries are doing things that we would never in a day allow or think the New York Stock Exchange or Nasdaq would do.</p></blockquote>
<p>“The platforms often are co-mingling and trading against you and have market makers that are on the other side of your trades. And we don&#8217;t allow that in the rest of our securities markets,&#8221; he continued.</p>
<p>The chairman of the SEC asserted:</p>
<blockquote><p>Right now, this is a field rife with fraud, rife with hucksters … there are good-faith actors as well but there are far too many that aren’t.</p></blockquote>

<p>The securities regulator recently requested <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/sec-asks-for-increased-funding-to-tackle-crypto-market-risks-and-wrongdoing/">a budget increase</a> to address the risks posed by the crypto market. Gensler said in March that the SEC <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/gary-gensler-sec-needs-new-tools-expertise-and-resources-to-regulate-crypto-industry/">needs new tools</a>, expertise, and resources to regulate the crypto industry.</p>
<p>Many people have criticized the SEC chairman for regulating the crypto industry by <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/lawmaker-calls-sec-enforcement-actions-against-crypto-exchanges-complete-contempt-for-congress/">enforcement</a>. U.S. Congressman Warren Davidson (R-OH) even introduced legislation to <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/us-lawmaker-introducing-legislation-to-remove-sec-chairman-due-to-long-series-of-abuses/">remove Gensler</a> as the chairman of the SEC &#8220;to correct a long series of abuses.&#8221; The lawmaker <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/republican-congressman-seeks-to-oust-sec-chair-gensler-with-sec-stabilization-act/">said</a>: “U.S. capital markets must be protected from a tyrannical chairman, including the current one.&#8221;</p>
<p><em><strong>What do you think about SEC Chairman Gary Gensler’s statements regarding the crypto industry? Let us know in the comments section below.</strong></em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/gensler-crypto-fraud-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[#SEC Chair Gary Gensler says #crypto is “a highly speculative asset class" that is "rife with #fraud." #cryptocurrency]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA["There are good faith actors as well but there are far too many that aren’t," said #SEC Chair #GaryGensler about the #crypto industry. #cryptocurrency]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>China Faces Opposition to Rapid BRICS Expansion From India and Brazil, Report</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/china-faces-opposition-to-rapid-brics-expansion-from-india-and-brazil-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lubomir Tassev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 21:30:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[applicants]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brazil]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[candidates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[China]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[discussions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[expansion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[India]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[member states]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[members]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Membership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Russia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[South Africa]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[summit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[talks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=600162</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="433" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2316169777-768x433.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="China Faces Opposition to Rapid BRICS Expansion From India and Brazil, Report" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2316169777-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2316169777-1024x578.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2316169777-768x433.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2316169777-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2316169777-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2316169777-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2316169777.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />BRICS member states India and Brazil stand in the way of China’s bid to quickly expand the bloc, unveiled a media report. The two nations have different reasons to have reservations about Beijing’s plan to soon increase the organization’s geopolitical influence while they both seem to want to slow down the enlargement, sources have indicated. [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="433" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2316169777-768x433.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="China Faces Opposition to Rapid BRICS Expansion From India and Brazil, Report" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2316169777-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2316169777-1024x578.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2316169777-768x433.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2316169777-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2316169777-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2316169777-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2316169777.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>BRICS member states India and Brazil stand in the way of China’s bid to quickly expand the bloc, unveiled a media report. The two nations have different reasons to have reservations about Beijing’s plan to soon increase the organization’s geopolitical influence while they both seem to want to slow down the enlargement, sources have indicated.</strong></p>
<h2>India and Brazil Push Back Against China’s Attempt to Expand BRICS, Officials Say</h2>
<p>Officials familiar with the discussions on the future composition of the BRICS bloc of developing economies have revealed that India and Brazil are pushing back against a Chinese bid to rapidly expand the group, which currently also includes Russia and South Africa.</p>
<p>According to a report by Bloomberg, New Delhi and Brasília have raised their objections in preparatory talks for the organization’s upcoming summit in Johannesburg. During the forum on Aug. 22 &#8211; 24, the five nations will discuss the induction of new members.</p>
<p>China has repeatedly lobbied for expansion during those meetings, said the officials who chose to remain anonymous. Indonesia and Saudi Arabia have been mentioned as candidates while dozens of other nations are either applying or showing interest in joining.</p>

<p>The large <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/brics-interest-soars-40-countries-seek-membership-as-de-dollarization-efforts-grow/">number</a> of potential members has fueled concerns in the West that the alliance may become a counterweight to the U.S. and the EU. Brazil hopes to avoid enlargement partly because of such worries while India seeks strict rules for the association of other countries without formally expanding BRICS. Both want to discuss granting observer status to candidates at the summit, the quoted officials added.</p>
<p>The hosting nation, South Africa, supports considering different membership options but doesn’t necessarily oppose expansion, two of the officials noted. “The BRICS leaders meeting last year authorized the expansion of membership, adding more members to BRICS is the political consensus of the five BRICS countries,” China’s foreign ministry pointed out in a statement.</p>
<h2>Decisions in Johannesburg Will Require Consensus Among Members</h2>
<p>Russia does not hold a firm position on expanding BRICS, according to Fyodor Lukyanov, head of the Council on Foreign and Defense Policy which advises the Kremlin’s administration. Commenting on the matter, he elaborated:</p>
<blockquote><p>It’s broadly in favor of BRICS expansion, but without any huge enthusiasm. It’s following the others’ lead. We won’t block any decision.</p></blockquote>
<p>And any decision at the August summit will require consensus among the current member states who meet at a time of heightened tensions between Washington and Beijing as well as a geopolitical clash with Russia with unprecedented Western sanctions imposed over its invasion of Ukraine.</p>
<p>Last week, the office of South Africa’s president Cyril Ramaphosa <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/historic-brics-summit-to-be-held-without-putin-in-person/">announced</a> that his Russian counterpart, Vladimir Putin, will not attend the meeting in person as a result of an indictment and an arrest warrant issued for him by the International Criminal Court (ICC) over the Ukraine war.</p>
<p>The report also revealed that following India’s opposition to China’s push for expansion, rules for admission were drafted and these will be discussed at the leaders’ summit next month, according to two Indian officials.</p>
<p>While trying avoid confrontation in <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/BRICS" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BRICS</a>, Brazil is working to resist Chinese pressure to make it an antagonistic body that challenges the G7, a Brazilian official said. The country is proposing to establish “observer” and “partner country” categories for candidates that will precede full membership.</p>
<p><em><strong>Do you expect BRICS to invite new members at the summit in Johannesburg? Tell us in the comments section below. </strong></em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/shutterstock_2316169777-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[#India and #Brazil oppose China’s push for rapid #BRICS #expansion, a recent report reveals. ]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA[#Brazil proposes BRICS to grant candidates “observer” and “partner” status before full membership, official says.]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Decade-Old Wisdom: Unpacking Satoshi Nakamoto&#8217;s Definitive Quote on Bitcoin Transaction Challenges, 13 Years On</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/decade-old-wisdom-unpacking-satoshi-nakamotos-definitive-quote-on-bitcoin-transaction-challenges-13-years-on/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jamie Redman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 19:30:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Featured]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcointalk.org]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital Currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[double spend attacks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Double Spending]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[escrow service]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[exponential growth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[network propagation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Payment processor]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[quote]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Satoshi Nakamoto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Scalability]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[snack machine thread]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[transaction confirmation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[transaction speed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vending machine]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=600146</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/w568-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Decade-Old Wisdom: Unpacking Satoshi Nakamoto&#039;s Definitive Quote on Bitcoin Transaction Challenges, 13 Years On" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/w568-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/w568-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/w568-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/w568-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/w568-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/w568-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/w568.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />Thirteen years ago to the day, the enigmatic creator of Bitcoin, Satoshi Nakamoto, pronounced a quote that has since reverberated across various contexts. This prominent aphorism: &#x201C;If you don&#x2019;t believe me or don&#x2019;t get it, I don&#x2019;t have time to try to convince you, sorry,&#x201D; was Nakamoto&#x2019;s curt response to questions surrounding the potential solutions [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/w568-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Decade-Old Wisdom: Unpacking Satoshi Nakamoto&#039;s Definitive Quote on Bitcoin Transaction Challenges, 13 Years On" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/w568-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/w568-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/w568-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/w568-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/w568-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/w568-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/w568.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>Thirteen years ago to the day, the enigmatic creator of Bitcoin, Satoshi Nakamoto, pronounced a quote that has since reverberated across various contexts. This prominent aphorism: &#x201C;If you don&#x2019;t believe me or don&#x2019;t get it, I don&#x2019;t have time to try to convince you, sorry,&#x201D; was Nakamoto&#x2019;s curt response to questions surrounding the potential solutions for Bitcoin&#x2019;s transaction speeds and double spending issues.</strong></p>
<h2>The 13th Year Anniversary of Nakamoto&#x2019;s Iconic Quote</h2>
<p>In the summer of 2010, Satoshi Nakamoto was a palpable presence in the nascent world of digital currency, busily shaping Bitcoin&#x2019;s path and engaging in lively dialogues online. Within a span of two weeks &#x2013; from July 2 to July 17, 2010 &#x2013; Nakamoto found the time to articulate <a href="https://www.bitcoin.com/satoshi-archive/forum/bitcoin-forum/">73 thoughtful responses</a> on specific discussions hosted on the forum bitcointalk.org. It was in this buzzing hub, on July 29, 2010, that Nakamoto memorably posted his now-famous line, &#x201C;If you don&#x2019;t believe me or don&#x2019;t get it, I don&#x2019;t have time to try to convince you, sorry,&#x201D; in a thread aptly titled: &#x201C;Scalability and transaction rate.&#x201D;</p>
<p>Nakamoto&#x2019;s <a href="https://bitcointalk.org/index.php?topic=532.msg6269#msg6269">comment</a> was in response to the statement from another crypto proponent who said: &#x201C;10 minutes is too long to verify that payment is good. It needs to be as fast as swiping a credit card is today.&#x201D; Nakamoto replied by saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>See the snack machine thread, I outline how a payment processor could verify payments well enough, actually really well (much lower fraud rate than credit cards), in something like 10 seconds or less. If you don&#x2019;t believe me or don&#x2019;t get it, I don&#x2019;t have time to try to convince you, sorry.</p></blockquote>
<h2>The Snack Machine Thread</h2>
<p>Bitcoin&#x2019;s creator left a link to the &#x201C;<a href="http://bitcointalk.org/index.php?topic=423.msg3819#msg3819">snack machine thread</a>,&#x201D; which discusses the problem of how to enable fast transactions for small purchases like from a vending machine using <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/BTC" 311996  target="_blank">BTC</a>. The issue is that <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/BTC" 311996  target="_blank">BTC</a> transactions take some time to confirm on the blockchain, so someone could double-spend before the transaction is confirmed and get a product from a vending machine without actually paying for it. The participants discussed ideas like debit accounts, escrow services, and prepaid accounts to enable fast transactions without waiting for blockchain confirmations.</p>

<p>The core problem is that the Bitcoin network takes about ten minutes on average to confirm transactions, but vendors need transactions to process instantly to deliver products right away. But if transactions aren&#x2019;t confirmed, people could double-spend <a class="lar-automated-link" href="https://markets.bitcoin.com/crypto/BTC" 311996  target="_blank">BTC</a> to cheat the system or vendor. In the bitcointalk.org thread, an escrow service is suggested to enable instant transfers between accounts while still doing blockchain confirmations, but this adds costs through a third party.</p>

<p>Nakamoto suggests a solution where a payment processor listens for double-spend attempts and alerts if it detects any before a transaction propagates across the whole network. This would prevent most double-spend attacks. Nakamoto then provides a simple example of how fast a transaction can spread throughout the network.</p>

<p>In this example, if one transaction has even a small head start, it will spread throughout the network faster than the other one (the double-spend). It illustrates the exponential growth of transaction propagation &#x2013; an early lead can result in an overwhelming advantage due to the geometric (exponential) nature of network propagation.</p>
<p>&#x201C;So if a double-spend has to wait even a second, it has a huge disadvantage,&#x201D; Nakamoto wrote at the time. &#x201C;The payment processor has connections with many nodes. When it gets a transaction, it blasts it out, and at the same time monitors the network for double-spends. If it receives a double-spend on any of its many listening nodes, then it alerts that the transaction is bad.&#x201D; Bitcoin&#x2019;s inventor added:</p>
<blockquote><p>A double-spent transaction wouldn&#x2019;t get very far without one of the listeners hearing it. The double-spender would have to wait until the listening phase is over, but by then, the payment processor&#x2019;s broadcast has reached most nodes, or is so far ahead in propagating that the double-spender has no hope of grabbing a significant percentage of the remaining nodes.</p></blockquote>
<p>The &#x201C;snack machine thread&#x201D; has played a recurring role in a multitude of discussions over time. After Nakamoto&#x2019;s initial response and a subsequent, seemingly rushed reply in a separate post, his comment was notably brief. Perhaps the architect of Bitcoin felt a robust certainty in the solution previously provided in the &#x201C;snack machine thread&#x201D; or, quite possibly, Nakamoto was inundated with other commitments that day, leading to a more clipped response.</p>
<p>The exact motivations remain shrouded in mystery, but the remark about lacking the time to explain has since been conjoined with the broader narrative of Bitcoin. It&#x2019;s celebrated as a poignant aphorism, encapsulating the inherent challenge in truly grasping the intricate mechanics of Bitcoin.</p>
<p><em><strong>How do you interpret Satoshi&#x2019;s wisdom today? Share your thoughts and opinions about this subject in the comments section below.</strong></em></p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/w568-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[Thirteen years ago to the day, the enigmatic creator of #Bitcoin, Satoshi Nakamoto, pronounced a quote that has since reverberated across various contexts.]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA[“If you don't believe me or don't get it, I don't have time to try to convince you, sorry,” was Nakamoto's curt response that day. #BitcoinHistory #BTC]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Report: French Privacy Regulator Probes Worldcoin&#8217;s Biometric Data Practices</title>
		<link>https://news.bitcoin.com/report-french-privacy-regulator-probes-worldcoins-biometric-data-practices/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jamie Redman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 17:30:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[backlash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bavarian authorities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[biometric data]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[biometric data collection]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CNIL]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[data acquisition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Data protection]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[data storage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[French oversight agency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investigation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[iris scans]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jurisdiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[National Commission on Informatics and Liberty]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[privacy concerns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[privacy program]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Scrutiny]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[two million registrants]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Worldcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Worldcoin Foundation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/?p=600198</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/worldcoinsssd-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Report: French Privacy Regulator Probes Worldcoin&#039;s Biometric Data Practices" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/worldcoinsssd-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/worldcoinsssd-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/worldcoinsssd-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/worldcoinsssd-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/worldcoinsssd-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/worldcoinsssd-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/worldcoinsssd.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" />The French oversight agency, National Commission on Informatics and Liberty (CNIL), has raised doubts about the legality of Worldcoin&#8217;s biometric data collection methods. Besides questioning the legitimacy of its data acquisition processes, CNIL is also delving into how this biometric data is stored. Notably, Worldcoin has collected this data for over two million registrants who [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="768" height="432" src="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/worldcoinsssd-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="Report: French Privacy Regulator Probes Worldcoin&#039;s Biometric Data Practices" decoding="async" loading="lazy" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" srcset="https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/worldcoinsssd-300x169.jpg 300w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/worldcoinsssd-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/worldcoinsssd-768x432.jpg 768w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/worldcoinsssd-190x107.jpg 190w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/worldcoinsssd-380x214.jpg 380w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/worldcoinsssd-760x428.jpg 760w, https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/worldcoinsssd.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /><p><strong>The French oversight agency, National Commission on Informatics and Liberty (CNIL), has raised doubts about the legality of Worldcoin&#8217;s biometric data collection methods. Besides questioning the legitimacy of its data acquisition processes, CNIL is also delving into how this biometric data is stored. Notably, Worldcoin has collected this data for over two million registrants who have participated in its project.</strong></p>
<h2>French Regulator CNIL Questions Worldcoin&#8217;s Biometric Data Storage</h2>
<p>Worldcoin debuted last Monday, and based on available data and footage of individuals enrolling, the venture has been amassing momentum and recognition. In an <a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/frances-privacy-watchdog-says-worldcoin-legality-seems-questionable-2023-07-28/">email conversation</a> with Reuters, CNIL disclosed to the media outlet that it was scrutinizing Worldcoin&#8217;s data gathering and has initiated inquiries. &#8220;The legality of this collection seems questionable, as do the conditions for storing biometric data,” CNIL informed the news platform.</p>
<p>Ahead of launching its worldcoin (WLD) token, Worldcoin asserted it had already enlisted more than 2 million users. As of now, over <a href="https://optimistic.etherscan.io/token/0xdc6ff44d5d932cbd77b52e5612ba0529dc6226f1">300,000 WLD token holders exist</a>, and on July 29, 2023, WLD documented upwards of 1 million transactions. Moreover, the CEO of Openai and co-founder of Worldcoin, Sam Altman, <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/worldcoin-adoption-said-to-be-accelerating-sam-altman-states-one-person-getting-verified-every-8-seconds/">presented a video</a> revealing Worldcoin registrants queuing up to undergo iris scans and shared that an individual was being scanned &#8220;every 8 seconds.”</p>
<p>Even prior to Worldcoin&#8217;s introduction, the project encountered backlash, and an <a href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2022/04/06/1048981/worldcoin-cryptocurrency-biometrics-web3/">article</a> published by MIT Technology Review detailed accusations of deceit and exploitation. In October 2021, former NSA contractor and whistleblower Edward Snowden <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/iris-scanning-worldcoin-idea-fuels-objections-from-privacy-advocates-snowden-says-dont-catalog-eyeballs/">criticized</a> the iris scanning initiative telling Altman they should abstain from cataloging people&#8217;s eyeballs. In correspondence with Reuters, the French regulator disclosed its commencement of investigations into Worldcoin.</p>

<p>CNIL also highlighted that Bavarian authorities are collaborating with the regulator in examining Worldcoin’s data collection practices. The Worldcoin Foundation responded to Reuters&#8217; request for comment concerning the investigation. The foundation noted that it falls under the jurisdiction of the European Union and Bavarian authorities such as the Bavarian State Office for Data Protection Supervision. “[Worldcoin] is designed to protect individual privacy and has built a robust privacy program,” the Worldcoin Foundation stated in its email.</p>
<p>Additionally, the group emphasized that the project adheres to all laws and regulations within every jurisdiction where Worldcoin operates. &#8220;The project will continue to cooperate with governing bodies on requests for more information about its privacy and data protection practices,&#8221; the Worldcoin Foundation added.</p>
<p><em><strong>What do you think about the French privacy regulator investigating Worldcoin&#8217;s practices? Share your thoughts and opinions about this subject in the comments section below.</strong></em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:url>https://static.news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/worldcoinsssd-760x428.jpg</bnmedia:url><bnmedia:width>760</bnmedia:width><bnmedia:height>428</bnmedia:height></bnmedia:post-thumbnail><bnmedia:barker_title><![CDATA[The National Commission on Informatics and Liberty (CNIL), has raised doubts about the legality of #Worldcoin's biometric data collection. #WLD]]></bnmedia:barker_title><bnmedia:late_barker_title><![CDATA["The legality of this collection seems questionable," CNIL explained in an email. #Worldcoin #WLD]]></bnmedia:late_barker_title>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
