<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 09:36:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Dogecoin Price Surges after Elon Musk Rebrands Twitter to X</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/dogecoin-price-twitter-x/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/dogecoin-price-twitter-x/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Babafemi Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 09:36:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[doge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogecoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[linda yaccarino]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[twitter]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[x]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=264180</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/dogecoin-price-twitter-x/">Dogecoin Price Surges after Elon Musk Rebrands Twitter to X</a></p>
<p>The rebranding of Twitter as X is part of Musk’s vision to create an “everything app” like WeChat.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/dogecoin-price-twitter-x/">Dogecoin Price Surges after Elon Musk Rebrands Twitter to X</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/dogecoin-price-twitter-x/">Dogecoin Price Surges after Elon Musk Rebrands Twitter to X</a></p>

<p>The price of meme token Dogecoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/dogecoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">DOGE</a>) soared to its highest in recent times following a surprise announcement by Twitter owner Elon Musk. Musk triggered the surge when he announced plans to change the Twitter name to X. DOGE surged by 10% in the past 24 hours, <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/dogecoin" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">according to CoinGecko data</a>.</p>
<h2>Dogecoin’s Rise in Popularity</h2>
<p>Dogecoin was created in 2013 as an internet meme token. Dogecoin’s popularity has grown over the years, thanks to its loyal fan base and celebrity endorsements, including from <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/elon-musk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Elon Musk</a>.</p>
<p>Musk has always been a vocal supporter of Dogecoin, calling it the future of currency. In April, Musk replaced the Twitter logo with the Dogecoin logo briefly and sparked a 30% spike in the price of the asset. He also teased the possibility of DOGE payments for Twitter’s premium service subscription.</p>
<p>Because it has no real utility, experts warn that dogecoin is highly volatile and risky and that investors should be cautious before buying it. Should X allow DOGE as a means of payment, everything about the token could change.</p>
<h2>Dogecoin Price Speculations Fanned by Musk</h2>
<p>Given Musk’s history with the meme token, it didn’t take long for the Twitter rebrand announcement to fuel speculations about DOGE. Since the token is already accepted as a form of payment at Tesla, analysts believe X could also do the same.</p>
<p>Real Vision CEO Raoul Pal said:</p>
<blockquote>
<p>“He will use crypto to be able to make global payments for creators, etc. My guess is he uses Doge.”</p>
</blockquote>
<p>“The speculation is that advertisers could be able to pay DOGE for ads and for other uses on Twitter,” Kryptomon Chief Marketing Officer Tomer Nuni explained.</p>
<p>To broaden the speculation, some users pointed out the X and D in Elon Musk’s profile location. They conclude that while the X refers to the Twitter rebrand, the D could be a reference to Dogecoin. Notably, much of the speculative moves are happening on UpBit, which is known for attracting speculative plays.</p>
<h2>Twitter to Morph into an Everything App</h2>
<p>Meanwhile, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-risks-logo-letter-x/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">the rebranding of Twitter as X</a> is part of Musk’s vision to create an “everything app” like WeChat. The app is expected to offer various services such as audio, video, messaging, payments, and banking.</p>
<p>According to Twitter CEO Linda Yaccarino, users should expect more features and innovations with the rebrand to X. She noted that the company was “just getting started”.</p>
<p>Already, Musk has purchased the X.com domain, which now redirects to Twitter. He has also asked Twitter users to submit their logo suggestions.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/blackrock-asia-bitcoin-etf/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/dogecoin-price-twitter-x/">Dogecoin Price Surges after Elon Musk Rebrands Twitter to X</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/dogecoin-price-twitter-x/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>BlackRock Expands Presence in Asia amid Its Bitcoin ETF Approval</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/blackrock-asia-bitcoin-etf/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/blackrock-asia-bitcoin-etf/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Darya Rudz]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 09:33:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funds & ETFs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blackrock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blackrock asia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blackrock bitcoin etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blackrock etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[spot bitcoin etf]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=264306</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/blackrock-asia-bitcoin-etf/">BlackRock Expands Presence in Asia amid Its Bitcoin ETF Approval</a></p>
<p>The changes in BlackRock's Asia-Pacific team come amid the SEC's decision on the future of the company’s spot Bitcoin ETF. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/blackrock-asia-bitcoin-etf/">BlackRock Expands Presence in Asia amid Its Bitcoin ETF Approval</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/blackrock-asia-bitcoin-etf/">BlackRock Expands Presence in Asia amid Its Bitcoin ETF Approval</a></p>
<p>Investment management corporation <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/blackrock/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BlackRock Inc</a> (NYSE: BLK) has made two important appointments within its expansion in Asia. In particular, the company has hired Mandy Lui as head of Greater China Wealth and Dennis Quah as head of Singapore Wealth.</p>
<p>Mandy Lui will be in charge of relationships with distributors throughout Hong Kong, Taiwan, and offshore China. Starting from the middle of August, former Baring Asset Management&#8217;s head of wealth and retail distribution will build strategic relationships with key distributors and ensure that BlackRock’s clients in the regions mentioned have access to the full range of investment capabilities.</p>
<p>As for Dennis Quah, he will be responsible for building relationships with consumer banks, private banks, and insurers, as well as helping in building client portfolios together with relevant specialists throughout the firm. Notably, Dennis Quah has twenty years of experience in asset management distribution. Previously, he worked for Columbia Threadneedle, Amundi, OCBC Bank, and Schroders.</p>
<p>James Raby, BlackRock’s Apac head of wealth, <a href="https://fundselectorasia.com/blackrock-hires-duo-to-build-out-greater-china-singapore-offering/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">commented</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We are delighted to welcome leaders like Mandy and Dennis to the firm. Their deep local market understanding and expertise in helping clients build whole portfolios are highly valuable as we serve the new and evolving needs of our investors in this current market environment.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Speaking further of the two appointments, it is also worth mentioning another shift in BlackRock’s Asia-Pacific team. Earlier this year, Nicholas Chiu left the company. He was the co-manager of the BlackRock GF China Fund, the BlackRock GF Asian Dragon Fund, the BlackRock GF China Flexible Equity Fund, and the BlackRock Asia Fund.</p>
<p>With headquarters in New York, BlackRock has as many as 78 offices in 36 countries. The firm had approximately $8.59 trillion in assets in management as of December 31, 2022. In the first quarter of 2023, this number soared to $9.09 trillion. Within the next five years, BlackRock’s assets under management are set to exceed $15 trillion. With expansion into Asian markets, this is a milestone possible to achieve.</p>
<h2>BlackRock Waiting for Bitcoin ETF Approval</h2>
<p>The changes in BlackRock&#8217;s Asia-Pacific team come amid the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>&#8216;s decision on the future of the company’s spot Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a>) ETF. Over the past decade, the SEC has rejected as many as 30 spot Bitcoin ETF applications from big-name companies, but many anticipate the approval of BlackRock&#8217;s application. If approved, it will be the first Bitcoin ETF in the United States. And if it happens, as much as $30 trillion worth of capital could be made available to the Bitcoin market.</p>
<p>Joshua Chu, group chief risk officer at blockchain technology group XBE, Coinllectibles and Marvion, said:</p>
<blockquote>
<p data-testid="paragraph-5">&#8220;The fact that BlackRock, a well-respected and established asset management company, has filed for a Bitcoin ETF could be seen as a positive development in the quest for regulatory approval. It also shows resilience of the public&#8217;s interest in crypto.&#8221;</p>
</blockquote>
<p data-testid="paragraph-5">If approved, the new iShares Bitcoin Trust will be listed on the Nasdaq exchange. The pricing will be based on the CF CME Bitcoin Reference Rate. All shares in the ETF will be fully backed by BTC, and no new shares can be issued without delivery of the corresponding value of tokens.</p>
<p><a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/x-platform-crypto-payments/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/blackrock-asia-bitcoin-etf/">BlackRock Expands Presence in Asia amid Its Bitcoin ETF Approval</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/blackrock-asia-bitcoin-etf/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Elon Musk’s X Social Media Platform Eyes Crypto Payments</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/x-platform-crypto-payments/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/x-platform-crypto-payments/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mercy Tukiya Mutanya]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 09:28:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[doge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[linda yaccarino]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[twitter]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[x]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[x coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[x platform]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=264335</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/x-platform-crypto-payments/">Elon Musk’s X Social Media Platform Eyes Crypto Payments</a></p>
<p>As part of an overall rebranding of the app, Elon Musk announced that Twitter was changing its name to X and that the popular bird would be replaced by an “X” logo.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/x-platform-crypto-payments/">Elon Musk’s X Social Media Platform Eyes Crypto Payments</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/x-platform-crypto-payments/">Elon Musk’s X Social Media Platform Eyes Crypto Payments</a></p>
<p>Elon Musk’s social media platform X, formerly known as Twitter, appears to be gearing up to make a foray into the world of cryptocurrencies. Amidst the looming possibility of an “X Coin”, Twitter Payments LLC has recently <a href="https://twitter.com/asunapg/status/1683448384437342208">obtained licenses</a> from several states that would permit it to process crypto payments.</p>
<p>This comes following reports in January that the social media giant was looking to diversify its revenue streams and launch an “everything app” whose features would include support for fiat and potentially cryptocurrency payments. The news of potential crypto integration drove the price of the dog-themed memecoin Dogecoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/dogecoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">DOGE</a>) to soar 7%.</p>
<p>The idea of crypto payments on the social media app has also been subject to criticism. Critics have raised concerns such as the question of regulatory approval, a valid concern given the increased regulatory scrutiny on cryptocurrency payments, especially in the United States. Technology costs and gaining the public’s trust were also presented as potential hurdles.</p>
<p>While Musk, a known Dogecoin supporter, has not explicitly named the coin the future currency of the “everything app,” the online Dogecoin community continues to speculate that he could. What is certain, in light of the recently obtained licenses, is that the company is still considering the possibility of crypto payments.</p>
<p>As part of an overall rebranding of the app, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/elon-musk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Elon Musk</a> announced that Twitter was changing its name to X and that the popular bird would be replaced by an “X” logo. The rebranding exercise is part of Musk’s attempts to diversify revenue streams and keep the company afloat amid declining ad revenue, which he had previously revealed had suffered a 50% blow. An integration of crypto payments could give X an edge over competitors such as Meta’s recently-launched Threads.</p>
<p>Commenting on the name change, the platform’s newly-appointed CEO Linda Yaccarino <a href="https://edition.cnn.com/2023/07/24/tech/twitter-rebrands-x-elon-musk-hnk-intl/index.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">stated</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“It’s an exceptionally rare thing – in life or in business – that you get a second chance to make another big impression. Twitter made one massive impression and changed the way we communicate. Now, X will go further, transforming the global town square.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Read other <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/technology/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">tech news</a> on our website.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/arkham-wallets-terra-do-kwon/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/x-platform-crypto-payments/">Elon Musk’s X Social Media Platform Eyes Crypto Payments</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/x-platform-crypto-payments/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Arkham Intel Exchange Has Its First Approval on Wallets Belonging to Terra and Do Kwon</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/arkham-wallets-terra-do-kwon/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/arkham-wallets-terra-do-kwon/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 09:23:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[arkham intel exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[daniel shin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[do kwon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[luna]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[terra]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[terraform]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ustc]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=264311</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/arkham-wallets-terra-do-kwon/">Arkham Intel Exchange Has Its First Approval on Wallets Belonging to Terra and Do Kwon</a></p>
<p>The submission by two "on-chain sleuths" includes evidence of wallets owned by Kwon and Terra. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/arkham-wallets-terra-do-kwon/">Arkham Intel Exchange Has Its First Approval on Wallets Belonging to Terra and Do Kwon</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/arkham-wallets-terra-do-kwon/">Arkham Intel Exchange Has Its First Approval on Wallets Belonging to Terra and Do Kwon</a></p>
<p>On Monday, July 24, Arkham Intel Exchange, a platform aimed at “deanonymizing the blockchain”, accepted the first submission for information on wallet addresses linked to Terraform Labs and its co-founder Do Kwon.</p>
<p>In a recent announcement on July 24, Arkham Intel Exchange disclosed that it received a submission from two &#8220;on-chain sleuths&#8221;. As a result, the platform rewarded them with a bounty payment of 9,519.2625 Arkham (ARKM), which is approximately $5,000 as per the current value. The announcement <a href="https://twitter.com/ErgoBTC/status/1683558237537435648" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reads</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The Arkham Intel Exchange now has its first approved submission: new evidence of wallets owned by Do Kwon / Terraform Labs. An anonymous on-chain sleuth and @ErgoBTC were the successful bounty hunters.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The submission included evidence of wallets owned by Kwon and Terra. Ergo, one of the sleuths associated with OXT Research, stated that this information could potentially contradict public statements from Terra about holding only one Luna Foundation Guard wallet, which has 313 <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoins</a> as reserves.</p>
<p>Introduced earlier this month on July 10, Arkham received criticism from various members of the crypto community, who view it as nothing more than a glorified snitching service. The company enables users to offer bounties for information on blockchain transactions. These bounties later go public 90 days after approval on Arkham. As a result, any information regarding the Kwon and Terra wallet addresses may be accessible around late October.</p>
<h2>Developments in Terra Case</h2>
<p>Terra faced significant controversy during the 2022 crypto market crash when its algorithmic stablecoin, TerraClassicUSD (USTC), deviated from its peg to the US dollar. Kwon&#8217;s whereabouts remained unknown from May 2022 until March 2023 when he was arrested and later sentenced to four months in prison in Montenegro for using forged travel documents.</p>
<p>In South Korea, individuals connected to Terra are currently under investigation by local authorities regarding the exchange. Co-founder Shin Hyun-seong, also known as Daniel Shin, reportedly had his <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/terra-co-founder-daniel-shin-court/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">first hearing</a> in July for charges related to allegedly making illicit profits from the sale of LUNA tokens.</p>
<p>According to allegations, Daniel Shin, a co-founder of Terraform Labs alongside Do Kwon, reportedly sold approximately $118 million worth of LUNA tokens before the token&#8217;s crash in May 2022. Shin faces accusations of employing similar strategies to profit from investor funds at Chai Corporation, a fintech company he founded after leaving Terraform Labs.</p>
<p>Shin&#8217;s defense has denied that he “sold Luna at a high point and realized profits or that he made profits through other illegal methods”.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-ceo-dismissal-cftc/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/arkham-wallets-terra-do-kwon/">Arkham Intel Exchange Has Its First Approval on Wallets Belonging to Terra and Do Kwon</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/arkham-wallets-terra-do-kwon/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance and Its CEO to Seek Dismissal of CFTC Lawsuit</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-ceo-dismissal-cftc/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-ceo-dismissal-cftc/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 09:04:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Binance News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance cz]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cftc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Changpeng 'CZ' Zhao]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[changpeng zhao]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cz]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=264318</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-ceo-dismissal-cftc/">Binance and Its CEO to Seek Dismissal of CFTC Lawsuit</a></p>
<p>The legal troubles continue to mount for Binance, as the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) also filed a lawsuit against the exchange and CZ in June.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-ceo-dismissal-cftc/">Binance and Its CEO to Seek Dismissal of CFTC Lawsuit</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-ceo-dismissal-cftc/">Binance and Its CEO to Seek Dismissal of CFTC Lawsuit</a></p>
<p>Renowned crypto exchange <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a> and its CEO <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/changpeng-zhao/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Changpeng ‘CZ’ Zhao</a>, have announced intentions to file a motion to dismiss a lawsuit brought against it by the United States Commodity Futures Trading Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/cftc/">CFTC</a>).</p>
<p>In a recent <a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.ilnd.431767/gov.uscourts.ilnd.431767.53.0_1.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener">filing</a> submitted to an Illinois District Court, Binance and Zhao, and former Chief Compliance Officer Samuel Lim announced their intention to file two separate motions to dismiss the CFTC’s complaint before July 27.</p>
<p>The CFTC’s Complaint filed in March outlines a litany of allegations against Binance and its key executives. It accuses the crypto exchange of facilitating illegal crypto derivatives trading activities within the United States. According to the CFTC, Binance allowed US residents to access and trade crypto derivatives without proper registration, which contravenes the regulatory requirements set forth by the Commodity Exchange Act.</p>
<p>With the deadline for their response to the complaint approaching on July 27, 2023, the defendants are formulating their <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-ceo-cz-cftc-complaint/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">defense strategies</a>. Accordingly, the Foreign Binance Entities and CZ, who are named in the action, there’s a plan to file a combined motion to dismiss the CFTC&#8217;s Complaint.</p>
<p>In contrast, Lim is prepared to file a second motion to dismiss the complaint. However, Lim also plans to align certain aspects of his motion with the arguments presented in the motion filed by the Foreign Binance Entities and Zhao. This suggests that the defendants may work together on certain aspects of their defense.</p>
<p>Additionally, Binance requested the court’s permission to exceed the standard 15-page limit for its brief, which will be utilized to support the exchange’s motion to dismiss the CFTC’s lawsuit. Binance argues that the complexity of the CFTC’s lawsuit warrants a more extensive submission of up to 50 pages to adequately present its defense.</p>
<h2>Binance’s Ongoing Lawsuits with US Regulators</h2>
<p>The legal troubles continue to mount for Binance, as the Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) also filed a lawsuit against the exchange and CZ in June. The SEC’s <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-sues-binance-securities-rules/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">complaint</a> spans a range of serious allegations against Binance and its CEO.</p>
<p>The regulatory body claims that Binance sold unregistered securities, a violation of securities regulations. Also, the SEC claims that Binance permitted US clients to access and use its worldwide platform despite not being authorized to do so. This accusation aligns with the CFTC’s lawsuit, which also contended that Binance permitted US residents to engage in prohibited activities on its platform.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the SEC accuses CZ of misusing customer funds, although specific details about the alleged misuse have not been disclosed yet. This allegation, if proven, could have significant consequences for the exchange and the CEO, potentially resulting in legal penalties and possibly reputational damage.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Binance is grappling with yet another legal challenge as the US Department of Justice (DOJ) reportedly launches an investigation. The investigation is <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-400m-zhao-trading-firm/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">centered</a> around allegations that Binance allowed Russian nationals to use its platform, which could be in violation of US sanctions.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-bing-chat-chrome-safari/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-ceo-dismissal-cftc/">Binance and Its CEO to Seek Dismissal of CFTC Lawsuit</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-ceo-dismissal-cftc/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Microsoft Starts Testing Bing Chat on Chrome and Safari, ‘Select Users’ Get Access to Tests</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-bing-chat-chrome-safari/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-bing-chat-chrome-safari/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Darya Rudz]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 09:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bing ai chatbot]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bing chat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bing chat chrome]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bing chat edge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bing chat safari]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[microsoft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[microsoft bing chat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[microsoft edge]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=264291</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-bing-chat-chrome-safari/">Microsoft Starts Testing Bing Chat on Chrome and Safari, &#8216;Select Users&#8217; Get Access to Tests</a></p>
<p>Previously, Microsoft's Bing Chat was available to users only within Microsoft products, like the Bing mobile app and Microsoft Edge browser. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-bing-chat-chrome-safari/">Microsoft Starts Testing Bing Chat on Chrome and Safari, &#8216;Select Users&#8217; Get Access to Tests</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-bing-chat-chrome-safari/">Microsoft Starts Testing Bing Chat on Chrome and Safari, &#8216;Select Users&#8217; Get Access to Tests</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/microsoft-corporation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Microsoft Corporation</a> (NASDAQ: MSFT) is bringing its Bing AI chatbot to non-Microsoft users. The company has started testing Bing Chat on other browsers – Google Chrome and Apple’s Safari. Within the move, Microsoft is expecting to grow its user base.</p>
<p>Caitlin Roulston, Microsoft’s director of communications, <a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/7/24/23805493/bing-ai-chat-google-chrome-safari" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">commented</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We are flighting access to Bing Chat in Safari and Chrome to select users as part of our testing on other browsers. We are excited to expand access to even more users once our standard testing procedures are complete.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Previously, Microsoft&#8217;s Bing Chat was available to users only within Microsoft products, like the Bing mobile app and Microsoft Edge browser.</p>
<p>Currently, a limited number of users have got access to the feature. And those who can now open Bing AI chatbot on Windows received a pop-up in the Windows 10 or 11 taskbar, offering the opportunity to test the Bing AI in Chrome. Otherwise, for accessing the chatbot, you just need to head to the Bing website and click on the &#8220;Chat&#8221; icon.</p>
<p>Bing Chat experience on Chrome and Safari is pretty similar to what users find on Edge. You can enter a prompt as well as choose a conversation style. However, compared to Edge, Chrome and Safari have a few limitations. In particular, users can only type 2,000-word prompts, in contrast to the 4,000-word limit when using Bing Chat on Edge. In addition, Bing Chat on Chrome and Safari resets conversations after five queries, while it happens after 30 queries on Edge. In Chrome and Safari, Bing Chat also shows repeated ads prompting users to install Edge.</p>
<p>Notably, Microsoft has not only rolled out its AI chatbot on other browsers but also added dark mode to Bing Chat. The feature is also available for select users who can click on the menu and select &#8220;Appearance/Dark&#8221; or &#8220;System Default&#8221;.</p>
<h2>Bing Chat Being the Best on Edge</h2>
<p>As mentioned above, Chrome and Safari users are facing some limitations when using Bing Chat on browsers other than Edge. The reason is that Bing Chat has been the first and only AI chatbot to be integrated with a web browser – Microsoft Edge. However, the Edge browser is not as popular as Chrome or Safari. According to statistics, Edge takes just a 5.13% share of all browser users in 2023, while Chrome dominates the market with 61.80% of users and Safari takes a 24.36% browser market share.</p>
<p>The availability of Bing Chatbot only on the Microsoft Edge browser has been inconvenient for some users, therefore, Microsoft&#8217;s decision to add support for Chrome and Safari has been obvious. However, the company has not commented on the differences between the various versions of Bing Chat or further plans for the chatbot&#8217;s expansion.</p>
<p>Earlier, Microsoft announced that Bing Chat would have a version with business-focused data privacy and governance controls.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/inflows-bitcoin-whales-high/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-bing-chat-chrome-safari/">Microsoft Starts Testing Bing Chat on Chrome and Safari, &#8216;Select Users&#8217; Get Access to Tests</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-bing-chat-chrome-safari/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Exchange Inflows from Bitcoin Whales Hit One-Year High</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/inflows-bitcoin-whales-high/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/inflows-bitcoin-whales-high/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 08:55:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=264272</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/inflows-bitcoin-whales-high/">Crypto Exchange Inflows from Bitcoin Whales Hit One-Year High</a></p>
<p>During the last two months of June and July, the Bitcoin whale exchange inflows have hit 4,000 to 6,500 BTC per day. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/inflows-bitcoin-whales-high/">Crypto Exchange Inflows from Bitcoin Whales Hit One-Year High</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/inflows-bitcoin-whales-high/">Crypto Exchange Inflows from Bitcoin Whales Hit One-Year High</a></p>
<p>RAs per the latest on-chain data, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> whale buying and selling this year in 2023 has been mostly from speculative investors. In its recent weekly newsletter, &#8220;The Week On-Chain&#8221;, crypto analytics firm Glassnode reveals that opportunistic entities are the most active whales.</p>
<p>After Bitcoin&#8217;s price reached $30,000 again, there has been a change in the behavior of Bitcoin traders. According to Glassnode, short-term holders (STHs) &#8211; those who hold coins for a maximum of 155 days &#8211; have become more prevalent. Interestingly, even the largest-volume investor group, the whales, consists of a significant number of short-term holders. In its report, Glassnode mentions:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Short-Term Holder Dominance across Exchange Inflows has exploded to 82%, which is now drastically above the long-term range over the last five years (typically 55% to 65%). From this, we can establish a case that much of the recent trading activity is driven by Whales active within the 2023 market (and thus classified as STHs).”</p></blockquote>
<p><div id="attachment_264273" style="width: 1189px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-264273" decoding="async" class="wp-image-264273 size-full" src="https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-BTC-STH-Exchange-Inflows.webp" alt="Crypto Exchange Inflows from Bitcoin Whales Hit One-Year High" width="1179" height="671" srcset="https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-BTC-STH-Exchange-Inflows.webp 1179w, https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-BTC-STH-Exchange-Inflows-230x131.webp 230w, https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-BTC-STH-Exchange-Inflows-768x437.webp 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1179px) 100vw, 1179px" /><p id="caption-attachment-264273" class="wp-caption-text">Photo: Glassnode</p></div></p>
<p>Even before May, there was a noticeable interest in trading short-timeframe moves on BTC/USD. Since the FTX meltdown in late 2022, speculators have become more enthusiastic about taking advantage of both upward and downward volatility.</p>
<p>The outcomes have been varied: Profits and losses have regularly surged in line with the volatile price movements. Glassnode further <a href="https://insights.glassnode.com/the-week-onchain-week-30-2023/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">explains</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“If we look at the degree of Profit/Loss realized by Short-Term Holder volume flowing into exchanges, it becomes evident that these newer investors are trading local market conditions. Each rally and correction since the FTX fallout has seen a 10k+ BTC uptick in STH profit or loss, respectively.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>Bitcoin Whale Activity Shoots Up in July</h2>
<p>During this month of July, when the Bitcoin price entered strong consolidation, the whale activity has also ramped up accounting for 41% of the total inflows at the exchanges. The Whale Netflow to Exchanges analysis can serve as an indicator of their impact on the supply and demand balance.</p>
<p>Over the past five years, Whale-to-exchange netflows have typically fluctuated between ±5,000 BTC per day. However, during June and July of this year, there has been a consistent trend of increased inflows, ranging from 4,000 to 6,500 BTC per day, reports Glassnode.</p>
<p><div id="attachment_264284" style="width: 1189px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-264284" decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-264284 size-full" src="https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-Whale-Exchange-Flows.webp" alt="Crypto Exchange Inflows from Bitcoin Whales Hit One-Year High" width="1179" height="671" srcset="https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-Whale-Exchange-Flows.webp 1179w, https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-Whale-Exchange-Flows-230x131.webp 230w, https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-Whale-Exchange-Flows-768x437.webp 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1179px) 100vw, 1179px" /><p id="caption-attachment-264284" class="wp-caption-text">Photo: Glassnode</p></div></p>
<p>Along with the Bitcoin whales, the Bitcoin long-term holders supply has reached a new all-time high of over 14.5 million BTC. As per Glassnode, this is equal to 75% of the total circulating supply.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="474" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">The <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Bitcoin</a> Long-Term Holder Supply has reached a new ATH of 14.52M BTC, equivalent to 75% of the circulating supply.</p>
<p>This suggests HODLing is the preferred market dynamic amongst mature investors. <a href="https://t.co/rfPmHM9hh2">pic.twitter.com/rfPmHM9hh2</a></p>
<p>&mdash; glassnode (@glassnode) <a href="https://twitter.com/glassnode/status/1683401299956465665?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 24, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Read other <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin news</a> on Coinspeaker.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-binance-us-exchange-wash-trading/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/inflows-bitcoin-whales-high/">Crypto Exchange Inflows from Bitcoin Whales Hit One-Year High</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/inflows-bitcoin-whales-high/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>SEC Condemns Binance.US, Says Exchange Engaged in ‘Wash Trading’ Activities</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-binance-us-exchange-wash-trading/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-binance-us-exchange-wash-trading/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 08:51:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Binance News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance cftc lawsuit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance changpeng zhao]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance sec lawsuit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cftc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[doj]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[securities and exchange commission]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=264275</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-binance-us-exchange-wash-trading/">SEC Condemns Binance.US, Says Exchange Engaged in &#8216;Wash Trading&#8217; Activities</a></p>
<p>SEC suggests that Binance.US may have fraudulently amplified its trading volumes, sometimes trading with itself, to appear very active in the markets.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-binance-us-exchange-wash-trading/">SEC Condemns Binance.US, Says Exchange Engaged in &#8216;Wash Trading&#8217; Activities</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-binance-us-exchange-wash-trading/">SEC Condemns Binance.US, Says Exchange Engaged in &#8216;Wash Trading&#8217; Activities</a></p>
<p>The US Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) has recently slammed Binance.US, the American arm of the global crypto exchange <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a>, with yet another accusation. According to a Wall Street Journal <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/some-binance-us-crypto-trading-was-a-mirage-the-sec-alleges-55a6e321?st=ruat3lr6wfei3rn&amp;reflink=desktopwebshare_permalink" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a>, the SEC claims that Binance.US was often involved in wash trading. That is, it fraudulently amplified its trading volumes, sometimes trading with itself, to appear very active in the markets.</p>
<p>Although the exchange has denied any such activities, albeit severally, the allegations may have influenced the ongoing SEC lawsuit. More so, the US Department of Justice (DoJ) is also actively investigating the exchange. So, as a result of the regulatory scrutiny, there have been reports of multiple resignations from the exchange&#8217;s top executives. That is not to mention the significant drop in the platform&#8217;s market share.</p>
<p>To put the above statement into perspective, Binance.US currently holds less than 1% of the market share. Hence, creating a situation that has forced customers to retrieve their funds from the platform.</p>
<p>Also, there is the recent wave of layoffs that hit the company following the SEC lawsuit and the DoJ probe. Earlier reports suggest that the parent exchange, Binance, has laid off 1,000 employees since the federal crackdown in the U.S. However, CNBC <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/07/14/binance-could-lay-off-thousands-in-response-to-doj-probe-source.html">claims</a> that that is only part of more layoffs that Binance has planned for the year. Citing a source with inside knowledge of the matter, CNBC says Binance intends to cut between 1,500 to 3,000 jobs within the year.</p>
<p>In his usual manner, Binance CEO <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/changpeng-zhao/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Changpeng Zhao</a> downplayed the layoff rumors, claiming that the numbers reported were inflated. He maintains that the layoffs have nothing to do with the ongoing scrutiny but rather an attempt to increase talent density.  Zhao also <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1679951762906595330?t=0-Cu_XGmnHsQis-XwwB3WQ&amp;s=19" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">noted</a> that the company is still hiring.</p>
<h2>Binance Maintains Relevance amid Regulatory Heat</h2>
<p>Binance currently faces regulatory heat from both the SEC and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/cftc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CFTC</a>. That is alongside an ongoing Justice Department investigation. Having been slammed with various securities and commodities violations, founder Zhao continues to downplay the concerns.</p>
<p>Interestingly, Zhao appears to be unruffled by the plethora of lawsuits against the exchange. And that may have contributed to the continued relevance of Binance.</p>
<p>Despite regulatory challenges, the parent exchange maintains its dominance in the global market. Though down from the 60% share it had in early 2023, Binance still holds a 52% share of the market as of publication.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-sbf-case-update-gag-order/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-binance-us-exchange-wash-trading/">SEC Condemns Binance.US, Says Exchange Engaged in &#8216;Wash Trading&#8217; Activities</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-binance-us-exchange-wash-trading/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>US vs FTX SBF Case Update: Judge to Review Proposed Gag Order Ahead of October 2 Hearing</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-sbf-case-update-gag-order/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-sbf-case-update-gag-order/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 08:48:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alameda research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Caroline Ellison]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sam bankman-fried]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sbf]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=264300</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-sbf-case-update-gag-order/">US vs FTX SBF Case Update: Judge to Review Proposed Gag Order Ahead of October 2 Hearing</a></p>
<p>Former FTX CEO has been accused of intimidating the witnesses including Caroline Ellison by leaking personal information to the press to influence his trial.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-sbf-case-update-gag-order/">US vs FTX SBF Case Update: Judge to Review Proposed Gag Order Ahead of October 2 Hearing</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-sbf-case-update-gag-order/">US vs FTX SBF Case Update: Judge to Review Proposed Gag Order Ahead of October 2 Hearing</a></p>
<p>As the former head of the derailed cryptocurrency exchange <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a> and sister firm Alameda Research <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/sam-bankman-fried/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Sam Bankman-Fried</a>, alias SBF, has been accused by the United States prosecutors of orchestrating one of the largest corporate scams in modern financial markets. Moreover, the FTX and Alameda exchange had received significant investments from institutional investors including government sectors in various jurisdictions around the world. Additionally, millions of cryptocurrency traders were left stranded after more than $30 billion was wiped out of the FTX exchange following alleged spendthrift by the former management.</p>
<p>Notably, the current FTX administration led by John Ray has signaled a move to reopen the exchange in a bid to make the creditors whole again. Moreover, the FTX recovery team has only managed to recover about $8 billion as of publication time. As a result, SBF has been charged with wire fraud and overstepping SEC securities laws.</p>
<p>Mind you, the former FTX management employees apart from SBF have admitted to committing the charges laid out by the prosecutors.</p>
<h2>Former FTX CEO SBF Fights Back Losing Battle</h2>
<p>In a letter dated July 22, 2023, from SBF lawyers and directed to Judge Lewis A. Kaplan, it is evident the former FTX top executive is in distress and intends to fight for his freedom. Currently under house arrest after a $250 million bail, SBF is under strict control not to use any messaging applications, VPNs, or any tech whatsoever until the trial happens on October 02.</p>
<p>Notably, SBF has been accused of intimidating crucial witnesses in his case including the current FTX CEO through messaging apps. Additionally, SBF has been accused of leaking a private journal belonging to Caroline Ellison to a reporter with the New York Times.</p>
<p>However, SBF lawyers responded by indicating that their client was clarifying to a reporter on misinformed reports about him and the case.</p>
<p>“….The reporter contacted Mr. Bankman-Fried about a story he was working on concerning Ms. Ellison and asked Mr. Bankman-Fried if he wished to respond. Mr. Bankman-Fried ultimately agreed to speak to the reporter and invited him for a visit at his parent’s home pursuant to the procedures outlined in the bail conditions imposed by this Court,” the SBF lawyers <a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.nysd.590940/gov.uscourts.nysd.590940.178.0.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener">noted</a>.</p>
<p>In a proposed motion by the United States government, Judge Kaplan is expected to rule on largely preventing all involved parties and their attorneys from contacting the media. If the proposed order is upheld by the United Court, SBF could be barred from using surrogates, family members, spokespersons, representatives, or volunteers to make statements on his behalf.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-vision-pro-developer-kit/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-sbf-case-update-gag-order/">US vs FTX SBF Case Update: Judge to Review Proposed Gag Order Ahead of October 2 Hearing</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-sbf-case-update-gag-order/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Apple to Share Its Vision Pro Developer Kit with Application Builders, AAPL Shares Up 1%</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-vision-pro-developer-kit/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-vision-pro-developer-kit/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 08:45:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wall Street]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[aapl]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[aapl shares]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[aapl stock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=264288</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-vision-pro-developer-kit/">Apple to Share Its Vision Pro Developer Kit with Application Builders, AAPL Shares Up 1%</a></p>
<p>Apple noted that only account holders in the Apple Developer Program can apply for the Vision Pro kit, which should be returned upon request.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-vision-pro-developer-kit/">Apple to Share Its Vision Pro Developer Kit with Application Builders, AAPL Shares Up 1%</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-vision-pro-developer-kit/">Apple to Share Its Vision Pro Developer Kit with Application Builders, AAPL Shares Up 1%</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/apple-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Apple Inc</a> (NASDAQ: AAPL) shares closed Monday trading at $192.75, up 0.42 percent from the day’s opening price. The gains had extended by approximately 0.36 percent during the after-hours trading session, thus solidifying its YTD performance of nearly 49 percent. Also, the $3 trillion valued tech company intends to work with application developers in order to wholly utilize the Vision Pro capabilities. Consequently, Apple opened applications for a Vision Pro developer kit to Apple Developer Program account holders with reputable publications.</p>
<p>The impressive performance YTD is partially attributed to the launch of a new product after several years dubbed Vision Pro. Notably, the Apple Vision Pro is set to revolutionize the 3D immersive industry after its planned launch in 2024 at a price of $3,499 per headset.</p>
<h2>Apple Vision Pro Developer Kit</h2>
<p>In addition to receiving the Vision Pro kit, application developers will also get help from the Apple team in setting up the device and onboarding. The company also announced application developers will also get check-ins with Apple experts for user interface (UI) design and development guidance in a bid to help refine their applications. Apple will also provide Vision Pro app developers with two additional code-level support requests to help troubleshoot any issues with the source code. Apple has, however, reserved the right to collect the Vision Pro device upon request.</p>
<p>“Availability is limited and on a first-come-first-served basis. If capacity gets full, you’ll be added to the waitlist and we’ll reach out when more spots become available,” the company <a href="https://developer.apple.com/visionos/compatibility-evaluations/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">noted</a>.</p>
<p>Interestingly, the company has directed all the developers that will be selected not to share access to the Vision Pro gadget with family, friends, or on social media platforms. Meanwhile, the company intends to work with developers from all over the world including through its Labs available in Cupertino, London, Munich, Shanghai, Singapore, and Tokyo.</p>
<h2>Apple and Its Performance</h2>
<p>Apple has undeniably dominated the hardware technology market around the world, having sold billions of devices since its inception. The tech giant has consistently upgraded existing hardware devices to match up with emerging markets and technologies. For instance, the company has upgraded its iOS and smartphone hardware to catch up with the 5G network development.</p>
<p>As a result, Apple has seen its stock market rise exponentially through the Covid and post-pandemic seasons. According to the latest stock market data, AAPL shares gained 26 percent last year and have almost doubled the performance YTD. Having been rated by 44 analysts, the Apple stock market received an average rating of Over.</p>
<p>Since the company began to manufacture its in-house semiconductor chips, Apple has managed to have better control of its output with more reliable performance.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-crypto-legislation-coinbase-ceo/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-vision-pro-developer-kit/">Apple to Share Its Vision Pro Developer Kit with Application Builders, AAPL Shares Up 1%</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-vision-pro-developer-kit/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4372 metric#misses=43 metric#hit-ratio=99.0 metric#bytes=1101065 metric#prefetches=220 metric#store-reads=22 metric#store-writes=3 metric#store-hits=227 metric#store-misses=4 metric#sql-queries=35 metric#ms-total=92.65 metric#ms-cache=5.61 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.2339 metric#ms-cache-ratio=6.1 -->