<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 21:20:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Emirates Group Reports Record Annual Profit of $3B after Prior Devastations of Covid-19 Restrictions</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/emirates-record-annual-profit-3b/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/emirates-record-annual-profit-3b/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 16:45:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[emirates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[emirates group]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=254504</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/emirates-record-annual-profit-3b/">Emirates Group Reports Record Annual Profit of $3B after Prior Devastations of Covid-19 Restrictions</a></p>
<p>Emirates Group announced global freight expansion to different destinations including Tanzania, Germany, Canada, and Brazil.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/emirates-record-annual-profit-3b/">Emirates Group Reports Record Annual Profit of $3B after Prior Devastations of Covid-19 Restrictions</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/emirates-record-annual-profit-3b/">Emirates Group Reports Record Annual Profit of $3B after Prior Devastations of Covid-19 Restrictions</a></p>
<p>Emirates Group, a state-owned Dubai-based international aviation holding company, released its 2022-2023 financial results. According to the announcement, Emirates achieved a record annual profit of AED 10.9 billion, approximately $3 billion. The airline service company was impressed with the financial year 2022-2023, after posting a huge decline in operations during the prior year due to Covid-19-related constraints.</p>
<h2>Emirates and Its Record Results</h2>
<p>The Emirates Group announced its yearly revenue grew by approximately 81 percent to AED 119.8 billion or about $32.6 billion. As a result, the Emirates Group ended the financial year with the highest-ever cash balance of AED 42.5 billion or about $ 11.6 billion.</p>
<p>In this regard, the Emirates Group has since declared a dividend of AED 4.5 billion, or about $1.2 billion to its owner Investment Corporation of Dubai (ICD). The airline has attributed its success to the leadership of HH Sheikh Ahmed bin Saeed Al Maktoum, Chairman and Chief Executive, of Emirates Airlines and Group.</p>
<p>“The Group is the biggest player in the UAE’s aviation sector, which supports over 770,000 jobs and generates an estimated contribution to GDP of over US$ 47 billion (AED 172.5 billion),” the Emirates Group’s CEO noted.</p>
<p>As a state-owned organization, the Emirates Group enjoyed tremendous support in debts to sustain its huge fleet and employees through the Covid pandemic.</p>
<p>“Our ongoing investments in our brand, and our products and services, helped drive customer preference and position us favorably in the market,” Sheikh Ahmed <a href="https://www.emirates.com/media-centre/emirates-group-announces-2022-23-results/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">noted</a>.</p>
<h2>Emirates Group Market Outlook</h2>
<p>The Emirates Group continued to restructure its airline operations to attract more passengers and cargo transportation. For the financial year that ended 31 March 2023, Emirates Group announced global freight expansion to different destinations including Tanzania, Germany, Canada, and Brazil. As a result, the Group anticipates reporting even better results for the financial year ahead as all the Covid-19 restrictions have already been removed.</p>
<p>“We go into 2023-24 with a strong positive outlook and expect the Group to remain profitable. We will work hard to hit our targets while keeping a close watch on inflation, high fuel prices, and political and economic uncertainty,” Sheikh Ahmed added.</p>
<p>Following increased business operations, the Group announced its total workforce increased by 20 percent to 102,379 employees from different nationalities.  The Emirates Group also plans to continue its professional hiring spree as it intends to add more multi-billion dollar aircraft.</p>
<p>According to the announcement, the Dubai-based airline received two new 777 freighter aircraft and intends to add five additional Boeing 777-300ER. Furthermore, the airline announced that it carried 43.6 million passengers during the financial year 2022-2023, representing an uptick of 123 percent.</p>
<p>Other business news can be found <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/business/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/pacwest-shares-decline-deposits/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/emirates-record-annual-profit-3b/">Emirates Group Reports Record Annual Profit of $3B after Prior Devastations of Covid-19 Restrictions</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/emirates-record-annual-profit-3b/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>PacWest (PACW) Shares Plunge 23% after Revealing 9.5% Decline in Deposits</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/pacwest-shares-decline-deposits/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/pacwest-shares-decline-deposits/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 16:42:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wall Street]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pacwest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PacWest Bancorporation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=254506</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/pacwest-shares-decline-deposits/">PacWest (PACW) Shares Plunge 23% after Revealing 9.5% Decline in Deposits</a></p>
<p>There are various choices accessible to PacWest Bancorp that could assist the business overcome the present shares devaluation.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/pacwest-shares-decline-deposits/">PacWest (PACW) Shares Plunge 23% after Revealing 9.5% Decline in Deposits</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/pacwest-shares-decline-deposits/">PacWest (PACW) Shares Plunge 23% after Revealing 9.5% Decline in Deposits</a></p>
<p>PacWest Bancorp (NASDAQ: PACW), a regional bank based in California, is seeing its shares plummet by 23%, days after <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/11/pacwest-shares-tumble-20percent-after-regional-bank-says-deposits-fell-9point5percent-last-week.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reporting</a> a 9.5% drop in deposits for the week ending May 4, 2023.</p>
<p>Notably, the decline in deposits was attributed to media reports that the regional bank was considering several strategic options in the wake of the current banking chaos in the US. Interestingly, stocks of PacWest were already down by 50% this month, and over 70% for the year.</p>
<p>The fact that PacWest&#8217;s stock price tumbled by 20% in response to the news highlights the level of concern among investors. When a bank&#8217;s deposits decline, it can be a sign of broader financial troubles that could ultimately threaten the bank&#8217;s long-term viability. As a result, shareholders might be more inclined to sell their bank shares, which could cause the stock price to drop significantly.</p>
<p>The regional banking sector has experienced a major contagion with Western Alliance Bancorporation (NYSE: WAL) stock <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/pacwest-shares-western-alliance-collapse/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">plunging by down</a> last week. The stock has shed more than 38% and changing hands at a price of $18.20. Similarly, shares of Zions Bancorporation (NASDAQ: ZION) also dropped by 2.7%, while the SPDR S&amp;P Regional Banking ETF (KRE) were down 1.9%.</p>
<p>Since the beginning of March, regional banks in the US have been facing regulatory actions due to concerns about their financial health. As a result, Silicon Valley Bank, Signature Bank, and were finally seized by regulators. <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/first-republic-bank/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">First Republic Bank</a> (OTCMKTS: FRCB) was also taken over and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/first-republic-bank-shares-q1-2023/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">sold</a> to <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/jpmorgan-chase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">JPMorgan Chase &amp; Co</a> (NYSE: JPM).</p>
<p>It is worth noting that the failure of a bank can have serious consequences for the broader economy. It can lead to job losses, financial market instability, and damage to confidence in the banking system.</p>
<h2>PacWest Shares Recovery Options</h2>
<p>There are various choices accessible to PacWest Bancorp that could assist the business overcome the present shares devaluation. Firstly, the regional bank could improve consumer confidence by talking openly about the bank&#8217;s financial health, emphasizing its strengths, and laying out strategies to rectify any weaknesses.</p>
<p>Secondly, PacWest may consider merging with or acquiring another bank in order to gain scale and improve its competitiveness. This could also help the bank diversify its operations and expand into new markets. Meanwhile, the bank has previously announced that it is considering <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/pacwest-sale-stock-drawdown/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">selling</a> its assets after efforts to raise capital remain afloat.</p>
<p>In addition, PacWest could cut its operating expenses to boost its profitability and financial health. This could entail laying off employees or closing branches, renegotiating contracts with suppliers, or establishing more efficient processes. Markedly, the bank has established to <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/pacwest-dividend-regional-banks/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">cut down</a> shareholders&#8217; dividends.</p>
<p>Finally, PacWest may also resort to repurchasing its own stock to bolster the stock price. This could indicate to investors that the bank believes its shares are undervalued and is optimistic about its long-term prospects.</p>
<p>Ultimately, the bank will need to thoroughly assess its condition and identify the best course of action to enhance its financial performance and restore investor trust.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/circle-usdc-reserves-us-default/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/pacwest-shares-decline-deposits/">PacWest (PACW) Shares Plunge 23% after Revealing 9.5% Decline in Deposits</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/pacwest-shares-decline-deposits/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Circle Adjusting Its USDC Reserves for Avoiding US Default Risks</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/circle-usdc-reserves-us-default/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/circle-usdc-reserves-us-default/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 14:07:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[circle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jeremy allaire]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[usdc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[usdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=254477</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/circle-usdc-reserves-us-default/">Circle Adjusting Its USDC Reserves for Avoiding US Default Risks</a></p>
<p>Amid the current banking crisis in the United States, stablecoin issuers like Tether and Circle have been moving their reserves to the safest instrument i.e. US Treasury.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/circle-usdc-reserves-us-default/">Circle Adjusting Its USDC Reserves for Avoiding US Default Risks</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/circle-usdc-reserves-us-default/">Circle Adjusting Its USDC Reserves for Avoiding US Default Risks</a></p>
<p>In a recent development, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/usd-coin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">USDC</a> stablecoin issuer <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/circle/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Circle</a> has reported that it has recently adjusted its reserve treasury in order to avoid the risks of US debt defaults. On Wednesday, May 10, Circle CEO <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/jeremy-allaire/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Jeremy Allaire</a> appraised the same stating that the firm has adjusted the mix of reserves backing the stablecoin USDC by switching to shirt-dated US Treasurys.</p>
<p>Allaire stated that Circle now no longer holds Treasurys maturing beyond early June since they don&#8217;t want to carry exposure “through a potential breach of the ability of the US government to pay its debts&#8221;.</p>
<p>“We don’t want to carry exposure through a potential breach of the ability of the US government to pay its debts,&#8221; <a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/circle-reportedly-adjusts-usdc-reserves-to-avoid-us-default-risk" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a> Allaire. As per the disclosure coming from Circle Reserve Fund, which is managed by BlackRock, the current US Treasury holdings by Circle don&#8217;t mature beyond May 31.</p>
<p>Circle&#8217;s USDC stablecoin is still the second-largest stablecoin with a market cap of $30 billion. Earlier this week, US Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen said that the Biden government will be forced to take a decision if Congress doesn&#8217;t come to a common ground on increasing the debt ceiling.</p>
<p>Currently, the Biden administration and the Republicans are in a conflict over raising the $31.4 trillion borrowing limit. The US is currently very close to a default on its debt. Thus, failing to raise the debt ceiling could cause havoc in the global financial system.</p>
<h2>Tether vs Circle</h2>
<p>Amid the current banking crisis in the United States, stablecoin issuers like Tether and Circle have been moving their reserves to the safest instrument i.e. US Treasury. In its recent <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tether-strong-q1-btc-gold/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">report</a>, Tether noted that they have also moved a majority of their reserves to US Treasury.</p>
<p>Circle has passed through turbulent times this year so far with the USDC stablecoin losing its peg earlier in March 2023. This led to major withdrawals from the USD Coin with its market cap dropping by more than 25% just over the last month. Despite this, USDC is currently the second-largest stablecoin with a market cap of $30 billion.</p>
<p>Over the last year, the USDC supply in the market has dropped by 46%. Last month in April Circle CEO Jeremy Allaire blamed the current banking crisis and the SEC&#8217;s war on crypto for USDC&#8217;s shrinking market cap.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/venom-kenya-blockchain-hub/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/circle-usdc-reserves-us-default/">Circle Adjusting Its USDC Reserves for Avoiding US Default Risks</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/circle-usdc-reserves-us-default/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Venom Foundation Inks Partnership with Kenyan Government to Create Blockchain Hub</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/venom-kenya-blockchain-hub/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/venom-kenya-blockchain-hub/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 13:06:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain Hub]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kenya Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[venom foundation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=254313</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/venom-kenya-blockchain-hub/">Venom Foundation Inks Partnership with Kenyan Government to Create Blockchain Hub</a></p>
<p>Venom’s blockchain hub is also expected to attract a wide range of stakeholders, including developers, entrepreneurs, investors, and regulators.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/venom-kenya-blockchain-hub/">Venom Foundation Inks Partnership with Kenyan Government to Create Blockchain Hub</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/venom-kenya-blockchain-hub/">Venom Foundation Inks Partnership with Kenyan Government to Create Blockchain Hub</a></p>
<p>Venom Foundation, which recently hit the news with its <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/venom-foundation-launches-hackathon-225000-prize-pool/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">testnet launch and hackathon</a>, has signed a Memorandum of Understanding (MOU) with the Kenyan government. This partnership is billed to help in setting up a blockchain hub in Kenya, focusing on the development of Web 3.0 applications.</p>
<p>As it was <a href="https://chainwire.org/2023/05/10/venom-to-launch-a-blockchain-hub-with-kenyan-government/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announced</a>, the hub aims to promote the adoption and development of blockchain technology in Kenya and the wider African region.</p>
<h2>Venom Unlocks Blockchain Potentials in Africa</h2>
<p>Interestingly, the leading blockchain-based payment gateway provider aims to empower African communities, create a bridge between traditional finance and the Web 3.0 world, and stimulate regional economic growth by enabling seamless cross-border trade and transactions. It will also provide tools and resources to support African countries in laying a solid foundation for digital transformation.</p>
<p>Likewise, Venom’s blockchain hub in Kenya will provide a platform for developers, startups, and established companies to collaborate and innovate with blockchain technology. The hub will also offer training and education programs to help individuals and businesses understand the potential of blockchain technology and how to integrate it into their operations.</p>
<p>The minister of treasury in Kenya expressed his enthusiasm for the partnership. In his <a href="https://twitter.com/honmoses_kuria/status/1656085322269356033?s=12&amp;t=y-TJeb_fYYjfzECkBHm4Tg" target="_blank" rel="noopener">tweet</a>, the partnership with Venom Foundation is a significant boost for Kenya and will drive further innovation in several industries, benefiting everyone both globally and nationally.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="474" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">This partnership with <a href="https://twitter.com/VenomFoundation?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank">@VenomFoundation</a> through <a href="https://twitter.com/VenomAfrica?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank">@venomafrica</a> signifies Kenya&#39;s stance towards next-gen technology, financial and technological developments, and will catalyze further innovations in various industries, benefitting people both nationally and globally.</p>
<p>&mdash; CS Moses Kuria (@HonMoses_Kuria) <a href="https://twitter.com/HonMoses_Kuria/status/1656085322269356033?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank">May 9, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Notably, Kenya is widely regarded as a leader in digital innovation in Africa, with a thriving fintech industry and a growing startup ecosystem. As such, the launch of Venom’s blockchain hub in the country will further cement Kenya’s position as a hub for digital innovation in the region. The partnership aims to promote efficiency, transparency, and trust across different sectors in the continent.</p>
<p>Venom’s blockchain hub is also expected to attract a wide range of stakeholders, including developers, entrepreneurs, investors, and regulators. The hub will provide a platform for collaboration and innovation, as well as an opportunity to explore the potential of blockchain technology in various industries in Kenya and the wider Africa region.</p>
<h2>Venom Foundation Secures Strategic Partnership</h2>
<p>Earlier in the year, the layer 1 blockchain firm <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/venom-foundation-and-hub71-partner-to-accelerate-growth-and-adoption-of-blockchain-technologies-from-abu-dhabi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">teamed</a> up with Hub71, a global tech ecosystem located in Abu Dhabi to provide enterprise-level solutions for startups and simplify blockchain adoption with a focus on the growth of businesses and acceptance of blockchain technologies in the MENA region and beyond.</p>
<p>The Venom Foundation collaboration with Hub71+ Digital Assets, an ecosystem dedicated to Web3 and Digital Assets seeks to complement the growth push for businesses. It aims to do this by helping with business development, digital asset regulation, blockchain adoption, and relevant technologies.</p>
<p>In a similar manner, Venom also <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/venom-blockchain-partners-dao-maker-incubate-web3-startups/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">entered a partnership</a> with leading blockchain solutions provider DAO Maker to incubate Web 3.0 projects centered on delivering real-world use cases.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/marathon-digital-subpoenaed-sec/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/venom-kenya-blockchain-hub/">Venom Foundation Inks Partnership with Kenyan Government to Create Blockchain Hub</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/venom-kenya-blockchain-hub/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Marathon Digital Subpoenaed by SEC Over Securities Law Violations</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/marathon-digital-subpoenaed-sec/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/marathon-digital-subpoenaed-sec/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 12:59:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marathon digital]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[robinhood]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=254471</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/marathon-digital-subpoenaed-sec/">Marathon Digital Subpoenaed by SEC Over Securities Law Violations</a></p>
<p>Marathon said it is cooperating with the SEC to provide the requested information, highlighting that it was dedicated to abiding by all relevant laws and rules.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/marathon-digital-subpoenaed-sec/">Marathon Digital Subpoenaed by SEC Over Securities Law Violations</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/marathon-digital-subpoenaed-sec/">Marathon Digital Subpoenaed by SEC Over Securities Law Violations</a></p>
<p>Bitcoin mining firm Marathon Digital Holdings Inc (NASDAQ: MARA) has gotten a subpoena from the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) in connection with suspected violations of Federal securities laws.</p>
<p>According to <a href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/bitcoin-miner-marathon-receives-another-subpoena-from-sec-1.1918564" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reports</a> from Bloomberg, the subpoena requests the production of certain documents related to the company&#8217;s recent public offering of securities. Specifically, the SEC is investigating whether the company violated the registration requirements of the Securities Act of 1933.</p>
<p>Markedly, the law mandates businesses to register with the SEC and give investors information, including financial statements, risk considerations, and other pertinent data. It is crucial to remember that receiving a subpoena does not necessarily mean the recipient has committed a crime. Rather, it simply means the SEC is interested in initiating an inquiry.</p>
<p>Notably, the news comes shortly after the Bitcoin miner <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-miner-marathon-digital-q1-2023/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">announced</a> an outstanding performance in its Q1 2023 report. Based on the report, Marathon Digital achieved its highest production month-on-month in March after mining a total of 825 BTC. Additionally, the company established that its Hashrate increased by 64% in Q1 2023 to 11.5 EH/s as of March 31, 2023.</p>
<p>In addition, Marathon also sold the Bitcoins it mined in February, as Coinspeaker reported at the time. According to the report, the company is currently having positive cash flow with total cash and cash equivalents unrestricted at $124.9 million.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Marathon has previously received a subpoena from the SEC earlier in 2021. At the time, the regulator asked the Bitcoin miner to provide documents and information pertaining to its Montana data center facility.</p>
<p>Marathon said it is cooperating with the SEC to provide the requested information, highlighting that it was dedicated to abiding by all relevant laws and rules. However, the company noted that it cannot predict the outcome of the investigation or any potential regulatory action that may result.</p>
<h2>Beyond Marathon Digital: Crypto Firms Come under SEC Scrutiny</h2>
<p>Interestingly, receiving a subpoena from the SEC is not an uncommon occurrence for publicly traded companies and service providers in the crypto ecosystem. This is because the SEC has broad investigative powers and routinely conducts investigations into potential securities law violations.</p>
<p>Markedly, companies that receive subpoenas are typically required to provide the requested information and cooperate with the SEC&#8217;s investigation.</p>
<p>Notably, the recent SEC subpoena against Marathon Digital comes amid a recent regulatory crackdown on the blockchain industry. In the US, regulators have been scrutinizing the crypto ecosystem, and there have been several high-profile enforcement actions in recent months.</p>
<p>For example, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/robinhood/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Robinhood Markets Inc</a> (NASDAQ: HOOD) recently <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/robinhood-crypto-subpoena-us-sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">received</a> a subpoena from the SEC regarding its crypto ventures. While commenting on the update, Robinhood highlighted that the subpoena was issued in response to several crypto bankruptcies that took place last year.</p>
<p>Similarly, US regulators also <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-prosecutors-funds-binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">probed</a> into Hedge funds linked to <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a>, the largest crypto exchange earlier in January. Additionally, some lawmakers were also mulling the possibility of criminal charges over concerns about money laundering.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/softbank-vision-fund-32b-loss/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/marathon-digital-subpoenaed-sec/">Marathon Digital Subpoenaed by SEC Over Securities Law Violations</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/marathon-digital-subpoenaed-sec/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>SoftBank Vision Fund Records $32B Loss in Its Fiscal 2022 Year amid Weakening Economy</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/softbank-vision-fund-32b-loss/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/softbank-vision-fund-32b-loss/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 12:10:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[arm]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[doordash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NYSE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[softbank]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[uber]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vision fund]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=254454</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/softbank-vision-fund-32b-loss/">SoftBank Vision Fund Records $32B Loss in Its Fiscal 2022 Year amid Weakening Economy</a></p>
<p>Vision Fund, SoftBank's tech investment arm, posted a loss of 4.3 trillion yen for its fiscal year that ended March 31st. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/softbank-vision-fund-32b-loss/">SoftBank Vision Fund Records $32B Loss in Its Fiscal 2022 Year amid Weakening Economy</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/softbank-vision-fund-32b-loss/">SoftBank Vision Fund Records $32B Loss in Its Fiscal 2022 Year amid Weakening Economy</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/softbank/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SoftBank</a> sustained a $32 billion record loss for its Vision Fund tech investment arm amid a challenging period for tech stocks. For its <a href="https://group.softbank/system/files/pdf/ir/financials/financial_reports/financial-report_q4fy2022_01_en.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">fiscal year ending March 31st</a>, the Japanese investment holding company’s Vision Fund posted a 4.3 trillion yen ($32 billion) deficit. This loss surpassed the 2.55 trillion yen that SoftBank sustained in the same period last year.</p>
<p>SoftBank’s latest overall Vision Fund investment loss of 5.28 trillion Japanese yen came in higher than the 3.43 trillion yen loss recorded a year before. The Tokyo-based financial conglomerate’s latest loss came despite the recent 2023 rally in tech stocks. The tech space endured one of its lowest lows in the past year, with the Nasdaq 100 index declining 11% during SoftBank’s fiscal year.</p>
<h2>SoftBank Vision Fund Loss Is the Result of Private &amp; Public Tech Valuation Markdowns</h2>
<p>SoftBank is the most prolific global investor in tech startups, and it continues to feel the ill effects of valuation corrections across its private and public tech portfolio. Over the quarter, the multinational investment holding company experienced a portfolio markdown of $2.3 billion to $138 billion. In its earnings report Thursday, SoftBank said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“For private portfolio companies, the fair value decreased in a wide range of investments, mainly reflecting markdowns of weaker-performing companies and share price declines among market comparable companies.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Amid a weakening economy, SoftBank posted a 970.14-billion-yen net loss for the fiscal year. This figure paled compared to the staggering 1.7 trillion deficit sustained in the preceding fiscal year. However, it still represented a considerable dent in SoftBank’s bottom line.</p>
<p>Despite gains from investments with high-profile companies, including <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/uber/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Uber</a> (NYSE: UBER), SoftBank logged losses in other business interests. These include falling share prices of Chinese AI platform SenseTime and Indonesian e-commerce mainstay GoTo. The company said it incurred an unrealized deficit of $1.6 billion each in SenseTime Group and GoTo. SoftBank also stated that it sustained another $800 million loss in the American online food delivery platform <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/doordash/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">DoorDash</a> (NYSE: DASH).</p>
<p>SoftBank’s chief finance officer Yoshimitsu Goto previously said the company had entered “defense mode” and braced for three different outcomes. Earlier this year, Goto explained that the investment company anticipated a linear market recovery in 2023. However, the SoftBank CFO added that the expected recovery could occur in H2 2023 or early 2024.</p>
<h2>SoftBank-Owned Arm Readies US IPO at London’s Expense</h2>
<p>All eyes are on SoftBank-owned British semiconductor giant Arm as it <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/softbank-arm-us-only-listing/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">prepares to list</a> on the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/nyse/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">New York Stock Exchange</a>. Arm’s decision to float its <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-initial-public-offering-ipo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">IPO</a> in America is a big blow to the UK government, which has hoped to entice its native tech player to <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/london-stock-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">London</a>. With Arm choosing a US listing as “the best way forward for the company”, tech observers have questioned the UK‘s credibility. According to these analysts, the Arm snub may cause the English capital market to lose out on prominent tech listings.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/new-york-bill-stablecoin-payments/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/softbank-vision-fund-32b-loss/">SoftBank Vision Fund Records $32B Loss in Its Fiscal 2022 Year amid Weakening Economy</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/softbank-vision-fund-32b-loss/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>New York Floats Bill to Allow Stablecoin Payments for Bail Bonds</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/new-york-bill-stablecoin-payments/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/new-york-bill-stablecoin-payments/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 12:02:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance us]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[celsius]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinex]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[kucoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[letitia james]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nyag]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[voyager]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=254384</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/new-york-bill-stablecoin-payments/">New York Floats Bill to Allow Stablecoin Payments for Bail Bonds</a></p>
<p>With the stringent measures that appear to have been established against crypto in New York, the acceptance of stablecoins for bail bonds is a win.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/new-york-bill-stablecoin-payments/">New York Floats Bill to Allow Stablecoin Payments for Bail Bonds</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/new-york-bill-stablecoin-payments/">New York Floats Bill to Allow Stablecoin Payments for Bail Bonds</a></p>
<p>The city of New York is currently planning to add stablecoin payments as a form of bail. According to a May 10 bill, the city is proposing legislation that will allow defendants to use fiat-backed stablecoins for bail bonds.</p>
<p>Noting that current methods allow the use of cash, credit cards, and insurance, the new bill seeks an amendment that will make room for stablecoins as well. Per the proposal, however, there is no mention of what particular stablecoins will be permitted.</p>
<h2>New York May Set Precedent for Stablecoin Payments</h2>
<p>If the new bill passes and stablecoins are accepted in New York, the move could pave the way for other states to follow suit. More so, the move is expected to impact the stablecoin ecosystem as a whole.</p>
<p>For what it&#8217;s worth, the stablecoin ecosystem has not been doing quite well in the past year or so. The current market capitalization of all stablecoins currently sits at around $131 billion. According to CoinGecko <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/research/publications/stablecoins-statistics#:~:text=Stablecoin%20dominance%20grew%20by%205.6,as%20of%20January%2031%2C%202023." target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">data</a>, that represents above 17.5% decline from its value in the previous year.</p>
<p>Therefore, such new proposals as this may help to bolster stablecoin adoption and improve its fortunes.</p>
<p>Interestingly, however, the bill comes at a time when there are calls to tighten the regulation of the crypto industry. On May 5, New York Attorney General (NYAG) Letitia James proposed a landmark legislation. According to her, the crypto industry suffers what she called “rampant fraud and dysfunction.”</p>
<p>To this end, her proposal seeks to ensure that New York carries out independent public audits of crypto exchanges. The proposal also calls for brokerage owners to be prohibited from owning tokens as this may present a case of conflicts of interest. And lastly, James also wants to prohibit lending and borrowing crypto assets.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, it might be worth mentioning that the NYAG has been actively clamping down on crypto companies recently. So far, she has taken action against the likes of CoinEX, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/kucoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">KuCoin</a>, and Celsius, among many others this year. She also stood against Binance.US in its bid to acquire troubled crypto lender Voyager.</p>
<p>But despite the stringent measures that appear to have been established against crypto in New York, the acceptance of stablecoins for bail bonds is a win. It strikes a balance and signals a step in the right direction for the state.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/standard-chartered-difc-digital-asset/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/new-york-bill-stablecoin-payments/">New York Floats Bill to Allow Stablecoin Payments for Bail Bonds</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/new-york-bill-stablecoin-payments/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Standard Chartered Signs MoU with DIFC to Launch Digital Asset Custody Services in Dubai</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/standard-chartered-difc-digital-asset/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/standard-chartered-difc-digital-asset/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 11:56:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[difc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[federal reserve]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[standard chartered]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=254431</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/standard-chartered-difc-digital-asset/">Standard Chartered Signs MoU with DIFC to Launch Digital Asset Custody Services in Dubai</a></p>
<p>Both parties look forward to partnering on opportunities that support their visions and promote a thriving digital asset ecosystem.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/standard-chartered-difc-digital-asset/">Standard Chartered Signs MoU with DIFC to Launch Digital Asset Custody Services in Dubai</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/standard-chartered-difc-digital-asset/">Standard Chartered Signs MoU with DIFC to Launch Digital Asset Custody Services in Dubai</a></p>
<p>Banking corporation <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/standard-chartered/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Standard Chartered</a> plans to launch digital asset custody services in the Dubai International Financial Centre (DIFC). While the plans are still subject to regulatory approval, Standard Chartered said the new digital asset custody services in Dubai will focus on institutional investors.</p>
<p>Also, one of the banking corporation subsidiaries, Zodia Custody, will power the new custody services. The institutional-grade crypto asset custodial platform recently secured approximately $36 billion in a funding round. The crypto startup noted that Japanese financial conglomerate SBI Holdings led the round with participation from SC Ventures. Following the financing, SBI Holdings has become the second-largest shareholder in Zodia Custody after Standard Chartered.</p>
<h2>Standard Chartered to Launch Digital Asset Custody in Dubai</h2>
<p>To execute the digital asset custody services, Standard Chartered signed a memorandum of understanding (MoU) with the DIFC. DIFC governor Essa Kazim and Standard Chartered group CEO Bill Winters signed the MoU at the Dubai Fintech Summit. Notably, the agreement is in line with Dubai’s vision to be at the forefront of the future of finance.</p>
<p>At the signing ceremony, the company’s CEO Bill Winters <a href="https://www.ledgerinsights.com/standard-chartered-digital-asset-custody-dubai/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">stated</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“We see digital assets as an important part of the future of financial services and we are committed to investing in the infrastructure and talent necessary to be a leader in this space. The UAE has a well-balanced approach to digital asset adoption and financial regulation, making it an ideal first market for us to launch our digital asset custody proposition.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Additionally, both parties look forward to partnering on opportunities that support their visions and promote a thriving digital asset ecosystem, to bring benefits to Dubai and the broader economy of the United Arab Emirates.</p>
<p>According to Kazim, the Dubai fintech sector can accommodate innovation. He noted that the Fintech market in Dubai has emerged as a critical driver of innovation and economic growth. The DIFC governor added that the development aligns with the government’s Dubai Economic Agenda (D33), which is targeted at making the jurisdiction one of the top four financial hubs in the world. Kazim continued:</p>
<blockquote><p>“DIFC welcome collaboration with partners such as Standard Chartered to further accelerate growth, and enable collaboration that triggers new innovation, as we continue to shape the future of finance together.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Last month, the consumer banking corporation predicted that Bitcoin could rise as high as $100,000 by the end of 2024. The Group said in a report that the “crypto winter” has ended, and BTC was set for increases.</p>
<p>The factors that informed the prediction are the Federal Reserve&#8217;s aggressive hike that is about to end and the recent improvement in crypto mining operations. However, the head of digital asset research at Standard Chartered, Geoff Kendrick, noted that there could be hindrances to the projected rally.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/palantir-sells-gold-bars/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/standard-chartered-difc-digital-asset/">Standard Chartered Signs MoU with DIFC to Launch Digital Asset Custody Services in Dubai</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/standard-chartered-difc-digital-asset/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Palantir Technologies Sells Off 100-Ounce Gold Bars Acquired in August 2021</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/palantir-sells-gold-bars/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/palantir-sells-gold-bars/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 11:36:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Commodities & Futures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investors News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dow jones]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[federal reserve]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[palantir]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[s&p 500]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[us treasury]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=254371</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/palantir-sells-gold-bars/">Palantir Technologies Sells Off 100-Ounce Gold Bars Acquired in August 2021</a></p>
<p>Palantir also revealed that it closed the quarter with $1.62 billion in US Treasury securities.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/palantir-sells-gold-bars/">Palantir Technologies Sells Off 100-Ounce Gold Bars Acquired in August 2021</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/palantir-sells-gold-bars/">Palantir Technologies Sells Off 100-Ounce Gold Bars Acquired in August 2021</a></p>
<p>Software company <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/palantir/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Palantir Technologies</a> (NYSE: PLTR) has sold all the gold bars it acquired in August 2021. The company invested $50.9 million to <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/palantir-buys-gold-bars-hedge-black-swan/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">buy</a> 100-ounce precious metal, which it said will be initially kept in a secure third-party facility in the northeastern United States. At a time when many companies put their money in Bitcoin and other digital assets, Palantir said the gold bars investment was a hedge against economic crisis. The crypto market was booming during the period, and other tech companies pumped cash into equity investments and even <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a>. However, Palantir decided to bet on gold bars, noting that it could “take physical possession of the gold bars stored at the facility at any time with reasonable notice”.</p>
<h2>Palantir Dumps Gold Bars</h2>
<p>The company’s chief financial officer Shyam Sankar said it was necessary “to be prepared for a future with more black swan events”.</p>
<p>Less than two years after purchasing gold bars, Palantir has bid farewell to the precious metal. The company announced the sale in its <a href="https://www.sec.gov/ix?doc=/Archives/edgar/data/0001321655/000132165523000044/pltr-20230331.htm" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Q1 financial filing</a>, noting that it resulted in “immaterial realized gain” on its statement of operations.</p>
<blockquote><p>“During the three months ended March 31, 2023, the Company sold all of its gold bars for total proceeds of $51.1 million.”</p></blockquote>
<p>The alarming inflation in mid-2021 through mid-2022 took a toll on both individuals and organizations. The princess and food and cost of energy soared from the high levels there were in the middle of 2021 till mid-last year. As a matter of fact, the YoY consumer price index peaked at 9.1% in June, above the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-the-dow-jones-industrial-average-index-djia/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Dow Jones</a> estimate of 8.8%. Since then, the numbers have steadily declined to 4.9% in April. Although it was less than expected, it represented the slowest pace since April 2021. The price of gold has increased more than 12% since early August 2021, while the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-the-sp-500-index/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">S&amp;P 500</a> has plunged around 6% over the same period.</p>
<h2>Palantir&#8217;s US Treasuries Securities</h2>
<p>In the same press release announcing the gold bars sale, Palantir revealed that it closed the quarter with $1.62 billion in US Treasury securities. This accounts for over 50% of its cash, equivalents, and short-term investments.</p>
<blockquote><p>“Cash equivalents primarily consist of money market funds and US treasury securities with original maturities of three months or less, which are invested primarily with US financial institutions. Cash deposits with financial institutions, including restricted cash, generally exceed federally insured limits. Management believes minimal credit risk exists with respect to these financial institutions and the Company has not experienced any losses on such amounts.”</p></blockquote>
<p>The disclosure came after the Federal Reserve increased its benchmark rate for the 10th time in a little over a year. The Fed raised the rate by another 0.25 percentage points.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/milady-nft-price-elon-musk/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/palantir-sells-gold-bars/">Palantir Technologies Sells Off 100-Ounce Gold Bars Acquired in August 2021</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/palantir-sells-gold-bars/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Milady NFT Floor Price and Milady Meme Coin Surges after Tweet by Elon Musk</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/milady-nft-price-elon-musk/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/milady-nft-price-elon-musk/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 11:29:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ladys]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[milady]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tesla]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=254424</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/milady-nft-price-elon-musk/">Milady NFT Floor Price and Milady Meme Coin Surges after Tweet by Elon Musk</a></p>
<p>With a market capitalization of approximately $126 million, the Milady Meme Coin saw its trading volume rally above $199 million.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/milady-nft-price-elon-musk/">Milady NFT Floor Price and Milady Meme Coin Surges after Tweet by Elon Musk</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/milady-nft-price-elon-musk/">Milady NFT Floor Price and Milady Meme Coin Surges after Tweet by Elon Musk</a></p>
<p>Tech billionaire and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/tesla/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tesla Inc</a> (NASDAQ: TSLA) CEO <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/elon-musk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Elon Musk</a>, has once again proved his influence in the meme coin industry through a tweet of Milady NFT. As a result, the price value of Milady-related tokens skyrocketed in the past 24 hours with increased demand demonstrated by a sharp uptick in traded volume. For instance, the floor price of Milady NFTs jumped to a high of about 7.8 ETH  from 3.8 ether on Wednesday. According to market data provided by OpenSea, Milady’s NFT floor price had since dropped to 5 ETH on Thursday.</p>
<p>Notably, the NFT collection reported a total volume of more than 43,148 ETH from about 3,387 owners. Created in August 2021 via the Ethereum blockchain, the Milady <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NFTs</a> have more than 34 percent unique owners out of the 9,825 items available.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, data by OpenSea shows that there are some Milady NFTs that sell as high as 75 ETH. The increased demand for Milady NFT is largely attributed to the tweet by Musk, which had the inscription &#8220;There is no Meme I Love You&#8221;.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="474" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="zxx" dir="ltr"><a href="https://t.co/4s6HwnCY74" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/4s6HwnCY74</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Elon Musk (@elonmusk) <a href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1656326406618619910?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank">May 10, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Apparently, this is not the first time that Musk has tweeted about his endorsement of the Milady creation. Back in 2019, Musk <a href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1119753087269236736?s=46&amp;t=a0FKeZLJZMjXfhSvxCyJKQ" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">tweeted</a> a note with Milady that attracted more than 65k likes.</p>
<h2>Milady NFT Controversy</h2>
<p>The Milady NFT collection and its creators have not had a smooth ride all along. In May 2022, the floor price of Milady NFTs plunged by more than 50 percent after allegations surfaced that its creator, Charlotte Fang, was involved in deadly ideologies on the anonymous imageboard site 4chan. The Milady collection, which is also endorsed by Su Zhu co-founder of bankrupt Singaporean hedge fund Three Arrows Capital, was apparently involved in the death through the suicide of a 17-year-old teenager from Canada.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="474" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">megathread on milady and their founders:</p>
<p>&#8211; miya&#39;s writings<br />&#8211; Grooming<br />&#8211; Gaslighting<br />&#8211; Systemspace and suicide of 17yo teen<br />&#8211; Remilia implication</p>
<p>proof of everything will be at the end of the thread</p>
<p>&mdash; 0xngmi (@0xngmi) <a href="https://twitter.com/0xngmi/status/1528572556894142464?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank">May 23, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Nevertheless, the Milady NFT team has remained relevant across the Web3 industry due to its attractive digital artwork.</p>
<h2>Side Notes</h2>
<p>Meanwhile, a memecoin dubbed Milady Meme Coin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/milady-meme-coin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">LADYS</a>) has spiked by around 10,000% in the past 24 hours following the Musk tweet. With a market capitalization of approximately $126 million, the Milady Meme Coin saw its trading volume rally above $199 million on Thursday.  According to on-chain data provided by ethplorer, the Milady Meme Coin had nearly 8k holders as of Thursday.</p>
<p>However, on-chain analytics platform Lookonchain has <a href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1656521884048195584?s=46&amp;t=vhblKFTfs6yl4f79tNIv5w" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">warned</a> LADYS investors of possible manipulation from the developers who own more than 23 percent of the total supply.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tether-strong-q1-btc-gold/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/milady-nft-price-elon-musk/">Milady NFT Floor Price and Milady Meme Coin Surges after Tweet by Elon Musk</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/milady-nft-price-elon-musk/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4743 metric#misses=43 metric#hit-ratio=99.1 metric#bytes=1316649 metric#prefetches=211 metric#store-reads=22 metric#store-writes=20 metric#store-hits=217 metric#store-misses=4 metric#sql-queries=34 metric#ms-total=103.76 metric#ms-cache=7.22 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.1761 metric#ms-cache-ratio=7.0 -->