<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 12:11:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Prices of Bitcoin ASIC Miners Drop to Multi-Year Lows</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/prices-bitcoin-asic-miners-lows/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/prices-bitcoin-asic-miners-lows/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 12:11:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[argo blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[asic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[core scientific]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[riot blockchain]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=230646</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/prices-bitcoin-asic-miners-lows/">Prices of Bitcoin ASIC Miners Drop to Multi-Year Lows</a></p>
<p>With the falling Bitcoin price, the miner's profitability has gone for a toss resulting into major bankruptcies and ultimately pushing the price of ASIC miners to a multi-year low. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/prices-bitcoin-asic-miners-lows/">Prices of Bitcoin ASIC Miners Drop to Multi-Year Lows</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/prices-bitcoin-asic-miners-lows/">Prices of Bitcoin ASIC Miners Drop to Multi-Year Lows</a></p>
<p>The year 2022 witnessed some of the harshest crypto winters in the history of the markets. The world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a>) continued its downfall correcting more than 65% year-to-date and is currently trading at $16,800 levels. As the price of Bitcoin has been on a constant decline, it has majorly squeezed the profit margins of Bitcoin miners. On the other hand, the rising energy costs have further added to the operational woes faced by Bitcoin miners. Over the last few months, some of the biggest Bitcoin miners like <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/core-scientific-bankruptcy-mining/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Core Scientific</a> and others have filed for bankruptcy. As this happens, the price of Bitcoin ASIC miners has considerably <a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-asic-miner-prices-hovering-at-lows-not-seen-in-years" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">dropped</a> as demand reduces along with the fall in the number of market competitors.</p>
<p>As a result, Bitcoin ASIC miners are currently seen at prices last seen in 2020 and 2021. This also reflects another sign of a major crypto bear market. The data from Hashrate Index shows that the most efficient ASIC miners which generate at least one terahash per 38 joules of energy have seen their prices fall by 86.82% from May 7, 2021 peak of $119.25 per terahash down to $15.71 as of Dec. 25.</p>
<p>In this category, some of the Bitcoin miners selling ASICs include MicroBTC’s Whatsminer M30s and Bitmain’s Antminer S19. A similar scenario holds true for mid-tier machines.</p>
<p>The prices of these mid-tier ASICs have dropped by 89.36% from its peak price of $96.24 on May. 7, 2021. to now averaging around $10.23. But the least efficient machines which require over 68 Joules per TH, are priced at $4.72. This is a 91% drop from its peak price of $52.85.</p>
<h2>Major Bankruptcies Faced by Bitcoin Miners</h2>
<p>As said, the crash in the ASIC miner prices can be attributed to the large Bitcoin mining companies which are struggling to remain profitable throughout the entire bear market this year. Amid huge debt and falling profits, several private and public-listed Bitcoin miners filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy over the last few months.</p>
<p>This includes names like Riot Blockchain, Marathon Digital, Core Scientific, Agro Blockchain and Bitfarms. However, the recent steep fall in the price of ASIC miners has also seen new buyers like Russia-based mining facility BitRiver. They are capitalizing on low electricity costs and some up-to-date hardware capable of mining one BTC at about $0.07 per kilowatt-hour in the energy-rich nation.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/baidu-driverless-taxi-wuhan/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/prices-bitcoin-asic-miners-lows/">Prices of Bitcoin ASIC Miners Drop to Multi-Year Lows</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/prices-bitcoin-asic-miners-lows/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>China’s Baidu Expands Driverless Taxi Operationality in Wuhan</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/baidu-driverless-taxi-wuhan/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/baidu-driverless-taxi-wuhan/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 12:08:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Transportation News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[baidu]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=230653</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/baidu-driverless-taxi-wuhan/">China’s Baidu Expands Driverless Taxi Operationality in Wuhan</a></p>
<p>Baidu rolled out its full-driverless robotaxis ride at about the same rate as the other ride-hailing services in August.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/baidu-driverless-taxi-wuhan/">China’s Baidu Expands Driverless Taxi Operationality in Wuhan</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/baidu-driverless-taxi-wuhan/">China’s Baidu Expands Driverless Taxi Operationality in Wuhan</a></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Chinese multinational technology Baidu has <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/12/26/baidu-night-time-driverless-robotaxis-china/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">expanded</a> its ride-hailing platform Apollo Go to include a driverless taxi service in Wuhan to operate at night. Before now, the autonomous vehicle startup was designed to function between 9 am and 5 pm in the city. The company has increased its operation time with the latest update. This means that the Baidu driverless taxi service is now available in Wuhan from 7 am to 11 pm. Also, the fresh update is expected to cater to one million customers in specific locations of the city, which accommodates over 10 million people. There are more than 50 Baidu’s Apollo Go driverless taxis covering over 130 square km in Wuhan.</span></p>
<h2>Baidu Speaks on Driverless Taxi Services Upgrade in Wuhan</h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Notably, the expansion of the commercial operation area and the times of its driverless taxi service places Baidu at a new level as the upgrade marks a new level of commercial operation for autonomous driving in China. Also, the nighttime operation will be able to serve the night travel needs of customers in Junshan New City in Wuhan Economic and Technological Development Zone. One of the major technical challenges facing autonomous driving technology is the nighttime environment. These driverless vehicles find it difficult to differentiate between obstacles and pedestrians in dim light. As for Baidu, the technology company utilizes a mixture of third-party cameras, lidars, and radars to provide its vehicles with better vision in low-visibility conditions. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Baidu rolled out its full-driverless robotaxis ride at about the same rate as the other ride-hailing services in August. At the time, the company </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/baidu-license-driverless-robotaxis/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">announced</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that it had received approval to operate in China as the first robotaxis service that does not require a human driver. It also mentioned the multiple safety measures, which include motoring redundancy, remote driving capability, and a safety operation system. By the third quarter, the Apollo Go had completed over 474,000 rides. The figures represented a massive 311% growth YoY. </span></p>
<h2>Baidu&#8217;s Autonomous Vehicle</h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The tech giant has been working on its self-driving vehicle visual-language model for identifying unseen or rare objects in long-tail scenarios. The company previously stated:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">“The model will enable autonomous vehicles to quickly make sense of an unseen object, such as special vehicle (fire truck, ambulance) recognition, plastic bag misdetection, and others. In addition, Baidu&#8217;s autonomous driving perception model &#8211; a sub-model of the WenXin Big Model &#8211; leveraging more than 1 billion parameters, is able to dramatically improve the generalization potential of autonomous driving perception.”</span></p></blockquote>
<p>Read other <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/technology/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">technology news</a> on Coinspeaker.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-funeral-company-shares-covid/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/baidu-driverless-taxi-wuhan/">China’s Baidu Expands Driverless Taxi Operationality in Wuhan</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/baidu-driverless-taxi-wuhan/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>China-Based Funeral Company Shares Surge 80% Since November amid Spike in Covid Cases</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-funeral-company-shares-covid/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-funeral-company-shares-covid/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 11:11:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[covid]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=230630</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-funeral-company-shares-covid/">China-Based Funeral Company Shares Surge 80% Since November amid Spike in Covid Cases</a></p>
<p>China funeral facilitator Fu Shou Yuan saw its shares recently rally to 7.04 Hong Kong dollars after being down 40%. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-funeral-company-shares-covid/">China-Based Funeral Company Shares Surge 80% Since November amid Spike in Covid Cases</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-funeral-company-shares-covid/">China-Based Funeral Company Shares Surge 80% Since November amid Spike in Covid Cases</a></p>
<p>The shares of a China-based funeral company recently surged to a new yearly high following a marked rise in Covid infections. According to a CNBC <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/12/27/china-funeral-company.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a>, Fu Shou Yuan International Group stock was trading at 7.04 Hong Kong dollars a pop late Friday. This rally represents an 80% increase in just two months and comes amid a new wave of Covid infections in China. After being down approximately 40% year-to-date in November, Fu Shou Yuan’s stock is now on course to attain a 15% year-to-date gain.</p>
<h2>Recap of China Funeral Company Shares Listing History</h2>
<p>Fu Shou Yuan <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2013/12/18/china-funeral-company-soars-in-hk-debut-leads-spate-of-1st-day-gains.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">debuted</a> back in 2013 and climbed as high as 66% in its Hong Kong trading debut. At the time of its listing entry, the company enjoyed backing from the Carlyle Group and hedge fund firm Farallon Investors. In 2010, Carlyle co-founder William Conway agreed to purchase $25 million in shares of the prominent China funeral operator before it went public. Conway arrived at this decision after visiting Fu Shou Yuan’s primary cemetery in Shanghai with a team of executives in December 2010.</p>
<p>At the time, the minority stake by Carlyle and Farallon Investors helped Fu Shou Yuan’s share price to 5.30 Hong Kong dollars. That price increase favorably compared with the company’s initial public offering (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-initial-public-offering-ipo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">IPO</a>) price of 3.33 Hong Kong dollars.</p>
<p>At the time of its Hong Kong public listing, Fu Shou Yuan’s IPO also experienced massive orders from small investors. Furthermore, the retail portion of orders from small investors was more than 681 times the available shares on offer.</p>
<p>Fu Shou Yuan’s stock had been on a downward trajectory from April 2021 to October this year. The reason for the slide was widespread <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/10/28/covid-cases-controls-spread-in-china.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Covid restrictions</a> that China instituted at the time. However, after going through a lull in infection outbreaks since 2020, China is currently amid a fresh resurgence.</p>
<h2>China Covid</h2>
<p>China experienced a resurgence in Covid case numbers after abruptly suspending most of its control measures. However, despite widespread accounts of a spike in Covid-related deaths, the country’s official Covid death toll remains low. These low numbers could be a result of the nature of reportage from health authorities. For instance, Chinese health authorities re-defined Covid-related deaths to comprise only those who die from pneumonia or respiratory failure. Meanwhile, in contrast, a majority of other countries ascribe any death to Covid provided the virus played some factor.</p>
<p>In other related China Covid news, the East Asian nation’s National Health Commission recently <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/12/25/china-to-stop-publishing-daily-covid-figures.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announced it would stop</a> infection publication. According to the State Council’s cabinet-level executive department, it planned to suspend publishing daily Covid numbers. The NHC statement read:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Relevant COVID information will be published by the Chinese Center for Disease Control and Prevention for reference and research.”</p></blockquote>
<p>However, the Commission did not specify the reasons for the change. Furthermore, the Chinese NHC did not provide details regarding the frequency of updated Covid information by its CDC.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/italy-nft-market-upward-projection/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-funeral-company-shares-covid/">China-Based Funeral Company Shares Surge 80% Since November amid Spike in Covid Cases</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-funeral-company-shares-covid/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Italy NFT Market Goes Wild, Upward Projection till 2028</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/italy-nft-market-upward-projection/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/italy-nft-market-upward-projection/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 11:03:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nft]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=230618</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/italy-nft-market-upward-projection/">Italy NFT Market Goes Wild, Upward Projection till 2028</a></p>
<p>The NFT buzz went beyond the art industry to reach the Italian fashion space.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/italy-nft-market-upward-projection/">Italy NFT Market Goes Wild, Upward Projection till 2028</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/italy-nft-market-upward-projection/">Italy NFT Market Goes Wild, Upward Projection till 2028</a></p>
<p>Italy is reportedly looking to develop the crypto art renaissance through its non-fungible token (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NFT</a>) market. As one of the cultural hubs in Europe, the country is grounded in culture, history, and art. <a href="https://www.researchandmarkets.com/reports/5636034/italy-nft-market-intelligence-and-future-growth?utm_source=GNOM&amp;utm_medium=PressRelease&amp;utm_code=6qc6mb&amp;utm_campaign=1800131+-+Italy+NFT+Market+Intelligence+and+Future+Growth+Dynamics+Databook+Report+2022%3a+50%2b+KPIs+on+NFT+Investments+by+Key+Assets%2c+Currency%2c+Sales+Channels+2019-2028&amp;utm_exec=chdo54prd" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Citing</a> Q2 2022 NFT Survey, data from Research and Markets “Italy NFT Market Intelligence and Future Growth Dynamics Databook” states the expected growth for the NFT market. Data projected the industry to surge 47.6% on an annual basis. With this projection, the NFT market in Italy will be worth $671 million.</p>
<h2>Italy NFT Market Projection</h2>
<p>In addition, the market is expected to continue to grow from now till 2028 at a compound annual growth rate of 34.6%. Also, the NFT Spend Value is forecasted to increase from its current level of $671.4 million. The spending value is expected to rise from its current state in 2022 to $3633.5 million by 2028. The report acknowledges young digital artists in Italy for the growth of NFTs in the country. Cambi Auction House hosted the first crypto art auction in Italy in July 2021, where Italian artists sold their artworks as NFTs. The sale signified that NFTs had a place and a bright future in Italy. Also, the country saw an exponential expansion in digital crypto arts and NFTs adoption resulting in its “crypto art Renaissance” title. The achievement resulted in its third global position for total gross sales in the main NFT market TremendousRare.</p>
<p>Italy’s ability to bring security to arts via NFTs has attracted investors to the revolutionized digital artwork market. Federico Clapis sold his work for about 44.7 ETH ($180,00), while Hackatao sold his for around 185 ETH ($575,000).</p>
<h2>Italian Fashion Industry Embraces NFT</h2>
<p>The NFT buzz went beyond the art industry to reach the Italian fashion space. While Gucci has raised $11.5 million from NFTs over the past year, Dolce &amp; Gabbana has secured about $25.6 million. D&amp;G rolled out Collezione Genesi, a group of one NFTs. The NFTs were launched on UNXD. Italian fashion brands are continuously partnering with NFT platforms to launch fashion NFTs. These luxury fashion houses release clothes, shoes, jewelry, accessories, and other unique items. Notably, these brands continue to see growth in their businesses as fans, collectors, and other interested buyers continue to amass the digital arts.</p>
<p>However, Italy is imposing a 26% capital gains tax on crypto profits of more than 2,000 euros ($2,062.) This is in line with the country’s effort to tighten digital currency regulations in 2023. Taxpayers can declare the value of all their digital assets holdings as of January 1st and pay a 14% tax if the proposed bill is signed into law.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fidelity-trademark-crypto-footprint/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/italy-nft-market-upward-projection/">Italy NFT Market Goes Wild, Upward Projection till 2028</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/italy-nft-market-upward-projection/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fidelity Investments Files Trademark Applications to Expand Its Crypto Footprint</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fidelity-trademark-crypto-footprint/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fidelity-trademark-crypto-footprint/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 10:58:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fidelity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fidelity investments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[metaverse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trademarks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=230611</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fidelity-trademark-crypto-footprint/">Fidelity Investments Files Trademark Applications to Expand Its Crypto Footprint</a></p>
<p>Investing in the digital currency ecosystem has been considered a major gamble by most multinationals.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fidelity-trademark-crypto-footprint/">Fidelity Investments Files Trademark Applications to Expand Its Crypto Footprint</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fidelity-trademark-crypto-footprint/">Fidelity Investments Files Trademark Applications to Expand Its Crypto Footprint</a></p>
<p>American multinational financial services giant, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/fidelity-investments/">Fidelity Investments</a> has filed trademark applications to offer services in the alternate reality that will include the metaverse. As <a href="https://www.theblock.co/post/197928/fidelity-files-for-metaverse-trademarks-in-latest-crypto-push">reported</a> by The Block citing the company’s trademark filings, the firm hopes to expand its footprint in the Web 3.0 world with three major trademark applications. The trademark filing by Fidelity mentions the creation of Non-Fungible Tokens (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NFTs</a>) as well as NFT Marketplaces as part of its intended crypto offerings. In addition, Fidelity Investments said it also plans to offer virtual real estate investments, crypto trading, and metaverse investment services.</p>
<p>While it is not uncommon for global financial service firms to file trademarks in the metaverse as <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/visa-inc/">Visa Inc</a> (NYSE: V) and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/mastercard/">Mastercard Inc</a> (NYSE: MA) have done in the past, it is completely unusual for investment managers, the size of Fidelity to make such a move. The trademark filing, if approved will push Fidelity at the top of the chart among firms pushing the new frontier in this regard.</p>
<p>Fidelity Investments’ push into the digital currency ecosystem dates back a few years ago and its involvement became even more definitive over the past year. Besides creating Fidelity Crypto which is tasked with the purpose of managing investments in the new niche, the company has been rolling out a number of innovative products to bridge the gap between the traditional financial services sector and the nascent industry.</p>
<p>One such service is the allowance of Bitcoin (BTC) <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microstrategy-allows-employees-access-to-fidelitys-bitcoin-401k-service/">investments in 401(k) Retirement Savings</a> Accounts for the American workforce. The company floated this service in April and companies have started subscribing to it. One of its forefront clients is MicroStrategy Incorporated (NASDAQ: MSTR), a company growing huge acclaim for its investments in BTC.</p>
<h2>Fidelity Defying All Odds to Expand Its Crypto Footprint</h2>
<p>Investing in the digital currency ecosystem has been considered a major gamble by most multinationals. Besides the fact that cryptocurrencies are not completely regulated in the United States which makes the offering of any crypto product, a hassle for Fidelity and other prospective players, the terrain’s volatility has also been cited as a major disadvantage.</p>
<p>Lawmakers in the United States have charged Fidelity Investments to rethink its approach to its 401(k) considering the extreme volatility of the industry. Fidelity has not just shunned this advice, it is exploring avenues to expand the workforce in its crypto arm so as to deepen its service offerings across the board.</p>
<p>From its <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fidelity-crypto-accounts/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">launch</a> of a commission-free crypto trading account this past November to the new metaverse trademark it is seeking, Fidelity is setting the pace among its peers as a crypto powerhouse.</p>
<p>Per the general projection, crypto and the technology powering it will shape the future of the digital economy through the evolution of Web 3.0. Fidelity is pushing its limits to be amongst the pioneers of this future that is evidently coming to life.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-japan-98m-back-taxes/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fidelity-trademark-crypto-footprint/">Fidelity Investments Files Trademark Applications to Expand Its Crypto Footprint</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fidelity-trademark-crypto-footprint/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Apple Japan to Pay $98 Million in Back Taxes for Missing Duty-Free Abuses</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-japan-98m-back-taxes/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-japan-98m-back-taxes/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Darya Rudz]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 10:47:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple japan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple japan sales]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple japan tax]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple tax]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=230605</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-japan-98m-back-taxes/">Apple Japan to Pay $98 Million in Back Taxes for Missing Duty-Free Abuses</a></p>
<p>Notably, iPhones are cheaper in Japan than abroad. As a result, Tokyo authorities suspect vendors trying to take advantage of the country's duty-free system, purchasing the products and then selling them overseas, turning a profit by bypassing consumption tax. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-japan-98m-back-taxes/">Apple Japan to Pay $98 Million in Back Taxes for Missing Duty-Free Abuses</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-japan-98m-back-taxes/">Apple Japan to Pay $98 Million in Back Taxes for Missing Duty-Free Abuses</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/apple-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Apple Inc</a> (NASDAQ: AAPL) unit in Japan has been charged with as much as 13 billion yen ($98 million) in additional taxes for bulk sales of Apple products to foreign tourists and their exemption from the consumption tax. As Nikkei has <a href="https://asia.nikkei.com/Business/Retail/Apple-Japan-hit-with-98m-in-back-taxes-for-missing-duty-free-abuses" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reported</a>, the Tokyo Regional Taxation Bureau found bulk sales in some of the stores, and one of them conducted a transaction that involved selling hundreds of handsets at once.</p>
<p>As per the policy applied in Japan, foreign tourists can stay in the country for up to six months without paying a 10% consumption tax. Consumption tax in Japan, known in other countries as VAT, GST, or sales tax, is applied on all items except food, drinks, and newspaper subscriptions for which it is 8%. Tax-free shopping is available to visitors at licensed stores when making purchases of over 5000 yen at a given store or mall on one calendar day. However, when it comes to resale, this exemption does not apply.</p>
<p>Notably, iPhones are cheaper in Japan than abroad. As a result, Tokyo authorities suspect vendors trying to take advantage of the country&#8217;s duty-free system, purchasing the products and then selling them overseas, turning a profit by bypassing consumption tax.</p>
<p>When reached for comment, Apple Japan said:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We do not offer tax-free shopping at our stores. We apologize for the inconvenience.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The company is believed to have filed the amended tax return.</p>
<p>Since Japan offered tax-free shopping for visitors as a measure of attracting them and bringing more money to the country, there have been a lot of cases of violations. According to tax authorities, there have been about 24,000 cases of failure by companies to report consumption tax payments in the year through June. A total of 86.9 billion yen in back taxes was levied, which is 11% higher than five years earlier.</p>
<h2>Apple in Japan</h2>
<p>In fiscal 2022, Apple&#8217;s sales in Japan totaled $26 billion. According to a Central News Agency Tokyo report, Japanese consumers have always been willing to pay for the latest gadgets. In the past, many Japanese were skeptical of second-hand goods such as electronics. But now, as the yen has fallen, some can no longer afford the price of a new iPhone, while second-hand trade is emerging in a key market for Apple Inc. Therefore, Apple&#8217;s sales in the region have been falling this year.</p>
<p>In July, Apple raised the price of the entry-level iPhone 13 by nearly 20%. The new iPhone 14, which was launched later, was another 20% more expensive than the iPhone 13, and the price in the US was flat at $799. As Apple said in its annual regulatory filing back in November, sales in Japan fell by 9% due to a weaker yen.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/mining-pool-btc-cyberattack-3m-loss/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-japan-98m-back-taxes/">Apple Japan to Pay $98 Million in Back Taxes for Missing Duty-Free Abuses</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-japan-98m-back-taxes/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Mining Pool BTC.com Faces Cyberattack and $3 Million Loss of Funds</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/mining-pool-btc-cyberattack-3m-loss/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/mining-pool-btc-cyberattack-3m-loss/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 10:41:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cybersecurity News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bit mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc.com]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[new york stock exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NYSE]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=230598</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/mining-pool-btc-cyberattack-3m-loss/">Bitcoin Mining Pool BTC.com Faces Cyberattack and $3 Million Loss of Funds</a></p>
<p>BIT Mining has reported this incident to authorities in Shenzhen, China, who are investigating the incident and collecting more evidence. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/mining-pool-btc-cyberattack-3m-loss/">Bitcoin Mining Pool BTC.com Faces Cyberattack and $3 Million Loss of Funds</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/mining-pool-btc-cyberattack-3m-loss/">Bitcoin Mining Pool BTC.com Faces Cyberattack and $3 Million Loss of Funds</a></p>
<p>BTC.com, one of the largest crypto mining pools, suffered a major cyberattack which resulted in a significant loss of customer funds. Parent firm BIT Mining Limited made the announcement on Monday, December 26.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Mining Pool and Recent Cyberattack</h2>
<p>As reported by BIT Mining, the attack took place earlier this month on December 3 with the attackers stealing around $700,000 in client assets and a staggering $2.3 million in company attacks. BIT Mining has reported this cyberattack to law enforcement authorities in Shenzhen, China.</p>
<p>As a result, the local authorities have launched an investigation into the matter. They have started collecting evidence and have requested assistance from several agencies in China. The announcement from BIT Mining notes that their efforts have helped BTC.com recover some of its assets.</p>
<p>“The Company will devote considerable efforts to recover the stolen digital assets,” noted BIT Mining. They also added that they have deployed technology to better &#8220;block and intercept hackers&#8221;. Despite the major hacking incident, BTC.com has continued to run its mining services. It <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/bit-mining-limited-subsidiary-experiences-cyberattack-301709947.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">noted</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“In the wake of discovering this cyberattack, the company has implemented technology to better block and intercept hackers. BTC.com is currently operating its business as usual, and apart from its digital asset services, its client fund services are unaffected.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>Not So Good Year for BTC.com</h2>
<p>This year of 2022 hasn&#8217;t been good enough for the entire <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> mining industry in general. With the fall in the price of Bitcoin, the margins for Bitcoin miners have been squeezed considerably. On the other hand, Bitcoin miners are also facing the heat of rising energy costs. As a result, over the last year, shares of the Bitcoin miner are down by 98%.</p>
<p>As said, BTC.com is one of the world&#8217;s largest crypto-mining pools offering multicurrency services for different assets like Bitcoin and Litecoin. Apart from the mining services, BTC.com also operates a blockchain browser. BIT Mining, the parent organization of BTC.com is a publicly-traded company operating on the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/nyse/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">New York Stock Exchange</a>.</p>
<p>Also, the mining pool BTC.com is the seventh-biggest worldwide accounting for nearly 2.5% of the total mining pool distribution. It also has a hash rate of 5.80 exahashes per second (EH/s). BTC.com&#8217;s all-time contribution also accounts for more than 5% of the total Bitcoin hashrate.</p>
<p>The recent development might give China another reason to crack down harder on the Bitcoin mining operations in the country.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nexo-terminates-vauld-deal/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/mining-pool-btc-cyberattack-3m-loss/">Bitcoin Mining Pool BTC.com Faces Cyberattack and $3 Million Loss of Funds</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/mining-pool-btc-cyberattack-3m-loss/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nexo Terminates Vauld Acquisition Deal Ending Six-Month-Long Discussions</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nexo-terminates-vauld-deal/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nexo-terminates-vauld-deal/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 10:31:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Deals News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nexo]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vauld]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=230601</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nexo-terminates-vauld-deal/">Nexo Terminates Vauld Acquisition Deal Ending Six-Month-Long Discussions</a></p>
<p>Swiss crypto lender Nexo recently terminated its acquisition deal with embattled Singaporean crypto lender Vauld.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nexo-terminates-vauld-deal/">Nexo Terminates Vauld Acquisition Deal Ending Six-Month-Long Discussions</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nexo-terminates-vauld-deal/">Nexo Terminates Vauld Acquisition Deal Ending Six-Month-Long Discussions</a></p>
<p>Nexo has ended discussions with rival crypto lender Vauld regarding a potential acquisition deal. According to new <a href="https://www.theblock.co/post/197894/nexo-vauld-deal-terminated" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reports</a>, Nexo opted out of potentially acquiring the troubled crypto lender after six months of dialogue. Both parties had been in <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nexo-acquisition-process-vauld/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">discussions</a> since early July.</p>
<p>The opportunity for Nexo to acquire Vauld initially came after Vauld suspended client withdrawals in early July due to a severe liquidity crunch. Vauld also hired legal and financial advisors to provide potential restructuring options.</p>
<p>At the time of the deal agreement, Nexo entered a two-month exclusive due diligence obligation with Vauld to potentially purchase the company. However, the Switzerland-based crypto lending platform extended the due diligence grace twice. Eventually, both parties formally terminated discussions.</p>
<p>Vauld founder and chief executive officer Darshan Bathija sent an email to the firm&#8217;s creditors lamenting the deal&#8217;s fate. Part of Bathija&#8217;s electronic memo read:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We have since sought a mutual agreement with Nexo to terminate the existing exclusivity arrangements and we are continuing our active engagement with the shortlisted fund managers in developing a viable strategy that would best serve the creditors&#8217; interests.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Alleged Reasons for the Nexo-Vauld Deal Termination</h2>
<p>According to inside sources, there are several reasons why the Nexos and Vauld deal fell through. One of these is the Singapore-based crypto exchange and lender losing a substantial amount of money in the failed Terra ecosystem. Other alleged reasons include Indian authorities freezing Vauld&#8217;s assets, frozen funds in sunken exchange FTX, and massive loan receivables from Amber Group. In addition, due to regulatory constraints, Nexo&#8217;s recent announcement to <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nexo-exit-us-market-regulatory/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">leave the US</a> did not augur well for Vauld. The Singapore-based company has a vast client base in the US, so the potential deal made little sense for Nexo.</p>
<p>Nexo reportedly tried to salvage the deal by presenting terms to Vauld twice, which the latter rebuffed. According to Bathija, Vauld and its creditors were not pleased with the terms Nexo offered. The Vauld CEO explained that Nexo&#8217;s revised terms would not accommodate a &#8220;debt tender offer by way of a Reverse Dutch Auction&#8221;. An RDA would allow creditors to exit early, which Vauld believes is crucial to its proposed restructuring success.</p>
<p>Bathija continued, stating that the benefits from the revised Nexo proposal, including early credit withdrawal, were set at a threshold. The Vauld CEO concluded that the proposed threshold is unachievable by most creditors and would not serve their best interests.</p>
<p>Vauld also accused Nexo of needing to be more transparent regarding its financial condition. As Bathija explained in his email to creditors:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Nexo has failed to respond to requests for a comprehensive due diligence exercise on them, including a solvency assessment of Nexo….&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The Vauld CEO added that Nexo subsequently failed to provide safety-net assurances to creditors in the event of its insolvency.</p>
<p>Following the termination of the acquisition deal, Vauld looks to select a fund manager for customer assets. This strategy makes up the company&#8217;s proposed restructuring plan.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/italy-albania-crypto-scam/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nexo-terminates-vauld-deal/">Nexo Terminates Vauld Acquisition Deal Ending Six-Month-Long Discussions</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nexo-terminates-vauld-deal/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Law Enforcement in Italy and Albania Clamp Down on Alleged Crypto Scam</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/italy-albania-crypto-scam/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/italy-albania-crypto-scam/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 15:19:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ocg]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[spak]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=230506</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/italy-albania-crypto-scam/">Law Enforcement in Italy and Albania Clamp Down on Alleged Crypto Scam</a></p>
<p>A joint task force from Italy and Albania recently busted a suspected crypto investment scam involving millions of dollars. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/italy-albania-crypto-scam/">Law Enforcement in Italy and Albania Clamp Down on Alleged Crypto Scam</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/italy-albania-crypto-scam/">Law Enforcement in Italy and Albania Clamp Down on Alleged Crypto Scam</a></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Law enforcement authorities in Albania and Italy have uncovered a 15 million euro ($16 million) suspected crypto scam. </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2022/12/23/authorities-in-italy-albania-bust-16m-suspected-crypto-investment-scam/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">According to reports</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, the Eurojust joint investigation team seized assets worth 3 million euros during the raid. The European Union’s cross-border organized crime-fighting agency also recently </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.eurojust.europa.eu/news/takedown-online-investment-fraud-responsible-losses-eur-15-million" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">reported</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that it confiscated more than 160 electronic devices. These include digital video recorders, computers, servers, and a cellphone. </span></p>
<h2><strong><span data-preserver-spaces="true">How Perpetrators Pulled Off Alleged Italy and Albania Crypto Scam</span></strong></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Eurojust also alleged that an organized crime group (OCG) operating out of a call center in Tirana, Albania was behind the fraudulent operation. The suspects successfully pulled off the investment fraud by telephoning victims using unidentifiable virtual numbers and delocalized virtual private networks (VPNs). According to Eurojust, these miscreants asked the victims to create an account on a portal and transfer an initial sum. Victims who obliged received an immediate financial gain, after which the perpetrators contacted them again – this time posing as brokers. According to the Eurojust statement, the organized crime group attempted to sell its victims profitable cryptocurrency investments without risk. However, it remains unclear if any digital currency purchase took place. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Victims were also implored to make far more substantial investments, which sometimes constituted their entire economic capital. Upon receipt of these larger sums, Eurojust alleged that the perpetrators reset the details of the newly-created accounts. Furthermore, the criminals locked unsuspecting victims out of their accounts, embezzled the received funds, and made themselves untraceable. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Eurojust noted that the organized crime group was able to fool its victims due to the bait-and-switch approach of its strategy. By allowing victims to secure an immediate financial gain against a small investment, the perpetrators gained the trust of clueless investors. </span></p>
<h2><strong><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Round Two</span></strong></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In the second phase of the scam, the organized crime group gained access to the victims’ personal home banking pages. According to Eurojust, these criminals could secure access using PC remote control software. At this point, the malevolent crime syndicate then proceeded to persuade investors to commit their entire economic capital. However, the scam was not done yet. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Eurojust also further alleged that victims who uncovered the deception were contacted in the final stages of the ruse by OCG members. These miscreants then convinced the victims to make additional payments to recover the lost funds. </span></p>
<h2><strong><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Other Details Pertaining to Case</span></strong></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The European Union’s organized crime fighting unit coordinated its actions on the Italy-Albania <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fca-crypto-financial-scam-uk/">crypto scam</a> between December 13th and 15th. In addition, the agency executed precautionary detention orders against the main suspects of the fraud. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">According to reports, Italian authorities opened the case at Eurojust in 2020, and thirteen locations underwent intense search exercises in Albania. In addition, during the action, the Eurojust organized four coordination meetings and a coordination center. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Authorities that participated in the action included the Public Prosecutor’s Office of Pisa and the Carabinieri Pisa in Italy. Furthermore, Albania’s Special Prosecution Office Against Corruption and Organised Crime (SPAK), and its State Police also took part in the investigation. </span></p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-funds-berkshire-hathaway/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/italy-albania-crypto-scam/">Law Enforcement in Italy and Albania Clamp Down on Alleged Crypto Scam</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/italy-albania-crypto-scam/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Twitter Speculates Binance Looking at Raising Funds from Berkshire Hathaway</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-funds-berkshire-hathaway/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-funds-berkshire-hathaway/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 15:17:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investors News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[berkshire hathaway]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[changpeng zhao]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cz]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[warren buffett]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=230508</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-funds-berkshire-hathaway/">Crypto Twitter Speculates Binance Looking at Raising Funds from Berkshire Hathaway</a></p>
<p>The likelihood that Berkshire Hathaway is going to invest in Binance is considered very slim as Binance is reportedly under the radar of authorities in the United States.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-funds-berkshire-hathaway/">Crypto Twitter Speculates Binance Looking at Raising Funds from Berkshire Hathaway</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-funds-berkshire-hathaway/">Crypto Twitter Speculates Binance Looking at Raising Funds from Berkshire Hathaway</a></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A major point of conversation on crypto Twitter is that Binance Exchange, the world’s largest digital currency brokerage by daily trading volume is in talks with Warren Buffett’s </span><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/berkshire-hathaway/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Berkshire Hathaway Inc Class A</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> (NYSE: BRK.A) for some equity funding.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Self-proclaimed “Engaged Value Investor” Mike Alfred broke the news on Twitter citing a source he claimed was a “fund manager closely connected to one of the earliest investors in Binance.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Considered one of the biggest critics of Binance and its Chief Executive Officer Changpeng “<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/changpeng-zhao/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CZ</a>” Zhao, Alfred said his source confirmed to him that “Binance is in active discussions with potential new &#8220;Keystone&#8221; investors, including <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/warren-buffett/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Warren Buffett</a>&#8216;s Berkshire Hathaway, about an equity round that would provide support and credibility to the company.”</span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="474" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">serve as a &quot;decentralized CFO&quot; according to the company.</p>
<p>2. Binance is an active discussions with potential new &quot;Keystone&quot; investors, including Warren Buffett&#39;s Berkshire Hathaway, about an equity round that would provide support and credibility to the company.</p>
<p>&mdash; Mike Alfred (@mikealfred) <a href="https://twitter.com/mikealfred/status/1606006113605808129?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 22, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Since FTX </span><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-exchange-files-for-bankruptcy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">imploded</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, Binance has come under intense scrutiny as many believed the collapse of the trading platform may be a signal of ill health for bigger exchanges to also go under. Binance spearheaded the publishing of Proof-of-Reserves (PoR) in November and despite its attempts to show transparency, the community </span><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-proof-of-reserve-system/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">faulted</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> the fact that the trading platform did not publish any form of debt or liabilities which makes its proofs faulty.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Since FTX’s file for bankruptcy, the questions surrounding the integrity of Binance’s internal operations have grown and this accounts for the need to secure a high-profile investor like Berkshire Hathaway to prop up its image.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to Alfred’s anonymous source, Binance has no centralized Chief Financial Officer (CFO) and that about 20 people working in the company’s Treasury are designated as decentralized CFOs. The FUD surrounding Binance’s operations has weighed down the trading platform in terms of volumes processed, and the valuation of BNB has plunged by 15.2% over the past 14 days.</span></p>
<h2><b>Is There a Likelihood of Berkshire Hathaway Investing in Binance?</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This remains a major question on the minds of many on Crypto Twitter as Warren Buffett is known to be a major critic of Bitcoin and the crypto ecosystem as a whole. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The likelihood that Berkshire Hathaway is going to invest in Binance is considered very slim as Binance is reportedly under the radar of authorities in the United States. This will not only make the American conglomerate refrain from furthering conversations with the trading platform.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A major point raised by some observers is the fact that CZ may be unwilling to open up Binance’s books for the kind of scrutiny that external investors like Berkshire Hathaway will require to place a bet on the company.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">While the impossibilities have been highlighted, chances are that Berkshire Hathaway may also inject some funds using one of its Venture Capital offshoots. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Berkshire Hathaway is building a history of investing in crypto-based companies. The company </span><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/buffett-berkshire-hathaway-nubank/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">invested</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> as much as $1 billion in the crypto financial institution, Nubank, carving out the premise that if it can invest in Nubank, it can also inject funds into Binance or any of its entities.</span></p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tsmc-plant-germany/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-funds-berkshire-hathaway/">Crypto Twitter Speculates Binance Looking at Raising Funds from Berkshire Hathaway</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-funds-berkshire-hathaway/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>