<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 19:50:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>XRP Price Goes Parabolic Following Big Win of Ripple against SEC</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/xrp-price-ripple-win-sec/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/xrp-price-ripple-win-sec/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 19:50:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ripple labs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=262995</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/xrp-price-ripple-win-sec/">XRP Price Goes Parabolic Following Big Win of Ripple against SEC</a></p>
<p>This great win of Ripple in its battle against the SEC can be viewed as a reminder that the existing regulatory frameworks may not always fit the unique characteristics of cryptocurrencies and may require modification or refinement. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/xrp-price-ripple-win-sec/">XRP Price Goes Parabolic Following Big Win of Ripple against SEC</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/xrp-price-ripple-win-sec/">XRP Price Goes Parabolic Following Big Win of Ripple against SEC</a></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In a significant legal development, US Judge Analisa Torres <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/07/13/xrp-surges-after-judge-delivers-a-huge-win-to-ripple-in-its-case-against-the-sec.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">pronounced</a> the much-awaited Summary Judgment, ruling</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> that </span><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/xrp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">XRP</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> is not a security. Interestingly, this verdict has not only breathed new life into the future prospects of the blockchain payments firm, </span><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ripple-labs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ripple Labs Inc</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> but has also triggered a remarkable surge in the price valuation of the XRP coin.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The ruling came after an extensive legal battle that started in December 2020 between Ripple Labs and the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (</span><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">SEC</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">). Recall that, the SEC had alleged that <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/xrp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">XRP</a> qualifies as an investment contract and should be subject to regulatory oversight. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">However, in her current ruling, Judge Torres disagreed, stating that XRP does not meet the criteria to be classified as a security under US law based on the provisions of the Howey Test. Meanwhile, the ruling, which has been applauded by top leaders in the digital currency ecosystem, is seen as a significant victory for Ripple Labs and the entire cryptocurrency industry. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The classification of XRP as a non-security means that it can continue to operate without the stringent regulations that govern securities. This decision provides clarity and certainty for other cryptocurrencies as well as sets a precedent for how similar tokens may be evaluated in the future.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is particularly necessary as the regulator has beamed its radar on other top digital currencies like </span><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/cardano/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Cardano</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> (ADA), </span><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/solana/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Solana</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> (SOL), and Decentraland (MANA) which it said are investment contracts in its recent crackdown on Binance and </span><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Coinbase Global Inc</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> (NASDAQ: COIN)</span></p>
<h2><b>XRP Price Goes Parabolic amid Celebration Over Ripple&#8217;s Win </b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Following the ruling, the demand for XRP skyrocketed as investors and cryptocurrency enthusiasts rushed to buy, thereby leading to a surge in its price and market capitalization. At the time of writing, XRP is trading at a spot price of $0.7938, up by more than 70% over the past 24 hours </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">per</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> data from <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/xrp/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">CoinMarketCap</a>.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Also, many industry experts believe that the ruling has provided a much-needed boost to the overall market sentiment surrounding cryptocurrencies.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The judge’s ruling has instilled confidence in investors who were previously hesitant to enter the cryptocurrency market due to regulatory uncertainties. With the clarification that XRP is not a security, potential investors are more inclined to consider the asset and other altcoins as viable investment options. In return, the increased investors’ confidence will lead to further growth and development within the cryptocurrency industry.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Likewise, the ruling highlights the need for regulators to adapt and develop frameworks that can effectively govern the rapidly evolving cryptocurrency space. As more cryptocurrencies emerge in the market, it becomes essential for regulators to keep up with technological advancements and provide a supportive environment for innovation.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Undoubtedly, Judge Torres’ decision serves as a reminder that the existing regulatory frameworks may not always fit the unique characteristics of cryptocurrencies and may require modification or refinement. </span></p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/delta-air-lines-revenue-profitability/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/xrp-price-ripple-win-sec/">XRP Price Goes Parabolic Following Big Win of Ripple against SEC</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/xrp-price-ripple-win-sec/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Delta Air Lines Announces Highest Quarterly Revenue and Profitability in Airline’s History</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/delta-air-lines-revenue-profitability/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/delta-air-lines-revenue-profitability/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 18:23:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wall Street]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[delat air lines]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[delta]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=262988</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/delta-air-lines-revenue-profitability/">Delta Air Lines Announces Highest Quarterly Revenue and Profitability in Airline&#8217;s History</a></p>
<p>Delta Air Lines shares are up today after the company reported an adjusted revenue of $14.61 billion vs. $14.49 billion expected by analysts.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/delta-air-lines-revenue-profitability/">Delta Air Lines Announces Highest Quarterly Revenue and Profitability in Airline&#8217;s History</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/delta-air-lines-revenue-profitability/">Delta Air Lines Announces Highest Quarterly Revenue and Profitability in Airline&#8217;s History</a></p>
<p>One of the oldest airlines in operations <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/delta-air-lines/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Delta Air Lines Inc</a> (NYSE: DAL) announced its highest quarterly earnings in the June quarter and provided its outlook for the September quarter of 2023. Resultantly, the company recorded a strong June quarter operating cash flow, which will ostensibly enable the airline to reduce its debt. During the quarter, Delta announced an adjusted revenue of about $14.61 billion versus the $14.49 billion expected by analysts surveyed by Refinitiv.</p>
<p>The airline, therefore, posted adjusted earnings per share of about $2.68 versus the $2.40 expected by Wall Street analysts surveyed by Refinitiv.</p>
<p>The company highlighted that the consumer demand for air travel remains high especially after the reopening of all global markets from the Covid-19 relayed restrictions. Furthermore, the company’s revenue for the June quarter was 19 percent higher than the same time last year.</p>
<p>According to the announcement, the June quarter recorded an operating income of around $2.5 billion with an operating margin of about 17.1 percent. With an operating cash flow of about $2.6 billion and a free cash flow of approximately $1.1 billion, Delta Air Lines announced its adjusted net debt of $19.8 billion at the end of the June quarter.</p>
<p>Delta Air Lines CEO Ed Bastian highlighted that the heightened demand for consumer air travel will continue in the coming years. Reportedly, Trans-Atlantic air travel jumped more than 60 percent from a year ago, compared with an 8 percent increment in domestic revenue and a 21 percent gain in passenger revenue overall.</p>
<h2>Delta Air Lines and the Marker Outlook</h2>
<p>Having recorded a profitable quarter, the company raised its 2023 earnings guidance to $6 &#8211; $7 per share and reiterated its recently updated outlook for $3 billion of free cash flow. For the third quarter, the company anticipates earning $2.20 to $2.50 per share, which is above analysts’ expectations, on a 16 percent increase in capacity.</p>
<p>“If you were to ask any quarter in which we grew capacity by high double digits and we held our overall pricing, that would be pretty amazing,” Bastian <a href="https://news.delta.com/delta-air-lines-announces-june-quarter-2023-financial-results" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>.</p>
<p>Following the announcement of the quarterly earnings, Delta shares gained approximately 2.5 percent on Thursday before retracting. Nonetheless, DAL shares are up approximately 43 percent in the past three months to trade around $47.60. The $30.82 billion valued company has convinced investors of its profitable future outlook. According to a survey conducted by MarketWatch, 21 analysts gave DAL shares an average rating of Buy with a target price of $59.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bnb-chain-hackvolution-growth/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/delta-air-lines-revenue-profitability/">Delta Air Lines Announces Highest Quarterly Revenue and Profitability in Airline&#8217;s History</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/delta-air-lines-revenue-profitability/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>BNB Chain Unveils Hackvolution to Boost Ecosystem Growth</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bnb-chain-hackvolution-growth/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bnb-chain-hackvolution-growth/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Babafemi Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 17:46:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Binance News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bnb]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bnb chain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hackvolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[opbnb]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=262892</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bnb-chain-hackvolution-growth/">BNB Chain Unveils Hackvolution to Boost Ecosystem Growth</a></p>
<p>Developers and users who participate in Hackvolution are contributing to the growthof the BNB chain ecosystem.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bnb-chain-hackvolution-growth/">BNB Chain Unveils Hackvolution to Boost Ecosystem Growth</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bnb-chain-hackvolution-growth/">BNB Chain Unveils Hackvolution to Boost Ecosystem Growth</a></p>

<p>Popular web3 blockchain platform BNB chain has <a href="https://twitter.com/BNBCHAIN/status/1679491954449731587?ref_src=twsrc%5Egoogle%7Ctwcamp%5Eserp%7Ctwgr%5Etweet" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announced</a> a new hackathon event called Hackvolution. The hackathon aims to boost innovation among its developers and users. For this project, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/binance-coin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BNB</a> has support from industry leaders, including COMBO, CyberConnect, and Hooked Protocol. Alibaba Cloud, Google Cloud, and Ultiverse are also in support.</p>
<p>According to Victor Genin, Senior Solution Architect at BNB Chain, the hackathon will allow developers to participate in building a blockchain while earning rewards. He said:</p>
<blockquote>
<p>“We are thrilled to invite participants from all over the world to join us in the BNB Chain Hackvolution.&#8221;</p>
</blockquote>
<h2>How the Hackvolution Will Run</h2>
<p>Hackvolution is expected to run from July 13 to September 1, 2023. As part of the hackathon, interested developers can build or improve decentralized applications (DApps) on the BNB chain. They can use any of two possible tracks: the OPBNB and BNB Greenfield.</p>
<p>The hackathon will showcase the potential of opBNB and BNB Greenfield in the blockchain industry. While projects in the opBNB track will leverage its high performance and low cost, projects in the BNB Greenfield track will leverage its eco-friendliness.</p>
<p>Projects developed will be categorized into Infrastructure, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-decentralized-finance-defi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">DeFi</a>, Gaming, and AI domains to ensure cross-sector innovation.</p>
<h2>Benefits of Participation</h2>
<p>As a reward, 1st place winners of each track will receive a $10000 prize. There will also be a separate $7500 prize pool for winners of the Local Hacker Stars awards among other benefits. other possible benefits include banking bonuses, 1-month trial participation in the BNB Chain Gas Grant program, marketing support, and access to the BNB Chain Kickstart program tools and services.</p>
<p>A panel of judges comprising Web3 media, community, and education sector members will select the winners. The judging criteria will be based on technical innovation, business model, and team configuration.</p>
<p>Again, participants will have access to grants and the Most Valuable Builder (MVB) program incubated under Binance Labs. Asides from the monetary reward, Hackvolution will also provide an opportunity for applicants to learn. Applicants can expect to learn through workshops, webinars, mentorship, documentation, and feedback. The hackathon will also enable participants to enjoy 24/7 tech support, early access to BNB Chain updates and exclusive access to the BNB Chain team network.</p>
<h2>Shaping the Future</h2>
<p>While enjoying the reward, developers and users who participate in Hackvolution are contributing to the growth and expansion of the BNB chain ecosystem. Invariably, it is a win-win for all. The Hackvolution registration is due to begin on July 13, 2023.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-alex-mashinsky-celsius-network/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bnb-chain-hackvolution-growth/">BNB Chain Unveils Hackvolution to Boost Ecosystem Growth</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bnb-chain-hackvolution-growth/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>BREAKING: SEC Sued Alex Mashinsky Former CEO of Bankrupt Crypto Lender Celsius Network</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-alex-mashinsky-celsius-network/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-alex-mashinsky-celsius-network/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 17:44:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alex mashinsky]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[celsius network]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=262964</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-alex-mashinsky-celsius-network/">BREAKING: SEC Sued Alex Mashinsky Former CEO of Bankrupt Crypto Lender Celsius Network</a></p>
<p>The problems with Celsius Network and Mashinsky first surfaced in June of last year when the platform abruptly froze withdrawals, leaving users anxious about the security of their cash.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-alex-mashinsky-celsius-network/">BREAKING: SEC Sued Alex Mashinsky Former CEO of Bankrupt Crypto Lender Celsius Network</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-alex-mashinsky-celsius-network/">BREAKING: SEC Sued Alex Mashinsky Former CEO of Bankrupt Crypto Lender Celsius Network</a></p>
<p>The United States Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) has <a href="https://www.courtlistener.com/docket/67604348/1/securities-and-exchange-commission-v-celsius-network-limited/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">filed</a> a lawsuit against Alex Mashinsky, the former CEO of bankrupt crypto lender Celsius Network. The SEC accused the firm and Mashinsky of securities fraud.</p>
<p>According to a Bloomberg <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-07-13/sec-files-lawsuit-against-celsius-network-alex-mashinsky?utm_source=twitter&amp;utm_medium=social&amp;utm_campaign=socialflow-organic&amp;utm_content=crypto&amp;cmpid=socialflow-twitter-business&amp;in_source=embedded-checkout-banner#xj4y7vzkg" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a>, which cited sources familiar with the matter, Mashinsky was taken into custody after authorities concluded their probe into the events leading to the bankruptcy of Celsius Network last year.</p>
<p>The arrest comes as investigators from the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/cftc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Commodity Futures Trading Commission</a> (CFTC) found Mashinsky guilty of multiple violations of U.S. regulations. The CFTC, responsible for regulating the derivatives markets in the US, determined that the former CEO had engaged in actions that contravened various rules before the implosion of Celsius Network in 2022.</p>
<h2>Celsius Network and Its Regulation Violations</h2>
<p>The news does not come as a surprise as an earlier <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/celsius-ex-ceo-cftc-lawsuit/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">report</a> suggested that Celsius Network and Mashinsky may face a lawsuit from the markets regulator. Investigators at the CFTC have reportedly concluded that the bankrupt crypto lender and its CEO violated crucial regulations by misleading investors.</p>
<p>The recent arrest of Alex Mashinsky, adds another layer of complexity to the situation being faced by the crypto lender. Mashinsky’s arrest comes in the midst of regulatory actions and lawsuits by US regulators against major players in the crypto industry, such as Binance and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase Global Inc</a> (NASDAQ: COIN).</p>
<p>The SEC’s lawsuits against Binance and Coinbase, two of the largest crypto exchanges, demonstrate the regulatory authorities’ increasing focus on enforcing compliance and accountability within the crypto space.  The timing of the lawsuit against Celsius Network and the arrest of Mashinsky suggests a broader trend of heightened scrutiny and regulatory action across the industry. These developments highlight the necessity of transparency and ethical behavior in the blockchain industry.</p>
<p>As the sector evolves, it is becoming increasingly important for businesses and their leaders to prioritize compliance, transparent communication with investors, and adherence to regulatory frameworks among other claims from the SEC.</p>
<h2>The Troubles of Celsius Network</h2>
<p>The problems with Celsius Network and Mashinsky first surfaced in June of last year when the platform abruptly froze withdrawals, leaving users anxious about the security of their cash. This abrupt move set in motion a series of events that would eventually lead to major regulatory attention and the company&#8217;s bankruptcy filing.</p>
<p>In June, securities authorities from five separate states launched an inquiry into Celsius Network, focusing on its operations and regulatory compliance. The investigation sought to shed light on the platform’s actions and assess any potential violations.</p>
<p>Within a month of the investigation’s launch, Celsius Network <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/celsius-files-chapter-11-bankruptcy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">filed</a> for bankruptcy, indicating the severity of its challenges at the time. The bankruptcy filing heightened concerns among users and investors who had entrusted their digital assets to the platform, raising questions about the management and financial stability of the company.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/polygon-upgrade-matic-tokens/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-alex-mashinsky-celsius-network/">BREAKING: SEC Sued Alex Mashinsky Former CEO of Bankrupt Crypto Lender Celsius Network</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-alex-mashinsky-celsius-network/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Polygon Announces Proposal Upgrade for MATIC Tokens</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/polygon-upgrade-matic-tokens/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/polygon-upgrade-matic-tokens/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 14:11:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[matic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[POL]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[polygon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon 2.0]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=262941</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/polygon-upgrade-matic-tokens/">Polygon Announces Proposal Upgrade for MATIC Tokens</a></p>
<p>The proposed POL token is designed to operate seamlessly across all platforms, including Proof of Stake (PoS), zkEVM, and Supernets.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/polygon-upgrade-matic-tokens/">Polygon Announces Proposal Upgrade for MATIC Tokens</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/polygon-upgrade-matic-tokens/">Polygon Announces Proposal Upgrade for MATIC Tokens</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a> scaling solution <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/matic-network/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Polygon</a> has recently unveiled an exciting proposal for a technical upgrade of its native token, MATIC. According to a <a href="https://polygon.technology/blog/polygon-2-0-tokenomics?utm_source=twitter&amp;utm_medium=social&amp;utm_content=token-2.0-blog" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">blog post</a>, the upgrade is a crucial step toward the emergence of Polygon 2.0, a comprehensive outfit aiming to improve the platform&#8217;s scalability, security, and user experience.</p>
<p>Pending community approval, this upgrade would result in the conversion of MATIC into Polygon (POL), a token that can be staked across multiple chains within the Polygon ecosystem. This revolutionary move strives to fulfill the critical demand for scalability while retaining the greatest level of security.</p>
<p>While the specific timing for the migration process will be determined by the Polygon community&#8217;s approval, the team has stated that the migration to POL might begin within a few months.</p>
<p>According to a Polygon spokesperson, the proposed POL token is designed to operate seamlessly across all platforms, including Proof of Stake (PoS), zkEVM, and Supernets. This strategic decision aims to leverage the full potential of the Polygon ecosystem, enabling Polygon validators to secure transactions across different chains within the network.</p>
<h2>The Upgrade Process</h2>
<p>Notably, the upgrade process from MATIC to POL is designed to be straightforward and user-friendly. Token holders will be required to follow a simple procedure to convert their MATIC tokens into POL tokens.</p>
<p>The process involves sending MATIC tokens to a specific smart contract, which will facilitate the conversion and return an equivalent number of POL tokens to the token holder.</p>
<p>To initiate the upgrade, token holders will need to send their MATIC tokens to a specific smart contract. Upon sending their MATIC tokens to the designated smart contract, the smart contract will execute the necessary calculations and verify the transaction. Once the transaction is confirmed, an equivalent number of POL tokens will be sent back to the token holder’s wallet address.</p>
<p>It is advisable to double-check the smart contract address and ensure the transaction is conducted on official platforms or approved channels to avoid any potential scams or fraudulent exploits.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Polygon has proposed a substantial grace period of at least four years for token holders to complete the upgrade process from MATIC to POL. The purpose of the grace period is to ensure a smooth transition for all token holders and allow sufficient time for them to become familiar with the upgrade process.</p>
<h2>Polygon Forms Notable Partnerships</h2>
<p>One of the aspects that contribute to Polygon’s success is its ability to seek collaborations with renowned projects and platforms. By integrating with Polygon, these projects can leverage its scalability solutions and offer improved user experiences.</p>
<p>For example, the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/lets-look-at-polygons-matic-partnerships-and-collaborations-the-force-of-the-alex-the-doge-alex-presale-is-strong/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">partnership</a> between Polygon (MATIC) and Alex The Doge (ALEX) has created new opportunities for the token’s growth and usage. The integration provides ALEX with a solid foundation, enabling it to leverage the network&#8217;s scalability and security features, a trend that Polygon will seek to retain in its alteration and new POL token ecosystem.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/spot-bitcoin-etf-30t-capital/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/polygon-upgrade-matic-tokens/">Polygon Announces Proposal Upgrade for MATIC Tokens</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/polygon-upgrade-matic-tokens/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>BlackRock Spot Bitcoin ETF Could Unlock $30T Worth of Capital</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/spot-bitcoin-etf-30t-capital/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/spot-bitcoin-etf-30t-capital/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mercy Tukiya Mutanya]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 13:53:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funds & ETFs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ark invest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=262928</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/spot-bitcoin-etf-30t-capital/">BlackRock Spot Bitcoin ETF Could Unlock $30T Worth of Capital</a></p>
<p>Over the past decade, the SEC has rejected as many as 30 spot Bitcoin ETF applications from firms such as Gemini, Fidelity, and WisdomTree.    </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/spot-bitcoin-etf-30t-capital/">BlackRock Spot Bitcoin ETF Could Unlock $30T Worth of Capital</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/spot-bitcoin-etf-30t-capital/">BlackRock Spot Bitcoin ETF Could Unlock $30T Worth of Capital</a></p>
<p>Bloomberg ETF analyst Eric Balchunas believes that $30 trillion worth of capital could be made available to the Bitcoin market if a <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> spot exchange-traded fund (ETF) was approved by the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>). That is the estimated amount of assets managed by US financial advisers who would be willing to get exposure to the top cryptocurrency through a regulated ETF.</p>
<p>Speaking in an <a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/blackrock-bitcoin-etf-could-unlock-30-trillion-worth-of-wealth-bloomberg-analyst-says" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">interview with Cointelegraph</a>, the analyst stated that a spot Bitcoin ETF could serve as a bridge between the Bitcoin market and an impressive amount of capital. When asked why the approval of a spot Bitcoin ETF in the United States would be a big deal, Balchunas stated that financial advisors and the older generation of investors prefer their investments delivered in ETF, a format that they are more familiar and comfortable with.</p>
<p>&#8220;ETF is the format in which the boomers and the financial advisors prefer their investments delivered in. And this matters because financial advisors manage about $30 trillion in assets,” he said.</p>
<p>A major talking point in some crypto investment circles, the spot Bitcoin ETF is yet to be approved by the SEC. In fact, over the past decade, the regulator has rejected as many as 30 spot Bitcoin ETF applications from firms such as Gemini, Fidelity, and WisdomTree.</p>
<p>However, Balchunas noted that the odds of approval in the next year have increased to about 50%. He attributed this to the recent filing by BlackRock, stating that the high-level assets manager – which has about $9 trillion in assets under management – is “very smart, and they don&#8217;t just throw filings out willy nilly [&#8230;] They clearly see something out there that they think they can get through the regulators.”</p>
<p>Commenting on when we are next likely to hear from the SEC on a spot Bitcoin application, the analyst stated that it was possible the regulator would make announce its decision on the ARK Invest application – submitted two months before BlackRock’s application – in early January of next year. He added that more decisions would likely be made in March or April.</p>
<p>Balchunas also expressed confidence that spot Bitcoin ETFs, if approved, have the potential to “crush the futures ETFs and assets.” He added that he could see crypto ETFs ultimately reaching the same level as gold ETFs in a matter of years.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/telegram-wallet-in-app-crypto-payment/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/spot-bitcoin-etf-30t-capital/">BlackRock Spot Bitcoin ETF Could Unlock $30T Worth of Capital</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/spot-bitcoin-etf-30t-capital/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Telegram’s Wallet Rolls Out In-App Crypto Payment Options, Offering New Opportunities for Merchants</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/telegram-wallet-in-app-crypto-payment/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/telegram-wallet-in-app-crypto-payment/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 11:50:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[telegram]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ton]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[toncoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[usdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=262916</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/telegram-wallet-in-app-crypto-payment/">Telegram&#8217;s Wallet Rolls Out In-App Crypto Payment Options, Offering New Opportunities for Merchants</a></p>
<p>While certain jurisdictions impose restrictions, Wallet's initiative aims to provide users with a seamless and convenient way to engage in digital asset transactions. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/telegram-wallet-in-app-crypto-payment/">Telegram&#8217;s Wallet Rolls Out In-App Crypto Payment Options, Offering New Opportunities for Merchants</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/telegram-wallet-in-app-crypto-payment/">Telegram&#8217;s Wallet Rolls Out In-App Crypto Payment Options, Offering New Opportunities for Merchants</a></p>
<p>Telegram Messenger, a widely-used social media platform, has recently unveiled an exciting feature that allows merchants to accept cryptocurrency payments directly within the app. The launch of in-app crypto payments brings new opportunities for businesses and expands the range of payment options available to <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/telegram/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Telegram</a> users.</p>
<p>The new payment feature was made possible through Wallet, a Telegram bot developed by independent company to facilitate the buying and selling of digital assets among users on the messaging app.</p>
<p>In an email announcement issued by the company on July 13, the Telegram bot, Wallet has launched a payment solution dubbed Wallet Pay. The new service is based on the Open Network (TON) blockchain, enabling seamless transactions between users and retail businesses within the messaging app.</p>
<h2>New Wallet&#8217;s Payment Services Not Available to Users in Restricted Countries</h2>
<p>A company spokesperson told <a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/telegram-wallet-bot-enables-in-app-payments-in-bitcoin-usdt-and-ton" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Cointelegraph</a> that the payment service is available in different jurisdictions already supported by Wallet, excluding countries under sanctions by the Financial Action Task Force and the United States, as local compliance regulations in these locations dictate whether businesses within these geographical regions can accept crypto payments. Wallet Pay is unavailable in countries like Iran, Myanmar, and North Korea.</p>
<p>While Wallet has collected many requests from merchants interested in implementing the payment feature, the company is yet to implement the Know Your Business (KYB) procedure into its protocol.  As a result, the firm has warned interested merchants to ensure that their local regulations allow them to accept payments in crypto before sending in applications.</p>
<p>&#8220;Businesses should decide if they are allowed to do business within their jurisdiction before applying to use Wallet Pay,&#8221; said the company&#8217;s spokesperson.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s important to note that Wallet operates independently from Telegram and is built on the Telegram Web Apps open protocol. This protocol allows developers to create their own applications and services within the Telegram ecosystem, fostering innovation and expanding the platform&#8217;s functionalities.</p>
<h2>Telegram Merchants Can Now Accept BTC, USDT, and TON for Crypto Payments</h2>
<p>According to Wallet, the new payment feature supports three cryptocurrencies: Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a>), Tether (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/tether/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">USDT</a>) stablecoin, and Toncoin (TON). In March, Telegram <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/telegram-tether-usdt-wallet-bot/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">announced</a> that users can now transfer USDT to each other directly within the app through Wallet Pay.</p>
<p>The bot serves as a payment facilitator and as a custodial wallet, which means it holds users&#8217; funds on their behalf. The platform applies a fee structure ranging from 1% to 3% during the beta period for crypto payments.</p>
<p>Users can access the payment service through the dedicated Wallet bot on Telegram or the official Wallet Pay website. The firm has warned users to exercise caution and ensure the legitimacy of the bot when interacting with it to protect against potential scams or unauthorized sources.</p>
<p>The expansion of crypto payment options within Telegram presents an exciting opportunity for merchants to tap into the growing crypto economy. While certain jurisdictions impose restrictions, Wallet&#8217;s initiative aims to provide users with a seamless and convenient way to engage in digital asset transactions.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-bard-ai-chatbot-eu/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/telegram-wallet-in-app-crypto-payment/">Telegram&#8217;s Wallet Rolls Out In-App Crypto Payment Options, Offering New Opportunities for Merchants</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/telegram-wallet-in-app-crypto-payment/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Google Bard AI Chatbot Launches in EU with Spoken Responses and Visual Prompts</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-bard-ai-chatbot-eu/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-bard-ai-chatbot-eu/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Babafemi Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 11:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chatgpt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Generative AI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[google]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[google bard]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=262823</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-bard-ai-chatbot-eu/">Google Bard AI Chatbot Launches in EU with Spoken Responses and Visual Prompts</a></p>
<p>With its latest expansion into the EU and the addition of new features, Bard is poised to make a significant impact on the way people communicate and interact with technology.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-bard-ai-chatbot-eu/">Google Bard AI Chatbot Launches in EU with Spoken Responses and Visual Prompts</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-bard-ai-chatbot-eu/">Google Bard AI Chatbot Launches in EU with Spoken Responses and Visual Prompts</a></p>

<p>Google has announced that its AI chatbot, Bard, is now available in the EU, with new features to improve user experience.</p>
<h2>Google Bard: New Features and Language Support</h2>
<p>As part of the new features, Bard will now be able to speak its answers out loud. According to the company, spoken responses will be available in more than 40 languages, including Arabic, Spanish, Chinese, German, and Hindi. Further, users will also be able to feed image prompts into the AI chatbot. Google first showed off this feature at its I/O conference in May but has now officially rolled it out.</p>
<p>Again, Google is the ability to pin and rename conversations and share responses with your friends. Likewise, users will be able to select from a number of preset options the tone and style of the responses they want from Bard.</p>
<p>With these new features, Google Bard has significantly improved. This would make it possible for users to interact with the chatbot in a more natural and engaging way. In particular, being able to add image prompts opens up new possibilities for creative expression and communication. Also, the spoken responses will provide a more immersive experience for users.</p>
<h2>Bard&#8217;s Progress in the Generative AI Market</h2>
<p>Google has been accelerating its work on Bard since OpenAI launched the revolutionary ChatGPT. Initially, the chatbot struggled to measure up to rival bots like ChatGPT in its response quality. This led employees to label the chatbot a ‘<a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/4/19/23689554/google-ai-chatbot-bard-employees-criticism-pathological-liar" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">pathological liar</a>’. However, following several iterations, Google allowed early access to Bard stated in March. It soon followed this with a global rollout in about 180 countries in May.</p>
<p>Despite this progress, Google had to pause its plans for the EU. The company postponed the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-postpones-bard-eu/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">rollout of Bard in Europe</a> after the Irish Data Protection Commission (DPC) raised concerns about data privacy. Since then, Google has continued to push forward with its development of Bard, positioning it as a strong contender in the rapidly growing market for generative AI tools. Today’s launch in Europe suggests that Google has been able to address those concerns.</p>
<p>Commenting on this, the company noted that it was “proactively engaged with experts, policymakers and privacy regulators.”</p>
<p>With its latest expansion into the EU and the addition of new features, Bard is poised to make a significant impact on the way people communicate and interact with technology. The chatbot’s new features and language support could also potentially set it apart from other generative AI tools available in the region.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-brokerage-startup-public-uk/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-bard-ai-chatbot-eu/">Google Bard AI Chatbot Launches in EU with Spoken Responses and Visual Prompts</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-bard-ai-chatbot-eu/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>US Brokerage Startup Public Makes Foray in UK</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-brokerage-startup-public-uk/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-brokerage-startup-public-uk/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 11:26:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FinTech News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[etoro]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[revolut]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=262909</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-brokerage-startup-public-uk/">US Brokerage Startup Public Makes Foray in UK</a></p>
<p>Public aims to reduce the overall costs for investors, making its platform more appealing to UK users.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-brokerage-startup-public-uk/">US Brokerage Startup Public Makes Foray in UK</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-brokerage-startup-public-uk/">US Brokerage Startup Public Makes Foray in UK</a></p>
<p>American stock brokerage firm Public has officially launched its services in the United Kingdom, marking its first international expansion since its inception in 2017.</p>
<p>As <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/07/13/us-brokerage-app-public-launches-in-the-uk-in-its-first-foray-overseas.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reported</a> by CNBC, the app backed by notable celebrities including Will Smith and Tony Hawk, aims to provide commission-free trading to UK users, granting them access to over 5,000 US-listed stocks during regular trading hours. In addition, the company aims to introduce other asset classes that are already available in the US, including Exchange-Traded Funds (ETFs), US government bonds, and crypto assets.</p>
<p>Also, the company has stated that it intends to introduce an “investment plans” tool in the future. This tool would allow users to set up customized recurring investments based on their individual financial goals and preferences.</p>
<p>Remarkably, this feature provides convenience and automation, empowering users to develop disciplined investment habits and potentially benefit from the compounding effect over time.</p>
<h2>Public in the UK: The Competitive Advantage</h2>
<p>Public’s debut into the UK market puts it against many well-known digital brokerage businesses, including AJ Bell and Hargreaves Lansdown. These conventional players make money through commissions and management fees, which have been the industry standard for many years.</p>
<p>In addition to these established firms, Public will also face competition from emerging players such as <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/revolut/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Revolut</a>, Freetrade, and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/etoro/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">eToro</a>. These startups have gained traction by offering innovative business models where revenue is derived primarily from subscriptions and other fees rather than traditional commission or charges.</p>
<p>This approach has appealed to a new generation of investors who seek transparency and lower costs. However, Leif Abraham, Public&#8217;s co-CEO, highlighted one key differentiating factor for the company. Abraham emphasized that while many of their competitors in the UK charge currency conversion fees on every trade, Public only applies these fees to the initial deposit, resulting in significantly lower costs for investors.</p>
<p>Notably, Public’s foreign exchange fee structure involves charging 30 basis points, or 0.3%, on each deposit made to convert British pounds into US dollars. By focusing the fee on the initial deposit rather than applying it to every trade, Public aims to reduce the overall costs for investors, making its platform more appealing to UK users.</p>
<h2>Impacts of Tough Market Conditions on Public</h2>
<p>The online brokerage industry has faced challenges recently, with the rising cost of living impacting consumer spending and investment habits. Consequently, consumers may be less eager to devote big sums to brokerage platforms than they were during the Covid-19 pandemic&#8217;s peak.</p>
<p>However, unlike several retail brokerage apps that have had funding challenges as interest rates have risen, Public has not faced comparable issues. Abraham noted that the company has a good cash balance, allowing it to expand into new countries such as the United Kingdom.</p>
<p>Furthermore, Abraham emphasized that Public has no intentions to raise additional capital at this time, as the firm has already received $300 million in funding from major investors such as Accel, Greycroft, and Tiger Global. With a $1.2 billion valuation, Public has attained the coveted “unicorn” status in the startup world.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/steve-hanke-us-inflation/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-brokerage-startup-public-uk/">US Brokerage Startup Public Makes Foray in UK</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-brokerage-startup-public-uk/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Veteran Economist Steve Hanke Suggests that US Inflation Is Now Gone</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/steve-hanke-us-inflation/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/steve-hanke-us-inflation/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 10:33:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cpi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[inflation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[steve hanke]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[united states]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=262863</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/steve-hanke-us-inflation/">Veteran Economist Steve Hanke Suggests that US Inflation Is Now Gone</a></p>
<p>Hanke's commentary follows barely 24 hours after the US inflation rate for June came in lower than expected at 3%.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/steve-hanke-us-inflation/">Veteran Economist Steve Hanke Suggests that US Inflation Is Now Gone</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/steve-hanke-us-inflation/">Veteran Economist Steve Hanke Suggests that US Inflation Is Now Gone</a></p>
<p>Steve Hanke, a highly-revered professor of applied economics at Johns Hopkins University, has shared an expert opinion on inflation in the United States. According to him, inflation, as far as the US is concerned, is now a thing of the past.</p>
<p>The veteran economist shared his view in the early hours of Thursday while <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/07/13/inflation-is-history-for-the-us-johns-hopkins-economist-steve-hanke-.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">speaking</a> on CNBC’s “Street Signs Asia”. He was quoted as saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>“I think the inflation story is history. One reason for that is that money supply has been contracting on a year-over-year basis by minus 4% in the United States.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Hanke also recalled that the last time changes in the money supply happened like that was in 1938. “Money supply changes cause changes in the price index and inflation,” he added.</p>
<p>Hanke&#8217;s commentary follows barely 24 hours after the US inflation rate for June came in lower than expected at 3%. That is, notably, the smallest year-on-year increase in two years. Also, the core consumer price index (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-are-the-consumer-price-index-cpi-and-the-producer-price-index-ppi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CPI</a>), which generally excludes food and energy prices, rose 4.8% in a year, but 0.2% month-on-month.</p>
<p>In his explanation, Hanke revisited how inflation rose, almost simultaneously, with the producer price index and the consumer price index. However, he also pointed out how the core was the slowest to rise at the time.</p>
<p>Similarly, now that policies are proving somewhat effective and the producer price, as well as consumer price indexes, are falling hard, the core lags yet again, he claims.</p>
<p>Nonetheless, Steve Hanke is positive that even the core would eventually come down significantly. But that is as long as policymakers “continue with quantitative tightening”.</p>
<p>As of publication, core inflation is still running well above the Fed’s 2% annual target. But if the Fed sustains its tightening policy, &#8220;it can reach the 2% range pretty fast,” Hanke concluded.</p>
<p>The US producer price index is due later today. And if it also shows prices falling, the Fed may have to end the rate hiking cycle soon.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the CMEFedWatch tool also suggests that traders have a 92.4% expectation that the Fed rates will remain unchanged in the Fed&#8217;s July meeting.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-lawyers-biden-loan-sec/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/steve-hanke-us-inflation/">Veteran Economist Steve Hanke Suggests that US Inflation Is Now Gone</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/steve-hanke-us-inflation/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4125 metric#misses=41 metric#hit-ratio=99.0 metric#bytes=1034198 metric#prefetches=199 metric#store-reads=19 metric#store-writes=2 metric#store-hits=205 metric#store-misses=2 metric#sql-queries=34 metric#ms-total=108.78 metric#ms-cache=5.00 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.2500 metric#ms-cache-ratio=4.6 -->