<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 22:04:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Riot Platforms stock has another 22% upside: HCW analyst</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/buy-riot-platforms-stock-hcw-analyst/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wajeeh Khan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 22:04:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=139622</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Riot Platforms reported strong results for its Q1 last week. HCW analyst raised his PT on Riot Platforms stock today. Mike Colonnese explained his bullish view in a research note. Shares of Riot Platforms Inc have already more than tripled this year but an H.C. Wainwright analyst says further upside will unravel moving forward. Riot [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/buy-riot-platforms-stock-hcw-analyst/">Riot Platforms stock has another 22% upside: HCW analyst</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Riot Platforms reported strong results for its Q1 last week.</li>
<li>HCW analyst raised his PT on Riot Platforms stock today.</li>
<li>Mike Colonnese explained his bullish view in a research note.</li>
</ul>
<p>Shares of Riot Platforms Inc have already more than tripled this year but an H.C. Wainwright analyst says further upside will unravel moving forward.</p>
<h2>Riot Platforms stock has upside to $13.50</h2>
<p>On Monday, Mike Colonnese reiterated his buy rating on the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/bitcoin/">bitcoin</a> miner and raised his price target to $13.50 a share &ndash; up another 22% from here.</p>
<p>His bullish note on Riot Platforms stock arrives only days after the company said a number of its key operating metrics, including hash rate, pushed to a record high in its first quarter.</p>
<blockquote><p>With strong balance sheet and significant runway for future mining expansion, RIOT is well positioned to outpace growth of network hash rate over the next year.</p></blockquote>
<p>Riot sees its aggregate hash rate to climb from 10.5 EH/s in Q1 to 12.5 EH/s in the back half of 2023.</p>
<h2>Riot Platforms revenue was up 22% sequentially</h2>
<p>At $73 million, the Nasdaq-listed firm came in shy of consensus estimates for revenue in its recently concluded quarter.</p>
<p>But the HCW analyst remains constructive on Riot Platforms stock since the revenue still represented a whopping 22% sequential growth. His <a href="https://hcwco.bluematrix.com/sellside/EmailDocViewer?encrypt=b64d6040-8b49-4939-b88d-8a4475c00087&amp;mime=pdf&amp;co=Hcwco&amp;id=jayson.derrick@investoogroup.com&amp;source=mail" target="_blank" rel="noopener">research note</a> also said:</p>
<blockquote><p>A premium is warranted given Riot Platforms&rsquo; industry leading operating capacity, low electricity costs, and strong balance sheet.</p></blockquote>
<p>Other notable figures in the company&rsquo;s <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/riot-platforms-inc-riot-surpasses-000512969.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">earnings release</a> include a 51% year-on-year increase in bitcoin produced and mining margins that more than doubled versus the previous quarter. Note that the bitcoin miner has already touched $13.50 (Mike Colonnese&rsquo;s price target) once this year.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/buy-riot-platforms-stock-hcw-analyst/">Riot Platforms stock has another 22% upside: HCW analyst</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Merov Introduces a Suite of Services for the Bitcoin Mining Industry</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/merov-introduces-a-suite-of-services-for-the-bitcoin-mining-industry/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/merov-introduces-a-suite-of-services-for-the-bitcoin-mining-industry/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire &#160;]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 22:03:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=139625</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Salem, Oregon, May 15th, 2023, Chainwire Merov is proud to announce the launch of its comprehensive suite of services designed for the Bitcoin mining industry. The suite of services includes Merov Hosting, Rejuvit Systems by Merov, and Merov Marketplace, each providing solutions to the needs of the Bitcoin mining industry. &#8220;As a pioneer in the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/merov-introduces-a-suite-of-services-for-the-bitcoin-mining-industry/">Merov Introduces a Suite of Services for the Bitcoin Mining Industry</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Salem, Oregon, May 15th, 2023, Chainwire</strong></p>
<p>Merov is proud to announce the launch of its comprehensive suite of services designed for the Bitcoin mining industry. The suite of services includes Merov Hosting, Rejuvit Systems by Merov, and Merov Marketplace, each providing solutions to the needs of the Bitcoin mining industry.</p>
<p>&ldquo;As a pioneer in the industry, we are excited about the opportunities these services present, and we look forward to continuing to innovate and provide exceptional services to the Bitcoin mining community,&rdquo; said Montana L. Dukes, Founder and Chief Executive Officer of <a href="https://www.merov.io/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><strong>Merov</strong></a>.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" src="https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/brands-pressrelease_1684184700E70DSCPeIE.jpg"></p>
<p><a href="http://hosting.merov.io" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><strong>Merov Hosting</strong></a> offers state-of-the-art colocation facilities designed to provide the highest levels of performance, reliability, and security for Bitcoin miners.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.rejuvit.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><strong>Rejuvit Systems</strong></a> by Merov is a US-based parts distributor and ASIC repair company with high-quality repair, training, and tools at competitive prices.</p>
<p><strong>Merov Marketplace</strong> is an innovative platform that provides due diligence, asset sale, distribution, and procurement services to the Bitcoin mining industry. It is currently in beta testing and will launch in Q3 &lsquo;23.</p>
<p><strong>Milestones Achieved</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>$771.96mm in ASIC mining infrastructure deals closed or currently engaged in.</li>
<li>105,455 ASICs processed through Merov&rsquo;s acquisition, verification, repair, or fulfillment services.</li>
<li>400+ megawatts of colocation capacity becoming available &rsquo;23-&rsquo;24.</li>
</ul>
<h3><span style="font-weight: normal">About Merov:</span></h3>
<p>Merov is a team of passionate and experienced professionals committed to enhancing the Bitcoin industry. With a deep understanding of the industry and a range of expertise in related fields, we strive to deliver innovative, reliable, and comprehensive solutions tailored to our clients&rsquo; needs.</p>
<p>Our mission is to bridge gaps and streamline operations, enabling businesses and individuals to thrive in the rapidly evolving world of Bitcoin. By pushing the boundaries of technology and staying at the forefront of industry developments, we are dedicated to driving growth, fostering innovation, and empowering our clients to reach their full potential.</p>
<p>Follow Merov on <a href="https://t.me/merov_io" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Telegram</a> and <a href="https://twitter.com/merov_io" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Twitter</a>.</p>
<p>Merov is a proud sponsor of the Bitcoin Conference, May 18-20, 2023. Come meet the Merov team at booth 1206.</p>
<p><b>Contact</b></p>
<p>Chief Creative Officer, Rachel Schimelman, Merov, press@merov.io</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/merov-introduces-a-suite-of-services-for-the-bitcoin-mining-industry/">Merov Introduces a Suite of Services for the Bitcoin Mining Industry</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/merov-introduces-a-suite-of-services-for-the-bitcoin-mining-industry/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>US default will see Bitcoin become a more trusted safe haven asset than the dollar, survey says</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/us-default-will-see-bitcoin-become-a-more-trusted-safe-haven-asset-than-the-dollar-survey-says/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/us-default-will-see-bitcoin-become-a-more-trusted-safe-haven-asset-than-the-dollar-survey-says/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 21:20:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Surveys and Reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gold]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/us-default-will-see-bitcoin-become-a-more-trusted-safe-haven-asset-than-the-dollar-survey-says/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Retail investors would prefer Bitcoin over the dollar in case of a default, a new survey says. A US default could be here as early as June 1, experts have warned. Standard Chartered analyst Geoff Kendrick previously predicted a 70% jump for Bitcoin price in case of a US default. A new survey has found [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/us-default-will-see-bitcoin-become-a-more-trusted-safe-haven-asset-than-the-dollar-survey-says/">US default will see Bitcoin become a more trusted safe haven asset than the dollar, survey says</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Retail investors would prefer Bitcoin over the dollar in case of a default, a new survey says.</li>
<li dir="ltr">A US default could be here as early as June 1, experts have warned.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Standard Chartered analyst Geoff Kendrick previously predicted a 70% jump for Bitcoin price in case of a US default.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">A new survey has found that retail investors would prefer to buy <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">Bitcoin (BTC)</a> over the dollar in the event of a US default.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to the <a href="https://markets.businessinsider.com/news/currencies/bitcoin-safe-haven-dollar-gold-us-default-debt-ceiling-crisis-2023-5" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">report</a>, while gold and Treasury&rsquo;s ranked higher on the list of trusted safe haven assets in case of a US default, BTC was seen as the third best asset, ahead of the US dollar.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Retail investors would buy BTC over the dollar</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The results were from a survey conducted by Bloomberg&rsquo;s Markets Live Pulse. The researchers had asked investors to indicate what they would buy were the US government to spiral to a debt ceiling.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/gold/">Gold</a> was the top pick as 51.7% of professional investors and 45.7% of retail investors going for the precious metal. A significant percentage chose Treasurys, with 14% and 15.1% of professionals and retail investors respectively showing faith with the asset class.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Meanwhile, Bitcoin ranked third among the responses as 7.8% of professional investors and 11.3% of retail investors picked it over the dollar. Per the survey, about 7.8% of professional investors and 10.2% of retail investors said they would still buy the dollar.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitcoin price predictions in case of US default</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The US faces a default that could hit as early as 1 June 2023 should lawmakers fail to strike a deal to lift the $31.4 trillion debt limit. Stock investors were on Monday upbeat on a possible deal. However, stocks were mainly weak as reports of no consensus on the cards yet emerged.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin on the other hand remained poised above $27,400 as analysts projected a potential decline to support levels seen last week or lower. However, with the BTC price having rode the banking crisis to break above $31,000, it is possible a default could provide fresh fuel for more gains.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As CoinJournal recently <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-for-2024/">highlighted</a>, this Bitcoin price prediction had been put forth by Standard Chartered analyst Geoff Kendrick. In his prediction, the head of FX research at Standard Chartered said the BTC price could explode by 70% in the event of a default.</p>
<p dir="ltr">While he suggested an initial drop on the day, or two or week, of the default would likely clip bulls by $5k or so, the analyst believes the price of the digital gold could see a new $20,000 leg.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/us-default-will-see-bitcoin-become-a-more-trusted-safe-haven-asset-than-the-dollar-survey-says/">US default will see Bitcoin become a more trusted safe haven asset than the dollar, survey says</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/us-default-will-see-bitcoin-become-a-more-trusted-safe-haven-asset-than-the-dollar-survey-says/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>DigiToads (TOADS) utility sets it apart from Shiba Inu (SHIB) and Pepe (PEPE) amid spike in meme coin interest</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/digitoads-toads-utility-sets-itself-apart-from-shiba-inu-shib-and-pepe-pepe-amid-spike-in-meme-coin-interest/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 16:51:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/digitoads-toads-utility-sets-itself-apart-from-shiba-inu-shib-and-pepe-pepe-amid-spike-in-meme-coin-interest/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>DigiToads is setting itself apart as a unique project in the meme coin ecosystem. Shiba Inu and Pepe remain popular meme tokens, but analysts and market experts see TOADS a a better long term bet. The DigiToads presale is seeing renewed investor interest in its &#8216;Lillypad 5&#8217; stage. Many analysts believe that 2023 is the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/digitoads-toads-utility-sets-itself-apart-from-shiba-inu-shib-and-pepe-pepe-amid-spike-in-meme-coin-interest/">DigiToads (TOADS) utility sets it apart from Shiba Inu (SHIB) and Pepe (PEPE) amid spike in meme coin interest</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">DigiToads is setting itself apart as a unique project in the meme coin ecosystem.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Shiba Inu and Pepe remain popular meme tokens, but analysts and market experts see TOADS a a better long term bet.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The DigiToads presale is seeing renewed investor interest in its &lsquo;Lillypad 5&rsquo; stage.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Many analysts believe that 2023 is the year of meme coins. Several new meme tokens have been launched in recent months, and some of the most popular ones, such as Shiba Inu and Pepe, have soared in value.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Amid this market optimism is the growing attention towards DigiToads, one of the new meme tokens currently in presale. The interest in this Ethereum-based meme token that launched earlier this year has seen multiple analysts and market experts bet big on its potential.</p>
<p dir="ltr">DigiToads has a unique economic design that allows users to generate passive income, and its community-centric approach gives community members a key role in the platform&rsquo;s growth and development.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">DigiToads: A trendsetter in the meme coin sector</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://digitoads.me/cjl" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>DigiToads</u></a> has been developed using a hybrid model that leverages the strength of different cryptocurrencies. So, with one single platform, you can stake NFTs, play Web 3.0 games, enter giveaways, bag prizes, crypto tokens as rewards, trade cryptocurrencies and participate in trading competitions. If you are looking for a <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/a-beginners-guide-to-crypto-advantages-and-risks-of-the-digital-currencies/">cryptocurrency for beginners</a>, DigiToads could be an ideal option as it lets its users figure out which opportunity works for them best.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The platform has developed a native token called TOADS which will facilitate all transactions and financial purposes on the network. Built on the ERC-20 protocol, the DigiToads team will maintain a supplly of 585 million TOADS tokens, with 69.2% of it set aside for the presale and rewards. The DigiToads presale, which will comprise 10 stages, continues to see huge success and is in the fifth stage called &lsquo;Lillypad 5&rsquo;.&nbsp;</p>
<h2>What makes DigiToads unique?</h2>
<p>What makes DigiToads a good crypto to buy is the way it balances gameplay, rewards, and the storyline to create an exciting Web 3.0 game.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In the game, players will face each other in a Metaverse swamp as they try to bag the highest scores in the season. To defeat the enemy, players can seek help from digital creatures called &lsquo;DigiToad&rsquo; who have special abilities. Gamers can also secure training equipment, food, and potions for DigiToads. User pay for both the items as well as the DigiToad using the TOADS tokens.</p>
<p><a href="https://digitoads.me/cjl" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>&gt;&gt; Buy DigiToads Now &lt;&lt;</u></a></p>
<h2>Here&rsquo;s why analysts are bullish on Shiba Inu</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/shiba-inu/">Shiba Inu</a> is among the top crypto coins that have managed to maintain their hold over the market despite being launched years back. The meme coin has rolled out a native token called SHIB which is the main crypto token on the network. It is based on memes inspired by a Japanese breed of dog.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Apart from SHIB, the Shiba Inu team has also launched two other cryptocurrencies &ndash; BONE and LEASH. While BONE is a governance token that helps Shiba Inu community members to participate in the decision-making process, LEASH is an exclusive token for dedicated community members who have been associated with the platform.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Given its popularity, analysts feel that the SHIB token might soar higher in 2023 and they expect it to stay in the bullish zone for now.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Pepe is likely to make further gains</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Pepe is among the tokens touted as being best crypto for beginners in today&rsquo;s market. The project &nbsp;features a user-friendly interface that helps one easily navigate the platform as well as the opportunities that come with investing in the token. The meme coin is inspired by the popular internet cartoon &lsquo;Pepe, the Frog&rsquo; and its native token is PEPE.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The PEPE token is the medium of exchange on the network and has a deflationary model, which means its supply is intentionally kept low to curb fluctuating prices. Another key advantage associated with Pepe is that token holders don&rsquo;t have to pay any transaction fee.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">While the &lsquo;no tax&rsquo; policy has helped Pepe ramp up its reach, the past few weeks have been tough for the meme coin with its price fluctuating wildly over the past few weeks. Despite this, analysts are bullish on PEPE and expect the token to rally again given there&rsquo;s still a sizable number of whales sitting on big positions.</p>
<h2>Conclusion&nbsp;</h2>
<p>While Shiba Inu and Pepe have demonstrated their ability to drive gains in the market, many analysts believe DigiToads has the potential to perform well over the long term. Its dynamic economic framework and multiple utilities can help a community member diversify a portfolio while building a sustained source of passive income.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Predicting token prices over the long term with certainty is not possible. However, looking at DigiToads&rsquo; unique features and strengths, coupled with broader market expectations, experts see the TOADS token as a long term investment with great potential.&nbsp;</p>
<p>If you wish to get more information on DigiToads, visit the project&rsquo;s <a href="https://digitoads.me/cjl" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>website</u></a>. You can also join the presale or join the <a href="https://twitter.com/digitoadsworld" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>community</u></a> to receive regular updates on DigiToads.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/digitoads-toads-utility-sets-itself-apart-from-shiba-inu-shib-and-pepe-pepe-amid-spike-in-meme-coin-interest/">DigiToads (TOADS) utility sets it apart from Shiba Inu (SHIB) and Pepe (PEPE) amid spike in meme coin interest</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>LOVESNOOPY&#8217; Token Lists on MEXC Exchange</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/lovesnoopy-token-lists-on-mexc-exchange/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/lovesnoopy-token-lists-on-mexc-exchange/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire &#160;]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 14:51:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=139575</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Seattle, USA, May 15th, 2023, Chainwire The recent surge of meme coins in the cryptocurrency market is nothing short of a phenomena, as meme coins have taken center stage in the world of cryptocurrencies. Amidst the impressive performance of PEPE, a coin that took the center of the meme coin ecosystem, is a new protagonist [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/lovesnoopy-token-lists-on-mexc-exchange/">LOVESNOOPY&#8217; Token Lists on MEXC Exchange</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Seattle, USA, May 15th, 2023, Chainwire</strong></p>
<p>The recent surge of meme coins in the cryptocurrency market is nothing short of a phenomena, as meme coins have taken center stage in the world of cryptocurrencies. Amidst the impressive performance of PEPE, a coin that took the center of the meme coin ecosystem, is a new protagonist -the beloved original dog character, Snoopy, who has garnered worldwide affection over a long period of time.</p>
<p>Today, the LOVESNOOPY project (<a href="https://www.snoopy.land/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">$LOVESNOOPY</a>) has announced the token will be listed on the MEXC exchange on May 16th of 10:00 UTC.</p>
<p>Right from its launch, $LOVESNOOPY expressed its ambitious goal of worldwide expansion through multilingual support on its website. Next, the $LOVESNOOPY team hired CERTIK to conduct an audit, <a href="https://twitter.com/ilovesnoopy1949/status/1657255202217668609" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">according to their Twitter</a>. In addition, the team will be burning 10% of its total token supply.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" src="https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/LOVESNOOPY_1684152291XuS6TMI4tk.jpg"></p>
<p>With its ambitious goal of world expansion through the power of memes, $LOVESNOOPY aspires to capture the hearts of individuals worldwide, infusing their lives with joy, warmth, and a renewed appreciation for the enduring magic of Snoopy.</p>
<h3>About LOVESNOOPY</h3>
<p>The main utility of <a href="https://www.snoopy.land/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">$LOVESNOOPY</a> is to establish a vibrant and impassioned meme community that we can embrace with all our hearts. LOVESNOOPY&rsquo;s path to global domination is simple! Just enjoy and &lsquo;LOVE SNOOPY&rsquo;! The more people enjoy and LOVE SNOOPY, the more indelible his legacy as a beloved meme will become.</p>
<p>LOVESNOOPY is the source of this content. This Press Release is for informational purposes only. The information does not constitute investment advice or an offer to invest.</p>
<p><strong>Contact</strong></p>
<p>I LOVE SNOOPY team, ilovesnoopy1949@gmail.com</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/lovesnoopy-token-lists-on-mexc-exchange/">LOVESNOOPY&#8217; Token Lists on MEXC Exchange</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/lovesnoopy-token-lists-on-mexc-exchange/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin roundup: active addresses fall, market makers scale back, price softens</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-roundup-active-addresses-fall-market-makers-scale-back-price-softens/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dan Ashmore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 13:57:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-roundup-active-addresses-fall-market-makers-scale-back-price-softens/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key Takeaways Number of addresses containing one Bitcoin or more crosses one million Bitcoin relatively subdued despite trading at 2-month low Two prominent market markers are scaling back activity in the space Active addresses show notable decline in last week &#160; We wrote last week that nearly one million addresses on the Bitcoin network now [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-roundup-active-addresses-fall-market-makers-scale-back-price-softens/">Bitcoin roundup: active addresses fall, market makers scale back, price softens</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2 dir="ltr">Key Takeaways</h2>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Number of addresses containing one Bitcoin or more crosses one million</li>
<li dir="ltr">Bitcoin relatively subdued despite trading at 2-month low</li>
<li dir="ltr">Two prominent market markers are scaling back activity in the space</li>
<li dir="ltr">Active addresses show notable decline in last week</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">We <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/nearly-a-million-addresses-hold-more-than-1-bitcoin-half-the-us-median-salary/"><u>wrote</u></a> last week that nearly one million addresses on the Bitcoin network now contain at least one Bitcoin. That mark has now been passed, as the below chart shows.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/13764910">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">As dramatic as that sounds, it doesn&rsquo;t equate to one million people, as aggregate wallets exist (such as exchange wallets), not to mention the fact that one person often has more than one address.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Looking beyond this quirky threshold, there has not been too much of note occurring in the markets in recent weeks. The market has been somewhat soft, Bitcoin trading at $27,300 as I write this, a two-month low. It is down 7% over the past ten days, but that is not exactly a dramatic decline by Bitcoin&rsquo;s standards.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Looking at activity on the network does show more notable developments, however. The below chart shows a perceptible break downwards when analysing the 7-day exponential moving average (EMA) of active addresses on the network.</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/13764828">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">It is the biggest decline in activity over the last year. It is not immediately obvious what is causing it, but with the 7-day EMA running roughly between 800,000 and 1,000,000 addresses, the fall towards 600,000 does stand out.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Regarding possible catalysts, there has not been much beyond the continued big story of the year: the regulatory crackdown from the US. Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong said the exchange would consider the UAE as an international hub, as the company reels from the punitive measures levelled against the industry in recent times &ndash; including a Wells notice served to Coinbase in March.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Congressman Brad Sherman was the latest lawmaker to slam the industry, making some startling comparisons that haven&rsquo;t exactly gone down well in the industry:</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;Peru is way ahead of us (the US) in cocaine production. China is way ahead of us in organ harvesting. We don&rsquo;t need to keep up on those things and we don&rsquo;t need to keep up on crypto&rdquo;.&nbsp;</em></p>
<p dir="ltr">Regardless of whether you agree or not, the industry is feeling the pinch of this hostile stance in the US. Last week, two prominent crypto market makers, Jane Street and Jump Crypto, announced they were <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-liquidity-falling-as-market-makers-pull-back-from-hostile-us-market/"><u>scaling back</u></a> their market making activity.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This amounts to a blow to markets that are already very thin. Indeed, we have written multiple times what role the thin liquidy has played in Bitcoin&rsquo;s run-up this year. In April, crypto profits, prices all hit their <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-price-volatility-and-profits-are-all-the-highest-since-june-2022-but-why-and-will-it-continue/"><u>highest marks</u></a> since June 2022. But so did volatility, as there has been a dearth of capital in the space ever since Alameda, one of the largest market makers, evaporated amid the FTX crash in November. And that liquidity is only going to get thinner again with the news out of Jane Street and Jump Crypto.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">With thin liquidity comes high volatility, as it takes less capital to move prices. The below chart shows that volatility has fallen off since March, but is still trading above 40% on an annualised basis and up markedly since the start of the year.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/13764971">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">While Bitcoin&rsquo;s price fall from close to $30,000 to where it currently sits at $27,200 is nothing to write home about, the shallow nature of the markets hint that more volatility could be on the way.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-roundup-active-addresses-fall-market-makers-scale-back-price-softens/">Bitcoin roundup: active addresses fall, market makers scale back, price softens</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin price prediction: analyst’s BTC forecast amid bulls attempts to reclaim key area</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-analysts-btc-forecast-amid-bulls-attempts-to-reclaim-key-area/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 13:57:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-analysts-btc-forecast-amid-bulls-attempts-to-reclaim-key-area/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin price has recovered from its dip to $25,800, with price currently above $27,400. BTC could continue to bounce into the $28,000-$30,000 range as broader market sentiment improves. However, an analyst&#8217;s Bitcoin price prediction suggests bad news for BTC if $27,600 becomes new resistance level. The price of Bitcoin as of May 15, 2023 9:50 [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-analysts-btc-forecast-amid-bulls-attempts-to-reclaim-key-area/">Bitcoin price prediction: analyst’s BTC forecast amid bulls attempts to reclaim key area</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Bitcoin price has recovered from its dip to $25,800, with price currently above $27,400.</li>
<li dir="ltr">BTC could continue to bounce into the $28,000-$30,000 range as broader market sentiment improves.</li>
<li dir="ltr">However, an analyst&rsquo;s Bitcoin price prediction suggests bad news for BTC if $27,600 becomes new resistance level.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">The price of <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> as of May 15, 2023 9:50 am ET is $27,405, with BTC up 2% in the past 24 hours. 911.81. While Bitcoin could yet break above a key resistance level and target old support above $28,000, a popular crypto analyst says failing to breach the said supply wall could see the digital gold retreat to a closely watched support level.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Analyst shares Bitcoin price prediction as markets eye new bounce</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The outlook for Bitcoin is however still broadly bullish long term, particularly after the crypto sector navigated the collapse of FTX. The current US regulatory environment remains a key concern for the ecosystem though and this as well as continued correlation with the stock market could prove another wobbly trajectory for crypto prices.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to crypto analyst Rekt Capital, Bitcoin price could dip past the largely anticipated buffer zone at $25,000 if current levels don&rsquo;t hold.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Although the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/stock-markets/">stock market</a> looks poised for gains as investors see a debt limit deal and inflation fears across corporate America easing, a flip in sentiment both in the equities and in crypto could send BTC below $25k.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Rekt thinks the flagship crypto&rsquo;s price could fall to the $20,000 level. He <a href="https://twitter.com/rektcapital/status/1658007738553872386" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">tweeted</a> early Monday as BTC/USD bounced from lows of $25,800:</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>First, #BTC failed to reclaim the $28800 level on the Weekly (orange). And then $BTC Weekly Closed below $27600, failing to hold it as support (black). Turn $27600 into resistance and this could enable further downside into the low $20,000s</em>.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The analyst explained his Bitcoin price prediction further in another <a href="https://twitter.com/rektcapital/status/1657992603122671617">tweet</a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>The problem with this #BTC bounce is that it is occurring after a Weekly Close below black support. Such a 1W close is setting BTC up for more downside especially if this rebound is a relief rally. Reject at $27570 (black) would likely force more downside</em>,&rdquo; he noted.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Below is the analyst&rsquo;s<a href="https://twitter.com/rektcapital/status/1658007738553872386/photo/1" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">&nbsp;<u>chart</u></a> highlighting the price levels, with potential downside wicks beyond the multi-month support line.</p>
<div class="fr-img-space-wrap"><span class="fr-img-caption fr-fic fr-dib fr-draggable" style="width: 700px"><span class="fr-img-wrap">
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/04/15/1684158225785-2cd33c36-f5c7-4a7b-9532-61760b829bf4.jpg" style="width: 700px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="700" height="435"><span class="fr-inner">Bitcoin price prediction on the weekly chart. Source: Rekt Capital on Twitter</span></p>
<p></p></span></span>
<p class="fr-img-space-wrap2">On the upside, the key challenge would be around $28,800. Consolidation is likely between $28k and $30k. Above that lies the supply zone near $33,000.</p>
</div>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-analysts-btc-forecast-amid-bulls-attempts-to-reclaim-key-area/">Bitcoin price prediction: analyst’s BTC forecast amid bulls attempts to reclaim key area</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>AltSignals and Polkadot price outlook as Bitcoin bounces above $27k</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-and-polkadot-price-outlook-as-bitcoin-bounces-above-27k/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 12:33:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-and-polkadot-price-outlook-as-bitcoin-bounces-above-27k/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin (BTC) price has bounced 2% in the past 24 hours to currently trade above $27,400. Polkadot (DOT) price on the other hand is around $5.40 as bulls assess a critical resistance zone.&#160; As the AltSignals (ASI) presale gathers momentum, we look at what the Bitcoin price prediction could mean for ASI and DOT. Bitcoin [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-and-polkadot-price-outlook-as-bitcoin-bounces-above-27k/">AltSignals and Polkadot price outlook as Bitcoin bounces above $27k</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Bitcoin (BTC) price has bounced 2% in the past 24 hours to currently trade above $27,400.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Polkadot (DOT) price on the other hand is around $5.40 as bulls assess a critical resistance zone.&nbsp;</li>
<li dir="ltr">As the AltSignals (ASI) presale gathers momentum, we look at what the Bitcoin price prediction could mean for ASI and DOT.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> bulls might yet reclaim control above $27,000 after pushing from the brink of fresh collapse when prices dipped under $26,000 last Friday (BTC price indeed touched $25,810 on crypto exchange Coinbase).</p>
<p dir="ltr">As analysts remain bullish on bitcoin price, what does the move to reclaim the uptrend mean for the broader crypto market? What about the AltSignals and <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/polkadot/">Polkadot</a> prices?</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitcoin price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr">BTC price is back above $27,000, with bulls having retested resistance above $27,600 in the past 24 hours. The rebound has market experts predicting further resilience for the price of the benchmark cryptocurrency.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The broader expectation is that holding above the $27k level could open up an upside retest of $30k &ndash; a key technical level where an upward breakout could put BTC on the path to new year-to-date highs.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Analysts have suggested Bitcoin could yet go parabolic in 2023 as a new bull cycle takes shape ahead of the upcoming BTC halving.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The important network event is now less than a year away and has historically been bullish for the flagship cryptocurrency. The enthusiasm that could build ahead of the even has the potential to help altcoins tick up too.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">For projects such as Polkadot and AltSignals, a rallying crypto market offers a chance to build momentum.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Polkadot?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Polkadot is a blockchain platform that is leading the new trajectory of interoperability. The protocol connects different blockchains, or parachains, allowing for the development of new use cases as chains easily communicate with each other. In this case, Polkadot allows for such uses as running of smart contracts, data storage and token issuance.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As the world of an interoperable Web3 grows, Polkadot&rsquo;s ecosystem is taking on an even greater outlook as one of the leading blockchain platforms. Interoperability, security and scalability mean the platform is taking on an integral role in the decentralised finance (DeFi) and non-fungible tokens (NFTs) ecosystem.</p>
<p dir="ltr">While there&rsquo;s more likely to come from the team, the potential to revolutionise the blockchain space is already possible with cross-blockchain transfers &ndash; including across Bitcoin and Ethereum.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Polkadot price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The price of DOT, the native Polkadot token is currently $5.40. The token is in the green on the daily timeframe. However, according to data from CoinGecko, DOT/USD is negative in the past week and month. It&rsquo;s also down more than 90% from its all-time high of $54.98 reached on 4 November, 2021.</p>
<p dir="ltr">DOT is poised at a critical support area as shown on the daily chart. The immediate targets for buyers are at the tough resistance line marked by the 50 and 200 MA around $5.87 and $6.10. The downside potential for <a href="https://coinjournal.net/polkadot/price-prediction/">Polkadot price prediction</a> suggests bears can in the short term target the primary support area near $4.22.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is AltSignals?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals launched back in 2017 and has grown its popularity as one of the leading trading signals platform in the world. Since rolling out its services, the platform has provided traders with signals for crypto, stocks and forex &ndash; with a growing degree of accuracy thanks to its AltAlgo indicator.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Now the platform&rsquo;s team is looking to take the trading tool to the next level using artificial intelligence and blockchain technology. The new direction for AltSignals involves taking the already successful AltAlgo system and revamping its capabilities via an AI-powered layer.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">AltSignals&rsquo; new AI-powered platform and ASI token</h2>
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals&rsquo; new AI enabled platform is called ActualizeAI and is set to go live for the public in the coming months.</p>
<p dir="ltr">ActualizeAI integrates the capabilities of machine learning via regression and predictive modelling. It also uses natural language processing via AutoML and natural language API, for an artificial intelligence layer that offers reinforcement learning to the trading algorithm.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The result is more accuracy for predicted price patterns from historical data and market trends, offering traders a chance to apply top signals to trades across any market conditions.</p>
<p dir="ltr">To give traders an opportunity to enjoy the features and more from the AI ecosystem, AltSignals has unveiled a cryptocurrency token with the ticker symbol ASI. The token is currently accessible to investors via the AltSignals presale, available <a href="https://token.altsignals.io/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">here</a>.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">AltSignals price: how high will ASI go during the presale</h2>
<p dir="ltr">ASI currently sits at $0.015 after jumping from $0.012 when the token launched a few weeks ago. With the current stage of the AltSignals presale about to end, the ASI price will increased by 25% $0.01875.</p>
<p dir="ltr">From here, the price of the ASI token is set to increase by another 25% to $0.021 and will have risen to $0.02274 at the end of stage five of the presale. Thereafter, ASI will list on major cryptocurrency exchanges, with the potential to see a massive increase as demand explodes amid the launch of ActualizeAI.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Can ASI token price reach $1 in 2023?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">With the crypto markets&rsquo; volatile nature in perspective, it is not possible to say with certainty where the AltSignals price will be at the end of 2023. However, with the project already a successful business, its possible the impetus within the AI ecosystem &ndash; highlighted <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-attracts-more-investors-even-as-google-goes-all-in-on-ai/">here</a> amid Google&rsquo;s mega move last week &ndash; could propel ASI higher.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The targets of $0.05 and $1 could be achievable in this time frame should the crypto market rally in a new bull cycle catalysed by huge gains for BTC. Building on this momentum could then offer bulls a chance to target the psychological $1.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">On the flipside, a dump in market sentiment, with macroeconomic headwinds prevailing, could see Bitcoin price retreat to lower support levels and trigger a broader slowdown in the altcoin market.</p>
<p dir="ltr">But with ASI largely a bargain at presale prices, investors can still look to tap into the potential gains. The advice is to do your own research and due diligence as you target an investment, noting that various factors can trigger a market sell-off.</p>
<p dir="ltr">If you see ASI as a discount buy at current prices, learn more about the project from the <a href="https://token.altsignals.io/whitepaper.pdf" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">whitepaper</a> or by visiting the <a href="https://token.altsignals.io/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">AltSignals presale page</a>.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-and-polkadot-price-outlook-as-bitcoin-bounces-above-27k/">AltSignals and Polkadot price outlook as Bitcoin bounces above $27k</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>OpenAI CEO reportedly in “advanced talks” for Worldcoin funding</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/openai-ceo-reportedly-in-advanced-talks-for-worldcoin-funding/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/openai-ceo-reportedly-in-advanced-talks-for-worldcoin-funding/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 07:53:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Events]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/openai-ceo-reportedly-in-advanced-talks-for-worldcoin-funding/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Worldcoin aims to &#8220;tackle two problems&#8221; raised by the growing complexity of artificial intelligence. Worldcoin is preparing to launch its blockchain protocol in six weeks after having been operating in beta. Worldcoin recently launched a gas-free crypto wallet. According to a report from The Information, OpenAI CEO Sam Altman, who is also a co-founder of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/openai-ceo-reportedly-in-advanced-talks-for-worldcoin-funding/">OpenAI CEO reportedly in “advanced talks” for Worldcoin funding</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Worldcoin aims to &ldquo;tackle two problems&rdquo; raised by the growing complexity of artificial intelligence.</li>
<li>Worldcoin is preparing to launch its blockchain protocol in six weeks after having been operating in beta.</li>
<li>Worldcoin recently launched a gas-free crypto wallet.</li>
</ul>
<p>According to a <a href="https://www.google.com/url?sa=t&amp;rct=j&amp;q=&amp;esrc=s&amp;source=web&amp;cd=&amp;cad=rja&amp;uact=8&amp;ved=2ahUKEwja98Ssrvb-AhXXt1YBHXKBAMEQFnoECAkQAQ&amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theinformation.com%2Farticles%2Fandreessen-horowitz-khosla-back-worldcoin-in-deal-valuing-tokens-at-3-billion&amp;usg=AOvVaw2ayFBIEG3a48CchOSI_8j2">report</a> from The Information, OpenAI CEO Sam Altman, who is also a co-founder of Worldcoin is in advanced talks to secure $100 million in funding for the Worldcoin project through a private token sale.</p>
<p>Worldcoin was co-founded in 2020 by Altman, Alex Blania, and Max Novendstern. According to the executives, the project aims to &ldquo;tackle two problems&rdquo; raised by the growing complexity of artificial intelligence.</p>
<h2>Preparations for launching Worldcoin blockchain</h2>
<p>Worldcoin launched its own gas-free crypto wallet for verified humans on May 8, 2023. Tiago Sada, a Worldcoin team member, talking to a popular media outlet said that the wallet was launched so &ldquo;there is an alternative wallet that is focused just on simplicity.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Currently, Worldcoin is preparing to launch its blockchain protocol. The team plans to launch the blockchain within the next six weeks.</p>
<p>Besides having a blockchain, Worldcoin also aims at creating a collectively owned and globally distributed cryptocurrency. According to a source familiar with the project, the proposed $100 million funding will be sourced from a mix of new and existing investors.</p>
<p>When Worldcoin was launched, the startup conducted a Series A funding round led by a16z among other investors that included Digital Currency Group, <a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/coinbase/">Coinbase </a>Ventures, former FTX CEO Sam Bankman-Fried, and LinkedIn co-founder Reid Hoffman.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/openai-ceo-reportedly-in-advanced-talks-for-worldcoin-funding/">OpenAI CEO reportedly in “advanced talks” for Worldcoin funding</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/openai-ceo-reportedly-in-advanced-talks-for-worldcoin-funding/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
