<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 14:30:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Binance delisting news plunges SRM, SNM and YFII tokens</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-delisting-news-plunges-srm-snm-and-yfii-tokens/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-delisting-news-plunges-srm-snm-and-yfii-tokens/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 14:30:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto exchange]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-delisting-news-plunges-srm-snm-and-yfii-tokens/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Binance news saw all three altcoins nosedive double-digits. Serum (SRM) was down 29%, Sonm (SNM) shed 58% and DFI.money (YFII) declined by 16% in 24 hours. Trading on all pairs for the tokens will end on August 22, 2023. Serum (SRM), Sonm (SNM) and DFI.money (YFII) are among the biggest losers in the crypto [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-delisting-news-plunges-srm-snm-and-yfii-tokens/">Binance delisting news plunges SRM, SNM and YFII tokens</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">The Binance news saw all three altcoins nosedive double-digits.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Serum (SRM) was down 29%, Sonm (SNM) shed 58% and DFI.money (YFII) declined by 16% in 24 hours.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Trading on all pairs for the tokens will end on August 22, 2023.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/serum/">Serum</a> (SRM), Sonm (SNM) and DFI.money (YFII) are among the biggest losers in the crypto market today. As of writing, SRM, SNM and YFII have all plummeted double-digits.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Binance to delist SRM, SNM and YFII</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/binance/">Binance</a> announced on Tuesday that it will &ldquo;<em>delist and cease trading on all trading pairs</em>&rdquo; for Serum, DFI.Money and Sonm from its platform on August 22. The exchange noted in a notice to customers that the delisting is part of its period review of every listed digital asset.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>When a coin or token no longer meets this standard, or the industry changes, we conduct a more in-depth review and potentially delist it. We believe this best protects all our users</em>,&rdquo; the exchange said in a general <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/support/announcement/binance-will-delist-snm-srm-and-yfii-on-2023-08-22-f43511a4c1d347a8a2dd1efbdd2fe716" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">announcement</a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Although Binance did not specify the reasons for removing support for each of the altcoin, it did cite certain metrics considered during the periodic reviews. These include team commitment, development activity, trading volume and liquidity and network safety with regard to attacks.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Market reaction plunges affected altcoins</h2>
<p dir="ltr">According to data from CoinGecko, Sonm has seen the most declines in its 24-hour performance as it traded 58% down around 9.45 am ET. The token was changing hands for around $0.105392.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Serum has nosedived 29% in the same period to just above $0.05 to see its 7-day returns reach -35% and over 50% in the past 30 days. Serum, a project linked to FTX and Alameda Research, is down 99.6% from its all-time high above $13 hit in September 2021.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Elsewhere, DFI.money, which is a yield farming aggregator forked from yearn.finance, was down 16% in the past 24 hours to trade around $605. YFII has declined by more than 24% in the past month and traded at a level that&rsquo;s more than 93% down from its ATH of $9,251 reached in September 2020.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Declines for the three altcoins come as most of the top 20 assets by market cap continued to trade flat, with Bitcoin constrained below $30k and Ethereum unable to breach $1,900.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-delisting-news-plunges-srm-snm-and-yfii-tokens/">Binance delisting news plunges SRM, SNM and YFII tokens</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-delisting-news-plunges-srm-snm-and-yfii-tokens/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>THORChain (RUNE) up 65%: here&#8217;s why the token is rising</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/thorchain-rune-up-65-heres-why-the-token-is-rising/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 12:52:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bull run]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[THORChain News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/thorchain-rune-up-65-heres-why-the-token-is-rising/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THORChain (RUNE) token price has gained 65% over the past week and 53% over the past month. There has been a significant surge in social volume around THORChain. The social volume is driving notable attention toward the cross-chain liquidity protocol. Although the price of THORChain (RUNE) is still down 10% from its start of the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/thorchain-rune-up-65-heres-why-the-token-is-rising/">THORChain (RUNE) up 65%: here&#8217;s why the token is rising</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>THORChain (RUNE) token price has gained 65% over the past week and 53% over the past month.</li>
<li>There has been a significant surge in social volume around THORChain.</li>
<li>The social volume is driving notable attention toward the cross-chain liquidity protocol.</li>
</ul>
<p>Although the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/thorchain/">price of THORChain (RUNE)</a> is still down 10% from its start of the year price, the token has been on a strong bullish trend since the beginning of August. It has risen by 68% since August 1, pushing the price from around $0.92 to the current price of $1.55.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/07/15/1692090659788-d5334d29-4591-45da-ab37-d960e0370988.jpg" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="615" height="435"></p>
<p>While some are super excited with RUNE&rsquo;s upward trajectory, some are sceptical that the token could experience a pullback seeing that the rise has been so sharp. To fully understand how far the token could rise and the possibilities of a pullback, we shall delve into the factors pushing the price up.</p>
<h2>Why THORChain (RUNE) price is rising</h2>
<p>According to data on Santiment, the THORChain price surge is fueled by a surge in social volume. According to the data, RUNE&rsquo;s social volume increased by 4,300% between August 7 and August 13, driving significant attention toward the THORChain protocol and its native token.</p>
<p>In addition, THORChain&rsquo;s positive investor sentiment also grew 6,100% within the same timeline. This further caused RUNE&rsquo;s trading volume to spike as more investors jumped in.</p>
<p>THORChain, which is a cross-chain liquidity protocol, in April, partnered with the web3 company Unizen to allow users to swap their <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/what-is-ethereum/">Ethereum (ETH)</a> and Avalanche (AVAX) for <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/what-is-bitcoin/">Bitcoin (BTC)</a> while also permitting users to store assets on different chains. This has been a great driver of the increased activity in the THORChain ecosystem.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/thorchain-rune-up-65-heres-why-the-token-is-rising/">THORChain (RUNE) up 65%: here&#8217;s why the token is rising</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>ApeCoin, Oasis Network, Injective prepare for token unlocks</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/apecoin-oasis-network-injective-prepare-for-token-unlocks/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/apecoin-oasis-network-injective-prepare-for-token-unlocks/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 12:16:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/apecoin-oasis-network-injective-prepare-for-token-unlocks/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>ApeCoin will unlock tokens worth over $31.4 million this week. Oasis Network will also unlock tokens worth over $8 million. Injective will also release more tokens this week. Some of the most popular cryptocurrencies are having their token unlock events this week. The Sandbox unlocked millions of tokens, leading to a major dilution among holders. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/apecoin-oasis-network-injective-prepare-for-token-unlocks/">ApeCoin, Oasis Network, Injective prepare for token unlocks</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">ApeCoin will unlock tokens worth over $31.4 million this week.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Oasis Network will also unlock tokens worth over $8 million.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Injective will also release more tokens this week.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Some of the most popular cryptocurrencies are having their token unlock events this week. The Sandbox unlocked millions of tokens, leading to a major dilution among holders. This dilution, helped push the SAND token to the lowest level since June.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to TokenUnlocks, ApeCoin, Oasis Network, and&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/injective/"><u>Injective</u></a> will flood the market with additional tokens this week. ApeCoin, the native token by Bored Ape Yacht Club (BAYC), will release additional 15.6 million tokens on Wednesday.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">These tokens represent about 4.3% of the total circulating supply and will be worth $31.5 million. Most of them will go to Treasury followed by Yuga Labs, Yuga Labs founder, and launch contributors. The last ApeCoin token unlock will happen in June 26th.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/apecoin"><u>ApeCoin&rsquo;s</u></a> token unlock will come at difficult for the ecosystem as demand for BAYC prices retreat. Its price has plunged by over 68% from the highest level this year.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/oasis-network/"><u>Oasis Network</u></a>, a smart chain platform, will unlock additional ROSE tokens worth over $8&nbsp;<a href="https://token.unlocks.app/oasis-network"><u>million</u></a>. Its last token sale happened in May 18th when the developers unlocked 199.50 million tokens. These tokens will go to partners and reserve, core contributors, and the community. The last token unlock will happen in February 2031.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The last major token unlock will be Injective, the DeFi-focused blockchain backed by Mark Cuban. Injective will release tokens&nbsp;<a href="https://token.unlocks.app/injective-protocol"><u>worth</u></a> over $20 million on Sunday, with most of them going to the ecosystem developers. Injective&rsquo;s final vesting will happen in April 2024.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In most cases, token unlocks tend to be bearish for cryptocurrencies since they lead to more dilution. They are often seen as the reversal of share buybacks in the corporate sector.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy ApeCoin</h2>
<p dir="ltr">
        </p><div class="relative">

            <div class="mb-3  pb-6  px-6  bg-slate-50  rounded-xl  ps-shadow-inner">

    <h3 class="inline-block">
        eToro    </h3>

            <p class="text-sm">eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>
    
    <div class="w-full  flex  flex-wrap  items-start  flex-col  gap-2">

        
<a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=MTQ5Nzcx&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="nofollow sponsored noopener" target="_self" class="inline-block  text-indigo-600  underline  hover:text-indigo-200  ease-in-out  duration-300  transition-all" title="Buy APE with eToro today">Buy APE with eToro today</a>

    </div>

</div><div class="  pb-6  px-6  bg-slate-50  rounded-xl  ps-shadow-inner">

    <h3 class="inline-block">
        Public    </h3>

            <p class="text-sm">Public is an investing platform that allows you to invest stocks, ETFs, crypto, and alternative assets like fine art and collectibles&mdash;all in one place.</p>
    
    <div class="w-full  flex  flex-wrap  items-start  flex-col  gap-2">

        
<a href="/visit/public-crypto?guid=MTQ5Nzcx&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="nofollow sponsored noopener" target="_self" class="inline-block  text-indigo-600  underline  hover:text-indigo-200  ease-in-out  duration-300  transition-all" title="Buy APE with Public today">Buy APE with Public today</a>

    </div>

</div>
        </div>



<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/apecoin-oasis-network-injective-prepare-for-token-unlocks/">ApeCoin, Oasis Network, Injective prepare for token unlocks</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/apecoin-oasis-network-injective-prepare-for-token-unlocks/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Logan Paul faces backlash after $1M bet proposal</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/logan-paul-faces-backlash-after-1m-bet-proposal/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/logan-paul-faces-backlash-after-1m-bet-proposal/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 11:50:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sport]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/logan-paul-faces-backlash-after-1m-bet-proposal/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Logan Paul will face Dillon Danis in a bocxing match on October 14. Paul, a social media personality and WWE star, is willing to bet $1 million he will win. The bet has attracted widespread criticism. Meanwhile, decentralised betting platform Chancer has raised over $1.3 million in presale. YouTuber and WWE personality Logan Paul is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/logan-paul-faces-backlash-after-1m-bet-proposal/">Logan Paul faces backlash after $1M bet proposal</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Logan Paul will face Dillon Danis in a bocxing match on October 14.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Paul, a social media personality and WWE star, is willing to bet $1 million he will win. The bet has attracted widespread criticism.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Meanwhile, decentralised betting platform Chancer has raised over $1.3 million in presale.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">YouTuber and WWE personality Logan Paul is buzzing for his next event &ndash; a boxing bout against Brazilian Dillon Danis. The match is set for October 14 in Manchester, England. Paul, whose YouTube fame has catapulted him into lucrative deals in combat sports, is confident he will beat Danis and is willing to bet $1 million on it.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The bet proposal has been heavily criticised across crypto &ndash; we tell you why and explain why legit bets such as Logan Paul&rsquo;s could find a home on a new <a href="https://coinjournal.net/learn/what-is-blockchain/">blockchain</a>-based betting platform called <a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news"><u>Chancer</u></a>.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Logan Paul&rsquo;s $1 million bet &ndash; what&rsquo;s the criticism?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">28-year old Logan Paul has had some high-profile matchups, including an exhibition bout against Floyd Mayweather. His appearances on WWE have also been great shows.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Now he&rsquo;s hyping up his upcoming boxing match against Dania, a 29-year old jiu-jitsu black belt holder and trainee of former UFC champion Conor McGregor.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Paul is confident he will beat the Brazilian and has proposed a $1 million bet with McGregor.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">You guarantee a win? I&rsquo;ll bet you $1,000,000 I beat Dildo Danis on October 14 <a href="https://twitter.com/TheNotoriousMMA?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@TheNotoriousMMA</a> <a href="https://t.co/cktDrH6jWa">pic.twitter.com/cktDrH6jWa</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Logan Paul (@LoganPaul) <a href="https://twitter.com/LoganPaul/status/1691164336952111104?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 14, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">The move has been heavily criticised across the crypto community, with many criticising the social media personality for considering such a bet when he hasn&rsquo;t followed through with a promise to reimburse victims of his CryptoZoo (ZOO) project.</p>
<p dir="ltr">CryptoZoo launched in 2021, promising a cryptocurrency game powered by the ZOO token and NFTs. The project rallied (<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/where-to-buy-cryptozoo-zoo-jumps-109-as-nft-games-rise-up/">read more here</a>) as NFTs exploded onto the scene during the bull market. However it has largely failed to live up to projections and Paul <a href="https://www.bbc.com/news/technology-64210289" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">said</a> earlier this year that he&rsquo;d make it right with the affected investors.</p>
<p dir="ltr">That hasn&rsquo;t happened yet and the latest events where he&rsquo;s willing to bet $1 million on a match&rsquo;s outcome has left many unamused. Shouldn&rsquo;t he be using that money to refund CryptoZoo NFT buyers? Danis himself had a go at Paul via a post on X (fka Twitter).</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Bro has the money to bet $1 million but can't pay off the people he scammed, that's crazy &#128514; <a href="https://t.co/icaMQKljB5">https://t.co/icaMQKljB5</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Dillon Danis (@dillondanis) <a href="https://twitter.com/dillondanis/status/1691205553614098432?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 14, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">While Logan Paul comes under fire for his crypto &ldquo;scam&rdquo;, the one thing that one can take from his bet proposal is that betting is here to stay. And so is crypto and, likely, the new betting project Chancer.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What&rsquo;s unique about Chancer?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The gambling and betting sector is one major global industry, currently projected to grow double figures annually for the next ten years. Traditional bookmakers will no doubt see this growth. But investors are taking note of a potential game-changer for the whole industry &ndash; Chancer?</p>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer is an online betting platform built on blockchain and offering a revolutionary model that could transform betting for millions of people. This is because unlike centralised betting companies, Chancer will allow users to create their own bets on thousands of events, from mainstream sports, esports, and entertainment and so on.</p>
<p dir="ltr">On Chancer, users can set their own odds and play by their own rules, including live streaming bets to invite others from across the globe to join. The peer-to-peer platform could therefore grow into the leading decentralised social betting platform in the world.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Learn more about how Chancer works <a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news"><u>here</u></a>.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Global investors flock to Chancer, over 31 million tokens sold in weeks</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer is looking to disrupt an $80 billion global gambling industry with its new blockchain-based betting platform. Investors have taken note of the potential for the project&rsquo;s revolutionary offering and are aggressively allocating funds to help bring it to the market.</p>
<p dir="ltr">That sentiment is what&rsquo;s likely behind the huge interest in the native $CHANCER token, whose presale has been one of the few highlights of an otherwise dull summer for crypto. So far, investors have scooped more than 31 million $CHANCER tokens, helping to raise over $1.3 million.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The presale currently has $CHANCER tokens priced at $0.011 and investors can buy with ETH, BNB, USDT and BUSD.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/logan-paul-faces-backlash-after-1m-bet-proposal/">Logan Paul faces backlash after $1M bet proposal</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/logan-paul-faces-backlash-after-1m-bet-proposal/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>New Zealand crypto exchange Dasset faces liquidation, customer funds trapped</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/new-zealand-crypto-exchange-dasset-faces-liquidation-customer-funds-trapped/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/new-zealand-crypto-exchange-dasset-faces-liquidation-customer-funds-trapped/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 10:07:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[New Zealand]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/new-zealand-crypto-exchange-dasset-faces-liquidation-customer-funds-trapped/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways Crypto exchange Dasset has denied customer access to funds.&#160; The New Zealand-based crypto exchange has gone into liquidation.&#160; Dasset denies customers access to funds Auckland-based crypto exchange Dasset has denied customers access to their funds as it faces liquidation. This is according to a&#160;report by The Herald earlier today.&#160; According to the report, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/new-zealand-crypto-exchange-dasset-faces-liquidation-customer-funds-trapped/">New Zealand crypto exchange Dasset faces liquidation, customer funds trapped</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Crypto exchange Dasset has denied customer access to funds.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The New Zealand-based crypto exchange has gone into liquidation.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr">Dasset denies customers access to funds</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Auckland-based crypto exchange Dasset has denied customers access to their funds as it faces liquidation. This is according to a&nbsp;<a href="https://www.nzherald.co.nz/business/customers-desperate-as-auckland-based-crypto-exchange-dasset-denies-access-to-their-funds/DNBZVIJTLFHJREG4KD3YOKUDTU/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>report by The Herald</u></a> earlier today.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to the report, some customers have tens of thousands of dollars worth of crypto trapped on the platform.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">A customer told The Herald that they had been trying to withdraw $40,000 &mdash; their entire life savings &mdash; from their Dasset account for three months. However, their attempts had been unsuccessful.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Another customer revealed that had been direct-credited by the company&rsquo;s CEO, Stephen Macaskill. However, they were still unable to access the funds in their account.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The CEO said the company has been unable to find a replacement banking provider after losing its previous provider earlier this year. He added that Dasset has gone into voluntary liquidation, and the company has appointed a liquidator.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, a liquidator hasn&rsquo;t been approved, and the customers are still unable to access their funds.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Dasset still accepting new users</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The cryptocurrency exchange is still accepting new users despite a halt in withdrawals.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The company has removed email addresses and phone numbers from their website. However, a request form is still available.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Dasset is the latest in a long line of cryptocurrency exchanges to face financial challenges. Last year, FTX, one of the leading crypto exchanges at the time, filed for bankruptcy following some financial mismanagement by the CEO and other executives.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Auckland-based Dasset exchange was launched in 2017. However, compared to Binance, which was launched around the same period, Dasset remains a relatively small cryptocurrency exchange.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/new-zealand-crypto-exchange-dasset-faces-liquidation-customer-funds-trapped/">New Zealand crypto exchange Dasset faces liquidation, customer funds trapped</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/new-zealand-crypto-exchange-dasset-faces-liquidation-customer-funds-trapped/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance seeks court&#8217;s protection against US SEC&#8217;s probe</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-seeks-courts-protection-against-us-secs-probe/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-seeks-courts-protection-against-us-secs-probe/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 07:54:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-seeks-courts-protection-against-us-secs-probe/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The US SEC charged Binance for offering unregistered securities in the United States. The SEC then went ahead to seek for the freezing of Binance.US assets although the two later reached an agreement. Binance.US is now complaining that the SEC is overstepping its mandate according to the agreement. Binance.US, the US subsidiary of Binance, has [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-seeks-courts-protection-against-us-secs-probe/">Binance seeks court&#8217;s protection against US SEC&#8217;s probe</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>The US SEC charged Binance for offering unregistered securities in the United States.</li>
<li>The SEC then went ahead to seek for the freezing of Binance.US assets although the two later reached an agreement.</li>
<li>Binance.US is now complaining that the SEC is overstepping its mandate according to the agreement.</li>
</ul>
<p>Binance.US, the US subsidiary of <a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/binance/">Binance</a>, has filed to limit the extent of investigations by the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) in its case against the cryptocurrency exchange.</p>
<p>The <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-sec-is-seeking-court-order-to-freeze-binance-uss-assets/">SEC attempted to freeze all of Binance.US&rsquo;s assets</a> in June after expressing worries about the security of clients&rsquo; digital assets owned by the company. However, the US arm of Binance, doing business as BAM Trading Services and BAM Management US Holdings, entered into an agreement with the SEC as a result.</p>
<p>The agreement, which some commentators referred to as &ldquo;burdensome&rdquo; gave the SEC permission to conduct &ldquo;limited expedited discovery&rdquo; about the custody and accessibility of client funds.</p>
<h2>SEC&rsquo;s investigations into Binance.US</h2>
<p>Binance in a late <a href="https://www.courtlistener.com/docket/67474542/95/securities-and-exchange-commission-v-binance-holdings-limited/">Monday filing</a> claimed that the SEC&rsquo;s discovery demands have exceeded the parameters set forth in the consent agreement and constitute an improper &ldquo;fishing expedition.&rdquo;</p>
<p>In particular, Binance.US asserts that the SEC is requesting lengthy correspondence and deposition evidence from firm executives on &ldquo;dozens of topics&rdquo; irrelevant to client assets, including its CEO and CFO, who the filing argues have no understanding of the custody concerns at the heart of the matter.</p>
<p>Binance&rsquo;s request states that the company &ldquo;worked in good faith to respond to the SEC&rsquo;s requests&rdquo; by supplying hundreds of documents, providing depositions from staff members knowledgeable about asset security, and taking actions to guarantee assets are in US custody.</p>
<p>The crypto exchange, in its protective request to the court, argues that despite years of investigation by the SEC and all the provided information, &ldquo;the SEC still has not identified the slightest evidence that customer assets have been misused or mishandled in any way.&rdquo; It also opposes deposing top executives like the CEO and CFO stating that that would be unproductive, unduly burdensome, and disruptive to operations.</p>
<p>The crypto exchange suggests that the SEC should first investigate employees responsible for asset custody since they are the ones with &ldquo;far deeper knowledge&rdquo; about digital asset custody.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-seeks-courts-protection-against-us-secs-probe/">Binance seeks court&#8217;s protection against US SEC&#8217;s probe</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-seeks-courts-protection-against-us-secs-probe/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu, Bone prices outperform as Shiba Memu token sale thrives</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-bone-prices-outperform-as-shiba-memu-token-sale-thrives/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-bone-prices-outperform-as-shiba-memu-token-sale-thrives/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 20:09:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-bone-prices-outperform-as-shiba-memu-token-sale-thrives/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Shiba Inu and Bone Shibaswap have outperformed BTC and ETH. They have all jumped by over 68% and 115% from the lowest level in June. Shiba Memu has raised almost $2 million from investors. Meme coins are doing relatively well, with some outperforming popular cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin and Ethereum.&#160;Shiba Inu price has jumped by over [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-bone-prices-outperform-as-shiba-memu-token-sale-thrives/">Shiba Inu, Bone prices outperform as Shiba Memu token sale thrives</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Inu and Bone Shibaswap have outperformed BTC and ETH.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">They have all jumped by over 68% and 115% from the lowest level in June.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu has raised almost $2 million from investors.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Meme coins are doing relatively well, with some outperforming popular cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin and Ethereum.&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/shiba-inu"><u>Shiba Inu</u></a> price has jumped by over 68% from the lowest level in July while Bone Shibaswap has surged by over 115% in the same period. Large-cap coins like BTC and ETH, on the other hand, have remained in a tight range while drifting downwards.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Shibarium launch ahead&nbsp;</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Inu and Bone Shibaswap prices have done well in the past few weeks as investors wait for the upcoming&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/how-could-shibarium-laer-2-solution-unlock-shib-value/"><u>Shibarium launch</u></a>. Shibarium is an important technology that is designed to change how the Shibaswap ecosystem works.</p>
<p dir="ltr">For starters, ShibaSwap is a platform in Shiba Inu&rsquo;s ecosystem that makes it possible for people to swap tokens and make money by staking. It is now powered by Ethereum, the biggest chain in the world.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Ethereum has its own challenges, which explains why many layer-1 and layer-2 alternatives have come up. Some of the top L2 networks seeking to supercharge its ecosystem are Polygon, Optimism, and Arbitrum.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Shiabarium will be a layer-2 network whose goal will be to supecharge Shibaswap&rsquo;s ecosystem by reducing its transaction fees and boosting its speed. Its testnet has attracted thousands of users and there is hope that the mainnet will be better.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Shibarium&rsquo;s success will be a testament that a meme coin can create an ecosystem and thrive.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Shiba Memu token sale booms</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Bone Shibaswap and Shiba Inu are not the only meme coins that are thriving.&nbsp;<a href="https://shibamemu.com/"><u>Shiba Memu</u></a>, a new meme coin is taking shape as its token sale has raised almost $2 million from investors. This makes its token sale one of the most successful in the industry.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu is aiming to take advantage of some of the most important themes in the market this year. It is combining the ongoing meme coin craze and the one on artificicial intelligence.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Its AI angle will involve concepts like Natural Language Processing (NLP), sentiment analysis, and image and video recognition. In its&nbsp;<a href="https://shibamemu.com/whitepaper.pdf"><u>white paper</u></a>, Shiba Memu says this about the use of NLP:</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;AI-powered NLP algorithms can be used to analyze social media posts, forums and other online communities in order to identify discussions and topics relevant to Shiba Memu. This information can then be used to develop targeted marketing campaigns and engage with potential investors. Sentiment Analysis&rdquo;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Is Shiba Memu a good investment?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">It is too early to determine whether Shiba Memu will be a good long-term investment. As a result, you should do your own research about the ecosystem before investing. In my view, I believe that the token has the potential to become the next big thing in the crypto industry.</p>
<p>For one, its name has a close resemblance to Shiba Inu, the biggest meme coin in the world. Also, it has already gained traction even before its public debut as evidenced by the amount of money it has raised in a month. Most mportantly, it is targeting the biggest themes this year. You can buy the Shiba Memu token&nbsp;<a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news"><u>here</u></a>.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-bone-prices-outperform-as-shiba-memu-token-sale-thrives/">Shiba Inu, Bone prices outperform as Shiba Memu token sale thrives</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-bone-prices-outperform-as-shiba-memu-token-sale-thrives/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase enters the Canadian market with Coinbase One, free 30-day trial</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-enters-the-canadian-market-with-coinbase-one-free-30-day-trial/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-enters-the-canadian-market-with-coinbase-one-free-30-day-trial/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 17:50:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Canada]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto exchange]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-enters-the-canadian-market-with-coinbase-one-free-30-day-trial/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Coinbase is seeking to expand into Canada as it faces tough times at home. Coinbase launched an Ethereum layer-2 network last week. It is worth noting that a number of crypto exchanges have excited Canada in the recent past citing poor crypto environment. Coinbase cryptocurrency exchange is extending its already solid grasp on the North [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-enters-the-canadian-market-with-coinbase-one-free-30-day-trial/">Coinbase enters the Canadian market with Coinbase One, free 30-day trial</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Coinbase is seeking to expand into Canada as it faces tough times at home.</li>
<li>Coinbase launched an Ethereum layer-2 network last week.</li>
<li>It is worth noting that a number of crypto exchanges have excited Canada in the recent past citing poor crypto environment.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/coinbase/">Coinbase cryptocurrency exchange</a> is extending its already solid grasp on the North American market by expanding into Canada.</p>
<p>Coinbase will also provide Canadian citizens with a free 30-day trial of its recently established subscription service Coinbase One in an effort to attract new consumers. Coinbase One emphasizes staking and offers free trading and top-notch customer care.</p>
<h2>Canadian crypto market</h2>
<p>According to Coinbase&rsquo;s statement, the crypto exchange chose Canada as its new home because of the country&rsquo;s supposed high level of &ldquo;crypto-awareness&rdquo; and solid regulatory environment. This stands in stark contrast to the legal problems the company is currently facing domestically.</p>
<p>After the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-sec-strikes-again-first-binance-now-coinbase/">US Securities and Exchanges Commission (SEC) sued the exchange</a> for allegedly failing to register as a securities exchange while allegedly providing unregistered securities to its users, Coinbase has felt the heat from American regulators.</p>
<p>A group of thirty Canadian parliamentarians made international headlines in late June when they released a study backing cryptocurrencies and blockchain technology, along with 16 recommendations for the government of the nation to develop a national strategy on the subject.</p>
<p>However, despite the research, Canadian authorities have given conflicting signals on cryptocurrencies and many crypto businesses have stopped operating in the country or have withdrawn. Binance, the largest cryptocurrency exchange in the world by trading volume was the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-announces-exit-from-canada/">latest to exit Canada</a>.</p>
<p>Justin Trudeau, the prime minister of Canada, harshly criticizes opposition figures who support cryptocurrency.</p>
<h2>Coinbase feels the heat of the bear market</h2>
<p>The expansion into Canada comes at a time when Coinbase, the world&rsquo;s second-largest exchange by trading volume, is suffering from the effects of a long-lasting bear crypto market. The exchange reported a $96 million loss for the second quarter despite its financial results exceeding expectations.</p>
<p><a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbases-base-mainnet-featuring-100-dapps-opens-to-the-general-public/">Coinbase opened Base</a>, an <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/what-is-ethereum/">Ethereum </a>layer-2 network, to the general public late last week in an effort to promote the creation of fresh decentralized applications within its ecosystem. Immediately after its launch, Base took off and quickly rose to the top five layer-2 networks by the quantity of bridged traffic.</p>
<p>The exchange has also been investigating how to incorporate Lightning Network, a layer-2 scalability solution for <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/what-is-bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a>.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-enters-the-canadian-market-with-coinbase-one-free-30-day-trial/">Coinbase enters the Canadian market with Coinbase One, free 30-day trial</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-enters-the-canadian-market-with-coinbase-one-free-30-day-trial/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin address with 1,005 BTC suddenly wakes up after nearly 13 years</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-address-with-1005-btc-suddenly-wakes-up-after-nearly-13-years/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-address-with-1005-btc-suddenly-wakes-up-after-nearly-13-years/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 17:12:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin whales]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wallets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-address-with-1005-btc-suddenly-wakes-up-after-nearly-13-years/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Bitcoin address with 1,005 BTC activated 12+ years later, shifts more than $29 million. Wallet speculated to be from a miner who mined a lot in 2010. Bitcoin price remains largely flat above $29k. According to Whale Alert, the blockchain tracker and analytics system that provides regular updates of large coin transactions, another dormant [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-address-with-1005-btc-suddenly-wakes-up-after-nearly-13-years/">Bitcoin address with 1,005 BTC suddenly wakes up after nearly 13 years</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">A Bitcoin address with 1,005 BTC activated 12+ years later, shifts more than $29 million.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Wallet speculated to be from a miner who mined a lot in 2010.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Bitcoin price remains largely flat above $29k.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">According to Whale Alert, the blockchain tracker and analytics system that provides regular updates of large coin transactions, another dormant <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> address has just woken up.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin that has remained dormant for a significant period waking up suddenly when being transferred has often been subject to market speculation regarding the intention of the hodler. Whale transactions such as these often see jitters hit traders afraid of a major dump, and that is the case even as this particular <a href="https://coinjournal.net/wallets/">wallet</a> moved coins not touched for nearly 13 years.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Per the details shared today around 12 pm ET, the said dormant address holds 1,005 bitcoin (BTC), whose market value at current prices is about $29,750,772. The wallet &ldquo;has just been activated after 12.8 years.&rdquo; Whale Alert posted on X:</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">&#128164; &#128164; &#128164;  A dormant address containing 1,005 <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/BTC?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#BTC</a> (29,750,772 USD) has just been activated after 12.8 years!<a href="https://t.co/rLkpUZUvfH">https://t.co/rLkpUZUvfH</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Whale Alert (@whale_alert) <a href="https://twitter.com/whale_alert/status/1691116790066106369?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 14, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">According to one analyst who <a href="https://twitter.com/luckyking223/status/1691118342550282240" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">commented</a> on the Bitcoin whale&rsquo;s actions, the address appears to be of an early miner. Mempool analysis shows the individual had actively mined the flagship cryptocurrency in 2010.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitcoin price outlook</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin&rsquo;s price has over the past few weeks struggled to strengthen towards the $30,000 levels even as bulls defend the critical support base near $29,000. Pressure remains given a technical outlook that could see bears target the buffer area in the $28,000-$28,500 range.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/btc/">BTC</a>&rsquo;s chopping as seen over the last few weeks has resulted in a downtrend line on the weekly chart. Attempts to break higher have seen multiple upside wicks but no conviction from bulls. While bulls are capable of bouncing higher in the short term, any slight hammering could welcome the all-important $25k zone.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-address-with-1005-btc-suddenly-wakes-up-after-nearly-13-years/">Bitcoin address with 1,005 BTC suddenly wakes up after nearly 13 years</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-address-with-1005-btc-suddenly-wakes-up-after-nearly-13-years/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
