<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 11:26:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>OpenAI Suspends Bing Integration in ChatGPT to Protect Content Owner Rights</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-bing-integration-chatgpt/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-bing-integration-chatgpt/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Darya Rudz]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 11:25:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[browse with bing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chatgpt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chatgpt app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chatgpt browse with bing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[openai]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[openai artificial intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[openai chatgpt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261683</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-bing-integration-chatgpt/">OpenAI Suspends Bing Integration in ChatGPT to Protect Content Owner Rights</a></p>
<p>The feature was available in a beta version, and while observing it in work, OpenAI learned that Browse with Bing was violating the rights of content owners.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-bing-integration-chatgpt/">OpenAI Suspends Bing Integration in ChatGPT to Protect Content Owner Rights</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-bing-integration-chatgpt/">OpenAI Suspends Bing Integration in ChatGPT to Protect Content Owner Rights</a></p>
<p>OpenAI, American artificial intelligence (AI) research laboratory renowned for the invention of the AI chatbot <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/everything-you-need-to-know-about-chatgpt-ai-chatbot/#:~:text=ChatGPT%20is%20an%20artificial%20intelligence,advanced%20and%20capable%20language%20models." target="_blank" rel="noopener">ChatGPT</a>, has announced its decision to put a new ChatGPT feature called Browse with Bing on hold. The feature, introduced as beta earlier this year, was enabling ChatGPT users to search the internet to help answer questions that benefit from recent information.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">We&#8217;ve learned that ChatGPT&#8217;s &#8220;Browse&#8221; beta can occasionally display content in ways we don&#8217;t want, e.g. if a user specifically asks for a URL&#8217;s full text, it may inadvertently fulfill this request. We are disabling Browse while we fix this—want to do right by content owners.</p>
<p>— OpenAI (@OpenAI) <a href="https://twitter.com/OpenAI/status/1676072388436594688?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 4, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>How did Browse with Bing work? It was supposed to be an effective integration of ChatGPT with Bing, which would make the flow of information more dynamic and current, leading to a revolution in how humans employ artificial intelligence. Basically, Browse with Bing was an innovative plugin added to ChatGPT Plus that gave AI access to the Internet for real-time information. The feature helped ChatGPT to search using Bing’s search results to provide the most accurate and up-to-date answers to users&#8217; queries. Notably, only those subscribed to ChatGPT Plus membership were able to benefit from the feature.</p>
<p>The feature was available as a beta version, and while observing it in work, OpenAI learned that Browse with Bing was violating the rights of content owners. As OpenAI has explained, users discovered a way to bypass paywalls using the feature. In particular, users could instruct the chatbot to retrieve the full text of articles behind paywalls, getting access the restricted content without subscribing to the respective websites.</p>
<p>One of the hot-discussed cases was a <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ChatGPT/comments/14j8q1u/it_looks_like_you_can_use_chatgpt_to_bypass/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">screenshot</a> of a Browse session made by a member of the r/ChatGPT subReddit. The user asked the chatbot to &#8220;print the text&#8221; of a link to a paywalled article from The Atlantic and received it in full without the paywall.</p>
<p>OpenAI did not wait for long to respond.</p>
<p>The company stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;As of July 3, 2023, we’ve disabled the Browse with Bing beta feature out of an abundance of caution while we fix this in order to do right by content owners. We are working to bring the beta back as quickly as possible, and appreciate your understanding!&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Notably, OpenAI does not exclude resuming the Browse with Bing feature for ChatGPT. Currently, it is working on improving its service and adding other tools that might enhance ChatGPT users&#8217; experience.</p>
<h2 data-hook="post-title">ChatGPT and Copyright Issues</h2>
<p>Being able to create almost unlimited content, ChatGPT gathers publicly-available information from the internet, expanding its own databases and creating its own new answers. However, ownership of the content varies depending on the sources of the training database, the database’s owner, and the degree of similarity between the database and the output generated. Therefore, using ChatGPT-generated output may result in copyright infringement if it contains protected material such as text, images, or audio without proper authorization from the original creator. This is exactly what happened in June when ChatGPT faced a class-action lawsuit in California over allegedly using private user information from the internet. This is also the case with Browse with Bing feature.</p>
<p>The response of OpenAI has been a significant step in the AI industry. It is a prime example of AI companies that should not stay away from making difficult decisions if it has anything to do with content creators&#8217; rights.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-australia-offices-raided/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-bing-integration-chatgpt/">OpenAI Suspends Bing Integration in ChatGPT to Protect Content Owner Rights</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-bing-integration-chatgpt/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Australia Offices Raided by Securities Regulator</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-australia-offices-raided/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-australia-offices-raided/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 11:09:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Binance News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[asic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binnace cz]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cftc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[changpeng zhao]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cz]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261699</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-australia-offices-raided/">Binance Australia Offices Raided by Securities Regulator</a></p>
<p>Binance is facing regulatory challenges in multiple jurisdictions worldwide.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-australia-offices-raided/">Binance Australia Offices Raided by Securities Regulator</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-australia-offices-raided/">Binance Australia Offices Raided by Securities Regulator</a></p>
<p>Binance, the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency exchange, faces intensified regulatory scrutiny as authorities search its offices in Australia. According to a Bloomberg <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-07-05/binance-australia-offices-searched-by-regulator-as-part-of-derivatives-probe" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a> on July 5 citing people familiar with the matter, the Australian Securities and Investments Commission (ASIC) invaded the company&#8217;s outlets in the country on Tuesday as part of an ongoing investigation into its derivative business.</p>
<p>Recall that Binance Australia <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/asic-binance-crypto-license/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">decided</a> to wind down the derivatives exchange in April after ASIC rescinded its regulatory license to operate in the country as a derivative broker while keeping its spot platform operational.</p>
<p>The world&#8217;s largest crypto exchange planned to offer derivative financial instruments to customers in the region through a partnership with Oztures Trading Pty Ltd. However, the plan changed following the license cancellation. ASIC is now investigating the company&#8217;s Australian division, reviewing its classification of retail and wholesale clients, as some users&#8217; positions were closed due to incorrect classification as wholesale investors.</p>
<h2>Binance Cooperating with Local Authorities</h2>
<p>While ASIC neither confirmed nor denied the office searches, a Binance spokesperson disclosed that the company is cooperating with local authorities. Binance emphasized its commitment to meeting the country&#8217;s regulatory standards and serving its Australian users fully compliantly. The company aims to work closely with authorities to address any compliance requirements that may arise during the investigation.</p>
<p>&#8220;We are cooperating with local authorities, and Binance is focused on meeting local regulatory standards in order to serve our users in Australia in a fully compliant manner,&#8221; a spokesperson for Binance Australia told Cointelegraph.</p>
<p>Aside from the ongoing investigation into the Binance derivatives business in Australia, the company had earlier faced regulatory scrutiny from the security regulator. In February, ASIC launched a probe into the company after the exchange abruptly closed certain derivatives positions. Binance explained at the time that its decision was driven by the need to comply with investor classification requirements, resulting in restrictions imposed on users who did not meet the qualifications to be considered wholesale investors.</p>
<h2>Binance Faces Global Regulatory Challenges</h2>
<p>Apart from Australia, Binance is facing regulatory challenges in multiple jurisdictions worldwide. French authorities recently raided the exchange&#8217;s subsidiary in France to investigate the alleged illegal provision of digital-asset services and aggravated money laundering. The company&#8217;s CEO, Changpeng Zhao (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/changpeng-zhao/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CZ</a>), however, denied the rumors of money laundering, stating that the exchange is in compliance with all laws in France and other markets of operation.</p>
<p>In the United States, the Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) filed a lawsuit against Binance and its CEO, accusing them of mishandling customer funds, misleading investors and regulators, and violating securities rules. Responding to the civil charges, the company said it plans to defend its platform against the SEC&#8217;s claims vigorously. Binance and Zhao also face a Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) lawsuit.</p>
<p>The crypto exchange has recently been ordered to cease operations in Belgium. The country&#8217;s market regulator, the Financial Services and Markets Authority, asked the company to suspend all its exchange and custody offerings for violating local rules and regulations.</p>
<p>In Belgium, the company&#8217;s application to secure a legal operating license was reportedly rejected due to its inability to meet the country&#8217;s regulatory standards.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-stocks-lower-economy/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-australia-offices-raided/">Binance Australia Offices Raided by Securities Regulator</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-australia-offices-raided/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>European Stocks Open Lower as Investors Worry about Downturn in Global Economy</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-stocks-lower-economy/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-stocks-lower-economy/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 11:01:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cac 40]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dax]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftse 100]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[s&p 500]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stoxx 600]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261705</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-stocks-lower-economy/">European Stocks Open Lower as Investors Worry about Downturn in Global Economy</a></p>
<p>There is a marked reduction in European stocks largely caused by the general apprehensiveness in the global economy.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-stocks-lower-economy/">European Stocks Open Lower as Investors Worry about Downturn in Global Economy</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-stocks-lower-economy/">European Stocks Open Lower as Investors Worry about Downturn in Global Economy</a></p>
<p>Stocks in the European market opened lower on Wednesday as general uncertainty continues to permeate the financial market and global economy. The Stoxx 600 fell 0.44%, as tech and mining stocks plunged by 1%. The market also saw a 0.41% fall in the CAC 40 Index and a 0.42% reduction in the FTSE 100. The DAX recorded the largest plunge, losing 0.53%.</p>
<p>European stocks seem to be responding unfavorably to the situation of the economy across the board. Stocks in China, along with markets in the Asia-Pacific region also fell with the Shenzhen Component dropping 0.91% to 11,029.3. The Shanghai Composite also fell, closing at 3,222.95 after losing 0.69%. Larger plunges were seen in the Hang Seng and Hang Seng Tech indexes, losing 1.6% and 1.5%, respectively.</p>
<p>Across other Asian markets, the Kospi in South Korea closed at 2,579 after losing 0.55%, while Japan’s Nikkei 225 and Topix indexes fell, with the Nikkei 225 losing 0.25.</p>
<p>Markets in the US also reflected the losses elsewhere. Although US markets were closed for Independence Day, stock futures fell. While the Nasdaq 100 futures lost 0.15%, the Dow Jones Industrial Average futures and the S&amp;P 500 fell 0.13% and 0.09%, respectively.</p>
<p>On the other hand, the Nasdaq&#8217;s first half was its <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/07/04/stock-market-today-live-updates.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">best Q1 in 40 years</a>, since 1983, The S&amp;P also had its best Q1 since 2019, following increased interest in artificial intelligence (AI) stocks. For some, the rise points to more increase in Q2.</p>
<h2>European Stocks React to Global Economy</h2>
<p>The uncertainty in economies across the world is causing ripple effects in European stocks and financial markets. For instance, Oil prices have fallen due to uncertainty with demand. Prices had initially <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/oil-prices-soars-saudi-arabia-oil/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">soared</a> following Russia and Saudi Arabia’s decision to cut output. At the time, Saudi’s decision was criticized by some who feared the move would weaken the oil market. Nonetheless, Saudi Aramco CEO Amin Nasser described oil market fundamentals for 2023 as “generally sound”. Despite the economic downturn in China and India, Nasser believes both countries would drive oil demand growth of over 2 million barrels per day.</p>
<p>Anxiety over the economy in China is also causing some unease for European stocks. According to customs data for May, exports from China fell 7.5% year-on-year (YoY), much higher than the 0.4% predicted by analysts Reuters polled. The same May data further revealed that Chinese exports to the EU dropped 4.9%.</p>
<p>Adding to the bleak forecast on China’s economy is a reduced growth outlook. Investment banking and management giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/goldman-sachs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Goldman Sachs</a> (NYSE: GS) reduced its growth outlook for China following troubles with recovering from the COVID-19 pandemic. Goldman Sachs expects China’s 2023 gross domestic product (GDP) to fall from 6% to 5.4%. Furthermore, Goldman Sachs predicts the GDP in 2024 will fall from 4.6% to 4.5%.</p>
<p>In recent times, European stocks have swung noticeably in response to several market events. For instance, these stocks <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/goldman-sachs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">opened higher</a> in early June after the US Senate suspended the official debt ceiling. The Stoxx 600 had climbed only a few days after its lowest point in two months.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shares-k-pop-investigation-watchdog/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-stocks-lower-economy/">European Stocks Open Lower as Investors Worry about Downturn in Global Economy</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-stocks-lower-economy/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shares of K-Pop Dip after Investigation by South Korea’s Antitrust Watchdog</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/shares-k-pop-investigation-watchdog/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/shares-k-pop-investigation-watchdog/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 10:47:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hybe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sm entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[yg entertainment]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261695</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shares-k-pop-investigation-watchdog/">Shares of K-Pop Dip after Investigation by South Korea’s Antitrust Watchdog</a></p>
<p>South Korea's Fair Trade Commission has launched an investigation on charges of power abuse in large entertainment firms such as SM Entertainment, YG Entertainment, and Hybe. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shares-k-pop-investigation-watchdog/">Shares of K-Pop Dip after Investigation by South Korea’s Antitrust Watchdog</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shares-k-pop-investigation-watchdog/">Shares of K-Pop Dip after Investigation by South Korea’s Antitrust Watchdog</a></p>
<p>On Wednesday, July 5, the price of shares of K-pop agencies <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/07/05/k-pop-stocks-hybe-sm-entertainment-fall-on-reports-of-antitrust-probe.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">dipped</a> briefly after South Korea’s antitrust watchdog initiated an investigation.</p>
<p>As per South Korea&#8217;s local news publication Yonhap News, the country&#8217;s Fair Trade Commission launched an investigation over allegations of power abuse in large entertainment agencies. The report notes that government agencies have sent &#8220;examiners&#8221; to the offices of SM Entertainment, YG Entertainment, and Hybe.</p>
<p>As per Yonhap, these companies allegedly violated the nation&#8217;s &#8220;subcontracting law&#8221; by using verbal contracts instead of written documents. Additionally, they have also been delaying payments while producing merchandise and albums.</p>
<p>Hybe, the company representing BTS, experienced a drop in its shares, with the value declining by as much as 3%. Similarly, SM Entertainment, another entertainment agency, saw its shares fall to a low of 2.19%. However, both companies managed to recover some of their losses by the midday break on Wednesday.</p>
<p>On the other hand, the shares of YG Entertainment, which manages the K-pop girl group Blackpink, had a smaller decrease of up to 1.49%, but later reversed its course and traded 2.23% higher. Note that the official developments aren&#8217;t yet confirmed.</p>
<h2>More About K-Pop Entertainment</h2>
<p>K-pop, short for Korean popular music, is a type of music that started in South Korea and is now a significant part of its culture. It encompasses various styles and genres from different parts of the world, including pop, hip hop, R&amp;B, rock, jazz, gospel, reggae, electronic dance, folk, country, disco, and classical, alongside its traditional Korean music influences. The term &#8220;K-pop&#8221; gained popularity in the 2000s, particularly in an international context.</p>
<p>The KPOP and Korean Entertainment ETF is an investment fund that consists of a portfolio of 30 stocks. These stocks primarily represent entertainment management companies that are responsible for managing popular K-pop bands. Some of the well-known bands included in this ETF are BTS, BlackPink, and Twice. The agencies associated with these bands are HYBE, YG Entertainment, and SM Entertainment.</p>
<p>Earlier this year, the K-pop group tripleS from South Korea <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/k-pop-triples-blockchain-voting/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">released</a> their newest album called &#8220;Assemble&#8221;, and it has received a lot of support from their dedicated community. This pop group is made up of 24 members, and their popularity in the world of K-pop is steadily growing.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/mark-cuban-john-reed-stark-crypto/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shares-k-pop-investigation-watchdog/">Shares of K-Pop Dip after Investigation by South Korea’s Antitrust Watchdog</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/shares-k-pop-investigation-watchdog/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mark Cuban, John Reed Stark Debate on Right Crypto Regulation Approach</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/mark-cuban-john-reed-stark-crypto/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/mark-cuban-john-reed-stark-crypto/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 09:22:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[japan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[john reed stark]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mark cuban]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[securities and exchange commission]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261673</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/mark-cuban-john-reed-stark-crypto/">Mark Cuban, John Reed Stark Debate on Right Crypto Regulation Approach</a></p>
<p>Cuban argued that the failure of the SEC to set “clear regulations” was what caused investors to lose their money in the FTX collapse.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/mark-cuban-john-reed-stark-crypto/">Mark Cuban, John Reed Stark Debate on Right Crypto Regulation Approach</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/mark-cuban-john-reed-stark-crypto/">Mark Cuban, John Reed Stark Debate on Right Crypto Regulation Approach</a></p>
<p>Billionaire businessman Mark Cuban has been seen having a public debate with former SEC official John Reed Stark. The debate which took place on Twitter, bordered on the role of regulators, such as the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>), on the collapse of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a> and the likes.</p>
<h2>Crypto Regulation: Mark Cuban Urges SEC to Take a Cue from Japan</h2>
<p>Stark had earlier suggested that cryptocurrencies, stablecoins, and even CBDCs do not have any real use. And that, even worse, the industry operates without regulation. This, according to Stark, was always a recipe for disaster as there couldn&#8217;t be any proper consumer protection.</p>
<p>Cuban then argued that the failure of the SEC to set “clear regulations” was what caused investors to lose their money in the FTX collapse.</p>
<p>To buttress his claim, Cuban noted how Japanese regulators have shown the world the right way to regulate. He <a href="https://twitter.com/mcuban/status/1676258204924407808?t=4tRnb8jpnea5sussXcbXRQ&amp;s=19" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">wrote</a> in part:</p>
<blockquote><p>“When FTX crashed, NO ONE IN FTX JAPAN LOST MONEY.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Furthermore, Cuban claims that things could have ended better for investors if the USA/SEC had followed Japan&#8217;s example by setting clear regulations. That is regulations that will ensure the separation of customer and business funds and clear wallet requirements.</p>
<p>According to the businessman, the SEC took the wrong approach by litigating to regulate, and that has ultimately cost billions.</p>
<h2>Stark Replies</h2>
<p>Meanwhile, Stark has also fired back. The ex-SEC employee says Cuban might be overreaching by blaming the SEC for the collapses of FTX, BlockFi, Celsius, Terra, and others.</p>
<p>Admittedly, Stark believes the regulator may have made some mistakes in its approach. However, he also insists that the regulator did save investors “millions, perhaps even billions” in crypto losses.</p>
<p>Stark also points to the fact that the crypto industry is undecided in its quest for regulatory clarity.  He says that the industry has a tradition of crying foul whenever rules are proposed, often resorting to lawsuits to fight the rules.</p>
<p>For example, Stark mentioned how the recent cases of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-sues-binance-securities-rules/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a> and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-sec-coinbase-unregistered-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase</a>. He says the SEC made it clear many months ago that they were not in compliance. However, after recently charging them, the crypto industry began wailing again.</p>
<p>Overall, Cuban has suggested what he feels is the “best way” to prevent the insecurities of cryptocurrency. The entrepreneur says that can only be achieved by implementing “bright line investor protection regulations”.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitget-dual-coin-crypto-loan-service/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/mark-cuban-john-reed-stark-crypto/">Mark Cuban, John Reed Stark Debate on Right Crypto Regulation Approach</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/mark-cuban-john-reed-stark-crypto/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitget Launches Dual-Coin Crypto Loan Service</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitget-dual-coin-crypto-loan-service/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitget-dual-coin-crypto-loan-service/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mercy Tukiya Mutanya]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 09:15:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitget]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockfi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[celsius network]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[genesis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261689</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitget-dual-coin-crypto-loan-service/">Bitget Launches Dual-Coin Crypto Loan Service</a></p>
<p>The announcement comes at a time when crypto loans are increasing in popularity owing, in large part, to the overall growth of the digital lending market.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitget-dual-coin-crypto-loan-service/">Bitget Launches Dual-Coin Crypto Loan Service</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitget-dual-coin-crypto-loan-service/">Bitget Launches Dual-Coin Crypto Loan Service</a></p>
<p>Crypto derivatives platform Bitget has announced the launch of a new product called “Crypto Loans” targeted at users not satisfied with traditional lending institutions. The new product will enable users to stake one coin as collateral to enable them to borrow the corresponding amount in another coin in what is known as a dual-coin approach.</p>
<p>According to Bitget, the borrowing process has been simplified and designed to emulate the process used by traditional lending institutions. This is in a bid to facilitate user onboarding. First, users will have to stake their collateral following which the requested loan amount will automatically be released. Loans will have varying interest rates, with the amount one can borrow depending on the market value of the staked collateral.</p>
<p>Bitget’s Managing Director <a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2023/07/04/2699197/0/en/Bitget-Launches-Crypto-Loans-To-Meet-The-Growing-Demand-For-Lending-Services.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Gracy Chen noted</a> that beyond providing credit, the Crypto Loans service will also help users expand their crypto investment portfolio.</p>
<p>&#8220;Bitget&#8217;s new product highlights the flexibility of collateralized currency usage, enhancing capital utilization. Users now have the opportunity to stake less-demanded coins, enabling them to obtain loans in more liquid assets for investment purposes,” Chen states. “Our platform&#8217;s flexible borrowing and repayment mechanism is designed to cater to the needs of all users, accommodating their requests and ensuring convenience.”</p>
<p>The announcement comes at a time when crypto loans are increasing in popularity owing, in large part, to the overall growth of the digital lending market. According to a <a href="https://www.gminsights.com/industry-analysis/digital-lending-platform-market" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report by Global Markets Insight</a>, the digital lending sector passed the $8.5 billion mark in 2022 and is expected a Compound Annual Growth Rate (CAGR) of 20.5% from 2023 to 2032. The industry’s value is projected to reach $60 billion in 2032. This growth, along with the increased mainstream adoption of technologies such as blockchain and artificial intelligence, is expected to continue to aid the growth of the crypto loans industry.</p>
<p>While several crypto lenders have experienced setbacks in recent years – with crypto lenders such as Celsius, BlockFi, and Genesis filing for bankruptcy – Bitget emphasizes that their loan disbursement process is modeled after existing processes used by lenders in traditional finance. The firm also states that it has taken steps to account for its holdings and ensure that user collateral is secure.</p>
<p>In late March, the platform partnered with decentralized data firm Space and Time to create a decentralized data warehouse. This tamperproof audit trail was created to provide users with an increased level of transparency in Bitget operations. The exchange, like many others following the collapse of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a>, also released its proof of reserves in the form of a dedicated section on its website.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-ceo-rate-limit-tweets/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitget-dual-coin-crypto-loan-service/">Bitget Launches Dual-Coin Crypto Loan Service</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitget-dual-coin-crypto-loan-service/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Twitter CEO Defends Elon Musk’s Rate Limit on Tweets</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-ceo-rate-limit-tweets/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-ceo-rate-limit-tweets/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 09:11:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[linda yaccarino]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[twitter]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261684</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-ceo-rate-limit-tweets/">Twitter CEO Defends Elon Musk’s Rate Limit on Tweets</a></p>
<p>In a recent blog post, Twitter provided an explanation for the imposition of rate limits, highlighting the need to take “extreme measures” to combat the presence of spam and bots on the platform.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-ceo-rate-limit-tweets/">Twitter CEO Defends Elon Musk’s Rate Limit on Tweets</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-ceo-rate-limit-tweets/">Twitter CEO Defends Elon Musk’s Rate Limit on Tweets</a></p>
<p>The new CEO of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/twitter/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Twitter Inc</a>, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/linda-yaccarino/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Linda Yaccarino</a> has come out in defense of<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/elon-musk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"> Elon Musk</a>&#8216;s decision to impose limits on the number of views user’s tweets receive.</p>
<p>In a <a href="https://twitter.com/TwitterBusiness/status/1676278441774292992" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Twitter post</a>, Yaccarino wrote that she is committed to upholding the platform&#8217;s mission and taking significant steps to enhance its functionality and impact. She highlighted that Twitter needs to make big moves to strengthen the platform as the outfit&#8217;s purpose goes beyond being a mere social media platform.</p>
<p>By supporting the imposition of limits on tweet views, the CEO is advocating for a more responsible and thoughtful approach to social media use, where the potential harm caused by misinformation and unchecked influence is mitigated.</p>
<h2>Concerns Raised by Industry Experts</h2>
<p>Last week Elon Musk imposed limits on the number of posts that can be viewed by users. Initially, the limit was set at 600 posts per day for unverified users and 6000 posts for verified users. However, the limit was later increased to 1000 posts per day for unverified accounts and 10,000 tweets for verified accounts.</p>
<p>The controversial measure, which has been met with mixed reactions aims to address “extreme levels of data scraping” and “system manipulation”, as stated by Musk. However, Twitter users have taken to the platform to share screenshots demonstrating their inability to view tweets, including those from corporate advertisers.</p>
<p>This limitation has raised concerns among marketing professionals who believe it could potentially undermine the efforts of Yaccarino to attract advertisers. In an earlier Coinspeaker <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-daily-tweet-views-ceo-efforts/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">report</a>, Jasmine Enberg, a principal analyst at Insider Intelligence, voiced concerns about the potential impact of limiting user views on Twitter&#8217;s advertising business.</p>
<p>Enberg has expressed worry that such a move could have a “catastrophic” effect and make it even more challenging for Twitter to attract advertisers back to the platform, which is already a difficult task.</p>
<h2>Twitter Raises Defense</h2>
<p>In a recent <a href="https://business.twitter.com/en/blog/update-on-twitters-limited-usage.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">blog post</a>, Twitter provided an explanation for the imposition of rate limits, highlighting the need to take “extreme measures” to combat the presence of spam and bots on the platform.</p>
<p>The company highlighted that the rate limits were implemented as a means to address two primary concerns: the scraping of public Twitter data for the development of AI models, and the manipulation of users and conversations on the platform.</p>
<p>In the same blog post, Twitter clarified that the rate limit restrictions had been imposed on only a small percentage of users at present, and added that the company would provide updates once their work is complete.</p>
<p>Regarding advertising, Twitter assured that the effects of the rate limit restrictions have been minimal. This statement is aimed at addressing potential concerns among advertisers who may have worried about the impact on their advertising campaigns and the reach of their content.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/voyager-134m-outflows-celsius/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-ceo-rate-limit-tweets/">Twitter CEO Defends Elon Musk’s Rate Limit on Tweets</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-ceo-rate-limit-tweets/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Voyager Digital Records $134M in Outflows while Celsius Network Remains Dormant</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/voyager-134m-outflows-celsius/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/voyager-134m-outflows-celsius/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 09:06:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[celsius network]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gemini]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[usdc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[voyager digital]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261676</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/voyager-134m-outflows-celsius/">Voyager Digital Records $134M in Outflows while Celsius Network Remains Dormant</a></p>
<p>Voyager and Celsius are forging ahead with their bankruptcy plans but only Voyager seems to be making any crypto transfers.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/voyager-134m-outflows-celsius/">Voyager Digital Records $134M in Outflows while Celsius Network Remains Dormant</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/voyager-134m-outflows-celsius/">Voyager Digital Records $134M in Outflows while Celsius Network Remains Dormant</a></p>
<p>Crypto lending firms Voyager Digital and Celsius Network have both received approvals to begin moving their crypto portfolios around. Both bankrupt lenders are still trying to resolve their bankruptcies in court and have been involved in court action since filing for bankruptcy last year. However, activity on the Celsius front has been stagnant, while Voyager is active.</p>
<p>According to a <a href="https://cases.stretto.com/public/x191/11749/PLEADINGS/1174906302380000000027.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">filing</a> on June 30, the Bankruptcy Court in the Southern District of New York authorized Celsius to exchange its remaining crypto for Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a>) or Ether (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ETH</a>). The firm had admitted to meeting with the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) over its recent decision to <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-binance-matic-sol-lawsuit/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">classify some cryptocurrencies</a> as securities. According to the Commission, MATIC, BNB, ADA, ALGO, and SOL, among others, are securities.</p>
<p>Following these talks, the court allowed Celsius to “maximize the value of [its] Altcoins” and sell them for ETH or BTC. Data from crypto intelligence platform Arkham Intelligence stated that Celsius held nearly $600 million at the time, including $187.04 million in altcoins.</p>
<p>Despite the approval, Celsius has yet to make any moves as of Tuesday. The lender’s last activity was moving $11.3 million worth of MATIC (17.3 million tokens) to a Polygon staking contract for rewards. Before then, Celsius had sent $7.1 million USDC to FalconX.</p>
<p>Celsius filed a bankruptcy exit plan following an agreement with crypto consortium Fahrenheit. After launching an auction last October and receiving multiple bids, Fahrenheit <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fahrenheit-consortium-celsius-network/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">beat</a> NovaWulf Digital Management to emerge the winner. The offer includes a $300 million cash payment and $700 million worth of Fahrenheit tokens. However, Celsius later filed an update that limits user recovery and is now <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/celsius-creditor-bankruptcy-exit/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">getting heavy pushback</a> from customers.</p>
<h2>Voyager Moves Crypto Around as Celsius Holds Off</h2>
<p>While the Celsius Network seems to be delaying any sales or transfer transactions, Voyager has recorded heavy activity. Nearly one year after suspending all operations, Voyager authorized user withdrawals from June 23. According to Arkham Intelligence, Voyager held nearly $413 million in multiple assets the day before withdrawals officially began. Withdrawals will only be possible for 30 days.</p>
<p>Last week, crypto exchange and custodian Gemini <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gemini-withdrawals-voyager-customers/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">announced</a> support for users looking to withdraw funds from its platform. Customers can only transfer assets supported by Gemini as attempts to do otherwise or transfer supported assets on unsupported networks, may result in loss.</p>
<p>Since officially starting withdrawals, Voyager has recorded consistent outflows, reducing its $413 million by 25% to $307.5 million. Calculated at current market prices, the total value of all crypto withdrawn is $134 million. The top three outflows are BTC, USDC, and ETH, respectively.</p>
<p>Last week, Voyager <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/voyager-digital-1-1m-legal-fees/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">received</a> a $1.1 million bill from its legal advisor, Kirkland &amp; Ellis, for April. The company charged Voyager for work done, at a blended hourly rate of $1,313.18. On the other hand, Voyager Creditors <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/voyager-creditors-5-1m-bill/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">got</a> a $5.1 million bill for services rendered from March to May. Law firm McDermott Will &amp; Emery has now billed the group of creditors more than $16 million.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/britains-house-lords-crypto-bill/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/voyager-134m-outflows-celsius/">Voyager Digital Records $134M in Outflows while Celsius Network Remains Dormant</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/voyager-134m-outflows-celsius/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Britain’s House of Lords Passes Bill to Seize and Freeze Crypto Used for Crime</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/britains-house-lords-crypto-bill/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/britains-house-lords-crypto-bill/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 08:46:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[house of lords]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261667</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/britains-house-lords-crypto-bill/">Britain&#8217;s House of Lords Passes Bill to Seize and Freeze Crypto Used for Crime</a></p>
<p>Having passed through UK's upper chamber, the new bill is close to law. The bill seeks to allow authorities to seize cryptocurrencies used for criminal activities. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/britains-house-lords-crypto-bill/">Britain&#8217;s House of Lords Passes Bill to Seize and Freeze Crypto Used for Crime</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/britains-house-lords-crypto-bill/">Britain&#8217;s House of Lords Passes Bill to Seize and Freeze Crypto Used for Crime</a></p>
<p>On Tuesday, July 4, the UK&#8217;s Economic Crime and Corporate Transparency Bill, entered its final stages thereby becoming law, after being passed by the House of Lords. Basically, this bill seeks to empower British agencies to seize and freeze cryptocurrencies used for criminal activities such as money laundering or terror financing.</p>
<p>Additionally, the bill has introduced an amendment to ensure that courts can also ask the authorities to take action on crypto used for crime. In order to identify cryptocurrencies linked to criminal activities, Britain has introduced crypto tactical advisers and police departments nationwide.</p>
<p>In March 2023, the British government said that they would be combating the criminal use of crypto under the three-year economic agenda.</p>
<p>The new bill has passed through the UK&#8217;s upper chamber, bringing it closer to becoming a law. There are a few more steps remaining: a review by the lower chamber called the House of Commons, agreement on any further changes by both chambers and approval by King Charles III.</p>
<p>Over the past months, UK lawmakers included various additions to the bill. In November, they introduced provisions that allow public authorities to seize digital assets associated with terrorism and take control of properties that can help identify cryptocurrencies linked to criminal activities.</p>
<p>Britain first introduced the UK&#8217;s Economic Crime and Corporate Transparency Bill back in September 2022. Back then, Graeme Biggar, director general of the National Crime Agency, <a href="https://www.finextra.com/newsarticle/41004/uk-government-launches-fraud-and-money-laundering-crackdown" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Domestic and international criminals have for years laundered the proceeds of their crime and corruption by abusing UK company structures, and are increasingly using cryptocurrencies. These reforms – long awaited and much welcomed – will help us crack down on both.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>The Purpose of the Bill Passed by the House of Lords</h2>
<p>In a statement released in September, the government mentioned that the Economic Crime and Corporate Transparency Bill will enhance the UK&#8217;s reputation as a favorable place for lawful businesses to flourish while also eliminating illicit money from the country. The reforms will require everyone registering a company in the UK to confirm their identity, addressing the misuse of companies for criminal purposes or by corrupt foreign officials.</p>
<p>The United Kingdom has initiated several <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-law-commission-digital-assets/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">measures</a> to legitimize the use of digital assets. Recently, the UK Law Commission submitted a proposal to the government to provide a comprehensive legal foundation for cryptocurrencies. Last month, the UK government also <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-passes-legislation-crypto-brexit/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">passed legislation</a> to promote the safe adoption of cryptocurrencies.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-ethereum-supply-goldman-sachs/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/britains-house-lords-crypto-bill/">Britain&#8217;s House of Lords Passes Bill to Seize and Freeze Crypto Used for Crime</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/britains-house-lords-crypto-bill/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Goldman Sachs Report: Bitcoin and Ethereum Supply on Exchanges Drops Sharply in June</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-ethereum-supply-goldman-sachs/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-ethereum-supply-goldman-sachs/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 08:22:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[goldman sachs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261671</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-ethereum-supply-goldman-sachs/">Goldman Sachs Report: Bitcoin and Ethereum Supply on Exchanges Drops Sharply in June</a></p>
<p>Goldman Sachs reported that the total monthly Bitcoin inflows from miners to centralized exchanges almost doubled from May to $99 million in June. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-ethereum-supply-goldman-sachs/">Goldman Sachs Report: Bitcoin and Ethereum Supply on Exchanges Drops Sharply in June</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-ethereum-supply-goldman-sachs/">Goldman Sachs Report: Bitcoin and Ethereum Supply on Exchanges Drops Sharply in June</a></p>
<p>A new report from Goldman Sachs Group Inc (NYSE: GS) shows that Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a>) and Ethereum (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ETH</a>) supply on centralized exchanges (CEXes) significantly reduced in June as holders migrated to self-custody services. The migration majorly caused by the ongoing crypto regulatory crackdown and increased fear of theft through hacks saw Bitcoin and Ether supply on CEX drop to levels not seen YTD. According to the report, Bitcoin supply <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/07/04/bitcoin-ether-supply-on-exchanges-fell-in-june-goldman-sachs/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">dropped</a> 4 percent, nearing the level of December 2022, while Ether supply declined 5.8 percent in June to levels not seen since May 2018.</p>
<p>As for Ethereum, most holders preferred to stake and earn passive returns while storing securely instead of just holding on centralized exchanges. Moreover, increased risks of hacks and rug pull on centralized crypto firms has the old slang ‘not your keys, not your coins’ at work.</p>
<p>Interestingly, crypto investors continued to hold and add more coins in recent months despite the prices showcasing overbought features. Investors remain highly bullish on Bitcoin and Ethereum in the long term, especially with increased institutional crypto demand.</p>
<p>In June, the Bitcoin market led the altcoins in gains following an ETF frenzy from key institutional investors. Although the SEC has remained adamant in approving the first Bitcoin ETF in the United States, the underlying crypto demand by institutional investors is undeniable.</p>
<p>As Bitcoin price rallied towards $31k last month, on-chain data analyzed by Goldman Sachs shows miners increased their profit taking, perhaps fueled by the fear of a possible correction. Specifically, Goldman Sachs reported that the total monthly Bitcoin inflows from miners to centralized exchanges almost doubled from May to $99 million in June.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin and Ethereum Market Outlook</h2>
<p>The top two digital assets by market capitalization continued to record increased on-chain activities in June. Heightened DeFi development on Ethereum and the uprising use of Bitcoin ordinal dubbed BRC-20 standard were identified as the root cause of increased activity. For instance, the Binance exchange was at one time forced to halt withdrawals following heightened network congestion that resulted in a sharp uptick in transaction fees.</p>
<p>The report by <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/goldman-sachs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Goldman Sachs</a> further highlighted that the monthly address activity for Bitcoin and Ethereum increased by approximately 15.5 percent and 37.5 percent respectively in June. The increase in on-chain activity was also underpinned by the fact that the daily average new address count for Bitcoin and Ethereum gained by approximately 9.8 percent and 48.2 percent monthly.</p>
<p>Worth noting, the Goldman report highlighted that the average daily Ether burnt on the beacon chain in June dropped by approximately 65.1 percent while the average daily fees dropped by about 63.3 percent.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-global-tech-semiconductor/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-ethereum-supply-goldman-sachs/">Goldman Sachs Report: Bitcoin and Ethereum Supply on Exchanges Drops Sharply in June</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-ethereum-supply-goldman-sachs/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4156 metric#misses=41 metric#hit-ratio=99.0 metric#bytes=1106582 metric#prefetches=210 metric#store-reads=20 metric#store-writes=2 metric#store-hits=217 metric#store-misses=2 metric#sql-queries=34 metric#ms-total=109.01 metric#ms-cache=5.08 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.2419 metric#ms-cache-ratio=4.7 -->