<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 11:10:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Coinbase and Binance Are Largest Beneficiaries of FTX Fallout</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-binance-beneficiaries-ftx/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-binance-beneficiaries-ftx/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 11:10:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=230074</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-binance-beneficiaries-ftx/">Coinbase and Binance Are Largest Beneficiaries of FTX Fallout</a></p>
<p>Binance and Coinbase lead the spot exchanges in the past 24 hours with trading volumes of approximately $8,582,628,378, and $1,192,133,466 respectively.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-binance-beneficiaries-ftx/">Coinbase and Binance Are Largest Beneficiaries of FTX Fallout</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-binance-beneficiaries-ftx/">Coinbase and Binance Are Largest Beneficiaries of FTX Fallout</a></p>
<p>Centralized cryptocurrency exchanges <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase Global Inc</a> (NASDAQ: COIN) and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a> have recorded a sharp uptick in user base and daily traded volume in the past six weeks following the collapse of FTX and Alameda. According to aggregate data from cryptocompare, Binance&#8217;s market share for crypto-only exchanges rose to 87 percent in December from approximately 82.7 percent in September. Coinbase Global, on the other hand, has seen its share of the fiat exchange market spike to 40 percent in December from 22.8 percent in September.</p>
<p>Nonetheless, decentralized exchanges (DEX) and non-custodial crypto wallets have recorded the largest gain in the global user base following the FTX implosion. Furthermore, approximately 1 million worldwide cryptocurrency traders and investors were affected by the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a> and Alameda implosion. As such, fear of rug pulls especially on centralized exchanges has significantly increased in the past few weeks.</p>
<p>According to market aggregate data from Coinmarketcap, Binance and Coinbase lead the spot exchanges in the past 24 hours with trading volumes of approximately $8,582,628,378, and $1,192,133,466 respectively.</p>
<p>Notably, Binance has gained popularity with AI traders since it allows traders to borrow funds and participate in margin trading of up to 10X leverage. With the vast regulatory approvals worldwide, Binance continues to be the top priority for both experienced and novice traders. Moreover, the Binance ecosystem supports almost all the top blockchains and its crypto wallets have a desirable reputation with most traders.</p>
<h2>Binance and Coinbase on the Limelight</h2>
<p>The cryptocurrency market has grown to a trillion-dollar industry within a decade of existence and market strategists forecast it will comfortably do another 10X in the next ten years. As such, crypto companies that have shown resilience during the 2022 bear market are expected to play a crucial role in global adoption. Furthermore, analysts have compared the 2022 bear market to the early 2000s when most internet companies were adopted by mainstream investors.</p>
<p>Binance has approximately 90 million customers worldwide and a daily trading volume of over $76 billion. While the company remains under private ownership, the company has BNB coins that largely derive value from the crypto exchange. Moreover, Binance holds the largest share of BNB coins.</p>
<p>Coinbase, on the other hand, is publicly traded with its stock market over 90% below its IPO price. According to market data from <a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/investing/stock/coin" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">MarketWatch</a>, COIN shares are trading around $35.10 on Wednesday, while a year ago they were trading above $350.</p>
<p>Notably, Coinbase has a market capitalization of approximately $7.9 billion with top investors including Cathy Woods Ark Investments.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/scottie-pippens-nfts-sell-out/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-binance-beneficiaries-ftx/">Coinbase and Binance Are Largest Beneficiaries of FTX Fallout</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-binance-beneficiaries-ftx/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Scottie Pippen’s NFTs Sell Out in 77 Seconds</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/scottie-pippens-nfts-sell-out/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/scottie-pippens-nfts-sell-out/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Babafemi Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 10:53:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[opensea]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=229888</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/scottie-pippens-nfts-sell-out/">Scottie Pippen’s NFTs Sell Out in 77 Seconds</a></p>
<p>Like Hopkins' NFT collection, Scottie Pippen’s NFTs were issued in partnership with Orange Comet.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/scottie-pippens-nfts-sell-out/">Scottie Pippen’s NFTs Sell Out in 77 Seconds</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/scottie-pippens-nfts-sell-out/">Scottie Pippen’s NFTs Sell Out in 77 Seconds</a></p>

<p>NBA legend Scottie Pippen’s <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NFTs</a> have sold out in seventy-seven seconds, breaking the OpenSea sales record. At 0.2 ETH per NFT, more than $240,000 in sales volume has been made.</p>
<p>The record was previously held by Anthony Hopkins&#8217; NFT collection. The <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hollywood-hopkins-nft-collection/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Hopkins NFT collection</a> sold out more than a thousand NFT art pieces in seven minutes. Also, former <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/donald-trump/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">President Trump</a> recently launched NFT trading cards with his picture. The entire <a href="https://opensea.io/collection/trump-digital-trading-cards" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">collection</a>, comprising about 45,000 trading cards, sold out in less than a day.</p>
<h2>A Curious Case</h2>
<p>What makes all these NFT drops interesting is that they come when NFT sales are at an all-time low. Following a prolonged winter, it has become increasingly hard to launch and sell NFT collections. Data provided by DappRadar showed that the top five NFT marketplaces only made sales of $394 million in November. Compared to global NFT sales of about $4.78 billion in January, the decline is obvious.</p>
<p>What’s common to the new NFTs selling out is that they offer real utility to the buyers. Thirty-three buyers of Scott Pippen’s NFTs will receive autographed physical sneakers. Another 33 will receive $100 gift cards for sneakers. Yet another two people will get to go on a golf outing with Pippen, and one person will visit Pippen, for a dinner, in his hometown.</p>
<p>It is clear that NFTs that invest more money into added benefits for owners of their set may be the only collections making enough sales soon enough.</p>
<h2>About Scottie Pippen’s NFTs</h2>
<p>Like Hopkins&#8217; NFT collection, Scottie Pippen’s NFTs were issued in partnership with Orange Comet. According to the CEO and co-founder, Dave Broome, “selling out this iconic NFT collection and beating our previous record with Sir Anthony Hopkins’ drop is an incredible way to close out 2022.” Broome also believes the success of the collections provides an accurate testimony of the work that goes into creating the NFT collections.</p>
<p>Essentially, Scott Pippen’s NFT collection represents the first line of digital wearables by Orange Comet. All those who own Scottie Pippen’s NFTs will get into the Allowlist for the next Orange Comet phydigital launch set for 2023.</p>
<p>Beyond profit, Broome believes the company will help onboard many more people into the Web3 space.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-tsla-stock-tanks-twitter/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/scottie-pippens-nfts-sell-out/">Scottie Pippen’s NFTs Sell Out in 77 Seconds</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/scottie-pippens-nfts-sell-out/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tesla (TSLA) Stock Tanks Another 8% amid Concerns of Musk’s Focus on Twitter</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-tsla-stock-tanks-twitter/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-tsla-stock-tanks-twitter/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 10:23:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wall Street]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tesla]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[twitter]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=230053</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-tsla-stock-tanks-twitter/">Tesla (TSLA) Stock Tanks Another 8% amid Concerns of Musk&#8217;s Focus on Twitter</a></p>
<p>Concerns that Elon Musk might further dilute his Tesla holdings to fund the Twitter acquisition have put the TSLA stock under a free fall. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-tsla-stock-tanks-twitter/">Tesla (TSLA) Stock Tanks Another 8% amid Concerns of Musk&#8217;s Focus on Twitter</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-tsla-stock-tanks-twitter/">Tesla (TSLA) Stock Tanks Another 8% amid Concerns of Musk&#8217;s Focus on Twitter</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/tesla/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tesla Inc</a> (NASDAQ: TSLA) stock continues to be under a free fall and tanked another 8% on Tuesday, December 20, ending the trading at $137.80. Since <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/elon-musk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Elon Musk</a>&#8216;s takeover of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/twitter/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Twitter</a>, Tesla stock has corrected by more than 40%.</p>
<p>There has been a growing concern within the investor community about Musk&#8217;s increasing focus on his latest acquisition of Twitter. Thus, citing Elon Musk&#8217;s Twitter distraction, a string of brokerages have cut their price targets for the TSLA stock.</p>
<p>On Tuesday, the Tesla (TSLA) stock touched a new two-year low. The Tesla stock price is already down by more than 65% since the beginning of 2022. Many analysts believe that Musk might be diluting his stake to fund his Twitter acquisition. Well, this has led to growing concerns among investors who believe that Musk&#8217;s antics are hurting the EV company. Speaking to Yahoo Finance, Wells Fargo auto analyst Colin Langan <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tesla-stock-concerns-go-beyond-elon-musk-multitasking-at-twitter-analyst-183159045.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;It&#8217;s very concerning about the weakness that we&#8217;re seeing in China. We are seeing incentives go up, and sales actually are not increasing there. And [a] driving concern is: Are we going to start seeing that in the U.S. and Europe? Is that just sort of the early days of softening demand? And I think that is really more of the large institutional investors&#8217; top concern.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>For now, Lagan has given an equal weight rating for the TSLA stock. He also acknowledged that investors need to carefully observe the situation at Twitter. &#8220;Everyone has seen that Elon could multitask, so that is not something traditional institutional investors are that concerned about. But I do think there is rising concern about potential brand damage from some of the headlines that are coming around the Twitter situation,&#8221; Langan added.</p>
<h2>Analysts Cut Price Targets for Tesla Stock amid Musk&#8217;s Focus on Twitter</h2>
<p>A number of market analysts have recently cut the price targets for the TSLA stock. Evercore ISI has slashed the price of TSLA stock to $200 from $300 amid fear of the impact on the Tesla brand. Similarly, Daiwa Capital Markets has also cut its price target to $177 from $240, citing a &#8220;higher risk profile from the Twitter distraction&#8221;.</p>
<p>Also, the weakening demand in China, Tesla&#8217;s one of the biggest markets, is also the reason behind the TSLA stock coming under pressure. For 2023, Daiwa has lowered the company&#8217;s delivery targets by 5% along with an 8% reduction in revenue per unit. As per Elon Musk, Tesla was targeting a 50% growth in delivery volumes. However, the EV maker said that they might miss the target this year citing logistics issue.</p>
<p>Amid the recent chaos, Elon Musk conducted a Twitter poll asking his followers whether he should step down as Twitter CEO. 57% of the votes said Yes. Responding to this Musk <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tesla-stock-concerns-go-beyond-elon-musk-multitasking-at-twitter-analyst-183159045.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">wrote</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;I will resign as CEO as soon as I find someone foolish enough to take the job! After that, I will just run the software &amp; servers teams&#8221;.</p></blockquote>
<p>Read other <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/business/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">business news</a> on Coinspeaker.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uniswap-moonpay-card-crypto/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-tsla-stock-tanks-twitter/">Tesla (TSLA) Stock Tanks Another 8% amid Concerns of Musk&#8217;s Focus on Twitter</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-tsla-stock-tanks-twitter/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Uniswap Partners with MoonPay for Bank Card Crypto Purchases</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/uniswap-moonpay-card-crypto/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/uniswap-moonpay-card-crypto/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mercy Tukiya Mutanya]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 10:19:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[matic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[moonpay]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[poligon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[uni]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[uniswap]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[usdc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[usdt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[WBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[weth]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=230028</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uniswap-moonpay-card-crypto/">Uniswap Partners with MoonPay for Bank Card Crypto Purchases</a></p>
<p>While users do not need to verify their identity to use the Uniswap Protocol, they need to observe  MoonPay’s KYC/AML policy to be able to buy crypto using a card or bank account.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uniswap-moonpay-card-crypto/">Uniswap Partners with MoonPay for Bank Card Crypto Purchases</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uniswap-moonpay-card-crypto/">Uniswap Partners with MoonPay for Bank Card Crypto Purchases</a></p>
<p>Decentralized exchange (DEX) <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/uniswap/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Uniswap</a> now allows users to purchase crypto on its web app via debit cards, credit cards, and bank transfers. This is made possible for Uniswap thanks to a partnership with fintech company MoonPay. The bank transfer option is available to users within most US states, Brazil, the UK, and the Single Euro Payments Area.</p>
<p>In a December 20 <a href="https://uniswap.org/blog/web-fiat-on-ramp" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announcement</a>, Uniswap revealed that it had enabled quick fiat-to-crypto conversions on the Ethereum mainnet, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/matic-network/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Polygon</a>, Optimism, and Artibrum. The service will initially support Dai, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ether</a>, USDC, USDT, Wrapped Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-wrapped-bitcoin-wbtc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">wBTC</a>), and Wrapped Ether (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-wrapped-ethereum-weth/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">wETH</a>) subject to the user’s location. For example, US users cannot purchase wETH or wBTC.</p>
<p>According to the announcement, the minimum purchase size on many of the supported cryptocurrencies is $15 or the local currency equivalent. The minimum purchase size for ETH, USDC, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/tether/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">USDT</a>, and DAI depends on market conditions. Buy limits, on the other hand, are dependent on what cryptocurrency is being purchased and which fiat currency is used. For example, USDC has a cap of “10,000 on Arbitrum and Optimism while popular fiat currencies are capped at USD at 12,000, GBP at 9,000, EUR at 10,000, and CAD at 16,000.” Users can also buy <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NFTs</a> on the Uniswap Web App using ETHh purchased through MoonPay.</p>
<h2>Privacy and the Challenge Facing the DeFi Onboarding Process</h2>
<p>The exchange revealed adoption has been greatly impacted by the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-decentralized-finance-defi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">DeFi </a>onboarding experience, adding that despite the risks, users view centralized exchanges (CEXs) as more convenient. The company hopes this latest feature will help the onboarding process with its “no spread fees on USDC, lowest processing fees in the market, and instant access.”</p>
<p>Uniswap asserts that DEXs are much safer than CEXs due to their built-in user protection, self-custodial wallets, permissionless, immutable protocols, and transparent public ledger. The exchange’s new feature comes at a time when sentiments towards centralized platforms are changing owing to the recent collapse of such platforms, most notably and recently, FTX.</p>
<p>While users do not need to verify their identity to use the Uniswap Protocol, they need to observe  MoonPay’s KYC/AML policy to be able to buy crypto using a card or bank account. MoonPay points out that it does not share user data with Uniswap Labs. Uniswap Labs, in turn, revealed that it does not collect and store financial data such as card and bank information, or personal data such as names, home addresses, dates of birth, email addresses, and IP addresses.</p>
<p>Uniswap has also received criticism from the part of the crypto community for its collection and storage of user data, which some believe goes against crypto’s core values. In its privacy policy, updated on November 17,  Uniswap revealed that it would collect publicly available blockchain data, information about user devices such as browser information and operating systems, and information on users’ interactions with its service providers.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bankman-fried-us-extradited/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uniswap-moonpay-card-crypto/">Uniswap Partners with MoonPay for Bank Card Crypto Purchases</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/uniswap-moonpay-card-crypto/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Former FTX CEO Sam Bankman-Fried to Face Criminal Charges in US, Set to Be Extradited Today</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bankman-fried-us-extradited/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bankman-fried-us-extradited/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 10:13:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx collapse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx sam bankman-fried]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sam bankman-fried]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sbf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[securities and exchange comission]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=230040</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bankman-fried-us-extradited/">Former FTX CEO Sam Bankman-Fried to Face Criminal Charges in US, Set to Be Extradited Today</a></p>
<p>Bankman-Fried would face up to eight federal charges ranging from securities fraud to money laundering and wire fraud.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bankman-fried-us-extradited/">Former FTX CEO Sam Bankman-Fried to Face Criminal Charges in US, Set to Be Extradited Today</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bankman-fried-us-extradited/">Former FTX CEO Sam Bankman-Fried to Face Criminal Charges in US, Set to Be Extradited Today</a></p>
<p>Following his recent arrest in the Bahamas and about three courtroom hearings this week, disgraced <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a> founder <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/sam-bankman-fried/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Sam Bankman-Fried </a>is set to be extradited to the United States. This follows after a CNBC <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/video/2022/12/20/sam-bankman-fried-defyed-the-advice-of-his-lawyers-by-agreeing-to-u-s-extradition.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a> that he defied the advice of his legal team on Tuesday, signing extradition papers.  That move will see that he flies out of the Bahamas no later than today to face a US trial.</p>
<h2>Sam Bankman-Fried Charged on 8 Counts</h2>
<p>In the U.S., Bankman-Fried would face up to eight federal charges ranging from securities fraud to money laundering and wire fraud. However, the charges are a total of allegations from both the country&#8217;s financial regulators as well as law enforcement. According to the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>), Bankman-Fried perpetrated one of the largest and arguably, the most “brazen” fraud in modern history.</p>
<p>For the office of the US Attorney for the Southern District of New York also, the 30-year-old MIT graduate has questions to answer. This is particularly concerning approximately $8 billion worth of customer assets that they claim SBF squandered on irrelevancies. According to the Attorney’s Office, he used customer funds to fulfill an extravagant lifestyle and fund several political movements. In some of his misuse antics, SBF also made extravagant real estate purchases and bought stadium naming rights among other vanity projects he pursued.</p>
<p>Nonetheless, expectations are that the trial will be a very long one. So, there&#8217;s a possibility that the one-time crypto billionaire walks free on bail, while the court proceedings continue.</p>
<h2>How It All Started</h2>
<p>Bankman-Fried&#8217;s problems began shortly after his crypto exchange, FTX, collapsed in November. The exchange did file for bankruptcy but several allegations soon began flying around.  For some,  the exchange was about as shady as any business gets, especially with its lack of &#8220;real&#8221; reserve and backing.</p>
<p>Bankman-Fried was later indicted in New York federal court on December 9 and was eventually arrested three days later.  Coinspeaker <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bankman-fried-arrested-bahamas/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a> at the time, that Bahamian authorities picked up SBF at the request of US prosecutors.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-shares-ftc-zuckerberg-vr/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bankman-fried-us-extradited/">Former FTX CEO Sam Bankman-Fried to Face Criminal Charges in US, Set to Be Extradited Today</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bankman-fried-us-extradited/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Meta Shares Up 3%, FTC Accuses Zuckerberg of Buying Company’s Way to Top of VR Industry</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-shares-ftc-zuckerberg-vr/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-shares-ftc-zuckerberg-vr/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 10:05:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Deals News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Virtual Reality & Augmented Reality News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wall Street]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[faang]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[facebook]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Meta]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meta platforms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meta stock]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=230060</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-shares-ftc-zuckerberg-vr/">Meta Shares Up 3%, FTC Accuses Zuckerberg of Buying Company’s Way to Top of VR Industry</a></p>
<p>The hearing on Tuesday focused on Meta’s acquisition of Within, a VR company that makes a fitness app dubbed Supernatural.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-shares-ftc-zuckerberg-vr/">Meta Shares Up 3%, FTC Accuses Zuckerberg of Buying Company’s Way to Top of VR Industry</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-shares-ftc-zuckerberg-vr/">Meta Shares Up 3%, FTC Accuses Zuckerberg of Buying Company’s Way to Top of VR Industry</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/meta/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Meta Platforms Inc</a> (NASDAQ: META) shares closed Tuesday trading at $117.09, up 2.28 percent from the day’s opening price. The gains extended during the after-hours trading session with approximately 0.74 percent. Under the leadership of Mark Zuckerberg, Meta has been accused of buying its way up the virtual reality (VR) industry by the Federal Trade Commission (FTC).</p>
<p>In the past decade, Meta &#8211; formerly Facebook &#8211; had been developing its ecosystem to shape the future of technology. Moreover, Meta has made several acquisitions worth billions, which has ostensibly made the FTC think the social media giant is killing competitors.</p>
<p>“Instead of competing on the merits, Meta is trying to buy its way to the top,” said FTC Bureau of Competition Deputy Director John Newman in a statement about the lawsuit. “Meta already owns a best-selling virtual reality fitness app, and it had the capabilities to compete even more closely with Within’s popular Supernatural app. But Meta chose to buy market position instead of earning it on the merits.”</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="474" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Mark Zuckerberg testifies that fitness in VR isn&#39;t even his top VR app &quot;use-case&quot; priority. He reiterates social, gaming and productivity are priorities, and he says his email about the Peloton partnership was spurred b/c the VR biz was doing better in 2021 than forecasted.</p>
<p>&mdash; Dorothy Atkins (@doratki) <a href="https://twitter.com/doratki/status/1605270032807665664?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 20, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The hearing on Tuesday focused on Meta&#8217;s acquisition of Within, a VR company that makes a fitness app dubbed Supernatural. During the hearing, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/mark-zuckerberg/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Zuckerberg</a> said that Meta focused on virtual reality (VR) fitness apps in 2021 due to its excess capital. However, the company’s stand has since changed as revenues hit a nosedive in 2022.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the privacy implementation by <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/apple-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Apple Inc</a> (NASDAQ: AAPL) has significantly reduced the revenues of most social media platforms that are heavily dependent on online advertisements.</p>
<h2>Meta Shares and the Market Outlook</h2>
<p>According to market data from <a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/investing/stock/meta" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">MarketWatch</a>, Meta shares have lost approximately 65 percent in 2022, thus retesting the lows of 2016. While most of the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-are-faang-stocks/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FAANG stocks</a> have recorded poor performance in 2022, market strategists are positive they will be profitable in the coming years. Moreover, the global economy is heavily reliant on emerging technologies including artificial intelligence (AI) and blockchain development.</p>
<p>As such, Meta remains under regulatory scrutiny due to its competitive prospects and ability to kill other smaller businesses. According to aggregate data from MarketWatch, Meta has a market capitalization of approximately $303.55 billion and 2.25 billion shares outstanding.</p>
<p>Meta has received significant criticism for its market dominance both domestically and internationally markets. During Tuesday’s hearing, the Federal Trade Commission lawyers attempted to show that Meta had planned to compete with apps like Within, arguing that executives identified fitness as a way to expand VR use beyond its existing fan base of young male gamers.</p>
<p>While the FTC continues to pressure Meta to stop the Within acquisition, the commission also wants to unwind two previous acquisitions, Instagram and WhatsApp, in a lawsuit filed in 2020.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nike-2023-q2-results-stock/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-shares-ftc-zuckerberg-vr/">Meta Shares Up 3%, FTC Accuses Zuckerberg of Buying Company’s Way to Top of VR Industry</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-shares-ftc-zuckerberg-vr/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nike Announces Fiscal 2023 Q2 Results, NKE Stock Surges</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nike-2023-q2-results-stock/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nike-2023-q2-results-stock/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Darya Rudz]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 09:38:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wall Street]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nike]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nike stock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nke stock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[rtfkt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=230025</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nike-2023-q2-results-stock/">Nike Announces Fiscal 2023 Q2 Results, NKE Stock Surges</a></p>
<p>Yesterday, NIKE shares closed the trading session at $103.21, or 0.16% up. After hours, NIKE shares added another 12.77% to reach $116.39. With a market cap of $161.481 billion, NIKE stock is still 38.08% down year-to-date.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nike-2023-q2-results-stock/">Nike Announces Fiscal 2023 Q2 Results, NKE Stock Surges</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nike-2023-q2-results-stock/">Nike Announces Fiscal 2023 Q2 Results, NKE Stock Surges</a></p>
<p>American sportswear company <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/nike/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Nike Inc</a> (NYSE: NKE) struck the Q2 fiscal 2023 balance with great earnings, blowing Wall Street expectations away. Analysts believe that better-than-expected performance came as a result of inventory level growth that has been inflated for several months because of supply chain disruptions. Following the company&#8217;s <a href="https://s1.q4cdn.com/806093406/files/doc_financials/2023/q2/FY23-Q2-Combined-NIKE-Press-Release-Schedules-FINAL.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener">announcement</a>, NKE stock went up.</p>
<h2>Nike&#8217;s Q2 Earnings Overview</h2>
<p>Yesterday, Nike shares closed the trading session at $103.21, or 0.16% up. After hours, NKE shares added another 12.77% to reach $116.39. With a market cap of $161.481 billion, Nike stock is still 38.08% down year-to-date.</p>
<p>The numbers for the fiscal 2023 second quarter reported by Nike are as follows:</p>
<div title="Page 1">
<div>
<div>
<ul>
<li>The revenue reported for the quarter totaled $13.3 billion. Meanwhile, analysts predicted $12.57 billion. The revenue is as much as 17% up compared to last year and 27% up on a currency-neutral basis.</li>
<li>The net income for the quarter made up $1.33 billion, or 85 cents per share. The expected number was 64 cents per share. Last year, it was $1.34 billion and 83 cents per share.</li>
<li>NIKE Direct sales grew by 25%, led by 34% growth in NIKE Digital sales and 11% growth in NIKE stores.</li>
<li>Inventories were $9.3 billion, or 43% higher compared to the prior year period, driven by an increase in units from lapping prior year supply chain disruption, as well as higher input costs.</li>
</ul>
<p>Nike President and CEO John Donahoe commented:</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div title="Page 1">
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Nike’s results this quarter are a testament to our deep connection with consumers. Our growth was broad-based and was driven by our expanding digital leadership and brand strength. These results give us confidence in delivering the year as our competitive advantages continue to fuel our momentum.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<div title="Page 1">
<p>Executive Vice President and Chief Financial Officer Matthew Friend added:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Consumer demand for NIKE&#8217;s portfolio of brands continues to drive strong business momentum in a dynamic environment. We remain focused on what we can control, and we are on track to deliver on our operational and financial goals — setting the foundation for sustainable, profitable growth.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>For the full fiscal 2023, the company&#8217;s leaders are expecting the revenue to grow &#8216;low teens on a currency-neutral basis.&#8217; According to Matthew Friend, Q3 revenue growth is likely to be higher than Q4 due to the timing of wholesale shipments.</p>
<h2>Nike&#8217;s Latest Initiatives</h2>
<p>Currently, the company is focused on expanding its portfolio. Last week, Nike announced the opening of its &#8220;Jordan World of Flight&#8221; store on Via Torino, Milan. The store is a 363-square-meter premium retail destination that carries Jordan Brand footwear and apparel for men, women, and kids. According to Nike, World of Flight Milan is the &#8220;future of Jordan retail.&#8221;</p>
<p>In addition, Nike recorded enormous success on the web 3.0 interface. In particular, it <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nike-web3-wearable-platform-swoosh/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">developed</a> its own web 3.0 wearables platform called .Swoosh (pronounced “dot Swoosh”). Besides, it collaborated with a digital collectibles firm RTFKT to unveil its web 3.0 sneakers. As we have <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nike-rtfkt-web-3-0-sneakers/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a>, the Cryptokicks iRL sneakers feature auto-lacing, enhanced lighting, haptic feedback, gesture control, walk detection, app connectivity, AI/ML algorithms, and wireless charging via the RTFKT power deck.</p>
</div>
</div>
<p><a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/blockfi-withdrawals-selected-customers/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nike-2023-q2-results-stock/">Nike Announces Fiscal 2023 Q2 Results, NKE Stock Surges</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nike-2023-q2-results-stock/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>BlockFi Seeks to Resume Withdrawals for Selected Customers</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/blockfi-withdrawals-selected-customers/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/blockfi-withdrawals-selected-customers/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 15:40:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockfi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=229989</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/blockfi-withdrawals-selected-customers/">BlockFi Seeks to Resume Withdrawals for Selected Customers</a></p>
<p>BlockFi intends to delete all “attempted” withdrawals after the platform pause from the user interface to sort out any confusion.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/blockfi-withdrawals-selected-customers/">BlockFi Seeks to Resume Withdrawals for Selected Customers</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/blockfi-withdrawals-selected-customers/">BlockFi Seeks to Resume Withdrawals for Selected Customers</a></p>
<p>Crypto lender BlockFi, which <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/blockfi-chapter-11-bankruptcy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">filed</a> for bankruptcy on the 28th of November, has filed a motion with a US court to resume withdrawals for customers with crypto locked in its wallet accounts. The bankrupt company filed the motion on the 19th of December with the US Bankruptcy Court in the District of New Jersey. If approved, BlockFi users will be able to withdraw the crypto that is locked up in the platform. The motion says that cryptos held in BlockFi wallets belong to customers, and the company does not have legal or equitable interest in friends from when it stopped operation on the 10th of November.</p>
<p>In addition to allowing withdrawals of funds in customers’ BlockFi wallets, the crypto lender is pushing to update the user interface to reflect transactions correctly. The company also seeks to conduct ordinary course reconciliation of accounts.</p>
<blockquote><p>“Simply put, the [clients] were unable to, and did not, effectuate any transaction on the BlockFi platform beginning the moment of the Platform Pause Time Stamp.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>BlockFi Pushes for Withdrawals of Certain Customers</h2>
<p>BlockFi intends to delete all “attempted” withdrawals after the platform pause from the user interface to sort out any confusion. The company also said in the filing that “for the avoidance of doubt, the Debtors do not seek to reverse any client deposits from outside the platform to Wallet Accounts which were received following the Platform Pause Time Stamp.</p>
<p>As <a href="https://twitter.com/TiffanyFong_/status/1604994112943374337?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1604994112943374337%7Ctwgr%5Ee9d42b4167970655ff8ca4c0ccc32bd1b7282d29%7Ctwcon%5Es1_&amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fcointelegraph.com%2Fnews%2Fblockfi-files-motion-to-return-frozen-crypto-to-wallet-users" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">shared</a> on Twitter, BlockFi sent an email to users, announcing the latest filing with the court. It added that it believes that clients unambiguously own the digital assets in their BlockFi Wallet Accounts. The crypto lender added:</p>
<blockquote><p>“We will be seeking similar relief from the Supreme Court of Bermuda with respect to BlockFi Wallet Accounts held at BlockFi International Ltd. This motion does not impact withdrawals or transfers from BlockFi Interest Accounts, which remain paused at this time.”</p></blockquote>
<p>BlockFi was one of the first victims of the crash trend led by crypto exchange FTX in early November. The crypto lender brokered a $680 million deal with FTX.US and hence was impacted with FTX’s financial health escalated. BlockFi’s bankruptcy petition showed that the company claimed over 100,000 creditors and between $1 billion and $10 billion in assets and liabilities.</p>
<p>Celsius Network, which also filed for bankruptcy, submitted a similar motion as it restructured. The company provided a status update on the 8th of December, saying that the court has authorized it to return “pure custody accounts” that were never in Celsius’ earn or borrow programs.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/central-african-republic-sango-crypto-2023/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/blockfi-withdrawals-selected-customers/">BlockFi Seeks to Resume Withdrawals for Selected Customers</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/blockfi-withdrawals-selected-customers/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Central African Republic Delays Sango Crypto Coin Listing Until 2023</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/central-african-republic-sango-crypto-2023/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/central-african-republic-sango-crypto-2023/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 15:35:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[car]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sango]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sango coin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=229983</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/central-african-republic-sango-crypto-2023/">Central African Republic Delays Sango Crypto Coin Listing Until 2023</a></p>
<p>The Central African Republic has pushed the anticipated listing of its national crypto to next year due to unfavorable parameters.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/central-african-republic-sango-crypto-2023/">Central African Republic Delays Sango Crypto Coin Listing Until 2023</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/central-african-republic-sango-crypto-2023/">Central African Republic Delays Sango Crypto Coin Listing Until 2023</a></p>
<p>The Central African Republic (CAR) recently <a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/central-african-republic-delays-crypto-token-listing-cites-market-conditions-2022-12-20/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announced</a> a delay in listing its national crypto token due to prevailing market conditions. According to the landlocked country, its Sango Coin listing would not launch until the first quarter of 2023.</p>
<p>The Central African nation also delayed a &#8220;release,&#8221; which would grant coin holders the ability to sell up to 5% of their tokens. As it stands, these coins remain &#8220;locked&#8221; for a year and cannot be sold. The country had earlier promised investors that they would receive 5% of their stake at the point of listing.</p>
<p>The Central African Republic did not specify whether the delay in the 5%-coin reimbursement resulted from central bankers or legal hurdles. In addition, the targeted crypto exchange(s) for listing the CAR&#8217;s national crypto also remain unspecified.</p>
<h2>Central African Republic Plans to Leverage Crypto as Means of National Development</h2>
<p>The Central African Republic is <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/central-african-republic-bitcoin-legal-tender/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">the second country in the world</a>, after <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/el-salvador-bitcoin-legal-tender-51k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">El Salvador</a>, to adopt crypto as a legal tender. In the first half of 2022, the CAR declared Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a>) as a legal currency alongside the CFA franc. At the time, President Faustin Archange Touadera&#8217;s chief of staff, Obed Namsio, described the move as putting the CAR on &#8220;the map of the world&#8217;s boldest and most visionary countries.&#8221; However, the nation&#8217;s most senior judges subsequently rebuffed an attempt to grant citizenship to crypto investors in exchange for acquiring $60,000 worth of Sango Coin. According to the CAR high court, the citizenship offer is unconstitutional as nationality has no market value. Following the court&#8217;s decision to deny the citizenship path, a CAR spokesperson said the government was exploring other avenues. Furthermore, an unidentified moderator recently promised more updates regarding foreign investor citizenship next month.</p>
<p>As the first African country to legally adopt crypto as legal tender, the CAR is actively looking to develop its impoverished economy. One primary goal is to become a digital currency hub for the entire Sub-Saharan African region. In addition, several CAR government stakeholders want the country to be one step ahead of new and emerging technology. The country currently has poor internet access and below optimal electricity supply.</p>
<h2>Sango Coin</h2>
<p>The war-torn Central African Republic <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/central-african-republic-launches-sango-coin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">launched the Sango Coin</a> back in July, with plans to generate $1 billion over the next year. This national agenda has held sway despite concerns about Sango&#8217;s transparency and a broader crypto decline. So far, the African country has managed sales of only $1.66 million worth of its Sango token. This underwhelming development comes after the CAR achieved around 7.9% of its first sales target and only 0.01% of its second.</p>
<p>Despite being on the back foot for much of the year, the crypto marketplace took a worse turn following the recent collapse of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a>. So far, the global crypto market cap is $2 trillion, down from its peak in November 2021.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gleec-btc-blocktane-brazil/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/central-african-republic-sango-crypto-2023/">Central African Republic Delays Sango Crypto Coin Listing Until 2023</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/central-african-republic-sango-crypto-2023/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gleec BTC Exchange Acquires BlockTane to Move into Brazilian Market</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/gleec-btc-blocktane-brazil/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/gleec-btc-blocktane-brazil/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 14:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blocktane]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gleec BTC Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[usdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=229870</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gleec-btc-blocktane-brazil/">Gleec BTC Exchange Acquires BlockTane to Move into Brazilian Market</a></p>
<p>Gleec has also dived into El Salvador, the country that was ranked as the first in the world to legalize Bitcoin back in September 2021.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gleec-btc-blocktane-brazil/">Gleec BTC Exchange Acquires BlockTane to Move into Brazilian Market</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gleec-btc-blocktane-brazil/">Gleec BTC Exchange Acquires BlockTane to Move into Brazilian Market</a></p>
<p>Estonia&#8217;s crypto trading platform <a href="https://exchange.gleec.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Gleec BTC Exchange</a> has announced its acquisition of <a href="https://www.blocktane.io/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Blocktane</a>, a Brazilian digital currency exchange as it makes strategic plans to deepen its push into the Latin American market. According to a Press Release shared with Coinspeaker, Gleec BTC Exchange’s acquisition of Blocktane involves the trading firm’s legal entity, brand name, and online domains.</p>
<p>The deal will also see the management of the trading platform stay on but under the leadership of Gleec in order to bring the parent firm’s ideologies to life in Brazil and the environs. The Blocktane platform was founded in 2020 as a direct and easy avenue for users to buy cryptocurrencies in a regulated way.</p>
<p>While the platform has temporarily ceased operations, it has grown to become one of the trusted venues for crypto trading, amassing a good market share that Gleec is hoping it will build on. Besides the primary aspects of Blocktane’s operations that will now be under the control of Gleec, the company’s native token BKT as well as its treasury inventory will also be directly handled by the new acquiring firm.</p>
<p>“We are pleased to partner with Gleec to bring their tool and products to Blocktane’s users in Brazil, and their first entry into that domestic market,” said John Willock, former Executive Chairman of Blocktane.</p>
<h2>Gleec Purchased Blocktane to Ride the Brazil Crypto Trend</h2>
<p>Gleec has a primary expansionary drive to move into new jurisdictions with a penchant for crypto adoption. The exchange’s push into Brazil was born out of the country’s latest disposition toward crypto in which lawmakers have passed the bill to legalize crypto as a means of payment.</p>
<p>The recently passed Bill No. 4,401 came after years of discussion by the lawmakers. In a bid to deepen the influence of the new bill in transforming the payment landscape in Brazil, a new oversight body has been established by the Brazilian Chamber of Deputies to oversee crypto payments in the country.</p>
<p>With the bills already passed by the lawmakers, only the President’s assent is remaining, and once appended, the bill is bound to get implemented within six months.</p>
<p>Brazil remains the most renowned crypto hotspot in the Latin American region over the past year, and the country has seen impressive growth in the past year. It has recorded more users adopting digital currencies including <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> (BTC) and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/tether/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">USDT</a> amongst others as shown in tax filings published by the Brazilian Federal Reserve (RFB).</p>
<p>Gleec has also dived into El Salvador, the country that was ranked as the first in the world to <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/el-salvador-bitcoin-legal-tender-51k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">legalize Bitcoin</a> back in September 2021. The Gleec presence in El Salvador is through its local subsidiary, <a href="https://gleec.sv/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Gleec SV</a>. As it looks to push its foothold around the world, Gleec said in a statement that it will reopen the Blocktane platform within the next few weeks.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-korean-court-92m-terra/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gleec-btc-blocktane-brazil/">Gleec BTC Exchange Acquires BlockTane to Move into Brazilian Market</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/gleec-btc-blocktane-brazil/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>