<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 08:41:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Trump’s Financial Disclosure Document Reveals Ethereum Holding</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/trump-ethereum-holding/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/trump-ethereum-holding/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Babafemi Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 08:41:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[donald trump]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nft]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=265927</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/trump-ethereum-holding/">Trump’s Financial Disclosure Document Reveals Ethereum Holding</a></p>
<p>Trump’s aversion to crypto is directly opposed to the position of the rest of his party.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/trump-ethereum-holding/">Trump’s Financial Disclosure Document Reveals Ethereum Holding</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/trump-ethereum-holding/">Trump’s Financial Disclosure Document Reveals Ethereum Holding</a></p>

<p>Donald Trump’s 2023 public financial disclosure has revealed that the former president holds Ethereum (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ETH</a>) worth between $250,000 and $500,000. These details were part of a <a href="https://www.documentcloud.org/documents/23876912-donald-trump-oge-public-financial-disclosure-report-2023-part-1" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">revised financial filing submitted</a> by Trump. The filing outlined various income sources for the Trump family and exceeded over $1.2 billion.</p>
<p>While the document only referenced an item described as a “Cryptocurrency Wallet (Ethereum)”, it did not elaborate on the exact source or content. However, the prevailing opinion suggests that the content may be linked to the president&#8217;s sale of non-fungible tokens (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NFTs</a>).</p>
<h2>Possible Source of Ethereum Holding</h2>
<p>In December 2022, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/donald-trump/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Donald Trump</a> launched a limited edition NFT collection after exiting the White House. The collection comprised 44,000 digital trading cards that sold at $99 apiece. Each piece showed the president in different poses and outfits. The NFT collection was generally successful selling out within a day and netting over $8.9 million in sales.</p>
<p>Donald Trump is believed to have earned around $298,000 in licensing fees from this NFT adventure. Interestingly, the crypto wallet that received the earnings is held under CIC Digital, the same Trump entity that collected the licensing fees.</p>
<p>Afterward, Trump launched a <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/trump-nft-trading-cards-4-6m/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">second edition</a> of NFTs which also sold out, although it did not gather as much traction as the first. Also, former first lady Melania Trump launched <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/melania-trump-us-nfts/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">an NFT collection</a>. The collection featured several popular images from NASA’s Apollo moon landings into digital pieces, selling them for $75 each.</p>
<h2>Is Trump’s Position on Cryptocurrencies Changing?</h2>
<p>This development may suggest that Trump’s view of cryptocurrency may be changing. In 2019, the former president tweeted that he was not a fan of Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies. Later, former White House Communications Director, Anthony Scaramucci, noted, that Trump himself may not have authored the tweet.</p>
<p>However, in 2021, Trump removed every doubt about his position, labelling the asset class as ‘fake”. Trump said: </p>
<blockquote>
<p>&#8220;I don’t like it, because it’s another currency competing against the dollar. I want the dollar to be the currency of the world. That’s what I’ve always said.&#8221;</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Such claims are contrary to the latest findings regarding his Ethereum holdings.</p>
<p>Trump’s aversion to crypto is directly opposed to the position of the rest of his party. Many Republicans in the House and Senate have been responsible for sponsoring new bills to improve regulations in the crypto industry.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-javier-milei-argentina/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/trump-ethereum-holding/">Trump’s Financial Disclosure Document Reveals Ethereum Holding</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/trump-ethereum-holding/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pro-Bitcoin Advocate Javier Milei Takes Lead in Argentina’s Primary Election</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-javier-milei-argentina/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-javier-milei-argentina/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 08:38:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266751</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-javier-milei-argentina/">Pro-Bitcoin Advocate Javier Milei Takes Lead in Argentina&#8217;s Primary Election</a></p>
<p>Milei's political platform has been characterized by his passionate advocacy for BTC and his calls for the dissolution of the Argentine central bank.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-javier-milei-argentina/">Pro-Bitcoin Advocate Javier Milei Takes Lead in Argentina&#8217;s Primary Election</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-javier-milei-argentina/">Pro-Bitcoin Advocate Javier Milei Takes Lead in Argentina&#8217;s Primary Election</a></p>
<p>Javier Milei, a prominent Argentinian politician known for his pro-Bitcoin stance and radical views on economic reform, has surged ahead in the country&#8217;s primary presidential election. Milei, who has been a vocal critic of the central bank and a staunch supporter of Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a>), is currently leading the race with over 30% of the votes counted, marking a significant shift in the country&#8217;s political landscape.</p>
<p>With an impressive 84% of the votes counted, Milei&#8217;s party, &#8220;La Libertad Avanza&#8221; (Freedom Advances), has secured 30.73% of the total votes. The figure puts him ahead of his competitors from the &#8220;Juntos por el Cambio&#8221; (Together for Change) party and the &#8220;Unidos por la Patria&#8221; (United for the Homeland) coalition, who have garnered 28.14% and 26.84% of the votes, respectively. The unexpected surge in support for Milei has surprised political analysts and pollsters, as pre-election polls had predicted a much narrower margin for him.</p>
<h2>Milei Says Central Bank Is a Scam</h2>
<p>According to <a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoiner-javier-milei-wins-argentina-presidential-primary" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reports</a>, Milei&#8217;s political platform has been characterized by his passionate advocacy for BTC and his calls for the dissolution of the Argentine central bank. He has repeatedly criticized the central bank, labeling it a &#8220;scam&#8221; that enables politicians to manipulate the economy through inflation.</p>
<p>&#8220;The central bank is a scam, a mechanism by which politicians cheat the good people with inflationary taxes,&#8221; he said.</p>
<p>His unwavering support for the crypto asset as an alternative to traditional financial systems has resonated with a significant portion of the electorate, particularly amid the country&#8217;s staggering annual inflation rate of 116%, the highest it has been in over thirty years.</p>
<p>However, Milei&#8217;s radical views extend beyond monetary policy. He identifies as an anarcho-capitalist and has made controversial statements, including advocating for the legalization of human organ sales and denying the existence of global warming.</p>
<p>Despite these unconventional viewpoints, his popularity has been fueled by his forceful critique of the current government&#8217;s economic policies and his promise to bring about substantial change.</p>
<h2>Half-Baked Support for Bitcoin</h2>
<p>While Milei has shown strong backing for BTC, the Argentinian politician does not endorse the idea of making the digital asset a legal tender within the country, as it was done in El Salvador in 2021 when the government officially adopted the use of the digital asset in the nation.</p>
<p>Instead, he believes in &#8220;dollarization&#8221; for the economy, implying that adopting the US dollar could offer stability and help alleviate the repercussions of inflation.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, according to Bloomberg <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/graphics/2023-argentina-election/">data</a>, the primary election results have set the stage for the general presidential election scheduled for October 22, where the candidates will compete in a three-way contest.</p>
<p>In order to secure the presidency outright, a candidate must receive at least 45% of the vote. However, if no candidate meets this threshold, a runoff vote will be held in November to determine the final winner.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/softbank-vision-fund-stake-arm/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-javier-milei-argentina/">Pro-Bitcoin Advocate Javier Milei Takes Lead in Argentina&#8217;s Primary Election</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-javier-milei-argentina/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>SoftBank Looking to Acquire Vision Fund’s 25% Stake in Arm</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/softbank-vision-fund-stake-arm/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/softbank-vision-fund-stake-arm/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Darya Rudz]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 08:27:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investors News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[IPO News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[arm]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[arm ipo]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[softbank]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[softbank arm]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[softbank group]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[softbank group corp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[softbank vision fund]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vision fund]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266745</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/softbank-vision-fund-stake-arm/">SoftBank Looking to Acquire Vision Fund’s 25% Stake in Arm</a></p>
<p>Arm is scheduled to go public in September, with the listing of its shares on the Nasdaq exchange. Arm's market capitalization by that time is expected to be $60 billion to $70 billion, which would make the deal the world's biggest initial public offering so far this year.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/softbank-vision-fund-stake-arm/">SoftBank Looking to Acquire Vision Fund’s 25% Stake in Arm</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/softbank-vision-fund-stake-arm/">SoftBank Looking to Acquire Vision Fund’s 25% Stake in Arm</a></p>
<p>Tokyo-based conglomerate <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/softbank/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SoftBank Group Corporation</a> (TYO: 9984) is <a href="https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/softbank-talks-buy-vision-funds-25-stake-arm-sources-2023-08-13/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reportedly</a> planning to buy a 25% stake in Arm, a semiconductor and software design company based in Cambridge, from Vision Fund 1 (VF1). Currently, SoftBank which owns 75% of Arm stake, is negotiating with Vision Fund 1 on the terms of the deal. If signed, the deal will benefit VF1 investors who have been struggling to get profit for years.</p>
<p>SoftBank made an agreed offer for Arm company back in 2016, the offer was subject to approval by Arm&#8217;s shareholders. At that time, the CPUs producer was valued at $32 billion. The transaction was completed in September 2016. In 2017, a 25% stake in Arm was transferred to the SoftBank Vision Fund, which received investment from Saudi Arabia&#8217;s Public Investment Fund and Abu Dhabi&#8217;s Mubadala Investment Company.</p>
<p>VF1 investors have been bearing losses until recently, and Vision Fund 2 did not generate revenue as well, which led to SoftBank failing to secure outside investors. Over the last two fiscal years, SoftBank’s Vision Fund lost about $48 billion. Only in the second quarter of this year, Vision Fund posted a revenue following the buzz around artificial intelligence (AI) and living up expectations of those who trusted SoftBank&#8217;s bets on AI startups. As we have <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/softbank-profit-vision-fund/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a>, after five consecutive losing quarters, the Vision Fund gained 159.8 billion yen, about $1.1 billion, in the quarter that ended on June 30.</p>
<div id="div-gpt-ad-1499653692894-0">
<p>Since May 2022, SoftBank has been in &#8216;defense mode&#8217;, which means it has been using an approach to protect against the competition amid economic uncertainty. Now, the company is shifting to &#8216;offense mode&#8217;, capitalizing on the AI revolution. Besides, it is planning to conduct an <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-initial-public-offering-ipo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">initial public offering</a> (IPO) for Arm. Preparation started in March.</p>
<h2>Upcoming Arm IPO</h2>
<p>Arm is scheduled to go public in September, with the listing of its shares on the Nasdaq exchange. Arm&#8217;s market capitalization by that time is expected to be $60 billion to $70 billion, which would make the deal the world&#8217;s biggest initial public offering so far this year.</p>
</div>
<p>Later this month, SoftBank will officially apply to the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">US Securities and Exchange Commission</a> (SEC) for the listing. Next, it will obtain approval from Nasdaq. Among those who will invest in Arm are giants like <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/apple-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Apple Inc</a> (NYSE: AAPL), <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/samsung/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Samsung Electronics</a>, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/nvidia/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Nvidia Corporation</a> (NYSE: NVDA), <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/intel/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Intel Corporation</a> (NASDAQ: INTC), and more.</p>
<p>Initially, Arm was eyeing the UK market for an IPO, which would be a great boost for the UK tech sector and secure London as an appealing destination for high-value IPOs. However, the lack of progress in the UK&#8217;s regulatory and market reform agenda made SoftBank change the target market. The US listing will come as a disappointment to UK ministers who had continually been lobbying the company to list on the London Stock Exchange.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-regulatory-approval-taiwan/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/softbank-vision-fund-stake-arm/">SoftBank Looking to Acquire Vision Fund’s 25% Stake in Arm</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/softbank-vision-fund-stake-arm/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Pursues Regulatory Approval in Taiwan via AML Registration</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-regulatory-approval-taiwan/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 15:08:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Binance News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266698</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-regulatory-approval-taiwan/">Binance Pursues Regulatory Approval in Taiwan via AML Registration</a></p>
<p>Binance is expanding its presence in Asia. The reports about its potential entrance into Taiwan come after the company re-entered the Japanese market last year.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-regulatory-approval-taiwan/">Binance Pursues Regulatory Approval in Taiwan via AML Registration</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-regulatory-approval-taiwan/">Binance Pursues Regulatory Approval in Taiwan via AML Registration</a></p>
<p>Leading global cryptocurrency exchange <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a> is seeking a regulatory license in Taiwan to enable the company to offer crypto services in the country. According to a recent <a href="https://www.theblock.co/post/244320/binance-is-applying-to-get-registered-in-taiwan-for-aml-compliance-sources" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a> by The Block citing people familiar with the matter, the exchange has applied to be registered under the country&#8217;s anti-money laundering (AML) rules.</p>
<p>Taiwan is one of the many nations in the world with stringent AML laws. The country&#8217;s financial watchdog, the Financial Supervisory Commission (FSC), introduced the legislation in 2021, making it mandatory for all digital asset service providers to comply with the law.</p>
<p>Despite its close ties with China, the island nation has underlined its distinct crypto policies from those of mainland China, as the Beijing government has enforced a comprehensive ban on crypto-related activities since 2021.</p>
<h2>Binance Seeks to Enter the Taiwanese Market</h2>
<p>Binance is now seeking national regulatory approval as part of the company&#8217;s commitment to compliance with local regulatory authorities. If approved, the exchange can legally enter the Taiwanese Market and provide its business offerings to customers in the region.</p>
<p>Sources familiar with the matter revealed that Binance is actively engaged in registration, aiming to ensure rigorous compliance with AML regulations as stipulated by Taiwan&#8217;s financial authorities. According to local news <a href="https://abmedia.io/binance-taiwan-application" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">media</a>, the FSC disclosed the information during a confidential meeting with domestic crypto exchanges in Taiwan.</p>
<h2>Binance Partners with Law Enforcement Agency in Taiwan</h2>
<p>While Binance&#8217;s full regulatory status in Taiwan remains pending, the exchange currently operates in the country through a registered entity known as &#8220;Binance International Limited Taiwan Branch (Seychelles).&#8221; The Taiwanese government approved the firm in May 2023, with a registered capital of NT$30 million ($944,000).</p>
<p>In addition to its registration within the nation, Binance has joined forces with the Taiwanese authorities to combat cybercrime. The exchange <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/blog/ecosystem/binance-partners-with-taiwan-law-enforcement-agencies-to-fight-cybercrime-7928081762268486180">announced</a> the partnership in June, noting that it is working with the country&#8217;s Criminal Investigation Bureau (CIB) to share its expertise in tackling digital asset-related crime with more than 200 Taiwanese law enforcement officers.</p>
<h2>Binance Faces Regulatory Hurdles in the US and Europe</h2>
<p>Binance is expanding its presence in Asia. The reports about its potential entrance into Taiwan come after the company re-entered the Japanese market last year. The exchange acquired Sakura Exchange BitCoin in November 2022 to enable it to explore the Asian market.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, while Binance is expanding its reach in Asia, the exchange faces regulatory hurdles in the United States and Europe. The exchange is battling various legal cases in the US, including one with the Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>).</p>
<p>In Europe, the company has chosen to withdraw from several European jurisdictions, including the Netherlands, due to regulatory concerns.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-stablecoin-pyusd-bank-of-america/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-regulatory-approval-taiwan/">Binance Pursues Regulatory Approval in Taiwan via AML Registration</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bank of America: Paypal Stablecoin (PYUSD) Immediate Adoption Might Be Subdued</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-stablecoin-pyusd-bank-of-america/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 14:32:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bank of america]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[paypal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pyusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stablecoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266694</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-stablecoin-pyusd-bank-of-america/">Bank of America: Paypal Stablecoin (PYUSD) Immediate Adoption Might Be Subdued</a></p>
<p>The introduction of PayPal stablecoin (PYUSD) represents a groundbreaking development in the realm of stablecoins and digital currencies.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-stablecoin-pyusd-bank-of-america/">Bank of America: Paypal Stablecoin (PYUSD) Immediate Adoption Might Be Subdued</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-stablecoin-pyusd-bank-of-america/">Bank of America: Paypal Stablecoin (PYUSD) Immediate Adoption Might Be Subdued</a></p>
<p>In a recent move that captured the attention of the financial world <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">PayPal Holdings Inc</a> (NASDAQ: PYPL) announced the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-paypal-usd-stablecoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">launch</a> of its own stablecoin PayPal USD (PYUSD).</p>
<p>While the launch of PYUSD is expected to drive efficiencies in payments, Bank of America analysts Alkesh Shah and Andrew Moss suggested in a recent research <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/08/11/paypals-stablecoin-unlikely-to-see-significant-adoption-in-the-near-term-bank-of-america/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a> that the immediate adoption of this stablecoin might not be as substantial as anticipated.</p>
<p>The report highlights a few key challenges that PYUSD could face on its adoption journey. One significant obstacle noted is the growing competition from <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-central-bank-digital-currency-cbdc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Central Bank Digital Currencies</a> (CBDCs). As governments explore their own digital currencies, the adoption landscape could shift, introducing new variables that could influence the adoption of private stablecoins like PYUSD.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the analysts at Bank of America predicted that yield-bearing stablecoins could sway investor preferences away from PYUSD. This prediction is rooted in the evolving interest rate environment.</p>
<p>When interest rates were nearly zero, non-yield-bearing stablecoins like Tether (USDT) and USD Coin (USDC) seemed acceptable to investors. However, the analysts projected that the emergence of yield-bearing stablecoins offering rates above 5% could alter this calculation, diverting interest and investment from PYUSD.</p>
<p>Remarkably, the Bank of America’s research dives into the regulatory aspects of the PYUSD’s introduction. While the introduction of the stablecoin may not significantly affect systemic risk in traditional markets, the paper notes that regulatory issues may arise if non-banks are barred from issuing stablecoins.</p>
<p>The report also suggests a longer-term perspective, acknowledging that while adoption challenges might persist in the short run, the trajectory could evolve as the financial landscape adapts to new offerings. The potential for PYUSD usage may grow as market dynamics alter, provided PayPal handles upcoming difficulties and successfully leverages its large user base.</p>
<h2>The PayPal Stablecoin (PYUSD) Launch and its Promise</h2>
<p>Stablecoins, a category of cryptocurrencies designed to minimize price volatility by pegging their value to a stable asset such as fiat currencies and commodities have gained prominence as a potential bridge between traditional financial and the world of digital currencies.</p>
<p>PayPal&#8217;s PYUSD is pegged to the US dollar and aims to offer users the advantages of cryptocurrencies without the rollercoaster ride of value fluctuations often associated with assets like <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> (BTC) and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a> (ETH).</p>
<p>The core promise of PYUSD lies in its potential to streamline payment processes and enhance user experiences. Traditional cross-border transactions are often riddled with delays, fees, and complexities arising from intermediaries and currency conversions.</p>
<p>With PYUSD, PayPal envisions a future where these barriers are dismantled, allowing for near-instantaneous cross-border transactions with minimal costs.</p>
<p>Overall, the introduction of PayPal stablecoin (PYUSD) represents a groundbreaking development in the realm of stablecoins and digital currencies. While immediate adoption might be constrained by emerging competition and evolving interest rate dynamics, the stablecoin&#8217;s potential to enhance payments efficiency and customer experience remains significant.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-cto-schwartz-fed-paypal/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-stablecoin-pyusd-bank-of-america/">Bank of America: Paypal Stablecoin (PYUSD) Immediate Adoption Might Be Subdued</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple CTO Schwartz Comments on Requirements Issued by Fed on Banks Transacting with PayPal Stablecoin</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-cto-schwartz-fed-paypal/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 13:44:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FinTech News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[david schwartz]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[paypal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[paypal usd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pyusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ripple]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266667</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-cto-schwartz-fed-paypal/">Ripple CTO Schwartz Comments on Requirements Issued by Fed on Banks Transacting with PayPal Stablecoin</a></p>
<p>David Schwartz seems unsurprised that the Fed is reacting negatively to the new stablecoin issued by PayPal.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-cto-schwartz-fed-paypal/">Ripple CTO Schwartz Comments on Requirements Issued by Fed on Banks Transacting with PayPal Stablecoin</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-cto-schwartz-fed-paypal/">Ripple CTO Schwartz Comments on Requirements Issued by Fed on Banks Transacting with PayPal Stablecoin</a></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true"><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ripple-labs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ripple</a>’s chief technology officer (CTO) David Schwartz has commented on the increased regulatory requirements imposed by the US Fed for the country’s cryptocurrency environment. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Schwartz </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/XRPMythBuster/status/1689682547331014659?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1689740895300763648%7Ctwgr%5E2adb958ecca8fa84343beabc167c8d416a47c9d1%7Ctwcon%5Es2_&amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fu.today%2Fripple-cto-reacts-to-new-fed-requirements-for-paypal-stablecoin-pyusd" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">tweeted</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> a shady remark, referring to PayPal’s newly launched stablecoin (PYUSD) and whether or not the company had the necessary approvals. In a recent </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/JohnReedStark/status/1689604991168737280" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">tweet</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, John Reed Stark Consulting President gave some insight into a new </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.federalreserve.gov/supervisionreg/srletters/SR2308.htm" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">announcement</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> from the Federal Reserve. The apex bank and regulator has now mandated that all state banks under the Federal Reserve system must receive a written supervisory nonobjection from the regulator before dealing with stablecoins. This covers all transactions, including holding, issuing, or otherwise transacting with stablecoins.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The announcement also explains the Fed’s expectation from the process of obtaining the nonobjection. It says:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">“To obtain a written notification of supervisory nonobjection, a state member bank should demonstrate that it has established appropriate risk management practices for the proposed activities, including having adequate systems in place to identify, measure, monitor, and control the risks of its activities, and the ability to do so on an ongoing basis.”</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In response to Schwartz’s comment on the announcement, the Ripple CTO was asked whether or not PayPal received the required approval. Schwartz answered and suggested that the Fed was not on PayPal’s list of regulatory approvals required. Although somewhat slyly, the same account then asked Schwartz about PayPal having the right political connections to be “covered in every aspect.” Schwartz then responded saying “so did they,” presumably another sly response at PayPal.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Schwartz Reaction to Fed Requirements</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Schwartz </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/JoelKatz/status/1689679146736312320" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">described</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the Fed’s issue as a “challenger,” suggesting that the requirements may be problematic. The Fed has identified a few risks and expects banks interested in transacting stablecoins to address these problems. According to the publication, these include operational, cybersecurity, liquidity, illicit finance, and consumer compliance risks. According to the Fed, all banks must notify the regulator before partaking in any activity related to stablecoins, including testing. The Fed also says it will continue a supervisory review and “heightened monitoring” of the activities even after issuing the nonobjection.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Reactions continue to pour in following PayPal’s launch of the PYUSD. Yesterday, Coinspeaker </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-house-committee-paypal-stablecoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">reported</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that the leadership of the Financial Services Committee of the US House of Representatives may feel differently about PayPal’s stablecoin. Both Reps. Maxine Waters and Patrick McHenry have called for a solid regulatory framework to guide these stablecoins. However, Waters has warned of inherent risks.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">According to her, a regulatory framework is necessary to assure compliance on the part of the company. She also says it is necessary to protect customers. Waters stated that regulation is essential mainly because PayPal, at 435 million customers worldwide, has more than the online accounts of megabanks. On the other hand, McHenry is more in favor. Although he also believes in a regulatory framework, the chairman sees stablecoins differently. McHenry described them as a “pillar of our 21st-century payments system.” </span><a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/canada-storage-crypto-assets/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-cto-schwartz-fed-paypal/">Ripple CTO Schwartz Comments on Requirements Issued by Fed on Banks Transacting with PayPal Stablecoin</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Canada to Create Solutions for Storing Seized Crypto Assets</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/canada-storage-crypto-assets/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 12:45:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Canadian RCMP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Fraud]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[matic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[polygon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sol]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[solana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[тае]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266657</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/canada-storage-crypto-assets/">Canada to Create Solutions for Storing Seized Crypto Assets</a></p>
<p>While the primary focus is on cryptocurrencies, the RCMP acknowledges the importance of including NFTs in its approach.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/canada-storage-crypto-assets/">Canada to Create Solutions for Storing Seized Crypto Assets</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/canada-storage-crypto-assets/">Canada to Create Solutions for Storing Seized Crypto Assets</a></p>
<p>In Canada, the Royal Canadian Mounted Police (RCMP) and Shared Services Canada (SSC) are collaborating to develop a groundbreaking digital asset solution aimed at streamlining the seizure and storage of crypto and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Non-Fungible Tokens</a> (NFTs) from multiple public blockchains.</p>
<p>On August 10, the RCMP <a href="https://ised-isde.canada.ca/site/innovative-solutions-canada/en/digital-asset-repository" target="_blank" rel="noopener">opened</a> a tender inviting applications from technology providers capable of developing a centralized repository solution. This move marks a significant stride in adapting law enforcement methods to the evolving digital era.</p>
<h2>The Essential Features of the Crypto Storage Solution</h2>
<p>The tender released by the RCMP outlines a comprehensive list of seventeen key features they seek from the future repository solution. Among these requirements is the capability to process transactions for the top 20 cryptocurrencies by market capitalization.</p>
<p>This demonstrates a forward-thinking approach, ensuring that the RCMP’s solution remains relevant as the crypto landscape evolves. Recognizing the ever-evolving nature of the digital asset landscape, the RCMP said the solution must not only onboard existing blockchains but also accommodate new ones that may emerge over time.</p>
<p>An equally significant aspect of this initiative is accessibility. The RCMP intends to grant authorized users access to the repository&#8217;s data, enabling efficient collaboration between law enforcement agencies and other stakeholders. Such accessibility could potentially enhance the effectiveness of investigations and asset recovery processes.</p>
<p>While the primary focus is on cryptocurrencies, the RCMP acknowledges the importance of including NFTs in its approach. Consequently, the repository is expected to handle NFTs created on <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a> (ETH), Solana (SOL), and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/matic-network/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Polygon</a> (MATIC). This emphasizes the adaptability of the system under consideration and its ability to accommodate various digital asset types.</p>
<p>Other features in the repository include transaction logging, robust security measures, automated verification, and a Web interface.</p>
<h2>The Changing Landscape in Crypto Fraud</h2>
<p>The RCMP’s recent pursuit of a secure digital asset solution is a proactive response to the surge in criminal activities involving cryptocurrencies and NFTs. The rise of cryptocurrencies has ushered in a new paradigm of financial transactions, with both legitimate and illicit applications being recorded.</p>
<p>While cryptocurrencies provide greater privacy and protection for legitimate users, it have also become a favorite way for criminals to participate in activities such as ransomware attacks, internet scams, money laundering, and fraud.</p>
<p>This not only poses a threat to individual financial security but also undermines the integrity of financial systems and erodes public trust in digital assets. Recognizing the urgency of tackling this emerging challenge, the RCMP’s decision to seek an advanced digital asset solution marks a pivotal moment in law enforcement&#8217;s adaptation to the digital age.</p>
<p>Recently, Canadian law enforcement began employing specialist tools from Chainalysis to trace crypto while investigating cybercrime. Local police may now trace blockchain transactions, identify suspects, and discover where funds have been put.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/visa-ethereum-gas-fees/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/canada-storage-crypto-assets/">Canada to Create Solutions for Storing Seized Crypto Assets</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>VISA Allows Users to Pay Ethereum Gas Fees via Credit Card</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/visa-ethereum-gas-fees/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 12:35:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[visa]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266658</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/visa-ethereum-gas-fees/">VISA Allows Users to Pay Ethereum Gas Fees via Credit Card</a></p>
<p>Visa's solution revolves around Ethereum's ERC-4337 account abstraction standard and the utilization of a "paymaster" smart contract feature which allows off-chain settlements of gas fees. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/visa-ethereum-gas-fees/">VISA Allows Users to Pay Ethereum Gas Fees via Credit Card</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/visa-ethereum-gas-fees/">VISA Allows Users to Pay Ethereum Gas Fees via Credit Card</a></p>
<p>On Thursday, August 10, payments giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/visa-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Visa Inc</a> made an important announcement allowing users to pay the on-chain Ethereum gas fees directly in fiat currencies, either using a credit or debit card.</p>
<p>Visa said that it first conducted the test on the Ethereum Goerli testnet by using a paymaster contract in order to sponsor gas fees on behalf of users. Thus, users can send blockchain transactions without having to worry about maintaining an ETH balance. As per Visa, the contracts would make transactions accessible to a wide range of users. Commenting on the development, Visa’s technical team <a href="https://usa.visa.com/solutions/crypto/paying-blockchain-gas-fees-with-card.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">wrote</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Our experiment aims to offer a promising approach to substantially addressing the challenges of blockchain-based transactions. By leveraging the innovative concept of a paymaster, in conjunction with account abstraction and the ERC-4337 standard, we explored the potential for a process that could redefine blockchain-based transactions.”</p></blockquote>
<p>A paymaster contract is a specialized variant of a smart contract in the blockchain ecosystem, intended for overseeing the settlement of gas fees.</p>
<p>The company has proposed that merchants or decentralized applications (Dapps) have the option to implement their own paymaster solution. Alternatively, established wallet and paymaster service providers could present a gas fee payment option using cards in conjunction with their existing paymaster services.</p>
<p>This initiative is a continuation of Visa&#8217;s ongoing efforts in the field. The company has been actively exploring methods to enhance the user-friendliness and accessibility of blockchain-based payments. At the beginning of 2023, Visa started converting digital assets into fiat payments on the Ethereum blockchain.</p>
<h2>Using Visa Card Payment for Gas Fee</h2>
<p>In the usual Ethereum usage process, individuals acquire <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ETH</a> through exchanges or on-ramp services. Then, they transfer the acquired ETH to their wallets to ensure they have enough to cover fluctuating gas fees. However, this dynamic gas pricing often leads to situations of overpayment or insufficient ETH supply, introducing complexity and challenges.</p>
<p>Visa&#8217;s solution revolves around Ethereum&#8217;s ERC-4337 account abstraction standard and the utilization of a &#8220;paymaster&#8221; smart contract feature. This approach enables off-chain settlements of gas fees. The five-step sequence is as follows:</p>
<ol>
<li>A user initiates an Ethereum transaction using their wallet, which forwards the transaction details to the paymaster web service.</li>
<li>The web service calculates the gas fee&#8217;s cost and charges the user&#8217;s Visa card using Visa&#8217;s Cybersource system for payment processing.</li>
<li>Once completed, the web service sends a digital signature back to the wallet, validating the payment. This validation is effective within a specified timeframe.</li>
<li>The wallet attaches this signature to the transaction and submits it to the Ethereum network.</li>
<li>The paymaster smart contract then verifies the signature&#8217;s authenticity and covers the gas fee, facilitating the transaction processing.</li>
</ol>
<p>This series of actions enables users to pay gas fees using their Visa card off-chain. It also eliminates the necessity to hold ETH solely for fee payments. This approach greatly streamlines the user experience, enhancing the convenience of transactions.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gold-prices-hit-2500-recession/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/visa-ethereum-gas-fees/">VISA Allows Users to Pay Ethereum Gas Fees via Credit Card</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gold Prices Expected to Hit $2,500 as Recession Fears Continue</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/gold-prices-hit-2500-recession/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 12:22:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Commodities & Futures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gold]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266643</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gold-prices-hit-2500-recession/">Gold Prices Expected to Hit $2,500 as Recession Fears Continue</a></p>
<p>Analysts and stakeholders expect gold prices to rise as the year runs out because of macroeconomic factors and recession risks.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gold-prices-hit-2500-recession/">Gold Prices Expected to Hit $2,500 as Recession Fears Continue</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gold-prices-hit-2500-recession/">Gold Prices Expected to Hit $2,500 as Recession Fears Continue</a></p>
<p>There is a general bullishness around gold prices as the yellow metal is on course to an all-time high in 2024. Analysts believe that the new record is likely because of economic uncertainty which indicates a possible recession, and a potential reduction in interest rates.</p>
<p>According to TD Securities’ managing director and global head of commodity strategy Bart Melek, gold will likely hit $2,100 as 2023 ends or early in 2024. Melek believes that a softened stance towards continuously increasing interest rates would be bullish for the yellow metal. Melek is also bullish because gold has performed better than most other assets over the last 12 months.</p>
<p>Generally, many people consider gold a safe haven asset and are likely to buy more in times of economic instability. According to a CME Group <a href="https://www.cmegroup.com/openmarkets/metals/2023/How-Does-Gold-Perform-with-Inflation-Stagflation-and-Recession.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a>, gold performed about 37% better than the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-the-sp-500-index/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">S&amp;P 500</a> in six of the last eight recessions. This suggests that gold is likely to soar higher in the event of an official recession.</p>
<p>Another stakeholder believes gold will hit $2,500 in a “couple of years”. According to Randy Smallwood, the CEO of Canadian company Wheaten Precious Metals, a recession would be good for gold. Smallwood is bullish because he expects some drawbacks in the economies of both the US and China.</p>
<p>More bullish predictions continue to pour in for gold. One indicator of a rise in spot prices is the inverse relationship between gold and interest rates. When interest rates increase, people tend to move away from gold to other more attractive investment assets like bonds. This eventually reduces the demand for gold.</p>
<p>Gold is trading at $1,916 as of writing time.</p>
<h2>More Predictions for Gold Prices</h2>
<p>Singaporean banking giant UOB is also bullish on gold prices. According to the head of markets strategy, global economics, and markets research, Heng Koon How, the Fed will likely stop increasing interest rates soon:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Key driver in our positive outlook for gold is anticipated peak in Fed rate hiking cycle as well as upcoming topping out of US Dollar strength.”</p></blockquote>
<p>The UOB exec also predicted higher prices and that a strong demand for gold would come as people regain their economic spending power. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“We also see a return of physical gold jewelry demand from China and India as both economies stabilize and retail spending returns.”</p></blockquote>
<p>In a recent report, Citi noted that retail demand for gold from China has been buoyant especially compared to other goods. According to Citi&#8217;s head of commodities strategy Aakash Doshi in a report, gold demand from China was only slightly lower than 200 tons. Doshi notes that this the “strongest seasonal” seen since 2015. The report expects the demand to hit 700 tons by the end of the year. This project would confirm a 22% increase year on year.</p>
<p>Wheaton CEO Smallwood also stated that there is an increase in demand. According to him, customers are getting more gold in all forms, including coins, jewelry, and bars.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/robinhood-investors-appeals-court/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gold-prices-hit-2500-recession/">Gold Prices Expected to Hit $2,500 as Recession Fears Continue</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Robinhood Beats Investors Again as Appeal Court Upholds Earlier Rule in Meme Stock Trading Suit</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/robinhood-investors-appeals-court/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 12:19:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meme stock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meme stock trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[robinhood]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266636</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/robinhood-investors-appeals-court/">Robinhood Beats Investors Again as Appeal Court Upholds Earlier Rule in Meme Stock Trading Suit</a></p>
<p>Robinhood had earlier motioned for the arguments against it to be completely dismissed.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/robinhood-investors-appeals-court/">Robinhood Beats Investors Again as Appeal Court Upholds Earlier Rule in Meme Stock Trading Suit</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/robinhood-investors-appeals-court/">Robinhood Beats Investors Again as Appeal Court Upholds Earlier Rule in Meme Stock Trading Suit</a></p>
<p>The federal appeals court of the United States has yet again dismissed a class-action lawsuit against online brokerage firm <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/robinhood/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Robinhood Markets</a>. This follows after 16 investors alleged that the platform did not allow them to buy 13 “meme stocks” during a January 2021 social media frenzy that sent prices to the moon.</p>
<p>According to the complainants, the restriction meant that they could not enjoy any profits. The decision also ended up causing the share prices of these stocks to plunge, they added.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the suit, which began in September 2021, only lasted for so long. By January 2022, Robinhood motioned for the complaint to be dismissed, and the court granted that request. In its motion at the time, the firm noted that the plaintiffs failed to state any claim.</p>
<p>Still doubtful about the earlier ruling in the Robinhood case, the plaintiffs then proceeded to the US appeals court in March 2023 to seek redress.</p>
<p>As it turns out, the investors may just have hit another setback. US Appellate Court Judge Britt Grant has <a href="https://www.courthousenews.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Juncadelia-v-Robinhood-order-11th-circuit.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">upheld</a> the earlier ruling, claiming that the case lacks legal merit.</p>
<p>Judge Grant clarified that Robinhood, according to its customer agreement, is permitted to restrict any transaction. That is, the platform may decide whether or not to accept a trade offer.</p>
<h2>Is Robinhood Finally in the Clear?</h2>
<p>The court may have established that Robinhood had no hand in the arguments against it. But that is only for the time being.</p>
<p>The investors may decide to take the case up a notch by heading to the US Supreme Court, in what would be a final showdown. To do that, however, they must first file a petition for a “writ of certiorari”, which is a document asking the Supreme Court to review the case.</p>
<p>But out of over 7,000 cases that the Supreme Court reviews, it only takes up about 100-150 cases. Therefore, it is not very likely that the investors will have one more day in court over this case.</p>
<p>As of publication, lawyers from both ends – Robinhood and the plaintiffs, have yet to comment on the development.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/huawei-revenue-h1-2023/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/robinhood-investors-appeals-court/">Robinhood Beats Investors Again as Appeal Court Upholds Earlier Rule in Meme Stock Trading Suit</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4244 metric#misses=51 metric#hit-ratio=98.8 metric#bytes=1070106 metric#prefetches=216 metric#store-reads=34 metric#store-writes=12 metric#store-hits=226 metric#store-misses=12 metric#sql-queries=44 metric#ms-total=1383.39 metric#ms-cache=7.79 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.1732 metric#ms-cache-ratio=0.6 -->