<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 12:13:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Tencent Reports Solid Q2 Results despite Failing to Meet Expectations</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tencent-q2-results-failing-meet-expectations/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tencent-q2-results-failing-meet-expectations/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 12:05:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tencent]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tencent music]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267137</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tencent-q2-results-failing-meet-expectations/">Tencent Reports Solid Q2 Results despite Failing to Meet Expectations</a></p>
<p>Although slightly below the expected 32.3 billion yuan, Tencent's profitability demonstrates its financial resilience in the face of economic turmoil.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tencent-q2-results-failing-meet-expectations/">Tencent Reports Solid Q2 Results despite Failing to Meet Expectations</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tencent-q2-results-failing-meet-expectations/">Tencent Reports Solid Q2 Results despite Failing to Meet Expectations</a></p>
<p>Chinese tech giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/tencent/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tencent Holdings</a> has released its second-quarter financial earnings report for the year. The company reported revenue of 149.2 billion yuan ($20.5 billion), showing an 11% increase compared to the 132 billion yuan it posted in the same period last year. Despite the current macroeconomic conditions in China and evolving market dynamics, the company&#8217;s revenue growth remains strong.</p>
<p>Bloomberg analysts had earlier projected Tencent&#8217;s revenue to reach 152 billion yuan. However, the Chinese firm, operating the world&#8217;s largest gaming business and owner of the social media platform WeChat, reported lower-than-expected income, missing market expectations by a slight margin.</p>
<h2>Tencent&#8217;s Gaming Revenue: Domestic Stability and Global Growth</h2>
<p>According to the <a href="https://static.www.tencent.com/uploads/2023/08/16/f283f2dfd05151ae7659e7a8e3d667ef.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announcement</a>, Tencent&#8217;s Q2 profits reached 26.2 billion yuan, marking an impressive 41% surge from last year. Although slightly below the expected 32.3 billion yuan, Tencent&#8217;s profitability demonstrates its financial resilience in the face of economic turmoil.</p>
<p>The company&#8217;s co-founder and chief executive officer, Pony Ma Huateng, said in a statement that the company is committed to boosting revenue quality and margins through innovative AI initiatives.</p>
<p>&#8220;We will continue to drive innovation, including through generative AI, where we will provide a library of models to our partners via our Tencent Cloud Model-as-a-Service (MaaS) offering, as well as refining our proprietary foundation model,&#8221; Huateng.</p>
<p>Tencent&#8217;s domestic gaming revenue held steady at 31.8 billion yuan year-on-year due to the integration of &#8220;less-commercial content&#8221; in key titles. However, this phenomenon is anticipated to be short-lived, with a projected resumption of year-on-year growth in the third quarter.</p>
<p>Revenue from its international games unit surged by 19% to 12.7 billion yuan, powered by popular games like Valorant. With a focus on bolstering global gaming revenue amidst weak domestic sales and regulatory challenges in China, Tencent expressed optimism about recovering from the pandemic-induced downturn in mobile gaming activity.</p>
<h2>Tencent Music Entertainment Group Scores 5.5% Profit Growth</h2>
<p>The company&#8217;s entertainment subsidiary, Tencent Music Entertainment Group, dubbed the &#8220;Spotify of China&#8221;, also <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tencent-music-q2-2023-revenue/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a> a 5.5% increase in its quarterly revenue. The growth was attributed to a rise in user subscriptions. However, the company has warned about its future income due to stricter controls on live-streaming activities.</p>
<p>Tony Yip, the company&#8217;s chief strategy officer, told Reuters during a phone call that Tencent Music Entertainment Group is taking steps to revamp its live-streaming business to exert better control over potential risks that might arise down the line.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, while the company&#8217;s revenue growth remains robust, Tencent has further reduced its headcount. During the first quarter report that ended in March, the Chinese company had about 106,221 employees. However, this quarter, the number decreased to 104,503 at the end of June.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/dutch-economy-recession/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tencent-q2-results-failing-meet-expectations/">Tencent Reports Solid Q2 Results despite Failing to Meet Expectations</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tencent-q2-results-failing-meet-expectations/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dutch Economy Enters Recession amid Consecutive Contractions</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/dutch-economy-recession/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/dutch-economy-recession/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 11:53:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Netherlands]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Recession]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267129</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/dutch-economy-recession/">Dutch Economy Enters Recession amid Consecutive Contractions</a></p>
<p>The Dutch economy, once a beacon of robust growth and stability, has hit a rough patch as it enters a recession following two consecutive quarters of contraction.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/dutch-economy-recession/">Dutch Economy Enters Recession amid Consecutive Contractions</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/dutch-economy-recession/">Dutch Economy Enters Recession amid Consecutive Contractions</a></p>
<p>The preliminary estimate <a href="https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/dutch-economy-enters-recession-inflation-bites-2023-08-16/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">published</a> by Statistics Netherlands revealed a 0.3% decline in the second quarter of the year, following a 0.4% contraction in the first quarter. The Dutch economy’s recent downturn comes as a surprise to many, especially considering its rapid rebound from the economic slump induced by the COVID-19 pandemic. Throughout 2021 and 2022, the Netherlands achieved yearly economic growth of about 5%.</p>
<p>This strong performance at the time was largely attributed to successful <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/azn-stock-up-0-68-now-astrazeneca-to-deliver-400m-doses-of-covid-19-vaccine-to-europe/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">vaccination campaigns</a>, increased consumer spending, and a resurgence in trade activities. The Netherlands was admired for its ability to adapt and emerge from the pandemic-induced crisis with resilience.</p>
<p>However, the consecutive quarterly contractions in the first half of 2023 have raised questions about the sustainability of this growth trajectory. Economists and analysts are now grappling to understand the underlying causes of this sudden reversal.</p>
<h2>Factors Influencing the Dutch Economy’s Recession</h2>
<p>As the first recession since the pandemic, it is imperative to dissect the contributing factors to gain a comprehensive understanding of the situation. A closer examination reveals that a drop in consumer spending and exports, exacerbated by surging inflation, lies at the heart of the Netherlands’ economic challenges.</p>
<p>The report highlighted that consumer spending, which is a key indicator of economic vigor, has suffered a significant blow, plunging by 1.6%. This decline is particularly concerning as it reflects a reduction in the purchasing power of households, indicative of broader economic uncertainty.</p>
<p>The surge in inflation, which has driven up costs across the board, has prompted individuals to tighten their belts and curtail discretionary expenditures. High prices for necessities like food and energy bills have caused people to reconsider their spending habits, resulting in lower overall consumption.</p>
<p>The Netherlands, renowned for its robust trade network, has also seen its exports shrink by 0.7% compared to the previous quarter. This drop in exports is indicative of global supply chain disruptions that have plagued economies since the outbreak of the pandemic.</p>
<p>The delicate web of international trade on which the Dutch economy depends has been stretched by disruptions, impeding the flow of products and services. As a result, exporters are dealing with delays, increased costs, and decreased demand from trading partners dealing with their own economic difficulties.</p>
<p>Inflation, a universal concern across economies, has played a pivotal role in the Dutch recession. While the country’s inflation rate peaked at 14.5% in September of the previous year, the figures have subsequently declined.</p>
<p>However, even with a decline, inflation remains relatively high, hovering around 6% in the second quarter of 2023. This <a href="https://tradingeconomics.com/netherlands/inflation-cpi" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">persistent inflationary pressure</a> has magnified the strain on household budgets, eroding purchasing power and contributing to the decline in consumer spending.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/intel-drops-tower-acquisition-us-china-tension/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/dutch-economy-recession/">Dutch Economy Enters Recession amid Consecutive Contractions</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/dutch-economy-recession/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Intel Drops $5.4B Tower Acquisition Deal amid Growing Tension between US and China</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/intel-drops-tower-acquisition-us-china-tension/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/intel-drops-tower-acquisition-us-china-tension/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 10:46:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Deals News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[intel]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tower semiconductor]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267113</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/intel-drops-tower-acquisition-us-china-tension/">Intel Drops $5.4B Tower Acquisition Deal amid Growing Tension between US and China</a></p>
<p>According to Intel Chief Executive Pat Gelsinger, all efforts to get the Tower deal approved by the regulators proved abortive.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/intel-drops-tower-acquisition-us-china-tension/">Intel Drops $5.4B Tower Acquisition Deal amid Growing Tension between US and China</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/intel-drops-tower-acquisition-us-china-tension/">Intel Drops $5.4B Tower Acquisition Deal amid Growing Tension between US and China</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/intel/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Intel Corporation</a> (NASDAQ: INTC) has announced that it will not be pursuing the acquisition of Israeli contract chipmaker Tower Semiconductor any further. According to a <a href="https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20230815632091/en/Intel-Announces-Termination-of-Tower-Semiconductor-Acquisition" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">press release</a>, the deal, which expired on Tuesday, August 15, will see Intel pay a termination fee of $353 million to Towers. However, the chipmaker assures that the contract termination has been mutually agreed to.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, sources with inside knowledge of the matter have claimed that the decision to drop the deal borders on Intel&#8217;s failure to secure regulatory approval from China. That is after signing the $5.4 billion acquisition deal over 18 months ago.</p>
<h2>Growing Tension between China and the US</h2>
<p>For what it&#8217;s worth, the situation only goes to prove further, that relations between the United States and China have recently deteriorated. That is especially in the aspect of trade and technology. And now, even <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-chip-bans-micron/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">corporate deal-making</a> such as the Intel/Tower acquisition is being affected.</p>
<p>DuPont De Nemours is another company that had a similar experience with Chinese regulators. Last year, Dupont also dropped an already agreed $5.2 billion acquisition deal for electronics materials maker Rogers Corp. And its reasons are quite similar to Intel&#8217;s. At the time, Dupont also claimed that there were delays in getting regulatory the Chinese regulators to approve the deal.</p>
<p>It remains unclear whether regulators would have approved the deal if Intel and Tower had extended the contract. However, Intel appears to be leaving nothing to chance.</p>
<p>According to Intel Chief Executive Pat Gelsinger, all efforts to get the Tower deal approved by the regulators proved abortive. Gelsinger, who visited the country as recently as a month ago, says even his meeting with government officials has not yielded any results either.</p>
<h2>Intel to Focus on Foundry Business</h2>
<p>According to Intel&#8217;s CEO, the goal is to regain transistor and power performance leadership by 2025. He said in a statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Our foundry efforts are critical to unlocking the full potential of IDM 2.0, and we continue to drive forward on all facets of our strategy.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Away from regulations, Intel will divert its attention to its foundry business, which makes chips for other companies. Intel will hope to achieve this, by investing heavily in its foundry, says Gelsinger.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-initiative-us-lawmaker-ethics-violation/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/intel-drops-tower-acquisition-us-china-tension/">Intel Drops $5.4B Tower Acquisition Deal amid Growing Tension between US and China</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/intel-drops-tower-acquisition-us-china-tension/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Political Initiative from Coinbase Features US Lawmaker with Ethics Violation</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-initiative-us-lawmaker-ethics-violation/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-initiative-us-lawmaker-ethics-violation/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 10:20:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267127</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-initiative-us-lawmaker-ethics-violation/">A Political Initiative from Coinbase Features US Lawmaker with Ethics Violation</a></p>
<p>Rep. David Schweikert, listed as a lawmaker with "very supportive" views on crypto in the United States, reached a settlement requiring him to pay $175,000 in connection to breaches of House ethics regulations.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-initiative-us-lawmaker-ethics-violation/">A Political Initiative from Coinbase Features US Lawmaker with Ethics Violation</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-initiative-us-lawmaker-ethics-violation/">A Political Initiative from Coinbase Features US Lawmaker with Ethics Violation</a></p>
<p>US-based cryptocurrency exchange <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase</a> has been recently working on actively advocating for crypto holders to directly speak to lawmakers. In its latest push, Coinbase <a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/coinbase-political-initiative-features-lawmaker-admited-ethics-violations" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">featured</a> a House of Representatives member who has been previously facing charges of 11 ethics violations.</p>
<p>By August 15th, over 54,000 people had joined Coinbase&#8217;s &#8220;Stand with Crypto Alliance&#8221; to connect with US lawmakers on the national level. This program enables users to track the &#8220;crypto sentiment&#8221; of members in the US Senate and House of Representatives.</p>
<p>As of the time of this report, the initiative&#8217;s webpage displayed Senator Elizabeth Warren and Representative Brad Sherman as being &#8220;strongly against&#8221; crypto policies, while Representatives Josh Gottheimer, Ritchie Torres, and David Schweikert were categorized as &#8220;very supportive&#8221;. Warren has often expressed concerns linking crypto to illicit activities like the fentanyl trade in China. Torres urged the US Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) to limit its enforcement actions against crypto firms.</p>
<p>According to the information provided by Stand with Crypto, Schweikert has supported three pro-crypto bills during his tenure and has made four statements regarding digital assets. The alliance mentioned that &#8220;Members of Congress may have views you strongly agree or disagree with&#8221;, without specifically mentioning any non-crypto policy positions.</p>
<h2>Crypto Donations and Campaign Finance</h2>
<p>In 2020, the House Ethics Committee imposed a $50,000 fine on Schweikert for violating campaign finance rules that breached House ethics guidelines. In 2022, the Federal Election Commission fined the Arizona representative $125,000 for related allegations. The violations centered around not reporting loans and misusing campaign funds for personal purposes. Cointelegraph contacted Schweikert&#8217;s office for comment, but no response was received at the time of this report.</p>
<p>Among the donations received by the Stand with Crypto Alliance, there was a contribution of over $215 from a crypto user using the X (formerly <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/twitter/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Twitter</a>) handle &#8220;Jerry Mander&#8221;, which is a play on the term &#8220;gerrymander&#8221;, referring to manipulating district boundaries for political advantage. Additionally, there was a $191.98 donation from an unverified account that might be associated with Roger Bartlett, Coinbase’s head of institutional operations solutions and Coinbase Treasury.</p>
<p>This political initiative represents the latest effort by Coinbase to encourage crypto users to support &#8220;pro-crypto candidates&#8221; in the United States. Currently, the exchange is facing a lawsuit from the SEC over alleged unregistered securities offerings, prompting calls from many lawmakers and industry advocates to dismiss the case.</p>
<div id="gtx-trans" style="position: absolute; left: 66px; top: 57.3333px;">
<div class="gtx-trans-icon"></div>
</div>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-inflation-sharp-drop-july/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-initiative-us-lawmaker-ethics-violation/">A Political Initiative from Coinbase Features US Lawmaker with Ethics Violation</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-initiative-us-lawmaker-ethics-violation/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>UK Inflation Sees Sharp Drop in July as Core and Services Show Mixed Trends</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-inflation-sharp-drop-july/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-inflation-sharp-drop-july/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 09:54:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bank of england]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cpi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[uk inflation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267119</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-inflation-sharp-drop-july/">UK Inflation Sees Sharp Drop in July as Core and Services Show Mixed Trends</a></p>
<p>While the easing of headline inflation is welcome news for consumers, experts are paying closer attention to the underlying trends. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-inflation-sharp-drop-july/">UK Inflation Sees Sharp Drop in July as Core and Services Show Mixed Trends</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-inflation-sharp-drop-july/">UK Inflation Sees Sharp Drop in July as Core and Services Show Mixed Trends</a></p>
<p>The United Kingdom&#8217;s inflation rate took a step back in July, registering an annual increase of 6.8%, a considerable decline from the 7.9% <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-inflation-falls-june/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">recorded</a> in June. The new UK inflation rate is the lowest level the country has seen since February 2022. On a monthly basis, the country&#8217;s Consumer Price Index (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-are-the-consumer-price-index-cpi-and-the-producer-price-index-ppi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CPI</a>) dropped by 0.4%, in line with expectations.</p>
<p>According to the latest data <a href="https://www.ons.gov.uk/economy/inflationandpriceindices/bulletins/consumerpriceinflation/july2023#:~:text=The%20Consumer%20Prices%20Index%20(CPI)%20annual%20inflation%20rate%20for%20housing,price%20cap%20in%20July%202023." target="_blank" rel="noopener">published</a> by the Office for National Statistics (ONS) on August 16, the cooling of inflation aligns with market predictions. While the headline figure is finding some stability, underlying trends in core inflation and services inflation send mixed signals.</p>
<h2>Gas and Electricity Prices Drive Down Inflation Rates</h2>
<p>The reduction in headline inflation was influenced mainly by declining gas and electricity prices, which played a vital role in driving down the overall index. Additionally, easing food price inflation contributed to the broader drop in consumer prices.</p>
<p>Despite this moderation, it&#8217;s crucial to note that the UK still maintains one of the highest inflation rates in Western Europe, surpassed only by Iceland and Austria.</p>
<p>While the easing of headline inflation is welcome news for consumers, experts are paying closer attention to the underlying trends.</p>
<p>Core inflation, which excludes the more volatile elements of energy, food, alcohol, and tobacco, remained stubbornly high at 6.9% year-on-year in July, holding steady from the previous month. This slight upward trend in core inflation contrasts with predictions of a 6.8% reading. This steadiness indicates that certain sectors of the economy continue to experience upward price pressures.</p>
<p>The services sector, a vital contributor to the UK economy, saw inflation rise to 7.4% in July, up from 7.2% in June. This upward movement in service inflation raises questions about the resilience of some industries and the potential impact on consumer behavior.</p>
<h2>Government Efforts to Curb Inflation is Working</h2>
<p>According to <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/08/16/uk-headline-inflation-rate-drops-sharply-to-6point8percent-in-july-in-line-with-expectations.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">CNBC,</a> the data published by ONS prompted responses from economic experts and officials. Ruth Gregory, an economist at consultancy Capital Economics, emphasized that the UK central bank, the Bank of England (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/bank-of-england/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BoE</a>), has more work to do given the unexpected strength in wage growth and services inflation.</p>
<p>While responding to the ONS report, Finance Minister Jeremy Hunt said falling inflation shows the government&#8217;s efforts towards the economy are &#8220;working&#8221;. He further stated that while efforts to curb price rises show results, there is still a journey ahead to reach the desired finish line.</p>
<p>&#8220;We must stick to our plan to halve inflation this year and get it back to the 2 percent target as soon as possible,&#8221; Hunt said.</p>
<h2>BoE to Raise Interest Rates</h2>
<p>The ONS data also provided an intriguing backdrop to the ongoing deliberations of the BOE. The central bank has closely monitored core inflation and service prices as indicators of potential economic trends.</p>
<p>The persistence of elevated core inflation hints at potential challenges in the labor market and the broader supply chain, creating a dilemma for the central bank as it seeks to balance managing inflation and supporting economic growth.</p>
<p>With inflation exceeding the 2% target, the BoE&#8217;s efforts to manage monetary policy have become more complex.</p>
<p>During a BoE monetary policy meeting earlier this month, the government decided to raise the interest rate by a quarter percentage point to 5.25%, signaling the 14th consecutive increase since the last <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-raises-interest-13th-time/">hike</a> in June 2022. The move shows the central bank&#8217;s commitment to addressing inflationary pressures.</p>
<p>The Monetary Policy Committee on the other hand believes that the increase will likely be the end of high-interest rates.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/stocks-fall-global-economic-worries-weigh/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-inflation-sharp-drop-july/">UK Inflation Sees Sharp Drop in July as Core and Services Show Mixed Trends</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-inflation-sharp-drop-july/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stocks Fall as Global Economic Worries Weigh on Wall Street</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/stocks-fall-global-economic-worries-weigh/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/stocks-fall-global-economic-worries-weigh/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 08:45:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wall Street]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dow jones]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jpmorgan chase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nasdaq composite]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stock market]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267107</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/stocks-fall-global-economic-worries-weigh/">Stocks Fall as Global Economic Worries Weigh on Wall Street</a></p>
<p>US financial giants witnessed their shares slide as credit rating downgrades cast a shadow over the sector.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/stocks-fall-global-economic-worries-weigh/">Stocks Fall as Global Economic Worries Weigh on Wall Street</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/stocks-fall-global-economic-worries-weigh/">Stocks Fall as Global Economic Worries Weigh on Wall Street</a></p>
<p>In a volatile trading session on Tuesday, stocks experienced a significant downturn as strain over the global economic outlook coupled with a decline in United States banking sector performance, exerted pressure on Wall Street.</p>
<h2>A Closer Look at Market Index Performance</h2>
<p>Reports <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/08/14/stock-market-today-live-updates.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reveal</a> that the stock market’s stumble was largely attributed to mounting concerns about the global economy, with China’s economic condition drawing particular attention.</p>
<p>These concerns resonated across the international financial landscape, impacting investor sentiment. As the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-the-dow-jones-industrial-average-index-djia/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Dow Jones Industrial Average</a> (INDEXDJX: .DJI) plummeted by 361.24 points, equivalent to a 1.02% drop, the prevailing unease was evident as its value is now pegged at 34,946.39.</p>
<p>Additionally, the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-the-sp-500-index/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">S&amp;P 500 Index</a> (INDEXSP: .INX) retreated by 1.16%, closing at 4,437.86 points. This marked a pivotal moment as the index fell below its 50-day moving average, a technical indicator that is often closely monitored by traders. Similarly, the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-the-nasdaq-composite-index/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Nasdaq Composite</a> (INDEXNASDAQ: .IXIC) experienced a decline, closing down by 1.14% at 13,631.05 points.</p>
<p>US financial giants also witnessed their shares slide as credit rating downgrades cast a shadow over the sector. <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/jpmorgan-chase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">JPMorgan Chase &amp; Co</a> (NYSE: JPM) and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/wells-fargo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Wells Fargo &amp; Co</a> (NYSE: WFC) saw their shares dip by 2%, while <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/bank-of-america/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bank of America Corp</a> (NYSE: BAC) shares declined by 3%. This move came after credit rating agency Fitch Ratings issued a warning that it might downgrade the credit ratings of several banks, including JPMorgan Chase.</p>
<p>The SPDR S&amp;P Regional Banking ETF (KBE) fell around 3% in trade on Tuesday. The drop followed remarks by Minneapolis Federal Reserve President Neel Kashkari, who pushed for stricter capital regulations. Kashkari expressed concern about potential vulnerabilities in the banking industry if inflation is not sufficiently controlled and interest rates are raised further.</p>
<h2>China’s Economic Data Deepens Global Strain</h2>
<p>The report further highlighted that global investor sentiment took another hit as China reported underwhelming economic data. China’s industrial production increased by 3.7% year on year in July, falling short of expectations. Additionally, retail sales growth was weaker than anticipated.</p>
<p>In response to these challenges, the People’s Bank of China (PBoC) unexpectedly lowered interest rates by 15 basis points to 2.5% from 2.65%. However, these measures failed to reassure investors and instead raised concerns about the struggling real estate market in China. The uncertainties surrounding China&#8217;s economic direction heightened market anxiety.</p>
<p>Against this backdrop of financial sector struggles and global economic concerns, earnings season for retailers commenced with a mix of results. <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/home-depot/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Home Depot Inc</a> (NYSE: HD) <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/home-depot-q2-2023-earnings/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">announced</a> earnings per share and revenue that exceeded analyst expectations, resulting in a little increase in its stock price.</p>
<p>Amidst the prevailing uncertainty, the July retail sales report in the United States revealed a silver lining. Retail sales increased by 0.7% month over month, beating economists’ expectations of a 0.4% increase.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/stellar-invests-moneygram-fintech-push/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/stocks-fall-global-economic-worries-weigh/">Stocks Fall as Global Economic Worries Weigh on Wall Street</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/stocks-fall-global-economic-worries-weigh/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stellar Foundation Invests in MoneyGram in a Push for FinTech</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/stellar-invests-moneygram-fintech-push/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/stellar-invests-moneygram-fintech-push/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 08:26:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FinTech News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investors News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[denelle dixon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[moneygram]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stellar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stellar foundation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267083</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/stellar-invests-moneygram-fintech-push/">Stellar Foundation Invests in MoneyGram in a Push for FinTech</a></p>
<p>Stellar Development Foundation said that the investment in MoneyGram in growing its digital business, researching blockchain technology, and contributing in other ways. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/stellar-invests-moneygram-fintech-push/">Stellar Foundation Invests in MoneyGram in a Push for FinTech</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/stellar-invests-moneygram-fintech-push/">Stellar Foundation Invests in MoneyGram in a Push for FinTech</a></p>
<p>On Tuesday, August 15, cross-border payments platform Stellar announced its decision of investing in the global money-transfer company <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/moneygram/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">MoneyGram International</a>. By using money from its own treasury for investment, the Stellar Foundation becomes a minority holder in MoneyGram.</p>
<p>Stellar Development Foundation CEO and Executive Director Denelle Dixon called the new investing decision &#8220;an easy one&#8221;. &#8220;After years of getting to know the business and the teams, we are excited to take part in MGI’s next chapter. It’s been an awesome few years working together, and we are excited for what’s next!&#8221; she <a href="https://twitter.com/DenelleDixon/status/1691456351955025920" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">noted</a>.</p>
<p>&#8220;Most importantly, it signifies a rededication from MoneyGram International, one of the world&#8217;s leading global financial technology, to becoming a digital-forward leader in fintech,&#8221; added Dixon. However, the Stellar Development Foundation hasn&#8217;t given enough details about the exact investment amount.</p>
<p>This investment allows SDF to support MGI&#8217;s efforts, especially in areas like growing its digital business, researching blockchain technology, and contributing to the various ways this fintech company helps people and businesses handle money worldwide. It&#8217;s also a significant commitment from MGI, a prominent global fintech, to embrace digital innovation and become a leader in the field.</p>
<h2>Stellar and MoneyGram Partnership</h2>
<p>The Stellar Development Foundation and MoneyGram started working together in 2021, but their collaboration on tools and technology goes back to 2019.</p>
<p>By November 2022, MoneyGram allowed users in the United States to buy, sell, and hold cryptocurrency using its mobile app. In July 2023, the company introduced a new service that lets people in Venezuela deposit funds into their accounts through its partnership with local bank Banesco.</p>
<p>Stellar&#8217;s goal is to use blockchain technology to make cross-border payments faster and more affordable. MoneyGram is one of the largest remittance companies in the United States, competing with <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/western-union/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Western Union</a>, Intermex, and Euronet.</p>
<p>Speaking to the crypto publication Decrypt, Stellar Development Foundation&#8217;s Director of Communications and Public Affairs Ellen Canale <a href="https://decrypt.co/152598/stellar-invests-in-moneygram-in-bid-to-become-a-digital-forward-leader-in-fintech" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Investment isn&#8217;t specific to any particular work&#8221; but because &#8220;we are confident in the organization, management, and board, and the company&#8217;s plans for the future focused on increasing MGI&#8217;s digital investment and bringing value to the under and unbanked through digital experiences.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Stellar Foundation has also been investing in other projects this year. Earlier in April, SDF <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/stellar-franklin-onchain-money-fund/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">invested</a> in Franklin OnChain US Government Money Fund.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-cheaper-versions-model-s-x-suv/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/stellar-invests-moneygram-fintech-push/">Stellar Foundation Invests in MoneyGram in a Push for FinTech</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/stellar-invests-moneygram-fintech-push/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tesla Launches Cheaper Versions of Some of Its EVs in US as Demand Wanes</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-cheaper-versions-model-s-x-suv/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-cheaper-versions-model-s-x-suv/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 08:05:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Transportation News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[electric vehicle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ev]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[model s sedan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[model x suv]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tesla]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tsla]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267084</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-cheaper-versions-model-s-x-suv/">Tesla Launches Cheaper Versions of Some of Its EVs in US as Demand Wanes</a></p>
<p>The latest decision is one of many attempts by Tesla to grow its sales by all means necessary.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-cheaper-versions-model-s-x-suv/">Tesla Launches Cheaper Versions of Some of Its EVs in US as Demand Wanes</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-cheaper-versions-model-s-x-suv/">Tesla Launches Cheaper Versions of Some of Its EVs in US as Demand Wanes</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/tesla/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tesla Inc</a> (NASDAQ: TSLA), an American automotive company, has introduced cheaper variants of some of its high-end electric vehicles (EVs) to the US market. According to a Reuters <a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-introduces-new-model-s-x-cars-us-2023-08-15/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a>, the decision might be in line with the firm&#8217;s resolve to increase sales at a time when demand for expensive EVs has gone extremely low due to the high costs of borrowing.</p>
<p>To this end, Tesla has now launched more affordable versions of its Model S sedan and Model X SUV. But the new versions will come with shorter driving ranges.</p>
<p>For reference, the new S model has a top range of 320 miles. Whereas, the regular dual-motor and tri-motor Plaid versions offer up to 405 miles and 396 miles, respectively. Similarly, the range of the new X SUV model can go up to 269 miles, a significant downgrade from the 348 miles that its expensive variant offers.</p>
<p>However, the performance and range may just be all the difference that exists between the old and new versions. According to a Tesla sales representative, the new versions will have the same battery as the expensive ones. That is, those that cost $10,000 or more.</p>
<h2>Tesla Keen on Sales Growth</h2>
<p>The latest decision is one of many attempts by Tesla to grow its sales by all means necessary. Before the new launch, the firm <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-slashes-price-japan/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">already cut down</a> on its vehicle prices in the US, China, and several other markets.</p>
<p>As further proof that Tesla might be prioritizing sales over profit margins at the moment, the company has also employed a strategy of offering incentives to reduce inventory.</p>
<p>Rollouts for the new variants will begin between September and October. But, according to an inside source, Tesla is not planning to improve the range and performance in the future.</p>
<p>For what it&#8217;s worth though, the launch is expected to lessen Tesla&#8217;s operating income which has been growing worrisome recently. And, more importantly, it is also expected that the launch will help Tesla to increase its dwindling revenue as well.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/lawmakers-gary-gensler-prometheum-sec-approval/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-cheaper-versions-model-s-x-suv/">Tesla Launches Cheaper Versions of Some of Its EVs in US as Demand Wanes</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-cheaper-versions-model-s-x-suv/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Republican Lawmakers Seek Answer from Gary Gensler over Prometheum’s SEC Approval</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/lawmakers-gary-gensler-prometheum-sec-approval/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/lawmakers-gary-gensler-prometheum-sec-approval/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 07:55:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gary gensler]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[prometheum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267080</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/lawmakers-gary-gensler-prometheum-sec-approval/">Republican Lawmakers Seek Answer from Gary Gensler over Prometheum&#8217;s SEC Approval</a></p>
<p>Republican lawmakers have questioned whether the US SEC has assured enough security measures before granting Prometheum Inc. the license to operate as crypto broker. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/lawmakers-gary-gensler-prometheum-sec-approval/">Republican Lawmakers Seek Answer from Gary Gensler over Prometheum&#8217;s SEC Approval</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/lawmakers-gary-gensler-prometheum-sec-approval/">Republican Lawmakers Seek Answer from Gary Gensler over Prometheum&#8217;s SEC Approval</a></p>
<p>Republican lawmakers at the US Congressional Committee overseeing the Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) are demanding an answer from SEC chair <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/gary-gensler/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Gary Gensler</a> over how Prometheum Inc secured a unique approval to operate as a crypto broker-dealer.</p>
<p>Led by Chair Patrick McHenry (R-N.C.), a group of 23 House Financial Services Committee lawmakers raised questions about how the recently revealed company managed to secure SEC registration as a special-purpose broker-dealer for digital assets. They also sought clarification on the factors that led to this decision and the timing of its conclusion, considering other applicants in the process.</p>
<p>Additionally, the lawmakers also sent a letter to the head of the Financial Industry Regulatory Authority (FINRA). It&#8217;s an industry-funded group that enforces securities standards under the SEC&#8217;s watch. The letter noted:</p>
<blockquote><p>“The timing of the approval raises concerns that it was aimed at demonstrating that legislation is not needed because there is a workable regulatory framework for the custody of digital asset securities.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>SEC&#8217;s Special Treatment to Prometheum?</h2>
<p>The letters ask important questions about whether the SEC chose Prometheum as a prime example to support Gensler&#8217;s view that new laws aren&#8217;t necessary for regulating crypto in the US. This happened just as McHenry&#8217;s committee was preparing to send digital assets legislation to the House floor.</p>
<p>However, Prometheum&#8217;s leaders have said they&#8217;ve been following the registration process like any other company. Co-CEO Aaron Kaplan believes his company will show how to create a crypto platform that follows the rules properly. In a statement on Tuesday, August 15, the company said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Prometheum purpose-built its technology with the goal to develop a market infrastructure for digital asset securities that is compliant with the federal securities laws. This technology will serve as a building block for a compliant and orderly digital asset securities marketplace that protects investors and serves their best interests.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Lawmakers are also joining others in asking for more details about Prometheum&#8217;s sudden appearance in Washington. The company hasn&#8217;t started trading yet. Both Republicans and Democrats in the Senate and House have raised concerns about this, and Ritchie Torres, a Democrat on McHenry&#8217;s committee, has asked for the SEC to be investigated.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-connect-shut-down/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/lawmakers-gary-gensler-prometheum-sec-approval/">Republican Lawmakers Seek Answer from Gary Gensler over Prometheum&#8217;s SEC Approval</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/lawmakers-gary-gensler-prometheum-sec-approval/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance to Shut Down Its Buy-and-Sell Service Binance Connect</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-connect-shut-down/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-connect-shut-down/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Darya Rudz]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 07:32:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Binance News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Editor's Choice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance buy-and-sell]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance connect]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance europe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance sec lawsuit]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267074</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-connect-shut-down/">Binance to Shut Down Its Buy-and-Sell Service Binance Connect</a></p>
<p>Binance has confirmed the news, stating it would shift its focus to its main products and long-term goals.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-connect-shut-down/">Binance to Shut Down Its Buy-and-Sell Service Binance Connect</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-connect-shut-down/">Binance to Shut Down Its Buy-and-Sell Service Binance Connect</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a> has decided to close its buy-and-sell service Binance Connect amid challenges its provider faced with support for card payments. Starting from August 16, Binance Connect is no longer available.</p>
<p>Binance has confirmed the news, the announcement has also been revealed by BNB Chain-based platform Biswap in a tweet.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="474" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Dear Biswappers,</p>
<p>The Biswap team keeps abreast of the latest DeFi news and aims to inform you right away.</p>
<p>After a thorough consideration, <a href="https://twitter.com/binance?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@binance</a> has made a difficult decision to disable <a href="https://twitter.com/Binance_Connect?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@Binance_Connect</a> on 15 August due to its provider closing the supporting card payments… <a href="https://t.co/HcooyLn4sg">pic.twitter.com/HcooyLn4sg</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Biswap (@Biswap_Dex) <a href="https://twitter.com/Biswap_Dex/status/1691358029914996736?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 15, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>As Binance has stated, it will shift its focus to its main products and long-term goals.</p>
<p>Binance representative commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We periodically review our products and services to ensure that our resources continue to be focused on core efforts that align with our long-term strategy. In the last six years, Binance has grown from being an exchange to a global blockchain ecosystem with multiple business lines. We consistently adapt and modify our business approach in response to changing market and user needs.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Launched in March 2022, Binance Connect (formerly Bitfinity) was connecting traditional finance to world-leading and emerging blockchains, transforming how businesses and people send and receive money around the world. Its aim was to create an open, financial world where people from all walks of life and businesses, big or small, can participate and realize their financial goals.</p>
<p>Serving as the official fiat-to-crypto payments provider for Binance, Binance Connect supported as many as 50 cryptocurrencies and major payment methods, including Visa and Mastercard. The service was also supposed to be the hub for the exchange’s <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-are-non-fungible-tokens-nfts/#:~:text=NFTs%20are%20created%20using%20blockchain,a%20token%20on%20the%20blockchain." target="_blank" rel="noopener">non-fungible tokens</a> (NFTs) checkout solution. The feature was not added.</p>
<h2>Binance&#8217;s Legal Battles</h2>
<p>One of the world&#8217;s largest crypto exchanges is currently facing challenges caused by regulatory scrutiny around its business. Earlier this year, Binance faced lawsuits filed by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) and the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/cftc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CFTC</a>) accusing the company of misleading investors through opaque business practices. The violations included operating unregistered exchanges, broker-dealers, and clearing agencies, misrepresenting trading controls and oversight on the Binance.US platform, as well as the unregistered offer and sale of securities. In total, SEC filed more than a dozen charges against Binance this year so far.</p>
<p>According to SEC, Binance has been manipulating its Know-Your-Customer (KYC) processes to conceal its US customer base and avoid regulatory oversight. Besides, the company has been accused of encouraging its US customers to use virtual private networks (VPNs) to hide their locations and bypass restrictions. Out of Binance’s 62 million global customers, only 25 million had submitted KYC documentation.</p>
<p>European regulators turned out to be not really welcoming as well. In June, Germany’s Federal Financial Supervisory Authority (BaFin) reportedly <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-german-license-denied-bafin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">denied</a> the Binance exchange’s application for a crypto custody license. Besides, Binance withdrew its application with the Financial Market Authority of Austria. Earlier this year, Binance also exited the Netherlands after failing to secure regulatory approval, as well as abandoned its Cyprus and UK registrations.</p>
<div id="gtx-trans" style="position: absolute; left: 773px; top: 1273.56px;">
<div class="gtx-trans-icon"></div>
</div>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/x-access-facebook-instagram-bluesky/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-connect-shut-down/">Binance to Shut Down Its Buy-and-Sell Service Binance Connect</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-connect-shut-down/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4044 metric#misses=43 metric#hit-ratio=99.0 metric#bytes=1013913 metric#prefetches=194 metric#store-reads=22 metric#store-writes=3 metric#store-hits=201 metric#store-misses=4 metric#sql-queries=35 metric#ms-total=95.24 metric#ms-cache=5.36 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.2235 metric#ms-cache-ratio=5.6 -->