<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 15:59:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Court allows Celsius to sell altcoins for BTC, ETH starting July 1</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/court-allows-celsius-to-sell-altcoins-for-btc-eth-starting-july-1/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/court-allows-celsius-to-sell-altcoins-for-btc-eth-starting-july-1/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 15:59:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Policy and Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CEL]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Celsius]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/court-allows-celsius-to-sell-altcoins-for-btc-eth-starting-july-1/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bankruptcy Judge Martin Glenn of the US Southern District Court of New York on Friday ordered that bankrupt crypto lender Celsius can begin to sell or convert altcoins to Bitcoin (BTC) and Ether (ETH). The price of CEL, the native Celsius Network token, rose sharply on Friday, trading above $0.15 with 33% gains in the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/court-allows-celsius-to-sell-altcoins-for-btc-eth-starting-july-1/">Court allows Celsius to sell altcoins for BTC, ETH starting July 1</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Bankruptcy Judge Martin Glenn of the US Southern District Court of New York on Friday ordered that bankrupt crypto lender <a href="https://coinjournal.net/celsius/">Celsius</a> can begin to sell or convert altcoins to Bitcoin (BTC) and Ether (ETH).</p>
<p dir="ltr">The price of CEL, the native Celsius Network token, rose sharply on Friday, trading above $0.15 with 33% gains in the past 24 hours.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Celsius can sell altcoins for BTC, ETH from July 1</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The liquidating of the said altcoins comes ahead of a planned distribution of assets to creditors and will start on or after July 1, the judge <a href="https://cases.stretto.com/public/x191/11749/PLEADINGS/1174906302380000000027.pdf" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">ordered</a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>The Debtors, in consultation with the advisors to the Committee, may sell or convert any non-BTC and non-ETH cryptocurrency, crypto tokens, or other cryptocurrency assets other than such tokens that are associated with Withhold or Custody accounts (collectively, the &ldquo;Altcoins&rdquo;) to BTC or ETH commencing on or after July 1, 2023</em>,&rdquo; reads part of the ruling.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Celsius is expected to use &ldquo;commercially reasonable efforts to maximize the value of the Altcoins to be sold or converted to BTC or ETH.&rdquo; However, with the SEC having recently alleged some of the altcoins held by the crypto lender as securities, the sales are expected to comply with the &ldquo;applicable exemptions to the US securities laws.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Among the tokens the US regulator recently highlighted as securities in its cases against Binance and Coinbase include Cardano (ADA), Polygon (MATIC) and Near (NEAR). Celsius holds these and other alts such as Bitcoin Cash (BCH), Litecoin (LTC) and Chainlink (LINK).&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The tokens have recently traded higher alongside the broader crypto market and it remains to be seen what impact, if any, the offloading will have on prices.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Here are the Celsius alts FWIW, these will be sold and the proceeds used to buy BTC and ETH. <a href="https://t.co/Bp7MWUhstB">https://t.co/Bp7MWUhstB</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Hal Press (@NorthRockLP) <a href="https://twitter.com/NorthRockLP/status/1674792909449879552?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 30, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">Celsius filed for bankruptcy in July 2022 after pausing customer withdrawals amid crypto contagion from the collapse of Terra and Three Arrows Capital.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to court documents, the company has been in dialogue with the SEC and state regulators as it looked to update its restructuring plan to only distribute crypto to creditors in bitcoin and ether.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/court-allows-celsius-to-sell-altcoins-for-btc-eth-starting-july-1/">Court allows Celsius to sell altcoins for BTC, ETH starting July 1</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/court-allows-celsius-to-sell-altcoins-for-btc-eth-starting-july-1/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin dominance surging amid changing market dynamics and regulatory crackdown</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-dominance-surging-amid-changing-market-dynamics-and-regulatory-crackdown/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-dominance-surging-amid-changing-market-dynamics-and-regulatory-crackdown/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dan Ashmore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 14:37:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-dominance-surging-amid-changing-market-dynamics-and-regulatory-crackdown/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key Takeaways Bitcoin dominance measures the ratio of the Bitcoin market cap to the cumulative cryptocurrency sector market cap It is currently at 58%, the highest mark since April 2021 Market dynamics are changing as institutions consider Bitcoin, while rest of crypto market still struggles amid tight monetary policy environment Regulatory clampdown has also declared [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-dominance-surging-amid-changing-market-dynamics-and-regulatory-crackdown/">Bitcoin dominance surging amid changing market dynamics and regulatory crackdown</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2 dir="ltr">Key Takeaways</h2>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Bitcoin dominance measures the ratio of the Bitcoin market cap to the cumulative cryptocurrency sector market cap</li>
<li dir="ltr">It is currently at 58%, the highest mark since April 2021</li>
<li dir="ltr">Market dynamics are changing as institutions consider Bitcoin, while rest of crypto market still struggles amid tight monetary policy environment</li>
<li dir="ltr">Regulatory clampdown has also declared many tokens as securities, while Bitcoin appears to be carving out its own niche&nbsp;</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p dir="ltr">The Bitcoin market is never boring.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Having said that, the year 2023 has (thus far at least) has not thrown up mayhem on the scale of what we saw in past years. In 2022, Bitcoin freefell as the world transitioned to tight monetary policy, while scandals such as the Terra collapse and the staggering deception at FTX coming to light. This came after the pandemic years of 2020 and 2021, when crypto surged into mainstream consciousness, Bitcoin printing dizzying gains and inspiring dinner table conversation around the globe as to what this mysterious Internet money was all about.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">So, 2023 cannot match the scale of that drama. But there is something very intriguing happening to the market dynamics of Bitcoin, at least relative to other cryptocurrencies. Bitcoin dominance, which measures the ratio of the Bitcoin market cap to the cumulative market cap of all cryptocurrencies, is at its highest level in over two years, at 52%. In other words, 52% of the cryptocurrency market cap, currently at $1.18 trillion, is Bitcoin.&nbsp;</p>
<h2><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/05/30/1688118673827-71a712e7-acd0-4d3b-8651-836d1ad218d0.png" style="width: 600px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="600" height="284">Dominance fell in the years 2020 and 2021</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The above chart shows that Bitcoin opened the year 2020 with a dominance of about 70%. Over the course of the next 365 days, it bounced around a bit and trickled down to the high 50s. However, it was the final quarter of 2020 when Bitcoin began to make serious moves, rising from $10,000 to $28,000. In this time period, the dominance ratio rose from 59% back to 70%, where it closed at, approximately the same dominance ratio it opened the year at twelve months earlier. &nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The following year, 2021, saw altcoins catch up. Bitcoin&rsquo;s dominance plunged like a stone, falling quicker than it ever had before. The wider cryptocurrency market exploded as stimulus cheques, lockdown-driven Robinhood trading and basement-level interest rates pushed capital into anything and everything remotely connected to a blockchain.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The total cryptocurrency market cap touched $3 trillion in November 2021, while Bitcoin&rsquo;s market cap peaked at $1.28 trillion. Bitcoin dominance, therefore, was down to 43%. However, the worst inflation crisis since the 1970s forced central banks into one of the fastest rate hiking cycles in recent memory, following years of zero (or even negative in some cases) rates.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14292455">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">For risk assets, this spelled trouble. And make no mistake, the entire crypto market is as far out on the risk spectrum as it gets. Capital flooded out of the space as rates continued rising, inflation got hotter, and several nefarious scandals struck the crypto sector (looking at you, Do Kwon, Sam Bankman-Fried and Alex Mashinsky). &nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Which brings us to now. While inflation peaked in Q4 last year, the macro climate is still uncertain. Employment is tight, the economy is still hot and inflation, while dropping, is well north of the Federal Reserve&rsquo;s 2% target. In Europe, inflation is even hotter (and don&rsquo;t even ask about the UK, if that still counts as Europe anyway).&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">In crypto, however, something is changing. Bitcoin&rsquo;s dominance has risen and appears to be in an uptrend again. It is currently up to 58%, the highest mark since April 2021. On the one hand, this is typical of what we have seen in the past: money begins to flow into Bitcoin after a prolonged and seismic pullback (2022), seeing dominance rise before it eventually filters into altcoins and the rest of the market catches up.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, there are two points to counter why this time could be different, and may give pause for thought to those assuming that altcoins will follow this time around. The first is, well, obvious: past cycles aren&rsquo;t indicative of future ones, and this is especially true for Bitcoin.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The asset was only launched in 2009, and it is only in the last five years that it has traded with any sort of reasonable liquidity (although even at that, <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/very-few-bitcoins-are-actually-moving-but-the-liquidity-picture-could-change-soon/"><u>it&rsquo;s thin</u></a>). It would be foolish to put too much weight into previous years, therefore, especially as its entire existence has, until last year, coincided with a remarkable bull market in the wider economy. This is Bitcoin, and crypto&rsquo;s, first rodeo in a high-interest rate environment, so all bets are off.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">But aside from that blindingly obvious caveat, there is more evidence to suggest that there may have been a structural shift with regard to the market in the last six months, or something that may change the dominance trend going forward. What I am referring to is regulation and, more recently, institutional moves.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The regulatory clampdown in the US has been brutal for the crypto sector, with a number of tokens being confirmed as securities by the SEC in recent times, including Solana, Polygon, Cosmos, BNB and Cardano. Bitcoin, on the other hand, appears to be carving out its own niche. Or, as Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong said when discussing the lawsuit levelled against his exchange by the SEC, &ldquo;we kind of got this information from the SEC that, well actually, everything other than Bitcoin is a security&rdquo;.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, it feels foolish to declare this rise in dominance over the past few months as temporary. If anything, it is surprising that it has not risen more, although a lot of this regulatory trouble may have been priced in already, while the biggest non-Bitcoin token, Ether, seems to have evaded the dreaded security label thus far.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, there is also the reality of what has been happening on the institutional side in recent weeks. Blackrock and Fidelity, two of the world&rsquo;s largest asset managers, have both filed for spot ETFs. These are Bitcoin ETFs, not crypto ETFs.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">In a sector where regulation is so hazy and the intimidation factor of actually buying physical Bitcoin is so high (the reality is that wallets and seed phrases are not ideal for new users or institutional funds, no matter how seductive the promise of self-custody is), this could do wonders for liquidity &ndash; one of the big factors holding Bitcoin back right now. It may also assuage concern around the lack of transparency and reliability of centralised exchanges, as institutions can simply bypass actors like Binance and go straight towards a (regulated) Bitcoin ETF. Of course, these ETFs are not approved yet, but we are a hell of a lot closer to a Bitcoin ETF than any other sort of crypto ETF.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The macro climate is still uncertain: inflation may have peaked but is still elevated, and with monetary policy notoriously operating with a lag, the full pain of a Fed rate north of 5% has yet to be felt. There are numerous challenges still to come. The regulatory crackdown could worsen, while who knows what is going behind the scenes at some of these crypto companies. But it feels undeniable that as bad as things are for crypto, Bitcoin has its head and shoulders above the rest of the gang.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">With all this in mind, the rising dominance makes sense. And while I have no idea what happens next (at the end of the day, <em>crypto is going to crypto</em>), I certainly see nothing that would make me confident that Bitcoin dominance, which is now at a two-year high, is bound to inevitably retreat soon.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-dominance-surging-amid-changing-market-dynamics-and-regulatory-crackdown/">Bitcoin dominance surging amid changing market dynamics and regulatory crackdown</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-dominance-surging-amid-changing-market-dynamics-and-regulatory-crackdown/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>OKX Named Official Sleeve Partner Of Manchester City In Expansion Of Partnership</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/okx-named-official-sleeve-partner-of-manchester-city-in-expansion-of-partnership/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/okx-named-official-sleeve-partner-of-manchester-city-in-expansion-of-partnership/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire &#160;]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 14:35:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=144709</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Manchester, UK, June 30th, 2023, Chainwire Manchester City and OKX, one of the leading crypto exchanges by trading volume and a leading Web3 technology company, today announced OKX as the Club&#8217;s Official Sleeve Partner in a new multi-year agreement. As part of the expanded deal, the OKX brand will feature on the left sleeve of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/okx-named-official-sleeve-partner-of-manchester-city-in-expansion-of-partnership/">OKX Named Official Sleeve Partner Of Manchester City In Expansion Of Partnership</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Manchester, UK, June 30th, 2023, Chainwire</strong></p>
<p>Manchester City and OKX, one of the leading crypto exchanges by trading volume and a leading Web3 technology company, today announced OKX as the Club&rsquo;s Official Sleeve Partner in a new multi-year agreement.</p>
<p>As part of the expanded deal, the OKX brand will feature on the left sleeve of both the men&rsquo;s and women&rsquo;s first team playing kits and will retain its position on the left sleeve of the first team training kits, in addition to appearing across further digital and physical club assets.</p>
<p>OKX&rsquo;s partnership with Manchester City began in March 2022, first expanding in July 2022 to become the Club&rsquo;s Official Training Kit Partner for the 2022/23 season. To date, the partnership has helped introduce the brand to millions of football fans around the world through innovative Web3 experiences like the <a href="https://www.okx.com/activities/okxcollectivemetaverse" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">OKX Collective</a>, through which fans can get up-close-and-personal with Manchester City players and OKX Ambassadors such as Jack Grealish and Alex Greenwood.</p>
<p>The partnership expansion was unveiled at an exclusive reveal at the Etihad Stadium featuring City Football Group Chief Executive Officer Ferran Soriano and OKX Global Chief Marketing Officer Haider Rafique. As part of the event, the sleeve was unveiled in a &lsquo;virtual reveal&rsquo; with a hero video featuring player avatars. Manchester City legend Ga&euml;l Clichy was also in attendance for a media Q&amp;A.</p>
<p>In a session moderated by Manchester City presenter <a href="https://www.mancity.com/wnrh/natalie-pike" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Natalie Pike</a>, Rafique and Soriano spoke about OKX&rsquo;s vision of reaching City fans around the world through the partnership. They also discussed the role Web3 technology can play in fan engagement, especially when it comes to designing engaging, immersive experiences for fans.</p>
<blockquote><p><strong>Ferran Soriano, Chief Executive Officer at City Football Group, said:</strong> &ldquo;We are very proud to have OKX represented on the sleeve of the Manchester City shirt. Both OKX and Manchester City are leading companies driven by a passion for innovation. We have already seen great Web3 experiences designed by OKX for Manchester City&rsquo;s global fan base and there will be many more to come. This is a very exciting partnership.&rdquo;</p></blockquote>
<blockquote><p><strong>Haider Rafique, CMO at OKX, said:</strong> &ldquo;The journey with the Man City team has been incredible. Manchester City was our first official global brand partnership and in just a year and a half we have come a long way. We always intended to integrate with the sport and help the Club lead on leaning into Web3. Fast forward fifteen months, we now have a metaverse, an NFT initiative and a number of other new projects that we are excited about.</p></blockquote>
<p>The sleeve partnership brings us closer to City fans across the globe, and we look forward to collaborating to create unique, exciting and innovative engagements through Web3 technology. As the Club&rsquo;s Official Cryptocurrency Exchange Partner, fans can expect amazing things every time they interact with OKX.&rdquo;</p>
<h3>About OKX</h3>
<p>OKX is a world-leading technology company building the future of trading and Web3. Its leading self-custody solutions include the Web3-compatible OKX Wallet, which allows users greater control of their assets while expanding access to DEXs, NFT marketplaces, DeFi, GameFi and thousands of dApps.</p>
<p>OKX partners with a number of the world&rsquo;s top brands and athletes, including: English Premier League champions Manchester City F.C., McLaren Formula 1, The Tribeca Festival, Olympian Scotty James, and F1 driver Daniel Ricciardo.</p>
<p>OKX is committed to transparency and security and publishes its <a href="https://www.okx.com/proof-of-reserves" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Proof of Reserves</a> on a monthly basis.</p>
<p>To learn more about OKX, download our app or visit:<a href="http://okx.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"> okx.com</a></p>
<h3 class="ql-align-justify">About Manchester City Football Club</h3>
<p>Manchester City FC is an English Premier League club initially founded in 1880 as St Mark&rsquo;s West Gorton. It officially became Manchester City FC in 1894 and has since then gone onto win the UEFA Champions League, European Cup Winners&rsquo; Cup, nine League Championship titles, seven FA Cups and eight League Cups. Manchester City FC is one of 13 clubs comprising the City Football Group.</p>
<p>Under manager Pep Guardiola, one of the most highly-decorated managers in world football, the Club plays its domestic and UEFA Champions League home fixtures at the Etihad Stadium, a spectacular 53,500 seat arena that City has called home since 2003. Today, the stadium sits on the wider Etihad Campus, which also encompasses the City Football Academy, a state-of-the-art performance training and youth development facility located in the heart of East Manchester. Featuring a 7,000-capacity Academy Stadium, the City Football Academy is also where Manchester City Women&rsquo;s Football Club and the Elite Development Squad train on a daily basis and play their competitive home games.</p>
<p>Disclaimer</p>
<p>OKX IS NOT REGULATED BY THE FCA, THUS, PROTECTIONS SUCH AS THE FINANCIAL OMBUDSMAN SERVICE OR FINANCIAL SERVICES COMPENSATION SCHEME WILL NOT BE AVAILABLE. YOU SHOULD CONSIDER WHETHER YOU UNDERSTAND HOW CRYPTO WORKS AS THE VALUE OF YOUR ASSETS, INCLUDING STABLECOINS, CAN INCREASE OR DECREASE AND PROFITS MAY BE SUBJECT TO CAPITAL GAINS TAX. PAST PERFORMANCE DOES NOT INDICATE FUTURE RESULTS.</p>
<h3>Contact</h3>
<p>Media, media@okx.com, 0788118718</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/okx-named-official-sleeve-partner-of-manchester-city-in-expansion-of-partnership/">OKX Named Official Sleeve Partner Of Manchester City In Expansion Of Partnership</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/okx-named-official-sleeve-partner-of-manchester-city-in-expansion-of-partnership/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin briefly falls below $30k as SEC says spot Bitcoin ETF filings are inadequate</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-briefly-falls-below-30k-as-sec-says-spot-bitcoin-etf-filings-are-inadequate/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 14:17:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-briefly-falls-below-30k-as-sec-says-spot-bitcoin-etf-filings-are-inadequate/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin price reacted sharply to news that the SEC had said Bitcoin ETFs filings were inadequate. The SEC had reportedly returned the filed documents to BlackRock, Fidelity. However, BTC recovered above $30k as more details emerged. Bitcoin briefly crashed to below $30k within minutes on Friday as the US Securities and Exchnage Commission (SEC) reportedly [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-briefly-falls-below-30k-as-sec-says-spot-bitcoin-etf-filings-are-inadequate/">Bitcoin briefly falls below $30k as SEC says spot Bitcoin ETF filings are inadequate</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Bitcoin price reacted sharply to news that the SEC had said Bitcoin ETFs filings were inadequate.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The SEC had reportedly returned the filed documents to BlackRock, Fidelity.</li>
<li dir="ltr">However, BTC recovered above $30k as more details emerged.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> briefly crashed to below $30k within minutes on Friday as the US Securities and Exchnage Commission (SEC) reportedly told Nasdaq and the Cboe that recently filed spot Bicoin ETFs by BlackRock, Fidelity and other Wall Street giants were &ldquo;not clear and comprehensive.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The regulator has reportedly returned the spot ETF documents.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The markets reaction to the initial <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/sec-says-spot-bitcoin-etf-filings-are-inadequate-390336e8" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">news</a> by the Wall Street Journal was swift, with Bitcoin falling to $29,790 and Ethereum below $1,840.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">According to WSJ, the U.S. SEC stated that the filing of spot bitcoin ETFs was insufficient, and regulators told Nasdaq that recent filings by companies such as BlackRock and Fidelity were not clear and comprehensive.  The SEC returned the documents.  <a href="https://t.co/HK75jdB3ks">https://t.co/HK75jdB3ks</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Wu Blockchain (@WuBlockchain) <a href="https://twitter.com/WuBlockchain/status/1674778074557337601?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 30, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">&nbsp;&ldquo;<em>A</em><em>ffected by the news, the market crashed within 30 minutes. BTC once fell by more than 5% to below $30,000, ETH fell by more than 4%, and BCH and COMP, which had a large increase today, fell by more than 10%. &nbsp;Coinglass data shows that in the past 1 hour, the liquidation of the entire network exceeded 84 million US dollars</em>,&rdquo; Blockchain news reporter Colin Wu tweeted.</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, as it was reported that BlackRock and other asset managers only had to refile their applications correctly, Bitcoin moved back above $30k. Crypto analyst Will Clemente <a href="https://twitter.com/WClementeIII/status/1674778064708935680" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">noted</a>:</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Think the market is overreacting here, seems like the "denial" is just a technicality and Blackrock/Fidelity just have to refile naming Coinbase as the exchange that they have a "surveillance-sharing agreement" with</p>
<p>&mdash; Will Clemente (@WClementeIII) <a href="https://twitter.com/WClementeIII/status/1674778064708935680?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 30, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-briefly-falls-below-30k-as-sec-says-spot-bitcoin-etf-filings-are-inadequate/">Bitcoin briefly falls below $30k as SEC says spot Bitcoin ETF filings are inadequate</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Cash jumps to 14-month high amid South Korea volume spike</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-cash-jumps-to-14-month-high-amid-south-korea-volume-spike/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-cash-jumps-to-14-month-high-amid-south-korea-volume-spike/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 13:26:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BCH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[South Korea]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-cash-jumps-to-14-month-high-amid-south-korea-volume-spike/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin Cash has skyrocketed to a 14-month high above $320, hitting highs of $326 on Coinbase. BCH upside momentum has increased since Wall Street-backed EDX listed the coin alongside BTC, ETH and LTC. A spike in volume on South Korea exchange Upbit helped push CBH price higher on Friday. Bitcoin Cash rallied to its highest [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-cash-jumps-to-14-month-high-amid-south-korea-volume-spike/">Bitcoin Cash jumps to 14-month high amid South Korea volume spike</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitcoin Cash has skyrocketed to a 14-month high above $320, hitting highs of $326 on Coinbase.</li>
<li>BCH upside momentum has increased since Wall Street-backed EDX listed the coin alongside BTC, ETH and LTC.</li>
<li>A spike in volume on South Korea exchange Upbit helped push CBH price higher on Friday.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin-cash/">Bitcoin Cash</a> rallied to its highest price in 14 months on Friday morning, trading at highs of $326 on US-based crypto exchange Coinbase.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Why is BCH price rallying today?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin Cash had stagnated below $165 since dipping below the level in June last year. However, with Bitcoin rallying to above $31k amid bullish sentiment buoyed by BlackRock&rsquo;s spot ETF filing, BCH roared to a <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-cash-price-hits-1-year-high-as-bch-soars-72-this-week/">one-year high</a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The bulls have been relentless since, with price crossing the psychological $300 mark today with more than 30% gains in 24 hours. The cryptocurrency has rallied nearly 200% over the past two weeks, and is now in the green by 110% over the past year.</p>
<p dir="ltr">It is notable that the price of <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/bch/">BCH</a> had raced to a new year high last week after EDX Markets, a new crypto exchange backed by major Wall Street companies including Fidelity and Charles Schwab, listed Bitcoin Cash. EDX only lists three other coins &ndash; BTC, ETH and LTC.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Enthusiasm across the BCH community from this listing has added to the upside momentum. On Friday, the positive outlook on the cryptocurrency&rsquo;s potential saw volume spike on a leading South Korea-based crypto platform.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As crypto markets bid to hold onto the positive sentiment, Bitcoin Cash appears to be getting some extra leg from South Korea. Over the past 24 hours, the BCH/KRW pair on crypto exchange Upbit rose to $557 million, more than thrice the volume of BTC/KRW and nearly 6x greater than BCH/USD.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Data from CoinGecko shows daily trading volume across all exchanges has increased 165% in the past 24 hours to over $2.4 billion. As IntoTheBlock <a href="https://twitter.com/intotheblock/status/1674432186660057092">points out</a>, BCH volume rose to above $750 million on Thursday, a one-year high.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">1/2 Bitcoin Cash (BCH) soars 70% in a week, riding high on its recent inclusion on <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/EDX?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#EDX</a>, the Citadel Securities-Backed Crypto Exchange. Yesterday saw the highest volume of BCH transacted in a year, exceeding a staggering $750M.&#128279; <a href="https://t.co/1qZbEChogW">https://t.co/1qZbEChogW</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/BitcoinCash?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#BitcoinCash</a> <a href="https://t.co/OEOYG61sQR">pic.twitter.com/OEOYG61sQR</a></p>
<p>&mdash; IntoTheBlock (@intotheblock) <a href="https://twitter.com/intotheblock/status/1674432186660057092?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 29, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-cash-jumps-to-14-month-high-amid-south-korea-volume-spike/">Bitcoin Cash jumps to 14-month high amid South Korea volume spike</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-cash-jumps-to-14-month-high-amid-south-korea-volume-spike/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Solana technical analysis update – can it jump to $40?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/solana-technical-analysis-update-can-it-jump-to-40/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/solana-technical-analysis-update-can-it-jump-to-40/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mircea Vasiu]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 13:02:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/solana-technical-analysis-update-can-it-jump-to-40/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Solana rallied in 2023 but failed to break above the horizontal resistance A bullish case remains valid unless the price moves below the 2022 lows If it breaks above horizontal resistance, Solana may trade above $40 Cryptocurrency investors must be thrilled with the 2023 price action. After all, Bitcoin bounced from last year&#8217;s lows, triggering [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/solana-technical-analysis-update-can-it-jump-to-40/">Solana technical analysis update – can it jump to $40?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Solana rallied in 2023 but failed to break above the horizontal resistance</li>
<li>A bullish case remains valid unless the price moves below the 2022 lows</li>
<li>If it breaks above horizontal resistance, Solana may trade above $40</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p>Cryptocurrency investors must be thrilled with the 2023 price action. After all, Bitcoin bounced from last year&rsquo;s lows, triggering a similar move in other major cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>Solana followed suit.</p>
<p>The price more than doubled this year, rising from $10 to over $25 in what appeared to be a clear bullish breakout.</p>
<p>However, after trading above $26 in January, the market failed to build on the bullish trend. Instead, a consolidation started, bringing doubts to bullish traders.</p>
<p>The best way to clear such doubts is to look at the bigger picture. As the chart below shows, it is difficult to build a bullish case while the market holds below horizontal resistance.</p>
<p>However, the 2022 lows remain in place, so one can build a bullish scenario as long as the market does not dip below those lows.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/05/30/1688128168792-a49e9d0f-ca7e-491c-b8fb-341615b6e752.jpg" style="width: 1800px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="1800" height="487"></p>
<p><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/SOLUSD/?exchange=CRYPTO" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Solana chart by TradingView</a></p>
<h2>A break above horizontal resistance should trigger more gains</h2>
<p>Solana&rsquo;s price remains bearish while below horizontal resistance. However, a break above it implies more strength ahead.</p>
<p>That is especially true if the US dollar&rsquo;s weakness resumes. So far in 2023, the dollar traded with a mixed tone.</p>
<p>But as the Fed is on pause, renewed weakness will bode well for cryptocurrencies and for Solana.</p>
<p>A daily close above horizontal resistance opens the gates for a move above $40. If the Fed believes that the US inflation data follows the right path, the dollar should weaken in the year&rsquo;s second half.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/solana-technical-analysis-update-can-it-jump-to-40/">Solana technical analysis update – can it jump to $40?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/solana-technical-analysis-update-can-it-jump-to-40/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A bullish case for Ripple – if current lows hold</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/a-bullish-case-for-ripple-if-current-lows-hold/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/a-bullish-case-for-ripple-if-current-lows-hold/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mircea Vasiu]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 12:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/a-bullish-case-for-ripple-if-current-lows-hold/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ripple builds energy to break higher A series of higher lows points to more upside The bullish case is valid as long as the price holds above $0.3 Ripple is one of the major cryptocurrencies that rallied in 2023. It opened the trading year at $0.3 and rallied all the way to $0.55. But traders [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/a-bullish-case-for-ripple-if-current-lows-hold/">A bullish case for Ripple – if current lows hold</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul class="decimal_type">
<li>Ripple builds energy to break higher</li>
<li>A series of higher lows points to more upside</li>
<li>The bullish case is valid as long as the price holds above $0.3</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p>Ripple is one of the major cryptocurrencies that rallied in 2023. It opened the trading year at $0.3 and rallied all the way to $0.55.</p>
<p>But traders now wonder if the inability to move above $0.55 is a sign of weakness.</p>
<p>It may well be.</p>
<p>However, if Ripple holds above $0.33, a technical trader can build a bullish case for it.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/05/30/1688125686653-40c677ee-6985-40bb-8063-ff3546997ede.jpg" style="width: 1800px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="1800" height="490"></p>
<p><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XRPUSD/?exchange=CRYPTO" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Ripple chart by TradingView</a></p>
<h2>Ripple tries to break above the $0.55 resistance level</h2>
<p>Ripple tried to break above the $0.55 resistance level three times in a row. It failed every time.</p>
<p>But each rejection brought nothing but new buyers buying the dip. Moreover, the series of higher lows holds intact, suggesting that the market builds energy to break above horizontal resistance.</p>
<p>Providing the price action holds above $0.3, which proved to be horizontal support part of a possible double bottom pattern, one can build a bullish case for Ripple.</p>
<p>First, the double bottom pattern does suggest that more upside should follow a break above $0.55.</p>
<p>Second, the market built a series of higher lows, a typical structure in bullish markets.</p>
<p>Therefore, bulls may want to wait for Ripple to close above $0.55 until establishing long positions. Ripple should find little or no resistance until the $0.75 level on such a move.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/a-bullish-case-for-ripple-if-current-lows-hold/">A bullish case for Ripple – if current lows hold</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/a-bullish-case-for-ripple-if-current-lows-hold/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chancer to usher a new era of betting as Mastercard eyes a multi-token network</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-to-usher-a-new-era-of-betting-as-mastercard-eyes-a-multi-token-network/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-to-usher-a-new-era-of-betting-as-mastercard-eyes-a-multi-token-network/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Motiur Rahman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 11:41:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technical Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-to-usher-a-new-era-of-betting-as-mastercard-eyes-a-multi-token-network/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Chancer raises $421.4k in two weeks The token&#8217;s P2P model in betting is attracting investors Chancer&#8217;s value to increase in the subsequent presale phases and upon listing Blockchain is revolutionising traditional sectors in good ways, with the latest being betting. Chancer has been the key project in this shift, focusing on new ways investors can [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-to-usher-a-new-era-of-betting-as-mastercard-eyes-a-multi-token-network/">Chancer to usher a new era of betting as Mastercard eyes a multi-token network</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Chancer raises $421.4k in two weeks</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The token&rsquo;s P2P model in betting is attracting investors</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Chancer&rsquo;s value to increase in the subsequent presale phases and upon listing</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Blockchain is revolutionising traditional sectors in good ways, with the latest being betting. Chancer has been the key project in this shift, focusing on new ways investors can participate in betting and earn. The primary innovative feature of Chancer is its peer-to-peer betting that allows investors to predict in markets created by themselves. Investors have shown enthusiasm for the project, buying more than $421.4k worth of Chancer tokens in the first phase of a&nbsp;<a href="https://chancer.com/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=invezz&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=investment_opportunity" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>presale</u></a> that opened two weeks ago. The successful presale underlines the growing uptake of crypto, with Mastercard considering a multi-token network (MTN).</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Mastercard to make digital transactions secure and interoperable with MTN.</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Payments giant Mastercard wants to enhance digital transactions&rsquo; security, interoperability, and scalability with a Multi-Token Network (MTN) product. The company&nbsp;<a href="https://www.mastercard.com/news/perspectives/2023/blockchain-and-digital-assets-putting-trust-at-the-center/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>says</u></a> MTN will enable efficient and cost-effective payments by using digital assets.</p>
<p dir="ltr">MTN is also expected to enhance identity management and permissions through blockchain networks, thus building trusted business interactions. Using digital identities will also help counter fraud common in card-related transactions.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The new product by Mastercard underlines that big players are getting into the sector, building needed trust. For a global payment network like Mastercard, it means the project will increase digital asset visibility and allow new ones to succeed.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Peer-to-peer betting by Chancer. What is it?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">As the name suggests, peer-to-peer (P2P) is a betting model permitting user relations with each other. Chancer is pioneering a P2P betting where users can build their betting markets via a secure decentralised system. Users can determine what instruments, events, or situations they want to bet on and invite others (peers) into that betting market.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer has the edge over the traditional betting markets in that investors are not restricted to the odds and rules common in betting platforms. They play by their rules and odds betting through Chancer.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">With the ability to create a betting market from almost anything, Chancer brings fun to betting and allows flexibility to investors. It also expands the earning opportunities for investors as they can create limitless betting markets via the P2P model.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>What is the value proposition of Chancer?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer carries value in letting investors create betting markets and earn rewards on successful outcomes against peers. Investors can bet on events from football to politics and elections. But of course, Chancer is built with an investment focus rather than betting.</p>
<p dir="ltr">One of the ways to unlock value through Chancer is by creating predictive markets. Investors get rewarded for market-making activities. It means investors are rewarded for their interests and expertise by participating in the Chancer project.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The second way is through staking $CHANCER. Investors can stake the tokens for yields, thus unlocking liquidity and facilitating the platform&rsquo;s growth. Other ways to earn include token rewards for promoting Chancer to others.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Is Chancer an ideal investment?&nbsp;</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer could be an ideal investment if you are looking for a project with huge growth potential. Betting markets are fast-growing, and the entry of Chancer offers a leeway for investors to do it differently.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Alongside the ability to earn through P2P betting, investors who feel locked out of the traditional markets can find Chancer ideal.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The growth of the Chancer platform could fuel an increase in the value of the token and generate enormous returns for investors. For a token of a novel project like betting, price increases for $CHANCER can be up to 1,000%.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Does buying $CHANCER on presale make sense?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Any token that is newly listed is best bought at the presale. The price level is low, and there is a potential to earn big when it is listed on exchanges.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer&rsquo;s presale will occur in 12 stages, each with a higher price than the previous one. As such, the price is the lowest in the first phase and the most attractive.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-to-usher-a-new-era-of-betting-as-mastercard-eyes-a-multi-token-network/">Chancer to usher a new era of betting as Mastercard eyes a multi-token network</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-to-usher-a-new-era-of-betting-as-mastercard-eyes-a-multi-token-network/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Memecoin MOOKY Raises $900,000 Ahead of Its Final Presale Stage</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/memecoin-mooky-raises-900000-ahead-of-its-final-presale-stage/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/memecoin-mooky-raises-900000-ahead-of-its-final-presale-stage/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire &#160;]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 10:36:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=144650</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>New York, New York, June 30th, 2023, Chainwire Memecoin Mooky is gearing up for its final presale phase, having raised $900,000 to date. More than just a novel crypto token, Mooky aims to support the environment through a major tree-planting campaign. Mooky will be a community-driven platform whose governance lies in the hands of its [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/memecoin-mooky-raises-900000-ahead-of-its-final-presale-stage/">Memecoin MOOKY Raises $900,000 Ahead of Its Final Presale Stage</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>New York, New York, June 30th, 2023, Chainwire</strong></p>
<p>Memecoin Mooky is gearing up for its final presale phase, having raised $900,000 to date. More than just a novel crypto token, Mooky aims to support the environment through a major tree-planting campaign.</p>
<p>Mooky will be a community-driven platform whose governance lies in the hands of its token holders. While the MOOKY token draws its cues from other successful memecoins, the project has a more ambitious mandate. Mooky was conceived to increase awareness of global environmental challenges and to provide real-world solutions.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" src="https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/1_1688110387jD2jn6a98F.jpg"></p>
<p>The project aims to raise enough funds to sustain an extensive reforestation initiative in key locations around the world. As part of its commitment to nature, Mooky has earmarked donations to charities working on sustainable environmental causes.</p>
<p>From a crypto-economic perspective, the MOOKY token features zero tax and low slippage, providing ample incentives for traders to get involved. Underpinning the project is a deep lore that aligns with Mooky&rsquo;s core goals.</p>
<p>Mooky is based on the concept of a mythical land called Pygmy. This fantastical realm has stunning landscapes, abundant vegetation, and wildlife. As settlers came to the island, they destroyed the vegetation and polluted the air. The monkeys of Pygmy decide to fight back peacefully, teaching the settlers how to respect nature and live harmoniously. Under the leadership of Mooky, they become united and restore nature.</p>
<p><iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/IiPyd5VoQIg"></iframe></p>
<p>To support the project&rsquo;s development while providing greater opportunities for community participation, Mooky has created a collection of 1,000 NFTs. Each NFT is linked to a tree planted in the real world. Holders can access the Ventures Club, which grants access to exclusive rewards and events.</p>
<p>With five days left in the <a href="blank" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">$MOOKY token presale</a>, there is still ample opportunity for crypto holders to get involved and capture the upside to a project that combines memes and nature to great effect.</p>
<h3>About MOOKY</h3>
<p>MOOKY is a community-driven initiative launched in 2023 that embraces the spirit of digital innovation to make a positive impact on the environment. More than just a meme token, MOOKY represents a global community united by a common goal: to inspire change and contribute to global tree-planting efforts.</p>
<p>MOOKY also stands as a symbol of creativity in the digital space, offering unique 3D NFTs that are each linked to real-world tree-planting initiatives. These NFTs serve not only as digital collectibles but also as an entry ticket to the exclusive Mooky Ventures Club, a vibrant community of environmentally conscious enthusiasts.</p>
<p>MOOKY is more than a digital token; it&rsquo;s a movement aiming to better our environment while fostering a unique and engaging digital ecosystem. Join MOOKY in its journey to make a difference and follow the community on various social channels to stay updated.</p>
<p>Users can purchase MOOKY <a href="https://buy.mooky.io/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">here</a>.</p>
<p><a href="https://mooky.io/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><strong>Website</strong></a><strong> | </strong><a href="https://buy.mooky.io/#buy" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><strong>Presale</strong></a><strong> | </strong><a href="https://t.me/MOOKYTOKEN" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><strong>Telegram</strong></a><strong> | </strong><a href="https://www.instagram.com/mookytroop/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><strong>Instagram</strong></a><strong> | </strong><a href="https://twitter.com/MOOKYcoin" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><strong>Twitter</strong></a><strong> | </strong><a href="https://discord.com/invite/xHZQMNztdG" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><strong>Discord</strong></a></p>
<h3>Contact</h3>
<p>Mookashi N, contact@mooky.io</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/memecoin-mooky-raises-900000-ahead-of-its-final-presale-stage/">Memecoin MOOKY Raises $900,000 Ahead of Its Final Presale Stage</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/memecoin-mooky-raises-900000-ahead-of-its-final-presale-stage/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
