<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 01:05:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Cerus Markets Announces 400:1 Leverage Update</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/cerus-markets-announces-4001-leverage-update/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/cerus-markets-announces-4001-leverage-update/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire &#160;]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 01:05:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=140741</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Labuan, Malaysia, May 26th, 2023, Chainwire Cerus Markets is thrilled to announce an exciting update to its leverage options for non-crypto instruments. Effective immediately, Cerus Markets clients can enjoy leverage of up to 400:1 for Forex, Commodities, Indices, and Single Stocks trading. This increase in leverage options allows traders to make the most of their [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/cerus-markets-announces-4001-leverage-update/">Cerus Markets Announces 400:1 Leverage Update</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Labuan, Malaysia, May 26th, 2023, Chainwire</strong></p>
<p>Cerus Markets is thrilled to announce an exciting update to its leverage options for non-crypto instruments. Effective immediately, Cerus Markets clients can enjoy <strong>leverage of up to 400:1</strong> for Forex, Commodities, Indices, and Single Stocks trading.</p>
<p>This increase in leverage options allows traders to make the most of their investments, providing greater market exposure and the potential for higher returns. By offering increased leverage options for non-crypto instruments, Cerus Markets aims to provide clients with even more opportunities to capitalize on market movements.</p>
<p>At Cerus Markets, the company prides itself on its commitment to providing clients with the best possible trading experience. This update is just one example of the company&rsquo;s dedication to ensuring that clients have access to the best tools and trading conditions.</p>
<p><strong>About Cerus Markets</strong></p>
<p>Established in 2022, Cerus Markets Limited is a multi-asset broker authorized and regulated by the Labuan Financial Service Authority, Malaysia. With a focus on innovation, Cerus offers unique crypto derivative products that allow clients to trade over 200 instruments paired with cryptocurrencies. Alongside crypto derivatives, Cerus provides trading opportunities in FX, Commodities, Indices, and Single Stocks.</p>
<p>Cerus Markets believes in empowering traders of all levels with easy and affordable access to the market. The trading platform stands out from traditional brokers by not charging entry fees and allowing trading of a wide range of digital assets starting from just $50, with leverage up to 400:1.</p>
<p>Moreover, traders can benefit from a <strong>100% deposit matching bonus</strong>, doubling the amount of their first deposit and further enhancing their trading experience.</p>
<p>Visit <a href="https://cerusmarkets.com/?&amp;PARTNER_ID=81328&amp;clientSource=PR_distribution&amp;referral=leverage_update&amp;utm_source=Chainwire_com&amp;utm_medium=PR_distribution" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">cerusmarkets.com</a> to learn more about Cerus Markets and its offerings.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.instagram.com/cerusmarkets/?&amp;PARTNER_ID=81328&amp;clientSource=PR_distribution&amp;referral=leverage_update&amp;utm_source=Chainwire_com&amp;utm_medium=PR_distribution" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Instagram</a> l <a href="https://twitter.com/CerusMarkets?&amp;PARTNER_ID=81328&amp;clientSource=PR_distribution&amp;referral=leverage_update&amp;utm_source=Chainwire_com&amp;utm_medium=PR_distribution" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Twitter</a> l <a href="https://t.me/cerusmarkets_official?&amp;PARTNER_ID=81328&amp;clientSource=PR_distribution&amp;referral=leverage_update&amp;utm_source=Chainwire_com&amp;utm_medium=PR_distribution" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Telegram</a></p>
<h5>Contact</h5>
<p><strong>Marketing Director at Cerus Markets</strong><br>
<strong>Veronica Imasheva</strong><br>
<strong>marketing@cerusmarkets.com</strong></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/cerus-markets-announces-4001-leverage-update/">Cerus Markets Announces 400:1 Leverage Update</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/cerus-markets-announces-4001-leverage-update/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Metacade price and the debt ceiling impasse opportunity</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-price-and-the-debt-ceiling-impasse-opportunity/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 20:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-price-and-the-debt-ceiling-impasse-opportunity/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Credit rating agencies are watching the ongoing debt ceiling debate in Washington. Fitch placed the US into a rating watch negative area. The debt ceiling crisis is creating a good buying opportunity. Metacade (MCADE), like other cryptocurrencies and stocks, has come under intense pressure as the debt ceiling crisis has escalated. The token was trading [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-price-and-the-debt-ceiling-impasse-opportunity/">Metacade price and the debt ceiling impasse opportunity</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Credit rating agencies are watching the ongoing debt ceiling debate in Washington.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Fitch placed the US into a rating watch negative area.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The debt ceiling crisis is creating a good buying opportunity.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=invezz&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news"><u>Metacade</u></a> (MCADE), like other cryptocurrencies and stocks, has come under intense pressure as the debt ceiling crisis has escalated. The token was trading at $0.022, which was much lower than its all-time high of $0.046. Other cryptocurrencies have also been in the red. Bitcoin has retreated from the year-to-date high of $31,000 to below $27,000.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Debt ceiling crisis opportunity</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade price has not retreated because of its bad fundamentals. Instead, it has dropped because of the ongoing risk-off sentiment among market participants. This is evidenced by the fact that the US dollar index has surged to the highest level in more than a month. The closely watched VIX index has also jumped by double-digits.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The main concern is that the American government will default on its debt obligations in June if Democrats and Republicans fail to reach an agreement. Recent reports show that talks between the two negotiators have hit a wall. As a result, Fitch, a major rating agency announced that it was placing the US in a rating watch negative area. The report said:</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;The brinkmanship over the debt ceiling, failure of the U.S. authorities to meaningfully tackle medium-term fiscal challenges that will lead to rising budget deficits and a growing debt burden signal downside risks to U.S. creditworthiness.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">I believe that the debt ceiling issue is creating a good opportunity for investors to buy the dip in key financial assets like Metacade and stocks. For one, odds are that the US will not default since the two sides will reach an agreement.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Janet Yellen, the head of the Treasury, has said that the US will run out of money on June 1. This means that there are still six weeks to reach an agreement. Historically, including in 2011, these deals are reached in the last day.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">A common saying in the market recommends buying when other people are fearful. This is a strategy that has worked well in the past crises. For example, it worked well when the Covid-19 pandemic was starting. Also, investors who bought the dip during the Global Financial Crisis made strong profits over the years.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Metacade fundamentals are strong</h2>
<p dir="ltr">For starters, Metacade is a new blockchain project that raised over $16 million in a token sale. The developers are building a gaming product that is expected to be much better than existing products like Axie Infinity and Decentraland.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to Metacade&rsquo;s&nbsp;<a href="https://metacade.co/whitepaper.pdf"><u>white paper</u></a><strong>,&nbsp;</strong>the developers are now working on the game, which will be launched in the next few months. At the same time, they are working to have the token listed by leading exchanges. As we wrote&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-price-prediction-one-day-to-mexc-global-listing/"><u>here</u></a><strong>,&nbsp;</strong>it has already been listed by MEXC and BitMart.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade has strong fundamentals since it is in an industry that is expected to grow in the next few years. A reccnt&nbsp;<a href="https://www.marketsandmarkets.com/Market-Reports/blockchain-gaming-market-167926225.html"><u>study</u></a> estimates that blockchain games made over $4.6 billion in 2022 and that the volume will jump to over $65 billion by 2027. I believe that Metacade will have a market share in this industry.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Metacade price prediction</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/04/25/1684994533941-e94bc508-631b-448f-babd-4b946a2c83cd.png" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="528" height="318"></p>
<p dir="ltr">On the hourly chart, we see that Metacade price has moved sideways in the past few days. This price action is the same as that of other cryptocurrencies like <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">bitcoin</a>, ethereum, and solana. The coin has moved slightly above the ascending trendline that is shown in black. It has also jumped above the 25-day moving average while the Relative Strength Index (RSI) has moved above the neutral point.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, I suspect that MCADE price will continue consolidating and then make a bullish breakout later this month. If this happens, the next level to watch will be at $0.024. A move above that level will bring the resistance at $0.30 into view.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-price-and-the-debt-ceiling-impasse-opportunity/">Metacade price and the debt ceiling impasse opportunity</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Blockchain.com CEO explains what a U.S. default could mean for cryptocurrencies</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/blockchain-com-ceo-us-default-cryptocurrencies/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wajeeh Khan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 19:06:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=140690</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Blockchain.com CEO says debt default will initially hit crypto. Peter Smith expects 2024 to be a strong year for cryptocurrencies. He made the comments today at the 2023 Qatar Economic Forum. In the short-term, cryptocurrencies will likely take a hit if the United States indeed ends up in its first-ever debt default, says Peter Smith [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/blockchain-com-ceo-us-default-cryptocurrencies/">Blockchain.com CEO explains what a U.S. default could mean for cryptocurrencies</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Blockchain.com CEO says debt default will initially hit crypto.</li>
<li>Peter Smith expects 2024 to be a strong year for cryptocurrencies.</li>
<li>He made the comments today at the 2023 Qatar Economic Forum.</li>
</ul>
<p>In the short-term, cryptocurrencies will likely take a hit if the United States indeed ends up in its first-ever debt default, says Peter Smith &ndash; the Chief Executive of Blockchain.com.</p>
<h2>Smith expects a quick recovery though</h2>
<p>Interestingly, though, he does not expect that weakness to last for long. Smith&rsquo;s medium to long-term outlook on the market remains positive as ever.</p>
<blockquote><p>On a long horizon, these are probably good for crypto &hellip; if the U.S. government defaults, we&rsquo;ll see a quick pullback and then a very strong push upward in the crypto market.</p></blockquote>
<p>He also confirmed today that the crypto exchange was considering expanding its small Middle Eastern Office in the United Arab Emirates.</p>
<p>It is also noteworthy that House Speaker Kevin McCarthy <a href="https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/white-house-republicans-seek-close-us-debt-ceiling-deal-deadline-nears-2023-05-25/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">expressed confidence</a> this morning that Republicans will reach a deal with the White House on debt ceiling in time.</p>
<h2>2024 could be a high year for crypto</h2>
<p>Also on Thursday, CEO Peter Smith forecast 2024 to be a very strong year for the crypto space.</p>
<p>His view is based on a pattern that this market seems to follow &ndash; 2021 was a high year, 2022 was a major correction, 2023 is recovery, and the next year will be of exponential growth again. Speaking at the <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/videos/2023-05-25/blockchain-com-ceo-on-cryptocurrency-moves" target="_blank" rel="noopener">2023 Qatar Economic Forum</a>, he added:</p>
<blockquote><p>I think the crypto market is going to be much bigger in the future than it is today. I expect the market to be positive for the next twelve to eighteen months.</p></blockquote>
<p>Remember that the total supply of <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/bitcoin/">bitcoin</a> is scheduled to <a href="https://www.investopedia.com/bitcoin-halving-4843769" target="_blank" rel="noopener">halve</a> in April of 2024 &ndash; an event known to benefit the crypto market at large.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/blockchain-com-ceo-us-default-cryptocurrencies/">Blockchain.com CEO explains what a U.S. default could mean for cryptocurrencies</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto casinos: revolutionizing payouts, privacy and fairness</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-casinos-revolutionizing-payouts-privacy-and-fairness/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 17:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto adoption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gaming]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-casinos-revolutionizing-payouts-privacy-and-fairness/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrency has transformed the casino withdrawal process. Crypto casinos are leveraging the power of blockchain tecchnology and cryptocurrencies to prioritize user privacy.&#160; Cryptographic algorithms and smart contracts are helping ensure provably fair gaming. In recent years, the world of online gambling has undergone a profound transformation with the advent of crypto casinos. These innovative platforms [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-casinos-revolutionizing-payouts-privacy-and-fairness/">Crypto casinos: revolutionizing payouts, privacy and fairness</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Cryptocurrency has transformed the casino withdrawal process.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Crypto casinos are leveraging the power of blockchain tecchnology and cryptocurrencies to prioritize user privacy.&nbsp;</li>
<li dir="ltr">Cryptographic algorithms and smart contracts are helping ensure provably fair gaming.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">In recent years, the world of online gambling has undergone a profound transformation with the advent of crypto casinos. These innovative platforms have brought about a wave of change, revolutionizing the way payouts are processed, privacy is upheld and fairness is ensured in the realm of online gaming.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How cryptocurrency transforms the casino withdrawal process</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Traditional online casinos often present challenges when it comes to the speed and security of withdrawals, leaving players frustrated with lengthy processing times and potential vulnerabilities. However, with the rise of crypto casinos, players can now experience a seamless and efficient withdrawal process. <a href="https://zamsino.com/crypto/casinos/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Zamsino&rsquo;s research</a> on crypto technology in online casinos has shed light on the transformative potential of crypto technology, highlighting its ability to revolutionize payments.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">By leveraging blockchain technology, transactions are conducted directly between the player and the casino, eliminating the need for intermediaries and reducing the processing time significantly. The decentralized nature of cryptocurrencies ensures that funds are securely transferred, providing players with peace of mind and prompt access to their winnings.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">The anonymity features of crypto casinos</h2>
<p dir="ltr">At the core of crypto casinos lies a paramount focus on privacy, offering players an unprecedented level of anonymity in their gambling activities.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Unlike traditional online casinos that often require personal information for registration and transactions, crypto casinos leverage the power of cryptocurrencies to prioritize user privacy. By using pseudonymous transactions through blockchain technology, players can enjoy a heightened sense of confidentiality. Personal details are not linked to the transactions, shielding players from potential privacy breaches and identity theft.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The anonymity <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/blockchain/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">features of crypto</a> casinos empower individuals to gamble without the fear of their personal information being compromised, providing a safe and discreet environment for online gaming.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">The role of blockchain technology in ensuring provably fair gaming</h2>
<p dir="ltr">With the emergence of blockchain technology, the concept of fairness in online gaming has been redefined, leading to the advent of provably fair gaming in crypto casinos. Traditional online casinos have often faced skepticism regarding the fairness of their games, leaving players uncertain about the integrity of their outcomes. However, blockchain technology has introduced a groundbreaking solution.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Through cryptographic algorithms and smart contracts, players can independently verify the randomness and fairness of each game&rsquo;s outcome.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Transparent and immutable records stored on the blockchain provide an auditable trail, ensuring that the casino cannot manipulate the results. This innovative approach has instilled a new level of trust among players, allowing them to engage in online gambling with confidence.</p>
<p dir="ltr">By leveraging the power of cryptocurrencies and blockchain technology, crypto casinos have emerged as a secure, transparent and decentralized alternative to traditional online casinos</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-casinos-revolutionizing-payouts-privacy-and-fairness/">Crypto casinos: revolutionizing payouts, privacy and fairness</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Circle launches its euro-backed stablecoin on Avalanche</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/circle-launches-its-euro-backed-stablecoin-on-avalanche/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/circle-launches-its-euro-backed-stablecoin-on-avalanche/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 16:29:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/circle-launches-its-euro-backed-stablecoin-on-avalanche/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The euro-backed stablecoin will bring more liquidity to the Avalanche network, Circle said in a press release. Developers using USDC can now easily integrate Euro Coin. Wallets that support Euro Coin on Avalanche include Coinbase Wallet and MetaMask. Circle, the issuer of the USDC, has launched its other fiat-backed stablecoin Euro Coin on Avalanche, a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/circle-launches-its-euro-backed-stablecoin-on-avalanche/">Circle launches its euro-backed stablecoin on Avalanche</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">The euro-backed stablecoin will bring more liquidity to the Avalanche network, Circle said in a press release.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Developers using USDC can now easily integrate Euro Coin.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Wallets that support Euro Coin on Avalanche include Coinbase Wallet and MetaMask.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Circle, the issuer of the USDC, has launched its other fiat-backed <a href="https://coinjournal.net/learn/what-are-stablecoins/">stablecoin</a> Euro Coin on <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/avalanche/">Avalanche</a>, a smart contracts enabled layer-1 blockchain.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Avalanche&rsquo;s AVAX, currently trading at around $14.05, is the 17th largest cryptocurrency with a market cap of $4.7 billion.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Euro liquidity comes to Avalanche</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Circle says it expects Euro Coin&rsquo;s launch on Avalanche will be the first in a series that&rsquo;s set to see the euro-backed stablecoin bring multi-chain euro liquidity to developers and ecosystem users around the world.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Deployment on Avalanche also means apps that support USDC will easily integrate Euro Coin, the digital technology firm said in a <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/circle-takes-euro-coin-multi-chain-with-launch-on-avalanche-301834001.html" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">press release</a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>When we first introduced Euro Coin on Ethereum last year, we wanted anyone with an internet connection to have access to the euro across borders and time zones</em>,&rdquo; said Joao Reginatto, VP of Product at Circle. He added:</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>By launching Euro Coin on Avalanche&rsquo;s fast and efficient platform, we can help developers and their users experience near-instant, more cost effective financial transactions and unlock new possibilities for payments, remittances and 24/7 FX</em>.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Ava Labs VP of Business Development John Nahas said having the euro-backed stablecoin on Avalanche opens up the blockchain network to new possibilities for developers and other users.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>We continue to see great adoption and volume behind Circle&rsquo;s USDC, and expect great feedback and usage of Euro Coin on Avalanche. DeFi continues to expand into a multi-currency, cross-border environment &ndash; delivering a trusted and fully reserved euro stablecoin like Euro Coin will greatly accelerate the adoption of instant payments and remittances to a much larger swath of the world</em>,&rdquo; Nahas noted.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to Circle, apps and wallets that support the stablecoin on Avalanche include Coinbase Wallet, MetaMask, BENQI, Cables, Core, and Curve.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Circle Account holders access to Euro Coin liquidity on the Avalanche platform, with support for trading or lending in crypto capital markets available. Euro Coin can also be held in custody, or used for payments.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/circle-launches-its-euro-backed-stablecoin-on-avalanche/">Circle launches its euro-backed stablecoin on Avalanche</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/circle-launches-its-euro-backed-stablecoin-on-avalanche/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>South Korea passes law requiring all officials to disclose crypto holdings</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/south-korea-passes-law-requiring-all-officials-to-disclose-crypto-holdings/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/south-korea-passes-law-requiring-all-officials-to-disclose-crypto-holdings/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 14:22:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Policy and Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[South Korea]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/south-korea-passes-law-requiring-all-officials-to-disclose-crypto-holdings/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Korean officials are now required to disclose any crypto holdings above $760. The bill outlining the new law was unanimously passed by lawmakers and ratified on Thursday, 25 May. Strict rules around crypto holdings for public officials come after a scandal where one Kim Nam-kuk was said to have held $4.5 million worth of crypto. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/south-korea-passes-law-requiring-all-officials-to-disclose-crypto-holdings/">South Korea passes law requiring all officials to disclose crypto holdings</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Korean officials are now required to disclose any crypto holdings above $760.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The bill outlining the new law was unanimously passed by lawmakers and ratified on Thursday, 25 May.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Strict rules around crypto holdings for public officials come after a scandal where one Kim Nam-kuk was said to have held $4.5 million worth of crypto.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/">Cryptocurrency news</a> out of <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/south-korea/">South Korea</a> states that the requirement that government officials disclose all their cryptocurrency holdings has been passed into law.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The National Assembly&rsquo;s move to adopt the bill means South Korea lawmakers and other high ranking government officials will now have to make public their Bitcoin or other crypto assets they hold.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Korean officials to disclose their crypto holdings</h2>
<p dir="ltr">According to a local <a href="https://www.news1.kr/articles/5058538" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">news report</a> by News1, the country&rsquo;s National Assembly unanimously passed the &ldquo;Kim Nam-guk Prevention Law&rdquo; on Monday, 22 May and approved it in plenary on Thursday, 25 May, 2023.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The bill comes into effect a few days after Kim Nam-kuk, a former opposition party member, was revealed to have held crypto assets worth roughly $4.5 million on the Wemix exchange. The revelations caused uproar, with allegations of money laundering surfacing.</p>
<p dir="ltr">South Korea&rsquo;s amendments to its National Assembly Act and the Public Service Ethics Act now obligates public officials to comply with the law if they hold any cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In particular, affected individuals will have to declare all crypto holdings that amount to $760 or more. The requirement is in place for disclosures involving cash, stocks, and bonds among other assets.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/south-korea-passes-law-requiring-all-officials-to-disclose-crypto-holdings/">South Korea passes law requiring all officials to disclose crypto holdings</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/south-korea-passes-law-requiring-all-officials-to-disclose-crypto-holdings/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stably Launches #USD as the First BRC20 Stablecoin on the Bitcoin Network</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/stably-launches-usd-as-the-first-brc20-stablecoin-on-the-bitcoin-network/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/stably-launches-usd-as-the-first-brc20-stablecoin-on-the-bitcoin-network/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire &#160;]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 13:09:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=140662</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Renton, United States, May 25th, 2023, Chainwire Stably, a leading Stablecoin-as-a-Service (SCaaS) and fiat on/off-ramp infrastructure provider for Web3 projects, is aiming to revolutionize the nascent Bitcoin ordinals market by launching its US Dollar (USD)-backed stablecoin, Stably USD, as a natively-issued BRC20 token under the symbol #USD. This groundbreaking development marks a critical milestone in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/stably-launches-usd-as-the-first-brc20-stablecoin-on-the-bitcoin-network/">Stably Launches #USD as the First BRC20 Stablecoin on the Bitcoin Network</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Renton, United States, May 25th, 2023, Chainwire</strong></p>
<p><a href="http://stably.io/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Stably</a>, a leading Stablecoin-as-a-Service (SCaaS) and fiat on/off-ramp infrastructure provider for Web3 projects, is aiming to revolutionize the nascent Bitcoin ordinals market by launching its US Dollar (USD)-backed stablecoin, <a href="https://stably.io/brc20-usd" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Stably USD</a>, as a natively-issued BRC20 token under the symbol <strong>#USD</strong>. This groundbreaking development marks a critical milestone in the exponentially growing Bitcoin ordinals ecosystem that is now reaching half a billion dollars in total market capitalization in less than six months.</p>
<p>#USD is a BRC20 standard stablecoin created via the Bitcoin <a href="https://docs.ordinals.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">ordinals protocol</a> which was introduced in January 2023 after the recent <a href="https://bitcoin.org/en/releases/0.21.1/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Taproot</a> upgrade. BRC20 tokens use a technique called ordinal inscriptions to attach data to individual &ldquo;satoshis,&rdquo; the smallest unit of a Bitcoin. These satoshis can then represent anything from digital art ownership to &ldquo;meme coins&rdquo; and even stablecoins.</p>
<p>According to Stably, every #USD token is backed 1-to-1 with USD in a collateral account managed by a US-regulated custodian for the benefit of KYC/AML-verified token holders. Monthly reports for the account are also conducted by a third-party stablecoin attestor to ensure #USD tokens are always fully collateralized with USD.</p>
<p>&ldquo;<strong>When I met Domo, the creator of the BRC20 standard, at the Bitcoin 2023 conference in Miami, I told him about our upcoming plans for #USD</strong>,&rdquo; said Kory Hoang, Stably&rsquo;s CEO and Co-Founder. &ldquo;<strong>He thought it was great and funny how we are creating a stablecoin on Bitcoin to enable Bitcoin trading on-chain&hellip; With a stablecoin built on Bitcoin. I&rsquo;m still chuckling about it to this day, actually</strong>. <strong>In just one week after that, however, we made it happen!</strong>&rdquo;</p>
<p>The integration of BRC20 #USD into the Bitcoin network is part of Stably&rsquo;s mission to power the next billion Web3 users with a seamless fiat-to-crypto and stablecoin onramp to all popular and emerging blockchain networks. The company&rsquo;s upcoming collaborations with prominent ordinals and BRC20 projects, including <a href="https://unisat.io/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">UniSat</a>&ndash;the world&rsquo;s largest decentralized wallet/marketplace for ordinals&ndash;and <a href="http://ordzaar.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Ordzaar</a>&ndash;Asia&rsquo;s first decentralized ordinals marketplace project, reflect Stably&rsquo;s aspiration to drive global innovation and adoption toward decentralized finance on the Bitcoin network, or &ldquo;BitFi.&rdquo; Additionally, Stably&rsquo;s engineers are now exploring the new <a href="https://academy.binance.com/en/glossary/orc-20-tokens" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">ORC20</a> standard for Bitcoin ordinals, which could significantly enhance the token properties of #USD once implemented.</p>
<p>#USD can be issued/redeemed with Fedwire, SWIFT, USDC, and USDT by KYC-verified users across 200+ countries/regions currently, including up to 44 US states. Stably states that it is employing a <a href="https://support.stably.io/en/articles/7933928-how-to-buy-and-sell-brc20-usd" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">manual process</a> of issuance/redemption for #USD&rsquo;s initial launch but plans to release support for automatic issuance/redemption through <a href="https://ramp.stably.io/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Stably Ramp</a>, the company&rsquo;s plug-and-play fiat gateway widget, during Q3 2023. By then, users of #USD will be able to on/off-ramp via more traditional payment methods like ACH, instant ACH, and credit/debit cards, in addition to bank wires.</p>
<p>Founded in 2018, the 20+ team member Seattle FinTech is backed by leading institutional and angel investors in the crypto space, such as Morgan Creek Capital, BEENEXT, 500 Startups, Hard Yaka, CREAM Labs, Sunny Lu of VeChain, and Paul Stahura of Donuts, Inc. The company has raised over $7.5-million in total funding to-date, $5-million of which was collected during its last Pre-Series A round in December 2021. Stably has also expanded its fiat on/off-ramp and stablecoin natively to more than ten emerging networks, including Arbitrum, XRP Ledger, Stellar, Tezos, VeChainThor, Harmony, Polymesh, Coreum, ICON, and Chia Network.</p>
<h3 class="ql-align-justify">About Stably</h3>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Stably is a Web3 payment infrastructure provider and FinCEN-registered MSB from Seattle. The company specializes in providing stablecoins and fiat &lt;&gt; crypto on and off-ramps to users of Web3 applications. Stably&rsquo;s mission is to power this decade&rsquo;s next billion Web3 users with regulatory-compliant payment infrastructure across both developed and emerging blockchain ecosystems.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Visit <a href="https://www.stably.io/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">stably.io</a> to learn more.</p>
<p><strong>Risk Disclaimer:</strong> Digital assets involve significant risks, including (but not limited to) market volatility, cybercrime, regulatory changes, and technological challenges. Past performance is not indicative of future results. Digital assets are not insured by any government agency and holding digital assets could result in loss of value and even principal. Bridged or wrapped digital assets (e.g. WBTC) involve additional risks, such as technical challenges, higher fees, security vulnerabilities, and reliance on third-party custodians. Please conduct your own thorough research and understand potential risks before purchasing/holding digital assets. Nothing herein shall be considered legal or financial advice. For more information about the risks and considerations when using our services, please visit: <a href="https://stably.io/terms-of-service/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">stably.io/terms-of-service</a>.</p>
<p><strong>Contact</strong></p>
<p>Stably Head of Marketing, Matthew Barrett, Stably, matt.barrett@stably.io</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/stably-launches-usd-as-the-first-brc20-stablecoin-on-the-bitcoin-network/">Stably Launches #USD as the First BRC20 Stablecoin on the Bitcoin Network</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/stably-launches-usd-as-the-first-brc20-stablecoin-on-the-bitcoin-network/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Herencia Artifex, an NFT project for artistic collaboration across genres, sells the first of NFT</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/herencia-artifex-an-nft-project-for-artistic-collaboration-across-genres-sells-the-first-of-nft/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/herencia-artifex-an-nft-project-for-artistic-collaboration-across-genres-sells-the-first-of-nft/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire &#160;]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 13:06:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=140639</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Tokyo, Japan, May 25th, 2023, Chainwire Herencia Artifex promotes collaboration across art world boundaries and provides a venue for artists of different backgrounds and styles to come together and produce creative works. The project name &#8220;Herencia Artifex&#8221; (abbreviated HXA) is Latin for &#8220;Herencia&#8221; (inheritance) and &#8220;Artifex&#8221; (artist). The HXA project aims to use NFT to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/herencia-artifex-an-nft-project-for-artistic-collaboration-across-genres-sells-the-first-of-nft/">Herencia Artifex, an NFT project for artistic collaboration across genres, sells the first of NFT</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Tokyo, Japan, May 25th, 2023, Chainwire</strong></p>
<p>Herencia Artifex promotes collaboration across art world boundaries and provides a venue for artists of different backgrounds and styles to come together and produce creative works.</p>
<p>The project name &ldquo;Herencia Artifex&rdquo; (abbreviated HXA) is Latin for &ldquo;Herencia&rdquo; (inheritance) and &ldquo;Artifex&rdquo; (artist). The HXA project aims to use NFT to pass on outstanding artists and crafts.</p>
<p>This genre-transcending artistic collaboration in the Web3 space will give birth to new art forms and expressions, contributing to enriching the field of art. The creators are determined to create a realistic artistic experience through the NFT collection.</p>
<h2>NFT First &ldquo;Gizan Katoh&rdquo;</h2>
<p>The first NFT &ldquo;Gizan Katoh&rdquo; is a collaboration with Gizan Kato, a Buddhist priest and the main artist of the exhibition, and is based on his work &ldquo;Kirin&rdquo; (Qilin).</p>
<p>&ldquo;Kirin&rdquo; is a phantom animal said to bring good fortune and to appear in a peaceful world in Japan. The &ldquo;Qilin&rdquo; will be reborn as a NFT by Mora, a 3D Artist</p>
<p>The collection has a variety of colors for sale as well as standard designs. In total, 600 NFTs will be sold, with only 15 of each special design.</p>
<p>The collection will be available in multiple colors and will be released all together at the beginning of June on OpenSea. The collection is currently on sale, ending on June 31.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" src="https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Wcw7Z8e_1685007398pHKitxitL8.jpeg"></p>
<h3>Future development</h3>
<p>The second NFT &ldquo;Nails by mei&rdquo; (<a href="https://www.instagram.com/nailsbymei/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"> https://www.instagram.com/nailsbymei/#</a>)</p>
<p>&ldquo;Nails by mei&rdquo;, will be a collaboration with Mei Kawajiri, an artist whose original and unconventional nail designs captivate the world and are supported by many celebrities and other famous people.</p>
<p>The team is excited to see her designs for HXA. In addition to NFT, the creators will also be developing a realistic art collaboration with Gisan Kato.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" src="https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/S4rUpI2_1685007398GI5GvbIDUa.jpeg">Photo Credit&#65306;Photo by Luisa Opalesky</p>
<p><strong>Mora Vieytes (3D Artist &amp; Designer)</strong></p>
<p><strong><img decoding="async" src="https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/igN8vSv_1685007398FB9UROmMYn.jpeg"></strong></p>
<p><a href="https://moravieytes.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://moravieytes.com/</a></p>
<p>3D artist &amp; designer with a focus on playful 3D illustrations, lettering, design and GIFs</p>
<h3><strong>About Herencia Artifex</strong></h3>
<p>Herencia Artifex NFT collections is for art purposes. NFT owners will have prioritized access to special events and community participation rights.</p>
<ul>
<li>Website: <a href="https://www.nft.herenciaartifex.io/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.nft.herenciaartifex.io/</a></li>
<li>Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/HerenciaArtifex" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://twitter.com/HerenciaArtifex</a></li>
<li>Discord: <a href="https://www.instagram.com/herencia_artifex/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.instagram.com/herencia_artifex/</a></li>
<li>Instagram: <a href="https://discord.gg/H8YSZbN9DT" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://discord.gg/H8YSZbN9DT</a></li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Contact</strong></p>
<p>Mizue, info@templecoin.io</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/herencia-artifex-an-nft-project-for-artistic-collaboration-across-genres-sells-the-first-of-nft/">Herencia Artifex, an NFT project for artistic collaboration across genres, sells the first of NFT</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/herencia-artifex-an-nft-project-for-artistic-collaboration-across-genres-sells-the-first-of-nft/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Coin price outlook as BNB Chain transactions slip</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-coin-price-outlook-as-bnb-chain-transactions-slip/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-coin-price-outlook-as-bnb-chain-transactions-slip/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 12:30:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-coin-price-outlook-as-bnb-chain-transactions-slip/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>BNB Coin, like other cryptocurrencies, has been in a consolidation phase recently. The number of transactions in the ecosystem has dropped from its April high. There are concerns about the US debt ceiling as divisions increase. Binance Coin price moved sideways as concerns about the debt ceiling issue continued. After soaring to a high of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-coin-price-outlook-as-bnb-chain-transactions-slip/">Binance Coin price outlook as BNB Chain transactions slip</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">BNB Coin, like other cryptocurrencies, has been in a consolidation phase recently.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The number of transactions in the ecosystem has dropped from its April high.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">There are concerns about the US debt ceiling as divisions increase.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/binance-coin/"><u>Binance Coin</u></a> price moved sideways as concerns about the debt ceiling issue continued. After soaring to a high of $346, in April, the token has dropped to $315, giving it a market cap of over $47 billion. The coin remains about 39% above the lowest level this year.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Debt ceiling concerns remain</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The main reason why the BNB price has gone nowhere in the past few days is the ongoing risk-off sentiment in the market. This sentiment is evidenced by the rising US dollar index (DXY) and the VIX index, as I wrote&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/arpa-iris-cream-bel-waves-prices-rise-as-btc-retreats/"><u>here</u></a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The biggest concern among investors is the ongoing debt ceiling discussion in the United States. With divisions between the democrats and republicans widening, there are concerns that the American government will default.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The plot thickened when Fitch, a leading credit rating agency, placed the American government in a watch for a rating downgrade. This means that the company will not delay downgrading the government in the coming days.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As I wrote in this&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-price-and-the-debt-ceiling-impasse-opportunity/"><u>article</u></a><strong>,&nbsp;</strong>this defauly will likely not happen since the two sides will likely reach an agreement in the 11th hour. In most periods, cryptocurrencies tend to move in sync with each other, which explains why other coins have dropped.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Binance Coin price has moved sideways as the number of&nbsp;<a href="https://www.bscscan.com/"><u>transactions</u></a> in the ecosystem wane. Data by BNB Explorer means that the number of transactions in the ecosystem dropped to 5.337 million on May 17th to $4.41 million on May 24th.</p>
<p dir="ltr">At the same time, the volume of BNB traded per day has been in a strong downward trend, as shown in the chart below. This is also the same as with other cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin, Ethereum, and Solana.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">BNB price prediction</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/04/25/1685017772936-0b845015-b9a1-4e12-a3ea-fdff6bac036f.png" style="width: 608px;height: 295.477px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="608" height="295.477"></p>
<p dir="ltr">The 4H chart shows that the Binance Coin price has moved sideways in the past few days. Looking back, the coin has struggled moving above the important resistance at $337, the highest point on August 9 2022. The coin has also failed to move above this level in February, March, and April this year.</p>
<p dir="ltr">BNB coin price has moved slightly below the 25-period and 50-period moving averages. Volume has dropped after peaking in November 2022. Therefore, the outlook of Binance Coin will likely continue falling below the key support at $300. A move below this level will open the possibility of the coin drop to the key support at $265.7.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy Binance Coin</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>

    <p>eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=MTQwNjU3&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy BNB with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    KuCoin</h3>

    <p>Kucoin is a cryptocurrency exchange which offers over 200 cryptocurrencies.

Kucoin has a wide range of services, such as; a built-in peer-to-peer exchange, spot and margin trading, bank level security and a wide range of accepted payment methods.

Users can benefit from a beginner-friendly interface and relatively low fees.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/kucoin-crypto?guid=MTQwNjU3&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy BNB with KuCoin today            </a>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-coin-price-outlook-as-bnb-chain-transactions-slip/">Binance Coin price outlook as BNB Chain transactions slip</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-coin-price-outlook-as-bnb-chain-transactions-slip/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
