<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 12:22:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Xpeng Shares Fall 7% after the EV Company Posts Q2 2023 Loss Worse Than Q1</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/xpeng-shares-fall-q2-2023-loss/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/xpeng-shares-fall-q2-2023-loss/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 12:22:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Transportation News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[byd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[li auto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tesla]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xpeng]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267388</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/xpeng-shares-fall-q2-2023-loss/">Xpeng Shares Fall 7% after the EV Company Posts Q2 2023 Loss Worse Than Q1</a></p>
<p>Xpeng shares fell because the company's loss increased in Q2 2023. However, deliveries and revenue are still looking good even for Q3.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/xpeng-shares-fall-q2-2023-loss/">Xpeng Shares Fall 7% after the EV Company Posts Q2 2023 Loss Worse Than Q1</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/xpeng-shares-fall-q2-2023-loss/">Xpeng Shares Fall 7% after the EV Company Posts Q2 2023 Loss Worse Than Q1</a></p>
<p>Shares of Chinese electric vehicle <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/xpeng/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Xpeng Inc</a> (HK: 9868) fell over 7% after the company announced disappointing figures for Q2 2023. Xpeng reported a loss of 2.8 billion yuan, higher than the 2.7 billion yuan recorded in Q1. It is also the company’s largest quarterly loss since its August 2020 US initial public offering (IPO).</p>
<p>Xpeng <a href="https://ir.xiaopeng.com/system/files-encrypted/nasdaq_kms/assets/2023/08/18/6-04-37/XPENG%20Reports%20Second%20Quarter%202023%20Unaudited%20Financial%20Results.pdf">reported</a> figures primarily affected by a falling economy in China, which has significantly reduced consumer spending. In addition to this, Xpeng has faced stiff competition from other EV companies throughout Q2. Competitors include <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/byd/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BYD</a>, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/tesla/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tesla</a>, Li Auto, and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/nio/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Nio</a>.</p>
<p>The competition is also getting stiffer as the Elon Musk-led Tesla reduced the prices of its Model S and Model Y vehicles. Tesla cut two Chinese versions of the Model Y by about 14,000 yuan, or $2,000. The different versions cost 349,000 and 299,000 yuan. Tesla has <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-slashes-price-japan/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">cut prices</a> of its vehicles more than a few times to boost sales. In Japan, the company cut prices for Model Y and Model 3 by about 4% and 3%, respectively.</p>
<p>Xpeng also said its revenue for Q2 2023 was 5.06 billion Chinese yuan. Although this met the expectations of analysts polled by Refinitiv, it is a 31% plunge year over year (YoY). Among other metrics, Xpeng revealed that its vehicle margin was negative 8.6% for the quarter, compared to the positive 9.1% in the same period last year.</p>
<h2>Xpeng Deliveries and Revenue Predictions for Q2 and Q3 2023</h2>
<p>The company has been struggling to repair its business after suffering a stock crash of over 80% last year. Xpeng now hopes its new G6 Ultra Smart Coupe SUV will help increase its margins. Co-president Brian Gu also expects that the G6 and other products will increase sales. As part of the earnings release, Gu said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“With the G6 and other new products accelerating sales growth, we expect gross margin to gradually recover while operating efficiency continues to improve and free cash flow to substantially improve.”</p></blockquote>
<p>On a positive note, Xpeng’s deliveries were healthy in Q2 2023, scaling the company’s own projections. The EV maker <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/xpeng-shares-growth-deliveries/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">delivered 23,205</a> vehicles, a 27% increase quarter on quarter. In July alone, Xpeng delivered 11,008 vehicles, a 28% monthly jump. July was the company’s sixth consecutive month of delivery increase. The Chinese auto company had delivered 8,620 cars the month before, which was a 15% improvement from May’s figure.</p>
<p>For Q3 2023, Xpeng believes it would deliver 39,000 to 41,000 products, which would be a YoY increase of between 31.9% to 38.7%. This would mean a lot more deliveries than either Q1 or Q2.</p>
<p>In addition to deliveries, Xpeng is also bullish on revenue, as it predicts a YoY jump of between 24.6% and 31.9% in Q3. Xpeng also expects revenue to sit between 8.5 billion yuan and 9 billion yuan for the upcoming quarter.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/securitize-acquires-onramp-invest/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/xpeng-shares-fall-q2-2023-loss/">Xpeng Shares Fall 7% after the EV Company Posts Q2 2023 Loss Worse Than Q1</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/xpeng-shares-fall-q2-2023-loss/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Securitize Acquires Onramp Invest Extending Tokenized Alts to RIAs </title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/securitize-acquires-onramp-invest/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/securitize-acquires-onramp-invest/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:39:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Deals News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[algo]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[algorand]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[avalanche]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[avax]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[carlos domingo]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[matic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[onramp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[polygon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[rai]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[securitize]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267380</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/securitize-acquires-onramp-invest/">Securitize Acquires Onramp Invest Extending Tokenized Alts to RIAs </a></p>
<p>Securitize intends to improve liquidity and transparency by transferring private investments onto public blockchains like Ethereum, Avalanche, Polygon, and Algorand.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/securitize-acquires-onramp-invest/">Securitize Acquires Onramp Invest Extending Tokenized Alts to RIAs </a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/securitize-acquires-onramp-invest/">Securitize Acquires Onramp Invest Extending Tokenized Alts to RIAs </a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/securitize/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Securitize</a>, a New York-based company focused on expanding investor and business access to tokenized alternative assets, announced Friday the acquisition of Onramp Invest, an asset management firm backed by <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase</a>. According to an official <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/securitize-acquires-onramp-invest-extending-tokenized-alts-to-rias-managing-40b-in-aum-for-first-time-301903561.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">press release</a>, the move is set to reshape the landscape for Registered Investment Advisors (RIAs) and their clients by providing unprecedented access to a diverse range of alternative asset classes, all through the familiar Onramp Invest platform.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="474" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Today we&#39;ve taken a big step forward in expanding access to private markets with our acquisition of <a href="https://twitter.com/Onrampinvest?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@Onrampinvest</a>. RIAs can now offer clients access to top-tier alternative asset classes, lower entry points, and potential for exit liquidity. Learn more: <a href="https://t.co/IfJKSQqgyc">https://t.co/IfJKSQqgyc</a> <a href="https://t.co/kd8T8J5vhy">pic.twitter.com/kd8T8J5vhy</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Securitize (@Securitize) <a href="https://twitter.com/Securitize/status/1692160196859097230?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 17, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>For the first time, RIAs will be able to offer their customers an opportunity to invest in top-performing assets, including private equity, a historically exclusive asset class offering investors exposure to non-publicly traded companies, private credit, a highly sought-after class that recorded a staggering $71.2 billion in capital influx during the last quarter, as well as secondaries and real estate. Securitize CEO Carlos Domingo said:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Our acquisition of Onramp is another big step forward in expanding investor access to top-performing alternative assets and in democratizing private capital markets. Onramp already offers RIAs easy access to digital assets, so it is a natural extension to offer them tokenized alternative assets to complement their portfolios.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Onramp to Continue Its Services as a Unit of Securitize</h2>
<p>Securitize said in its release that Onramp will continue its operations in the US as a subsidiary of the company. The asset management firm with over $40 billion in assets under management already has a business relationship with notable asset managers and digital asset space leaders like WisdomTree, CoinDesk, Global X, and Valkyrie Invest. The firm already partnered with these companies to create crypto investment indexes.</p>
<p>The collective power of Securitize and Onramp will transform how RIAs approach investments. The combined capabilities offer an unmatched fusion of technology and financial expertise, expanding the horizons for advisors and their clients.</p>
<p>Securitize intends to improve liquidity and transparency by transferring private investments onto public blockchains like <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum,</a> <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/avalanche/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Avalanche</a>, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/matic-network/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Polygon</a>, and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/algorand/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Algorand</a>.</p>
<p>Eric Ervin, founder and CEO of Onramp, said that Securitize offers lower minimums and cheaper fees than other companies focused on tokenized assets.</p>
<p>&#8220;More advisors would choose alternatives for their clients because the benefits are clear, but challenges like illiquidity and restricted access were previously significant problems to overcome. Securitize solves this through offering lower minimums, lower fees, and the potential for exit liquidity through secondary markets,&#8221; he said.</p>
<h2>Tokenization Paves the Way for Finance&#8217;s Blockchain Transition</h2>
<p>According to a Decrypt report, Securitize&#8217;s acquisition of Onramp indicates the rising wave of merging traditional financial structures with cutting-edge digital asset solutions. The move highlights the potential for tokenization, a game-changer that could shift financial operations onto blockchain networks.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/blackrock/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BlackRock</a> CEO, Larry Fink, has called this domain the &#8220;next generation for markets&#8221;. During a New York Times DealBook event last December, Fink expressed his views on tokenization, emphasizing its ability to offer &#8220;instantaneous settlement&#8221; and reduced fees.</p>
<p>Despite these advantages, he reassured the audience that the evolution of this technology would not affect BlackRock&#8217;s current business model.</p>
<div id="gtx-trans" style="position: absolute; left: 909px; top: 1131.56px;">
<div class="gtx-trans-icon"></div>
</div>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cypher-protocol-600k-stolen-crypto-cexs/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/securitize-acquires-onramp-invest/">Securitize Acquires Onramp Invest Extending Tokenized Alts to RIAs </a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/securitize-acquires-onramp-invest/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cypher Protocol Freezes $600K Stolen Crypto Across CEXs</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/cypher-protocol-600k-stolen-crypto-cexs/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/cypher-protocol-600k-stolen-crypto-cexs/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:20:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cypher Protocol]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[zachxbt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267381</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cypher-protocol-600k-stolen-crypto-cexs/">Cypher Protocol Freezes $600K Stolen Crypto Across CEXs</a></p>
<p>Cypher Protocol announced this groundbreaking achievement via a post on its official X account on Thursday. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cypher-protocol-600k-stolen-crypto-cexs/">Cypher Protocol Freezes $600K Stolen Crypto Across CEXs</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cypher-protocol-600k-stolen-crypto-cexs/">Cypher Protocol Freezes $600K Stolen Crypto Across CEXs</a></p>
<p>In a recent development, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/solana/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Solana</a>-based decentralized futures exchange, Cypher Protocol has successfully frozen about $600,000 worth of crypto that were stolen during a security exploit recorded on August 7th.</p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/cypher_protocol/status/1692254663884644669" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">According</a> to the post, over 50% of the funds stolen during the security breach have been frozen across several Centralized Exchanges (CEXs). This achievement marks a significant step forward in the battle against cybercrime within the blockchain industry and showcases the potential for blockchain networks to counteract malicious activities.</p>
<p>The stolen funds’ return, however, hinges on a two-pronged approach, the cooperation of the CEXs involved and the issuance of seizure warrants by law enforcement agencies. This dual requirement underscores the complexities surrounding the recovery of stolen digital assets and the jurisdictional challenges that arise in the decentralized landscape.</p>
<p>In its most <a href="https://twitter.com/cypher_protocol/status/1692266915387814275" target="_blank" rel="noopener">recent statement</a>, Cypher Protocol expressed profound gratitude to ZachXBT, an on-chain sleuth and analyst, highlighting his invaluable contributions in the initial freezing of the funds.</p>
<p>ZachXBT’s involvement showcases the power of collaboration and expertise. As the Decentralized Finance (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-decentralized-finance-defi/">DeFi</a>) community navigates the complexities of recovering stolen assets, it&#8217;s individuals like him who lend their skills to ensure that wrongdoers are held accountable and users’ trust is restored.</p>
<h2>Cypher Protocol Navigating Security Breach</h2>
<p>The attack, which unfolded with alarming precision, underscores the vulnerability of even the most technologically advanced platforms. Cypher Protocol fell prey to the attackers who identified and exploited vulnerabilities within its smart contract system.</p>
<p>This breach granted unauthorized access to user funds, leading to a significant loss of assets. Data sourced from Solscan, a Solana blockchain explorer, paints a stark picture of the extent of the attack, a staggering 38,530 Solana (SOL) tokens and approximately $123,184 worth of USD Coin (USDC) were siphoned off.</p>
<p>In reaction to this severe security violation, Cypher Protocol made the difficult choice to <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cypher-protocol-1m-exploit/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">suspend</a> its smart contracts. This decisive measure, while disruptive to the platform&#8217;s operations, was a key step in controlling the breach and avoiding further unwanted access.</p>
<p>Furthermore, Cypher Protocol initiated communication with the hacker on August 10th by offering a 10% white hat bounty, amounting to roughly $120,000. Unfortunately, despite the incentive, the hacker missed the given deadline, prompting the protocol to open the bounty to the public.</p>
<p>Overall, the Cypher Protocol security breach highlights the perpetual maneuvers between security experts and malicious actors within the crypto sector. While blockchain technology is praised for its security features, vulnerabilities and exploits still manage to surface, putting users’ funds at risk.</p>
<p>According to the REKT database, Cypher Protocol&#8217;s security breach came in third in terms of the amount exploited during the month of August. Leveraged yield aggregation platform Steadefi experienced an exploit resulting in a loss of $1.1 million on August 7th. Similarly, Zunami, a DeFi protocol, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/zunami-protocol-manipulation-attack/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">suffered</a> a staggering $2.1 million flash loan attack on August 13th.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tether-discontinue-bitcoin-stablecoin-lack-of-usage/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cypher-protocol-600k-stolen-crypto-cexs/">Cypher Protocol Freezes $600K Stolen Crypto Across CEXs</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/cypher-protocol-600k-stolen-crypto-cexs/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tether Decides to Discontinue Bitcoin Stablecoin amid Lack of Usage</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tether-discontinue-bitcoin-stablecoin-lack-of-usage/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tether-discontinue-bitcoin-stablecoin-lack-of-usage/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:42:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin omni layer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mastercoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[paolo ardoino]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[usdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267364</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tether-discontinue-bitcoin-stablecoin-lack-of-usage/">Tether Decides to Discontinue Bitcoin Stablecoin amid Lack of Usage</a></p>
<p>Along with Bitcoin Omni Layer, Tether has also decided to discontinue the stablecoin versions of Bitcoin Cash and Kusama.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tether-discontinue-bitcoin-stablecoin-lack-of-usage/">Tether Decides to Discontinue Bitcoin Stablecoin amid Lack of Usage</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tether-discontinue-bitcoin-stablecoin-lack-of-usage/">Tether Decides to Discontinue Bitcoin Stablecoin amid Lack of Usage</a></p>
<p>Tether, the issuer of the world&#8217;s largest stablecoin <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/tether/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">USDT</a>, has announced to discontinue its Bitcoin Omni Layer version amid the lack of interest from the users. This Bitcoin stablecoin from Tether was one of the first created.</p>
<p>During its recent announcement, the Tether CTO Paolo Ardoino noted that they would also be discontinuing the stablecoin versions of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin-cash/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin Cash</a> and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/kusama/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Kusama</a>.</p>
<p>As per the statement, Tether has revealed that it will no longer be generating new tokens on the Bitcoin Omni Layer, Kusama, or Bitcoin Cash platforms. While the redemption option will remain accessible for at least a year, the company intends to provide additional notifications before the year&#8217;s end regarding the future handling of redemptions.</p>
<p>The Bitcoin Omni Layer is a smart contract framework constructed atop the Bitcoin blockchain. Originally named &#8220;Mastercoin&#8221;, Tether launched it in July 2013, making it operational two years before Ethereum. Tether introduced USDT as the pioneer stablecoin on the Omni Layer system later in October 2014. It rapidly gained prominence as the highest market capitalization stablecoin, surpassing earlier entrants like BitUSD and NuBits.</p>
<p>During its announcement on Thursday, August 17, the Tether CTO acknowledged the historical importance of the Omni Layer Tether. Ardoino <a href="https://twitter.com/paoloardoino/status/1692154723875328228" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">noted</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“We understand the significance of this decision, particularly for Omni, as it was the first transport layer that Tether used in 2014. The Omni Layer, built on top of Bitcoin, played a crucial role in Tether’s early journey, and we acknowledge the contributions and innovations the team has made to the crypto landscape.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>Challenges of Bitcoin Omni Layer</h2>
<p>The Tether team has highlighted that the Omni Layer confronted obstacles due to the limited popularity of its tokens and the widespread availability of USDT on alternate blockchains. This prompted exchanges to opt for different transport layers instead of Omni, leading to a decline in the usage of USDT Omni. Consequently, the company decided to cease its issuance.</p>
<p>Tether has expressed that it might reconsider issuing the Omni Layer version if Omni experiences increased adoption. Additionally, the company has revealed its efforts in developing a new Bitcoin smart contract system named &#8220;RGB&#8221;. Upon completion, Tether intends to reintroduce an RGB version of itself, effectively returning Tether to the Bitcoin blockchain.</p>
<p>As the stablecoin market continues to expand, even Tether&#8217;s USDT stablecoin could face challenges moving ahead in terms of increasing competition from PayPal and other players.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nikkei-225-biggest-loss-since-dec-2022/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tether-discontinue-bitcoin-stablecoin-lack-of-usage/">Tether Decides to Discontinue Bitcoin Stablecoin amid Lack of Usage</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tether-discontinue-bitcoin-stablecoin-lack-of-usage/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Japan’s Nikkei 225 Average Records Biggest Weekly Loss Not Seen Since December 2022</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nikkei-225-biggest-loss-since-dec-2022/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nikkei-225-biggest-loss-since-dec-2022/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:35:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alibaba]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alibaba group]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hsbc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[japan stock exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jpx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nikkei]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nikkei 225]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tencent]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267307</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nikkei-225-biggest-loss-since-dec-2022/">Japan’s Nikkei 225 Average Records Biggest Weekly Loss Not Seen Since December 2022</a></p>
<p>As the global economic downturn continues, especially with headwinds in China, the Nikkei 225 recorded a big weekly loss as stocks fell.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nikkei-225-biggest-loss-since-dec-2022/">Japan’s Nikkei 225 Average Records Biggest Weekly Loss Not Seen Since December 2022</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nikkei-225-biggest-loss-since-dec-2022/">Japan’s Nikkei 225 Average Records Biggest Weekly Loss Not Seen Since December 2022</a></p>
<p>The Japanese <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-nikkei-225-stock-average-index/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Nikkei 225 index</a> has seen its largest weekly loss in eight months. On Friday, the Nikkei average posted the loss following problems stemming from the outlook on the Chinese economy.</p>
<p>For the week ending Friday, the Nikkei loss came in at 3.1%, the biggest weekly loss since the week that ended on Friday, December 23. The plunge is the third session of loss caused by worry about the Chinese economy, according to Daiwa Securities senior strategist Shuji Hosoi. According to the strategist:</p>
<blockquote><p>“The Japanese market slipped for the same reasons as the past few sessions &#8211; concerns about China’s economy and rising global yields. Japanese equities are easily affected by overseas cues as there are no market moving catalysts at the moment.”</p></blockquote>
<p>According to GCI Asset Management senior portfolio manager Takamasa Ikeda, the Nikkei has peaked as foreign investors are no longer buying as much since July.</p>
<p>Uniqlo owner Fast Retailing fell 1.15%, while department store business Isetan Mitsukoshi Holdings lost 3.77%. The worst performance came from J.Front Retailing, which fell 4.31%. Other stock losses include Fujikura Ltd losing 3.99% to 1,143.00</p>
<p>On the other hand, companies like Tokyo Electron gained 0.68%, while Advantest rose 1.54%, both lending support to the Nikkei. There also was the Mitsubishi Heavy Industries, Ltd up 1.68% to 7,576.00, and Ebara Corp’s 159-point increase, or 2.32%, to 6,999.00. Kuraray Co., Ltd. climbed 3.4% to 1,537.50, the best performance for the session.</p>
<h2>Nikkei Loss Seems Continuous and Has Set Pace for Similar Plunges in Other Indexes</h2>
<p>Last month, Coinspeaker <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/japans-nikkei-225-plunge/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a> a fifth straight loss in the Nikkei. Even though the index rose 27% the week before, it fell below the 25-day moving average for the first time in three months. Individual stocks like Honda and Nissan lost 1.72% and 2.55%, respectively. Yaskawa Electric Corporation posted the biggest loss at 3.44%.</p>
<p>The Nikkei 225 has been retracing from highs in June and cannot yet be sure of a rebound. DailyFX <a href="https://www.dailyfx.com/news/nasdaq-100-dow-and-nikkei-225-hit-one-month-low-as-china-worries-intensify-20230817.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">noted</a> that for the first time since March, the Nikkei 225 fell below the 100-day simple moving average (SMA). The analysis predicts that the Nikkei 225 could find some support around 30,963. Anything lower could cause the index to struggle with the 200-day SMA.</p>
<p>There were also similar losses recorded in other regions. For instance, Australia’s ASX 200 fell 0.68% on Thursday following China’s economic problems and the seemingly hawkish outlook from the Fed. By the close of day, the ANX Group and the Commonwealth Bank of Australia had lost 0.93% and 0.14%, respectively. There also were losses recorded by Westpac Banking Corp, which fell 1.93%, with the National Australia Bank losing 2.08%.</p>
<p>Hong Kong’s Hang Seng Index also fell for the same reasons, although only slightly. Bank stocks were generally bearish, with <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/hsbc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">HSBC Holdings PLC</a> losing 1.08%, while <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/china-construction-bank/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">China Construction Bank</a> lost 0.49%. However, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/alibaba-group/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Alibaba Group Holding Ltd</a> and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/tencent/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tencent Holdings Ltd</a> rose 0.95% and 1.22%, respectively.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/opensea-disable-creator-fees-enforcement/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nikkei-225-biggest-loss-since-dec-2022/">Japan’s Nikkei 225 Average Records Biggest Weekly Loss Not Seen Since December 2022</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nikkei-225-biggest-loss-since-dec-2022/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>OpenSea Moves to Disable Creator Fees Enforcement</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/opensea-disable-creator-fees-enforcement/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/opensea-disable-creator-fees-enforcement/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:27:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Editor's Choice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[creator fee]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFT creators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[opensea]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[operator filter]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267341</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/opensea-disable-creator-fees-enforcement/">OpenSea Moves to Disable Creator Fees Enforcement</a></p>
<p>The change will take effect from August 31, meaning that creators may no longer blacklist NFT marketplaces that don’t enforce royalties.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/opensea-disable-creator-fees-enforcement/">OpenSea Moves to Disable Creator Fees Enforcement</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/opensea-disable-creator-fees-enforcement/">OpenSea Moves to Disable Creator Fees Enforcement</a></p>
<p>Popular non-fungible token (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-are-non-fungible-tokens-nfts/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NFT</a>) marketplace <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/opensea/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">OpenSea</a> is planning to turn off its royalty enforcement tool – Operator Filter. The idea, according to a recent <a href="https://opensea.io/blog/articles/creator-fees-update" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">blog post</a> is to stop creators from receiving additional fees from secondary trades. That is every time their work exchanges hands following the initial sale.</p>
<p>In a statement by OpenSea founder and CEO Devin Finzer, the change will take effect from August 31, meaning that creators may no longer blacklist NFT marketplaces that don’t enforce royalties.</p>
<p>Recall that the Operator Filter feature launched in November 2022. With the tool, artists required buyers to continue paying them creator fees, typically ranging from 2.5% to 10% of the transaction fee. However, the tool wasn&#8217;t nearly as successful as OpenSea had hoped it would be.</p>
<p>Firstly, the NFT ecosystem was not as supportive as expected. Also, some NFT marketplaces such as Blur, Dew and LooksRare sabotaged their prospects by bypassing Operator Filter to avoid OpenSea’s blacklist and ultimately avoid creator fees.</p>
<p>Lastly, some creators also kicked. This set of creators claimed that the tool was impeding their control over where their collections were sold.</p>
<h2>‘Creator Fees Not Going Away’, OpenSea CEO Says</h2>
<p>Even though OpenSea will be ditching Operator Filter from August 31, the tool is currently being used by some existing collections on non-Ethereum blockchains and other projects. Interestingly, despite that some of these platforms themselves made creator fees optional, using OpenSea’s Operator Filter means that they will continue to guarantee creator fees up until February 29, 2024. And only then, can NFT creator fees become fully optional, albeit on all platforms.</p>
<p>Finzer also noted that creator fees are not going away. He suggested that creators and artists have every right to make gains from their works. However, enforcement is not the way to go, he added. Part of his statement reads:</p>
<blockquote><p>“To be clear, creator fees aren’t going away &#8211; simply the ineffective, unilateral enforcement of them.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Essentially, once Operator Filter shuts down in the next two weeks, creators will no longer be able to enforce fees. However, they may still indicate what amount they would love to charge as fees, while buyers can also choose to pay (as a tip) or not.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/mastercard-joins-ripple-consensys-cbdc-partner-program/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/opensea-disable-creator-fees-enforcement/">OpenSea Moves to Disable Creator Fees Enforcement</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/opensea-disable-creator-fees-enforcement/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mastercard Joins Hands with Ripple on Its CBDC Partner Program</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/mastercard-joins-ripple-consensys-cbdc-partner-program/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/mastercard-joins-ripple-consensys-cbdc-partner-program/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 09:45:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Deals News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FinTech News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[consensys]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mastercard]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ripple labs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[visa]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267299</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/mastercard-joins-ripple-consensys-cbdc-partner-program/">Mastercard Joins Hands with Ripple on Its CBDC Partner Program</a></p>
<p>As part of its CBDC Partner Program, Mastercard has joined hands with prominent CBDC leaders and payment giants to work along with the central banks to bring CBDCs to the market under a regulatory framework. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/mastercard-joins-ripple-consensys-cbdc-partner-program/">Mastercard Joins Hands with Ripple on Its CBDC Partner Program</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/mastercard-joins-ripple-consensys-cbdc-partner-program/">Mastercard Joins Hands with Ripple on Its CBDC Partner Program</a></p>
<p>On Thursday, August 17, global payments giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/mastercard/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Mastercard</a> disclosed its CBDC partner program while naming initial partners as <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ripple-labs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ripple</a> and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/consensys/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ConsenSys</a>. Top economies worldwide have been working on central bank digital currencies and thus payment giants like <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/visa-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Visa</a> and Mastercard have also shown interest in this.</p>
<p>In a recent press release, Mastercard unveiled this advancement, emphasizing the rising significance of Central Bank Digital Currencies (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-central-bank-digital-currency-cbdc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CBDC</a>s) in the financial landscape, a trend strongly pursued by central banks.</p>
<p>This trend underscores the growing influence of CBDCs within finance. Consequently, Mastercard aims to capitalize on this mounting interest to solidify its stance within the CBDC domain. As part of its CBDC Partner Program, Mastercard has joined hands with prominent CBDC leaders and payment giants to work along with the central banks to bring CBDCs to the market under a regulatory framework.</p>
<p>Ripple is one of the top players in the CBDC world and is one of the first five partners chosen. Mastercard sees Ripple as a platform for CBDCs, which is because Ripple has been working a lot in the CBDC area. Recently, Ripple also started its own CBDC Platform. Mastercard also talked about how Ripple has been working with the Republic of Palau, which is a big accomplishment for them.</p>
<p>The new CBDC program is created to encourage working together with important people in this area. This was mentioned by Raj Dhamodharan, who is in charge of digital assets and blockchain at Mastercard. Dhamodharan <a href="https://www.mastercard.com/news/perspectives/2023/cbdcs-trust-and-the-evolution-of-money/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">added</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“We believe in payment choice and that interoperability across the different ways of making payments is an essential component of a flourishing economy. As we look ahead toward a digitally driven future, it will be essential that the value held as a CBDC is as easy to use as other forms of money.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>MasterCard&#8217;s CBDC Progress</h2>
<p>This is not the company&#8217;s first push towards central bank digital currency (CBDC) development. Back in September 2020, Mastercard introduced a testing platform that central banks could use to assess CBDC systems. Then, in February 2021, the company began issuing prepaid cards in the Bahamas, which allowed users to convert the Sand Dollar, the CBDC of the country.</p>
<p>In a recent podcast <a href="https://www.theblock.co/post/245364/mastercard-cbdc" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">interview</a> with The Block, Dhamodharan emphasized the importance of flexibility, consumer protection, and privacy in building a CBDC that serves both businesses and consumers from the outset.</p>
<p>Although Mastercard didn&#8217;t provide specifics about the new program&#8217;s details, it highlighted the notion that CBDCs shouldn&#8217;t be implemented in isolation. The CBDC Partner Program aims to assist central banks in creating CBDCs that bring innovative value to the economy rather than being adopted without context.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/evergrande-bankruptcy-protection-in-us/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/mastercard-joins-ripple-consensys-cbdc-partner-program/">Mastercard Joins Hands with Ripple on Its CBDC Partner Program</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/mastercard-joins-ripple-consensys-cbdc-partner-program/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>China’s Evergrande Group Files for Bankruptcy Protection in the US</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/evergrande-bankruptcy-protection-in-us/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/evergrande-bankruptcy-protection-in-us/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Darya Rudz]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 09:38:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Editor's Choice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chapter 15 us]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[China Evergrande]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[china evergrande group]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[evergrande]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[evergrande bankruptcy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[evergrande chapter 15]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[evergrande default]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267301</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/evergrande-bankruptcy-protection-in-us/">China’s Evergrande Group Files for Bankruptcy Protection in the US</a></p>
<p>Evergrande's affiliate Tianji Holdings and the company's subsidiary Scenery Journey have also filed for Chapter 15 protection in the US court.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/evergrande-bankruptcy-protection-in-us/">China’s Evergrande Group Files for Bankruptcy Protection in the US</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/evergrande-bankruptcy-protection-in-us/">China’s Evergrande Group Files for Bankruptcy Protection in the US</a></p>
<p>Evergrande Group, the Chinese second-largest property developer, has filed for Chapter 15 bankruptcy protection in the Manhattan bankruptcy court. The application would allow Evergrande to protect its assets in the US while it is working on a multi-billion dollar deal with creditors.</p>
<h2>Evergrande&#8217;s Crisis</h2>
<p>Evegrande is an investment-holding real estate company engaged in property development, property investment, property management, and property construction. With more than 1,300 projects in more than 280 cities in China, Evergrande has cooperated with more than 860 well-known companies around the world. The company was prospering until 2020 when Chinese authorities introduced new rules to control the amount that big real estate firms could borrow.</p>
<div data-component="text-block">
<div>
<p>In 2020, the Chinese government imposed a &#8220;three red lines&#8221; policy to regulate the leverage taken on by developers, limiting their borrowing based on the following metrics: debt-to-cash, debt-to-equity, and debt-to-assets. Notably, by October 2021, those regulations were violated by 14 of China&#8217;s 30 biggest developers at least once.</p>
<p>The real-estate crisis began, as major property giants ran out of cash. It affected Evergrande Group, leading to its multiple debts and default. The company missed a crucial deadline and failed to repay interest on around $1.2 billion of international loans. In October 2021, Evergrande <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/evergrande-trading-halted-hong-kong/" rel="">announced</a> that it would raise $5 billion by selling a 51% stake in its property management unit to Hopson Development.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div data-component="text-block">
<p>For 2021 and 2022, Evergrande <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/evergrande-81b-loss-two-years/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">suffered</a> an $81 billion combined loss that was primarily attributed to write-downs of properties, return of land, losses on financial assets, and mounting finance costs. By the end of 2022, Evergrande&#8217;s total liabilities surged from $300 billion at the time of its default to $340 billion.</p>
<h2>Filing for Chapter 15 Protection</h2>
</div>
<div data-component="text-block">
<div>
<p>Earlier this year, Evergrande revealed its plans to restructure around $20 billion in overseas debt. The filing for Chapter 15 in the US court is a part of the restructuring strategy. Within the filing, Evergrande Group is seeking the court’s approval to restructure more than $19 billion in the company’s offshore debts.</p>
</div>
</div>
<p>Later this month, Evergrande&#8217;s creditors will vote on the company&#8217;s restructuring proposal, with possible approval by Hong Kong and British Virgin Islands courts in the first week of September.</p>
<p>Chapter 15 is a new chapter added to the Bankruptcy Code by the Bankruptcy Abuse Prevention and Consumer Protection Act of 2005. In general, it aims to provide effective mechanisms for dealing with insolvency cases involving debtors, assets, claimants, and other parties of interest involving more than one country.</p>
<p>Once a foreign entity files for bankruptcy under Chapter 15, the US bankruptcy court can authorize the appointment of a trustee or examiner to act in the other country on behalf of the bankruptcy estate in the United States. Besides, Chapter 15 allows US courts to offer additional aid to foreign representatives, assistance to foreign companies filing bankruptcy cases when the laws of the foreign court may be lacking, and gives foreign creditors the right to participate in bankruptcy cases in the US.</p>
<p>Evergrande&#8217;s affiliate Tianji Holdings and the company&#8217;s subsidiary Scenery Journey have also filed for Chapter 15 protection.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/spacex-reports-profit-q1-2023/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/evergrande-bankruptcy-protection-in-us/">China’s Evergrande Group Files for Bankruptcy Protection in the US</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/evergrande-bankruptcy-protection-in-us/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>SpaceX Reports Profit in Q1 2023 amid Surging Revenue</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/spacex-reports-profit-q1-2023/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/spacex-reports-profit-q1-2023/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 09:34:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[spacex]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[starlink]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267326</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/spacex-reports-profit-q1-2023/">SpaceX Reports Profit in Q1 2023 amid Surging Revenue</a></p>
<p>According to the report, the company recorded a profit of $55 million on revenue of $1.5 billion during the first three months of the year after two consecutive years of losses.  </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/spacex-reports-profit-q1-2023/">SpaceX Reports Profit in Q1 2023 amid Surging Revenue</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/spacex-reports-profit-q1-2023/">SpaceX Reports Profit in Q1 2023 amid Surging Revenue</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/elon-musk/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Elon Musk</a>&#8216;s aerospace company, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/spacex/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SpaceX</a>, has managed to turn a profit in the first quarter of 2023, propelled by its rapidly increasing revenue, The Wall Street Journal reported Thursday, citing internal documents.</p>
<p>WSJ <a href="https://www.wsj.com/tech/behind-the-curtain-of-elon-musks-secretive-spacex-revenue-growth-and-rising-costs-2c828e2b" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a> the financial documents it reviewed showed that the first-quarter results were labeled &#8220;preliminary&#8221;. In contrast, the annual results are considered final, offering a more comprehensive understanding of the company&#8217;s performance over the past year.</p>
<h2>SpaceX Now Valued at $150 Billion</h2>
<p>The company, founded over two decades ago, has emerged as a dominant force in the US space industry, known widely for its satellite-internet enterprise, Starlink. Some of its major customers include NASA, which relies on its products for transporting astronauts to and from the International Space Station.</p>
<p>According to the report, the company&#8217;s financial trajectory has been marked by rapid growth, recently leading to an estimated valuation of around $150 billion during an employee stock sale. This valuation puts SpaceX on par with industry giants like <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/intel/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Intel</a> and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/disney/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Disney</a>.</p>
<p>Before SpaceX&#8217;s modest quarterly profit in 2023, the company reported approximately $5.2 billion in total expenses for the preceding year, a significant increase from the $3.3 billion recorded in the year prior.</p>
<h2>SpaceX Faces Setback in Launching Starship</h2>
<p>Despite its financial successes, SpaceX has also faced setbacks, notably the test flight of its <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/spacex-starship-rocket-system-musk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Starship</a> in April, which ended prematurely due to technical issues. The company is required to obtain regulatory approval before attempting another flight.</p>
<p>Additionally, SpaceX&#8217;s financial resources have been channeled into ventures like Starlink, a satellite-based internet service, and establishing a new factory in Texas.</p>
<p>Last year, SpaceX allocated significant funds to areas including employee salaries, materials, and spacecraft depreciation, demonstrating its commitment to advancing its projects. The company has also invested heavily in research and development, showcasing its dedication to innovation.</p>
<h2>SpaceX Sells Its Bitcoin Holdings</h2>
<p>As per the WSJ report, SpaceX held approximately $373 million worth of Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">BTC</a>) on its balance sheet in 2021 and 2022 and has sold the assets.</p>
<p>While the exact extent of the sale remains undisclosed, indications from the reviewed documents suggest that the crypto asset was indeed liquidated.</p>
<p>In 2021, Musk said he acquired BTC for an undisclosed amount. Shortly after, he also revealed that his company, Tesla, would invest $1.5 billion in the asset, leading to a notable increase in BTC&#8217;s value at the time.</p>
<p>Tesla&#8217;s Q2 2023 report confirmed the sale of almost all its BTC holdings, retaining only $184 million, marking a conversion of roughly 75% from the initial $1.5 billion investment.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-approve-ether-futures-us/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/spacex-reports-profit-q1-2023/">SpaceX Reports Profit in Q1 2023 amid Surging Revenue</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/spacex-reports-profit-q1-2023/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>SEC to Approve Ether Futures ETF in US</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-approve-ether-futures-us/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-approve-ether-futures-us/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Babafemi Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 08:57:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[exchange traded fund]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266925</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-approve-ether-futures-us/">SEC to Approve Ether Futures ETF in US</a></p>
<p>The Ether futures ETF tracks the futures contract of Ethereum.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-approve-ether-futures-us/">SEC to Approve Ether Futures ETF in US</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-approve-ether-futures-us/">SEC to Approve Ether Futures ETF in US</a></p>

<p>The US Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) is reportedly ready to approve Ether futures exchange-traded funds (ETFs), <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-08-17/sec-said-to-be-poised-to-allow-us-debut-of-ether-futures-etfs-eth" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">according to Bloomberg</a>. Thus, its approval would mark a significant milestone for investors looking to gain exposure to the second-largest cryptocurrency by market capitalization.</p>
<p>So far, there have been 16 active filings for an Ether Futures ETF. It is unclear which ETF application the SEC may approve. However, officials suggest there may be an approval by October.</p>
<h2>New Territory for Ether Futures ETF Approval</h2>
<p>Valkyrie Investments, Volatility Shares, Direxion, Grayscale, VanEck, Roundhill, Proshares, and Bitwise have all filed <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ethereum-etf-sec-bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ETF applications</a>. The longest of these filings is by Valkyrie Investments and has been active for 19 days.</p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/EricBalchunas/status/1692314639235735836?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1692314639235735836%7Ctwgr%5E6c424b12a9f7b38cd37da91a53e93905d8e826c8%7Ctwcon%5Es1_&amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fcointelegraph.com%2Fnews%2Fsec-to-approve-ethererum-eth-futures-etf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">According to Bloomberg analyst Eric Balchunas</a>, historically, the SEC would have asked companies seeking approval for Ether futures ETF to withdraw their filing in 5-6 days.</p>
<p>“We are now on Day 13 and no withdrawals. Not home-free yet but very good sign. As we predicted these will likely hit market in mid-October,” tweeted Balchunas.</p>
<p>Another analyst, James Seyffart, <a href="https://twitter.com/JSeyff/status/1691842682346201510" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">noted</a> that the odds of an approval increases as more days pass between the filing and the SEC’s response.</p>
<h2>Spot ETF vs Futures ETF</h2>
<p>While the SEC is more likely to approve the Ether futures ETF, it remains unclear what its stance is on filings for the Bitcoin spot ETFs. This is not surprising since the SEC has different standards for approving futures-based ETFs and spot-based ETFs.</p>
<p>Previously, the SEC has expressed concerns about the potential for fraud and manipulation in the BTC spot market. It also noted the lack of reliable data and custody solutions. Consequently, the regulator has rejected several proposals for spot bitcoin ETFs, citing these reasons. Conversely, the SEC has approved several proposals for futures-based bitcoin ETFs.</p>
<p>The first Bitcoin (BTC) futures ETF launched in the US in 2021. Since then, BTC futures ETFs have attracted billions of dollars in inflows. The largest Bitcoin ETF is the ProShares Bitcoin Strategy ETF, with over $980 million in assets under management. The Ether Futures ETF is more similar to the Bitcoin Futures ETF, so the chances of approval remain.</p>
<p>Following the news, the price of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/">ETH</a> rallied after crashing just a few hours before. At the time of writing, Ether was trading at $1691.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-26k-tests-investor-resilience/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-approve-ether-futures-us/">SEC to Approve Ether Futures ETF in US</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-approve-ether-futures-us/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4256 metric#misses=43 metric#hit-ratio=99.0 metric#bytes=1090225 metric#prefetches=220 metric#store-reads=22 metric#store-writes=3 metric#store-hits=227 metric#store-misses=4 metric#sql-queries=35 metric#ms-total=109.61 metric#ms-cache=6.66 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.2775 metric#ms-cache-ratio=6.1 -->