<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 22:01:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Why is Bitcoin is outperforming Ethereum? Market changing in 2023</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/why-is-ethereum-being-outperformed-by-bitcoin-historical-pattern-changing-in-2023/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dan Ashmore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 22:01:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/why-is-ethereum-being-outperformed-by-bitcoin-historical-pattern-changing-in-2023/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key Takeaways Ethereum has historically outperformed Bitcoin in bull runs The pattern has flipped to start the year, with Bitcoin dominance rising&#160; Our Analyst Dan Ashmore looks through history to show how and why the pattern is changing The Flippening, huh? Nothing incites debate within crypto circles quite like it.&#160; Referring to a scenario where [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/why-is-ethereum-being-outperformed-by-bitcoin-historical-pattern-changing-in-2023/">Why is Bitcoin is outperforming Ethereum? Market changing in 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2 dir="ltr">Key Takeaways</h2>
<ul>
<li>Ethereum has historically outperformed Bitcoin in bull runs</li>
<li>The pattern has flipped to start the year, with Bitcoin dominance rising&nbsp;</li>
<li>Our Analyst Dan Ashmore looks through history to show how and why the pattern is changing</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"></p>
<p dir="ltr">The Flippening, huh? Nothing incites debate within crypto circles quite like it.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Referring to a scenario where <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/ethereum/"><u>Ethereum</u></a> flips <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/bitcoin/"><u>Bitcoin</u></a> for the number one spot in the cryptocurrency ranks, the Flippening is anything from inevitable to delusional, depending on who you ask.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">I&rsquo;m not sure I want to walk across the eggshells of that debate, for fear of my Twitter DMs, but I noticed something pretty interesting today when digging into the data on Ethereum vs Bitcoin.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Ethereum is strongly correlated with Bitcoin</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Firstly, the obvious. Ethereum is incredibly correlated with Bitcoin because, well, it is a cryptocurrency, and every crypto&rsquo;s fate is tied to that of the orange coin. We know this by now.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The graph below shows how tight this relationship has been since Ethereum went live back in 2015.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/12547125">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">But while these two best buddies follow each other around across the price charts, there are scenarios where they diverge a little bit. The famous ETH/BTC ratio is one which Ether fans in particular keep a keen eye on.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">It peaked in June 2017 at close to 0.15 before freefalling down to 0.025 before the end of the year. Today, it trades at around 0.07.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/12547322">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<h2 dir="ltr">Ether is better at bull markets than Bitcoin</h2>
<p dir="ltr">You may have noticed that the previous ETH/BTC chart resembled the shape of the crypto market overall, through its many ups and downs.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">I plotted the price of Bitcoin against this ETH/BTC ratio. Indeed, the ratio rises as Bitcoin rises, and falls and Bitcoin falls. Using the Bitcoin price as a proxy for the whole industry, this suggests that the ETH/BTC ratio rises in bull markets and falls in bear markets.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/12547350">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">This makes sense. Bitcoin is often referred to as the boomer coin. I quite like it that way, despite it being meant as an insult, by the way. But it&rsquo;s an understandable moniker because Bitcoin does move like a pensioner during bull markets when compared to altcoins.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Ether may be the largest of the altcoins, but it still outperforms Bitcoin when the bulls are out to play.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">On the flip side, Bitcoin outperforms when the party ends. And by outperform, I mean that it tends to drop 60% as opposed to 70%. But hey, that&rsquo;s for another day.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Pattern has flipped in 2023</h2>
<p dir="ltr">But the price charts are showing something different. One month into the new year, Bitcoin has surged while the ETH/BTC ratio has fallen &ndash; precisely the opposite of what has happened historically.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">I charted the ratio back to the start of November, when Sam Bankman-Fried&rsquo;s <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ftx-insolvent-what-next-for-crypto/"><u>fun and games</u></a> were revealed to the world and crypto fell, with Bitcoin cratering down to $16,000.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The chart shows that the pattern remained as you would expect, i.e. the ratio fell as crypto and Bitcoin pulled back. But as we turned the page into 2023, the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/why-are-crypto-prices-rising-2023-off-to-hot-start/"><u>crypto market flipped</u></a> and Bitcoin soared. Only problem is, ETH didn&rsquo;t follow, but rather the ratio has fallen, from 0.077 on January 11th to 0.068 currently, despite Bitcoin spiking from $17,400 to close to $23,000 over the same period.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/12547367">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">Why? Honestly, I&rsquo;m not sure. It&rsquo;s unusual.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin is up 36% on the year whereas Ether is only up 29%. Yet looking at the returns of other altcoins, perhaps it is nothing to do with Ether. Many are being outperformed by Bitcoin, while even the outperformers are not doing so by as much as has been seen previously (note I have removed Solana for scale purposes, which is up 125% thus far this year, following <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/is-solana-dead-top-projects-flee-the-blockchain/"><u>being decimated</u></a> by links to Sam Bankman-Fried and multiple projects fleeing the blockchain at the end of last year).&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/12547705">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">In truth, this has just been a remarkable rise for Bitcoin from the depths of bear market pain. The rest of the market is not quite ready to forget the armageddon that was 2022, with many altcoins paring down over 90%.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Ethereum wasn&rsquo;t quite as bad, but still fell from an all-time high of nearly $5,000. The free money and stimulus packages of the pandemic are over. It is a different climate now, and it is proving more challenging to kick up hype for altcoins.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The web3 narrative has faltered. NFTs have been crushed. There is no doubt that the narrative around ETH has been torn down. I have written about how institutional adoption <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/even-cathie-wood-admits-institutional-adoption-of-crypto-will-fall-off/"><u>will pare back</u></a> in crypto, and how the sector&rsquo;s reputation will take a long time to fix.</p>
<p dir="ltr">That is true for Bitcoin. Perhaps it rings even more true for ETH and altcoins, which have even more to do to regain investors&rsquo; trust.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/why-is-ethereum-being-outperformed-by-bitcoin-historical-pattern-changing-in-2023/">Why is Bitcoin is outperforming Ethereum? Market changing in 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Aptos (APT) hits new all-time high above $18 after 400% rally</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/aptos-apt-hits-new-all-time-high-above-18-after-400-rally/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 21:08:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/aptos-apt-hits-new-all-time-high-above-18-after-400-rally/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Aptos price rose 44% to hit an all-time high of $18.50 on OKX. The Layer 1 blockchain launched in October last year, and its native token has soared more than 400% in the past 30-days. Analysts suggest APT price could pare some of the gains as suggested by negative funding rates. The Aptos (APT) token [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/aptos-apt-hits-new-all-time-high-above-18-after-400-rally/">Aptos (APT) hits new all-time high above $18 after 400% rally</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>Aptos price rose 44% to hit an all-time high of $18.50 on OKX.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>The Layer 1 blockchain launched in October last year, and its native token has soared more than 400% in the past 30-days.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><strong><em>Analysts suggest APT price could pare some of the gains as suggested by negative funding rates.</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">The Aptos (APT) token has hit a new all-time high amid fresh buying pressure for the layer 1 blockchain platform&rsquo;s native token.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Aptos shines amid crypto market rally</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/aptos/">Aptos</a>, whose mainnet launch was in October last year, is a cryptocurrency platform developed by two ex-Meta Platforms staff. The smart contracts-enabled blockchain had somewhat a rough start, with controversy surrounding its token distribution.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, its native token has enjoyed one of the best runs in recent weeks, outperforming the leading cryptocurrencies by market cap amid a broader rally across the digital assets market.</p>
<p dir="ltr">On Wednesday, the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/aptos/">price of Aptos</a> rose more than 44% to push the token to above $18.00 across major exchanges. Indeed, the token hit an all-time high of $18.50 on <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/okx-review-a-one-stop-platform-for-crypto-defi-dapps-nfts-and-gamefi/">OKX</a>.&nbsp;</p>
<div class="fr-img-space-wrap"><span class="fr-img-caption fr-fic fr-dib fr-draggable" style="width: 900px"><span class="fr-img-wrap">
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/00/25/1674680675449-3604cc06-5f16-4b6c-a41f-67ee7223d345.png" style="width: 900px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="900" height="270"><span class="fr-inner">Chart showing Aptos price on OKX. APT surged to highs of $18.50 on the exchange. Source: TradingView</span></p>
<p></p></span></span>
<p class="fr-img-space-wrap2">In reaching the new peak, the APT token had rallied more than 136% in the past week. According to data from CoinGecko, the token had surged more than 400% over the past 30 days, with APT having changed hands around $3.69 on 25 December 2022.</p>
</div>
<p dir="ltr">Aptos&rsquo; total market cap has jumped to over $2.7 billion and APT currently ranks as the 28th largest cryptocurrency project.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What next for Aptos token price?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Can APT price continue its vertical movement? It is likely the coin could still test new highs as the optimism around Bitcoin and some of the top altcoins drive market speculation. However, on-chain data suggests there is a chance the price begins to fall sharply amid profit booking.</p>
<p dir="ltr">One suggestion that bulls may give up some of the gains is the negative funding rates. Pseudonymous crypto trader HornHairs pointed this out earlier Wednesday.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24APT&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$APT</a> funding through the roof on the negative side</p>
<p>shorts paying an arm &amp; a limb to bet against the top gainer</p>
<p>imagine being at a horse race and you could bet on any of the horses to lose and you choose the fastest one to bet against and you have to pay extra fees to do so <a href="https://t.co/9LeZtZhFkK">pic.twitter.com/9LeZtZhFkK</a></p>
<p>&mdash; HornHairs &#127754; (@CryptoHornHairs) <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoHornHairs/status/1618243599380152320?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 25, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Another crypto trader Altcoin Sherpa <a href="https://twitter.com/AltcoinSherpa/status/1618310186158157829" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">thinks</a> APT may provide a great short opportunity later, suggesting that shorting the coin at current levels might not be the safer bet. Instead, he points to a scenario where there is a lower high in play.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/aptos-apt-hits-new-all-time-high-above-18-after-400-rally/">Aptos (APT) hits new all-time high above $18 after 400% rally</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>MarketAcross named Web3 media partner of Europe&#8217;s premier blockchain event</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/marketacross-named-media-partner-of-european-blockchain-convention/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 19:48:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Europe]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/marketacross-named-media-partner-of-european-blockchain-convention/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>MarketAcross will help market the upcoming European Blockchain Convention worldwide. EBC 2023 is set for 15-17 February in Barcelona and will bring together industry heavyweights, including from Aave and Bittrex. MarketAcross is a leading blockchain PR and marketing firm, also tapped as the official media partner for the upcoming Paris Blockchain Week conference in March. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/marketacross-named-media-partner-of-european-blockchain-convention/">MarketAcross named Web3 media partner of Europe&#8217;s premier blockchain event</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr"><strong>MarketAcross will help market the upcoming European Blockchain Convention worldwide.</strong></li>
<li dir="ltr"><strong>EBC 2023 is set for 15-17 February in Barcelona and will bring together industry heavyweights, including from Aave and Bittrex.</strong></li>
<li dir="ltr"><strong>MarketAcross is a leading blockchain PR and marketing firm, also tapped as the official media partner for the upcoming Paris Blockchain Week conference in March.</strong></li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">MarketAcross, a leading Tel Aviv-based blockchain and fintech marketing firm, will be the main Web3 media partner at this year&rsquo;s European Blockchain Convention (EBC) convention. The event organisers <a href="https://twitter.com/EBlockchainCon/status/1618287068710592512" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">confirmed</a> the collaboration today.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Web3 event, set for 15-17 February at the Hyatt Regency in Barcelona, is expected to welcome over 2,500 participants. The annual event launched in 2018 and will be held in-person this year.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Notably, MarketAcross previously acted as <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/marketacross-is-named-korea-blockchain-weeks-official-media-partner/">official media partner</a> of the Korea Blockchain Week last June, and as web3 media partner during the Future of Crypto conference held on 7 December 2022 in New York City.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The media group is similarly set to be this year&rsquo;s Paris Blockchain Week&rsquo;s official media partner, with the event scheduled for March 2023.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Marketing Europe&rsquo;s blue chip Web3 event</h2>
<p dir="ltr">As a global leader in blockchain PR and marketing, MarketAcross has been tapped to spearhead all pre and post-event EBC 2023 marketing efforts. The experienced firm is expected to leverage its global reach, through prominent thought leaders and speakers to help highlight the Barcelona event to the world.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Itai Elizur, COO and Partner at MarketAcross, said the firm was hyped about the upcoming event and looked forward to making it &ldquo;the best one yet.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>We are thrilled to join EBC as the main media partner, especially this year, as the speaker list will showcase a lot of exciting personas and projects</em>,&rdquo; Elizur noted in a press releas shared with CoinJournal.</p>
<p dir="ltr">MarketAcross&rsquo;s strategic partnership with the EBC comes as Europe&rsquo;s most influential blockchain event bids to bring, yet again, some of the world&rsquo;s top industry players together. Expected at the three-day event are Bittrex CEO Oliver Linch, <a href="https://coinjournal.net/solana/">Solana</a> co-founder Stephen Akridge and <a href="https://coinjournal.net/aave/">Aave</a> founder Stani Kulechov, among others.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Like in previous events, EBC 2023 will bring together a diverse audience cutting across decentralised finance (DeFi) non-fungible tokens (NFTs), blockchain gaming and Web3.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Organisers have also planned an inaugural EBC Blockchain Awards, which will recognise Europe&rsquo;s top 100 early-stage startups. Ten finalists will have a chance to pitch their projects to a panel of investors.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/marketacross-named-media-partner-of-european-blockchain-convention/">MarketAcross named Web3 media partner of Europe&#8217;s premier blockchain event</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Marinade Finance looks to boost liquid staking on Solana</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/marinade-finance-looks-to-boost-liquid-staking-on-solana/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 18:05:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/marinade-finance-looks-to-boost-liquid-staking-on-solana/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Marinade Finance will reward Solana holders who stake SOL via its liquid protocol. The incentive program will run for the next 12 months and see the plaform offer up to 160 million native Marinade tokens. The goal is to grow Solana TVL by 40 million SOL, and liquid staking is key to that. Marinade Finance, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/marinade-finance-looks-to-boost-liquid-staking-on-solana/">Marinade Finance looks to boost liquid staking on Solana</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>Marinade Finance will reward Solana holders who stake SOL via its liquid protocol.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>The incentive program will run for the next 12 months and see the plaform offer up to 160 million native Marinade tokens.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><strong><em>The goal is to grow Solana TVL by 40 million SOL, and liquid staking is key to that.</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Marinade Finance, a liquid staking platform that supports the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/solana/">Solana</a> blockchain, is looking to bring more liquidity to the Solana ecosystem via a major incentive program.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The protocol noted in an <a href="https://twitter.com/MarinadeFinance/status/1617944708780814337" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">announcement</a> that the program &ldquo;Open Doors&rdquo; is designed to incentivise Solana builders, validators and wallets into increasing the blockchain platform&rsquo;s asset liquidity.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Accordingly, Marinade is looking to offer rewards in the form of its tokens to users who contribute to growing the total value locked (TVL) of Solana on the protocol.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Marinade Finance&rsquo;s 12-month incentive program for Solana</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Over the next 12 months, users have a chance to earn some of the 160 million Marinade (MNDE) tokens when they deposit SOL for mSOL, the liquid staking token they will get in exchange. The target is to get 40 million SOL staked for mSOL, &ndash; a scenario that could significantly increase the ecosystem&rsquo;s liquidity and help with decentralisation.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Currently, only 2-3% of SOL is <a href="https://twitter.com/MarinadeFinance/status/1617944715403603975" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">reportedly</a> in liquid staking, which makes the plan to have more brought into the ecosystem crucial for Solana. This is because staked SOL doesn&rsquo;t contribute to Solana&rsquo;s DeFi TVL. However, mSOL&rsquo;s liquid stake does as it flows across different protocols.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">As for decentralisation, Marinade supports hundreds of validators staking through its delegation strategy.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>For Solana DeFi to rebound stronger, more $SOL (LOTS MORE) must be made liquid. Those who contribute this through $mSOL, on their protocols, or via the referral program will be rewarded with direct Marinade ownership</em>,&rdquo; the Marinade team said.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to <a href="https://defillama.com/chain/Solana" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">data</a> from DeFiLlama, the Solana chain has about $278 million in TVL as of 25 January 2023, down from over $10 billion in November 2021. More than 53% of the total TVL on this chain is on Marinade Finance, while Lido&rsquo;s liquid staking accounts for the second-largest share.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/marinade-finance-looks-to-boost-liquid-staking-on-solana/">Marinade Finance looks to boost liquid staking on Solana</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Price Prediction V/S Metacade: Which Is The Better Long Term Crypto Investment?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-price-prediction-v-s-metacade-which-is-the-better-long-term-crypto-investment/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-price-prediction-v-s-metacade-which-is-the-better-long-term-crypto-investment/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice Davies]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 17:19:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-price-prediction-v-s-metacade-which-is-the-better-long-term-crypto-investment/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Ethereum price prediction 2023 looks like it will start to pick up once again, as investors are expecting some major price action for the ETH token into the long-term. While the Ethereum price prediction for 2023 is bullish, it is arguably not the best crypto to invest in right now. On the other hand, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-price-prediction-v-s-metacade-which-is-the-better-long-term-crypto-investment/">Ethereum Price Prediction V/S Metacade: Which Is The Better Long Term Crypto Investment?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">The Ethereum price prediction 2023 looks like it will start to pick up once again, as investors are expecting some major price action for the ETH token into the long-term. While the Ethereum price prediction for 2023 is bullish, it is arguably not the best crypto to invest in right now.</p>
<p dir="ltr">On the other hand, if its presale is anything to go by, Metacade (MCADE) could easily post insane gains over the coming years, which makes it the number one best crypto to invest in for 2023 and beyond.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Metacade is, without a doubt, the best crypto to invest in</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The Ethereum price prediction for 2023 looks bullish as the token is expected to start building some momentum after <a href="https://www.forbes.com/uk/advisor/investing/cryptocurrency/understanding-ethereum-merge/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>the merge</u></a> took place in September 2022. While the current bear market is expected to continue for some time, the Ethereum price prediction 2023 is forecasting a trend reversal.</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, the best crypto to invest in during 2023 is <a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade</u></a>. <strong>The MCADE presale was recently launched and over $3.5 million was raised in just over 9 weeks since the announcement</strong>. The project could rapidly become a key player in the GameFi revolution, and it is showing major promise in terms of future price action.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Ethereum (ETH)?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Ethereum is a layer-1 blockchain and the biggest ecosystem of decentralized applications (dApps) in Web3. The blockchain was initially built using a proof-of-work (PoW) consensus mechanism but was recently updated to a proof-of-stake (PoS) protocol during the merge in 2022.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Ethereum&rsquo;s new <a href="https://coinjournal.net/glossary/proof-of-stake-pos/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>PoS protocol</u></a> allows for a more economical blockchain system that requires less computing power and is less taxing on the environment as a result. The key difference is that the mining process delegates to trusted participants, who are incentivized to behave in a trustworthy manner, instead of using an expensive system where nodes compete to mine blocks using their GPU power.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Ethereum is still one of the best cryptos to invest in, as it was the first Turing complete blockchain. This has led to Ethereum supporting over 2000 independent projects, as an increasing number of use cases have been found for blockchain technology due to Ethereum&rsquo;s innovative solution.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Ethereum Price Prediction 2023: Will ETH reach $2500?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The Ethereum price prediction 2023 is more bullish than in 2022, when Ethereum suffered an 80% price reduction. The ETH token is expected to reverse this trend and could begin to climb back toward its previous all-time high at $4865.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>ETH faces strong resistance at $1775. However, if the token can break through this price level, the next target is $2500 for the Ethereum price prediction 2023</strong>.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Metacade (MCADE)?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade, which is the best crypto to invest in now, is a comprehensive gaming platform that brings classic arcade-style titles onto the blockchain. All Metacade games have integrated earning mechanics, allowing players to earn an income while playing some of the hottest titles in the GameFi sector.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The platform has been built by gamers, for gamers, and aims to become a hub for the Web3 community. Metacade can drive innovation in the blockchain gaming space through its Metagrants program, and will also give users the chance to kickstart a career in Web3.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How does MCADE work?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade&rsquo;s <a href="https://coinjournal.net/glossary/play-to-earn-play2earn/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Play2Earn</u></a> arcade will offer a range of different games for its community. Gameplay can be either casual or competitive, as users will also be able to enter paid entry tournaments for the chance to win exciting MCADE prizes.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Create2Earn mechanic will reward users for sharing valuable information and contributing to the <a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade</u></a> community. Contributions can include sharing alpha, posting game reviews, or interacting with other members, as Metacade aims to incentivize a buzzing platform that is brimming with useful information about Web3.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade will also introduce a jobs board in 2024. This feature intends to connect users with full-time job opportunities at Metacade&rsquo;s partner projects in Web3. Users will also have the chance to complete tasks, apply for short-time gig work, or land freelance roles through the Metacade platform.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade is seeking to boost the overall level of innovation in the GameFi sector through its Metagrants program. This will give the community the chance to vote for the best new blockchain-based games proposals, directing Metacade to provide early-stage funding to support development and bring exclusive titles to the arcade platform.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Will MCADE reach $5?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade has extremely high potential, which makes the presale a rare opportunity. MCADE is the best crypto to invest in now, especially since the presale is launching MCADE at a an early-bird low price.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>The long-term price prediction for MCADE places it next to the biggest GameFi projects in the space, with $5 being a key target for 2025</strong>. In 2023, MCADE could hit the $1 mark as it begins to gain momentum for the long term. Without a doubt, Metacade is the best crypto to invest in at the current price level.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Is MCADE worth buying?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade&rsquo;s $5 target is a 250x price rise from the end of the presale, so it&rsquo;s certainly a strong addition to any investment portfolio and by many accounts, is the best crypto to invest in during 2023. On the other hand, the Ethereum price prediction in 2023 could increase by 2x, with up to 10x gains forecasted for the next crypto bull market.</p>
<p dir="ltr">For investors looking to buy into the MCADE presale, it is worth knowing that the price is continually rising. MCADE was initially launched at $0.008 but will climb to $0.02 before the end of the event, which gives investors a limited time to get involved before it starts reaching higher price levels.</p>
<p><strong>You can participate in the Metacade presale&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong><u>here</u></strong></a><strong>.</strong></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-price-prediction-v-s-metacade-which-is-the-better-long-term-crypto-investment/">Ethereum Price Prediction V/S Metacade: Which Is The Better Long Term Crypto Investment?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-price-prediction-v-s-metacade-which-is-the-better-long-term-crypto-investment/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>TRON Price Prediction: TRX and MCADE Are Primed to Pump in 2023. Is Now A Good Time To Invest?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/tron-price-prediction-trx-and-mcade-are-primed-to-pump-in-2023-is-now-a-good-time-to-invest/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/tron-price-prediction-trx-and-mcade-are-primed-to-pump-in-2023-is-now-a-good-time-to-invest/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice Davies]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 17:13:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TRON News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/tron-price-prediction-trx-and-mcade-are-primed-to-pump-in-2023-is-now-a-good-time-to-invest/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Tron (TRX) price prediction is looking strong for the future and now could be a good time to invest in the token. However, a brand-new project called Metacade (MCADE) may just be the best-performing token over the coming years. MCADE&#8217;s potential for gains is much higher than Tron&#8217;s price prediction, according to recent reports, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tron-price-prediction-trx-and-mcade-are-primed-to-pump-in-2023-is-now-a-good-time-to-invest/">TRON Price Prediction: TRX and MCADE Are Primed to Pump in 2023. Is Now A Good Time To Invest?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">The Tron (TRX) price prediction is looking strong for the future and now could be a good time to invest in the token. However, a brand-new project called Metacade (MCADE) may just be the best-performing token over the coming years.</p>
<p dir="ltr">MCADE&rsquo;s potential for gains is much higher than Tron&rsquo;s price prediction, according to recent reports, which means that now is a good time to invest before prices start to rise.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Metacade looks like the best crypto buy in 2023</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The crypto market may start to pick up during 2023, with Tron and Metacade ready to pop when the inevitable trend reversal occurs. The year 2022 saw price reductions across the board, with many altcoins losing over 90% of their value, but these two tokens are well-positioned for the future, and now is a good time to invest.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;Buy the dip!&rdquo; is a common saying in Web3. <strong>At bear market lows, investors have the biggest potential for returns, which is a key reason why now is a good time to invest in both TRX and MCADE</strong>. While TRX has been around for a while, MCADE is a brand-new GameFi platform that has been attracting widespread interest in recent weeks.</p>
<p dir="ltr">$3.5 million worth of funding was raised in just over nine weeks during MCADE&rsquo;s initial presale stages. The project has also doubled its following on social media and looks set to become one of the leading figures in the blockchain gaming space over time.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Metacade (MCADE)?</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade</u></a> is the first community-driven arcade and the biggest platform of its kind that can be found in Web3. It will offer many different play-to-earn games, aiming to become a central hub for all things GameFi.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The project offers advanced crypto-earning mechanics and a vast number of unique features. Users will be able to access some of the most valuable alpha in blockchain gaming, including the latest trends and tips for making the most out of the playing experience.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade also aims to support the expansion of the GameFi sector directly. The Metagrants program will allow game developers to submit investment proposals to the community, who will vote to decide which new games are best. The developers who gain the most votes will receive early-stage funding to support the development of a new arcade title.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How does MCADE work?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade&rsquo;s&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/glossary/play2earn-play-to-earn/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>play-to-earn</u></a> arcade will offer both casual and competitive gameplay. Gamers can earn MCADE tokens for progressing through endless levels and trying to beat their high score or by competing head-to-head against other users in paid entry tournaments hosted by Metacade.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As well as this, Metacade will reward users for contributing to the community. The Create2Earn feature will incentivize content creation on the platform, which can include game reviews, interactions with other users, or sharing the latest information about the blockchain gaming space.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade is also introducing a job creation feature called Work2Earn. This will connect its community with paid opportunities in Web3, ranging from part-time to full-time positions. Users can apply for gig work, freelance roles, or full-time positions when the crypto jobs board goes live in 2024.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Will MCADE reach $5 in 2025?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">In 2023, the Metacade platform will begin to offer its games to the community, and the MCADE token will also be launched on decentralized exchanges (DEXs) after the IDO. This is expected to boost demand for MCADE, with experts predicting some bullish price action over the coming years.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The MCADE presale is a great time for those wondering if now is a good time to invest, as the price is unlikely ever to be this low again. <strong>By 2025, MCADE could reach $5, which would be a 250x price rise from the end of the presale</strong>. This kind of price action is similar to the gains made by other major GameFi platforms, such as The Sandbox in 2021, and Metacade looks set to follow suit in a major way.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Tron (TRX)?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The Tron price prediction is not quite as bullish as Metacade&rsquo;s, as the platform has been around for several years already. Despite this, Tron is a leading&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/glossary/layer-1-blockchain/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>layer 1 blockchain</u></a> network that can support a high number of transactions at a low cost to users, so the project is well positioned over the coming years.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Tron price prediction: Will TRX reach $0.50 in 2025?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The Tron price prediction forecasts new all-time highs for Tron in 2025. The TRX ecosystem continues to grow, with more new projects building in the Tron space. Another crypto bull market is expected to occur after the Bitcoin halving event in 2024, which should attract more users to the TRX ecosystem.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In 2025, the Tron price prediction is $0.50. This would be a 10x gain from the current price level, which makes now a good time to invest in Tron.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Is now a good time to invest in MCADE?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The MCADE presale is a good time to invest, that&rsquo;s for sure. The price looks set to skyrocket at the end of the presale, and the current price will likely look tiny compared to the future value of MCADE. <a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade</u></a> has tremendous potential for the future, and the Tron price prediction is also bullish, so now is a good time to invest.</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, the price for MCADE is rising from $0.008 to $0.02 over the course of the presale. <strong>Investors have a limited time to buy MCADE at the lowest possible, as the value of MCADE will be raised every time a funding round sells out</strong>. Be quick to get involved before it&rsquo;s too late, as Metacade looks ready to blow in 2023 and beyond.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>You can buy TRX at eToro&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://coinjournal.net/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=MTAxMDIy" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong><u>here</u></strong></a><strong>.</strong></p>
<p><strong>You can participate in the Metacade presale&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong><u>here</u></strong></a><strong>.</strong></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tron-price-prediction-trx-and-mcade-are-primed-to-pump-in-2023-is-now-a-good-time-to-invest/">TRON Price Prediction: TRX and MCADE Are Primed to Pump in 2023. Is Now A Good Time To Invest?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/tron-price-prediction-trx-and-mcade-are-primed-to-pump-in-2023-is-now-a-good-time-to-invest/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Doodles releases new NFT collection Doodles 2 on Flow</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/doodles-releases-new-nft-collection-doodles-2-on-flow/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/doodles-releases-new-nft-collection-doodles-2-on-flow/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 16:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital content]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/doodles-releases-new-nft-collection-doodles-2-on-flow/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Doodles 2 are collectibles that will be accessible across multiple ecosystems, including computer, phone and social media. The Doodles team chose Flow for its scalability, composability, security and no gas fees. Users can mint their first wearables and create Doodles 2 NFTs on Flow as from 31 January. Doodles, the non-fungible token (NFT) platform that&#8217;s [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/doodles-releases-new-nft-collection-doodles-2-on-flow/">Doodles releases new NFT collection Doodles 2 on Flow</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>Doodles 2 are collectibles that will be accessible across multiple ecosystems, including computer, phone and social media.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>The Doodles team chose Flow for its scalability, composability, security and no gas fees.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><strong><em>Users can mint their first wearables and create Doodles 2 NFTs on Flow as from 31 January.</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Doodles, the non-fungible token (<a href="https://coinjournal.net/glossary/non-fungible-token-nft/">NFT</a>) platform that&rsquo;s been one of the hits of the NFT ecosystem, has <a href="https://flow.com/post/flow-blockchain-doodles-2-announcement" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">announced</a> the launch of its highly anticipated drop dubbed Doodles 2.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Doodles 2 is a series of collectibles that allows holders to customize their Doodle with wearables, including apparels, accessories, and gadgets. It&rsquo;s an offshoot of the core Doodles collection, one of the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/top-5-nft-collections-to-buy-in-2022/">top NFT collections from last year</a> and which features 10,000 unique NFTs on the Ethereum blockchain.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Doodles 2 comes to Flow</h2>
<p dir="ltr">According to the project&rsquo;s team, the new collection is launching on the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/flow/">Flow</a>, an eco-friendly Web3 blockchain.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Doodles CEO Julian Holguin said they chose Flow because of its powerful composability, security, no gas fees and on-chain scalability &ndash; a key functionality for the new set of collectibles. In short, having portable and interoperable NFTs is the goal, with the feature allowing for access across social platforms, live events, and gaming worlds.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>As we open Doodles up to the world, we know we can rely on an architecture that was built to scale from day one. Flow offers an easy onboarding to Doodles for newcomers to NFTs and web3, from seamless checkout experiences to world-class security, safety and recoverability of their Doodles</em>,&rdquo; Holguin added.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Flow team tweeted:</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">(2/6)<br>Flow was built from the ground up to unlock mass-scale user experiences like <a href="https://twitter.com/doodles?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@Doodles</a> </p>
<p>&#128515; Frictionless onboarding<br>&#128200; Proven scalability<br>&#128184; Seamless checkout flows<br>&#128272; World-class security<br>&#129514; Composability</p>
<p>With Doodles 2 collectibles, there's no limit to the possibilities</p>
<p>&mdash; Flow (@flow_blockchain) <a href="https://twitter.com/flow_blockchain/status/1618273479899635714?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 25, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">Doodles core holders can expect to mint their first Doodles 2 wearables and create Flow NFTs beginning 31 January. Fans will be able to buy, sell and trade their Doodle wearables on the Gaia marketplace.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Those new to the Doodles ecosystem can easily create a wallet via Gmail and buy wearables using credit cards. All this happens &ldquo;<em>in just a few clicks</em>,&rdquo; the team tweeted, highlighting that this is &ldquo;<em>how Top Shot got 400k people to buy the first NFT</em>.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/doodles-releases-new-nft-collection-doodles-2-on-flow/">Doodles releases new NFT collection Doodles 2 on Flow</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/doodles-releases-new-nft-collection-doodles-2-on-flow/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The 6 Best Cryptocurrencies to Buy for a Solid Long-Term Crypto Investment Strategy in 2023</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/the-6-best-cryptocurrencies-to-buy-for-a-solid-long-term-crypto-investment-strategy-in-2023/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/the-6-best-cryptocurrencies-to-buy-for-a-solid-long-term-crypto-investment-strategy-in-2023/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice Davies]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 16:44:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/the-6-best-cryptocurrencies-to-buy-for-a-solid-long-term-crypto-investment-strategy-in-2023/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>After a challenging year, the dust is finally starting to settle in the crypto markets. The seismic events of 2022 have changed market dynamics and investment strategies for the foreseeable future. Instead of seeking a quick return, many investors are now looking to play the long game. So which are the 6 best cryptocurrencies to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-6-best-cryptocurrencies-to-buy-for-a-solid-long-term-crypto-investment-strategy-in-2023/">The 6 Best Cryptocurrencies to Buy for a Solid Long-Term Crypto Investment Strategy in 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">After a challenging year, the dust is finally starting to settle in the crypto markets. The seismic events of 2022 have changed market dynamics and investment strategies for the foreseeable future. Instead of seeking a quick return, many investors are now looking to play the long game. So which are the 6 best cryptocurrencies to buy for a solid long-term crypto Investment strategy in 2023? </p>
<h2 dir="ltr">The 6 Best Cryptocurrencies for Your Crypto Investment Strategy</h2>
<ol>
<li>Metacade (MCADE)</li>
<li>Ethereum (ETH)</li>
<li>ApeCoin (APE)</li>
<li>Ripple (XRP)</li>
<li>Polygon (MATIC)</li>
<li>Bitcoin (BTC)</li>
</ol>
<h2 dir="ltr">1. Metacade (MCADE)</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The play-to-earn (P2E), GameFi, and blockchain gaming sectors are all widely tipped for explosive growth in 2023 and beyond. That&rsquo;s why there&rsquo;s such a buzz around <a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade (MCADE)</u></a>, with its wide upcoming choice of metaverse and arcade games. The company plans to become the ultimate Web3 gaming hub, where gamers, developers and entrepreneurs connect, communicate and interact for mutual benefit and possible financial gain.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Here&rsquo;s how Metacade (MCADE) works. Players will have the chance to generate income from P2E games, online competitions, creating content, alpha and beta testing, and new job opportunities. Developers can interact directly with gamers to test and develop products, launch new games, organize paid competitions, and recruit skilled employees. Finally, entrepreneurs and crypto fanatics can stake and invest their MCADE tokens.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade (MCADE)&rsquo;s business model is aimed at everyone with an interest in crypto gaming. This inclusive approach is further enhanced by the company&rsquo;s stated intention to become a DAO, where every member is given control over input, and platform direction. The company&rsquo;s <a href="https://metacade.co/whitepaper.pdf." rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>forward-thinking roadmap</u></a> also includes Metagrants, a program that provides funding for the development of the next-generation titles on the platform.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Why buy MCADE?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade (MCADE) has yet to launch, so when considering your crypto investment strategy, it&rsquo;s vital to look at the success of its presale, and the vision within its roadmap. With $3.3m raised rapidly in its beta stage presale, and already heading towards $5m, it&rsquo;s a compelling offering in the P2E and GameFi industries. Both target markets are set to explode, and with <a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>a hot presale price</u></a>, Metacade (MCADE) is the top pick of the best cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>&gt;&gt;&gt; You can participate in the Metacade presale&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong><u>here</u></strong></a><strong>&nbsp;&lt;&lt;&lt;</strong></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">2. Ethereum (ETH)</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The giant crypto number two features second on this list of the best cryptocurrencies. Some observers see <a href="https://ethereum.org/en/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Ethereum (ETH)</u></a> as being in the permanent shadow of Bitcoin (BTC), but that misses the point. Both these behemoths are digital currencies, but Ethereum (ETH) offers much more, by supporting a huge range of smart contracts, decentralized apps and DeFi services.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Ethereum (ETH) has inspired many competitors who aim to address the well-known criticisms of the platform, namely high costs, scalability issues and slow transaction processing. Yet although some of the competition has succeeded in those goals, Ethereum (ETH) still marches on, thanks to its powerful functionality, widespread acceptance, stability, security and liquidity. Pretenders to the Ethereum (ETH) throne still have a long way to go before they can match its qualities.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Why buy ETH?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">In uncertain times, investors often look to steady, established, and durable performers &ndash; and that rule applies equally to the crypto market. Typically it also means investors look to bigger companies, who are better placed to overcome any short-term blips or issues. Ethereum (ETH)&rsquo;s size is definitely one factor that drives people&rsquo;s crypto investment strategy, but its many other qualities are also what make it one of the best cryptocurrencies for the long term.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">3. ApeCoin (APE)</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://apecoin.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>ApeCoin (APE)</u></a> may not be everyone&rsquo;s choice when it comes to the best cryptocurrencies, but it remains stubbornly popular with its enthusiastic fans. Backed by famous names like Paris Hilton and Justin Bieber, ApeCoin (APE) seems to divide opinions when it comes to crypto investment strategy. Critics point to a drop in value since its March 2022 launch, whilst fervent supporters mention successful NFT launches and the fact that is was barely affected by the FTX crash.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Those hugely successful NFT launches are a large part of the reason why ApeCoin (APE) is such a darling of the crypto world. Certain holders of Bored Ape Yacht Club and Mutant Ape Yacht Club NFTs enjoyed spectacular returns, and&nbsp;<a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ericmack/2022/09/07/bored-ape-yacht-club-nfts-are-still-selling-and-being-stolen/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>it&rsquo;s that promise</u></a> &ndash; alongside super savvy marketing, clever merchandising, exciting future plans, and the association with Yuga Labs &ndash; that keep investors flocking to ApeCoin (APE).</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Why buy APE?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Given that ApeCoin (APE) is widely accepted and wildly popular, there are plenty of investors who see this meme coin as an integral part of their crypto investment strategy. But is it a good long-term bet amongst the best cryptocurrencies? Yes, based on its continued popularity, peerless promotion, a burgeoning ecosystem including gaming, and high liquidity. ApeCoin (APE) may well prove that sometimes, the hype is fully justified.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">4. Ripple (XRP)</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Ripple (XRP) is a classic example of how cryptos have the power to shake up old-fashioned market dynamics and deliver a new service that is faster, cheaper and more secure than traditional methods. If you&rsquo;ve ever experienced the frustrations of trying to make an international transfer with a conventional financial institution, you&rsquo;ll appreciate the lightning-fast speed, convenience and low fees of Ripple (XRP).</p>
<p dir="ltr">Some people assume that Ripple (XRP) focuses on individual customers, but the company is more targeted at financial services companies, who use it to deliver a better service to their customers. Ripple (XRP)&rsquo;s clients include some of the world&rsquo;s best-known financial institutions, such as Santander, Bank of America and UBS. Names like that underline why Ripple (XRP) scores so highly amongst the best cryptocurrencies, and why it&rsquo;s an investment for the long term.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Why buy XRP?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">For all its reputation as being amongst the best cryptocurrencies, there is an elephant in the room with Ripple (XRP) &ndash; its ongoing lawsuit with the SEC over a possible breach of regulations. A negative verdict will obviously have severe negative consequences, but the opposite is also true. If Ripple (XRP) can win its case &ndash; and remember, it has many big-name customers and partnerships &ndash; then it should definitely be part of a solid long-term crypto investment strategy.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">5. Polygon (MATIC)</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Some cryptos are all about the hype, backed by high-profile celebrities, glitzy marketing and prestigious sponsorships. But when you probe beneath all that style, often you find very little substance.&nbsp;<a href="https://polygon.io/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Polygon (MATIC)</u></a> couldn&rsquo;t be further away from that model. If Polygon (MATIC)&rsquo;s marketing was as good as its platform, product range and functionality, it would surely be an even greater success than it already is.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Polygon (MATIC) is widely recognized as the leading layer-2 solution for Ethereum (ETH). It works by offering faster, more scalable, cheaper and more flexible transaction processing. Those qualities, plus its ease of use, have made Polygon (MATIC) hugely popular with developers and investors. With so many apps running on the platform, and so many developers on board, Polygon (MATIC) is an essential element in any long-term crypto investment strategy.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Why buy MATIC?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Many investors now prefer to back industry giants like Ethereum (ETH). Such a crypto investment strategy is likely to have a positive effect on companies like Polygon (MATIC) which are closely aligned to Ethereum (ETH). But it underplays the excellent functionality, reputation and partnerships that make Polygon (MATIC) one of the best cryptocurrencies in its own right. Its ongoing success and impressive future plans mark it out as a fine long-term prospect too.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">6. Bitcoin (BTC)</h2>
<p dir="ltr">If you ever needed evidence of the merits of a long-term crypto investment strategy, you need look no further than <a href="https://bitcoin.org/en/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Bitcoin (BTC)</u></a>. Investors who bought BTC in early 2017 paid a price of around $1,000. At the start of 2023, that investment is worth an 18x multiple. Admittedly, that figure is not as impressive at the 2021 high of over $68,000, but it does illustrate the value of taking a long-term view.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Naturally, Bitcoin (BTC)&rsquo;s sheer size means that it invariably features on any list of the best cryptocurrencies. Bitcoin (BTC) has weathered many storms since its <a href="https://www.forbes.com/advisor/investing/cryptocurrency/bitcoin-price-history/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>launch way back in 2009</u></a>. Other companies have come and gone, but Bitcoin (BTC) has resisted and persisted. For many, it&rsquo;s the &ldquo;go-to&rdquo; cryptocurrency, and its market dominance doesn&rsquo;t look to be under threat any time soon. All long-term crypto investment strategy plans should include Bitcoin (BTC).</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Why buy BTC?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">There&rsquo;s a widespread acceptance by big institutional investors that, despite everything, cryptocurrencies are here to stay. Those investors also understand the importance of following the biggest, longest-established, most popular, and most valuable player in any market. Finally, they know better than anyone that if you play the long game, markets almost always recover. If Bitcoin (BTC) is the choice for institutional investors, it should be the choice for everyone.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Best Cryptocurrencies for Your Crypto Investment Strategy: The Verdict</h2>
<p dir="ltr">If you&rsquo;re looking at the best cryptocurrencies to buy as part of a solid long term crypto Investment strategy, all of the candidates here have their specific attractions. What&rsquo;s more, ApeCoin (APE), Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH), Metacade (MCADE), Polygon (MATIC) and Ripple (XRP) all have the potential to enjoy a long and prosperous future.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Choosing an outright winner can be hard, but in the end, it&rsquo;s actually an easy decision. The boom in P2E and GameFi means that<strong>&nbsp;Metacade (MCADE) is an amazing prospect for the long term, with its current presale offering excellent short and mid-term gains too.</strong> However, there&rsquo;s no time to delay if you want a piece of the action at <a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>the best presale price</u></a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>You can buy the best cryptocurrencies at eToro&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://coinjournal.net/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=MTAxMDE4" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong><u>here</u></strong></a><strong>.</strong></p>
<p><strong>You can participate in the Metacade presale&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong><u>here</u></strong></a><strong>.</strong></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-6-best-cryptocurrencies-to-buy-for-a-solid-long-term-crypto-investment-strategy-in-2023/">The 6 Best Cryptocurrencies to Buy for a Solid Long-Term Crypto Investment Strategy in 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/the-6-best-cryptocurrencies-to-buy-for-a-solid-long-term-crypto-investment-strategy-in-2023/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Can Metacade Avoid The Great Cryptocurrency Crash?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/can-metacade-avoid-the-great-cryptocurrency-crash/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/can-metacade-avoid-the-great-cryptocurrency-crash/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice Davies]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 16:35:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/can-metacade-avoid-the-great-cryptocurrency-crash/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The FTX collapse added fuel to the fire for the great cryptocurrency crash of 2022. Cryptocurrency is a high-risk, high-return asset class, and the FTX fiasco highlighted inherent weaknesses that the industry can learn from. In spite of the FTX collapse, Web3 continues to grow. Brand-new projects such as Metacade (MCADE) reflect the level of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/can-metacade-avoid-the-great-cryptocurrency-crash/">Can Metacade Avoid The Great Cryptocurrency Crash?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">The FTX collapse added fuel to the fire for the great cryptocurrency crash of 2022. Cryptocurrency is a high-risk, high-return asset class, and the FTX fiasco highlighted inherent weaknesses that the industry can learn from.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In spite of the FTX collapse, Web3 continues to grow. Brand-new projects such as Metacade (MCADE) reflect the level of innovation that can be found in the space. Read on to learn why MCADE could be the year&rsquo;s best investment.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">The great cryptocurrency crash: 2022 was a year to forget</h2>
<p dir="ltr">After a major cryptocurrency crash in 2022, investors are starting to wonder where the bottom of the bear market could be. Bitcoin (BTC) has lost over 75% of its value already, while many altcoins, including Axie Infinity (AXS), Shiba Inu (SHIB), and Avalanche (AVAX), have suffered through a 90% price reduction since reaching their all-time highs in 2021.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The cryptocurrency crash has had catastrophic effects on some major market players, with FTX &ndash; the second-biggest centralized exchange (CEX) at the time &ndash; <a href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-63601213" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>announcing bankruptcy</u></a> in the wake of falling prices and causing the entire market to drop even further after going bust in November 2022.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The FTX capitulation was caused in no small part by treasury mismanagement from Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF) and the embezzlement of user funds through Alameda Research, which was a hedge fund under SBF&rsquo;s control.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">After FTX and Alameda&rsquo;s insolvency became apparent early in November, FTX halted customer withdrawals. As a result, all cryptocurrency held on the platform was lost, and it is currently unclear whether users will ever see their digital assets again. It was a stark reminder of the inherent risks involved with centralization, especially in an industry where regulatory guidelines remain unclear.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The cryptocurrency crash has taken several major casualties, with the majority being custody platforms under centralized leadership. FTX, <a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2022/jul/14/celsius-networks-cryptocurrency-lender-files-for-bankruptcy" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Celsius Network</u></a>, Three Arrows Capital, Voyager, and even the Terra Ecosystem, to some extent, are all reminders that self-custody is, by far, the safest way for investors to hold digital assets during a cryptocurrency crash.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bear markets don&rsquo;t last forever, and Metacade could be the best buy right now</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Despite the cryptocurrency crash and the ongoing bear market, there are still many millions of investors across the world who are looking to buy while prices are low. One of the best buys right now is <a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade</u></a>. It is a brand-new project and with the hype starting to build, it could entirely avoid the crypto market crash.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade recently announced the start of its token presale, with 70% of MCADE&rsquo;s total supply being made available to early investors. Almost $3.2 million flowed into the project in the first nine weeks, and major returns are now being predicted for this new GameFi platform.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Metacade?</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>Metacade is the first community-driven arcade and the largest blockchain project of its kind</strong>. The platform will have many different play-to-earn (<a href="https://medium.com/udonis/play-to-earn-games-101-how-do-they-work-56b07ad2117c" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>P2E</u></a>) arcade games, ranging from classic titles to new games developed specifically for the metaverse arcade.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Aiming to become a social hub for Web3 users, Metacade is attracting a significant following already. Users can discover the latest trends, learn tips and tricks for a variety of blockchain games, and access plenty of earning opportunities directly on the platform.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How does MCADE work?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Gamers can progress through infinite levels in a range of P2E games, playing casually or competitively. Metacade will host tournaments, where gamers can go head-to-head for the chance to win major prizes paid in MCADE tokens.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade</u></a> is also introducing a Create2Earn mechanic, rewarding its community for sharing information and creating content on the platform. Content can include alpha, game reviews, insights, and interactions with other users &ndash; all of which will generate token rewards for the content creator.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Work2Earn feature is another method for earning a crypto income in the Metacade. Users can access paid job opportunities, ranging from short-term work to full-time positions at Web3 companies. Metacade aims to support users who want to kickstart a career in blockchain.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Metacade is (literally) a game changer</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>Metacade is built by gamers, for gamers</strong>. One of the team&rsquo;s aims is to support the future of blockchain gaming itself, with the Metagrants program being a vehicle to encourage developers as they innovate in the space.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Developers will submit game proposals and the community will vote to decide which new games they would most like to play. Winning ideas will receive early-stage funding through Metagrants and launch on Metacade, which will help introduce brand-new games into the world of Web3 and drive the gaming industry forward.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Could MCADE reach $5 in 2023?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade is starting to take off already, despite the FTX capitulation and the cryptocurrency crash of 2022. The project is selling out of its presale quickly, and the MCADE token will soon be launched on decentralized exchanges (<a href="https://www.coindesk.com/learn/what-is-a-dex-how-decentralized-crypto-exchanges-work/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>DEXs</u></a>), which will further boost its reach.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Experts are predicting explosive price action after the market recovers from the cryptocurrency crash. <strong>By 2025, MCADE could reach $5 in value &ndash; a 250x gain from the end of the presale</strong>.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Is MCADE worth buying?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The MCADE presale is a prime investment opportunity. The token launched at just $0.008, and the price is rising gradually to $0.02 during the presale. The FTX capitulation had no effect on demand for MCADE, and the token is expected to sell out during every presale stage.</p>
<p dir="ltr">To get the best possible price for MCADE, investors need to be fast. The presale is first-come, first-served, and the price will rise when each round sells out. Metacade looks like one of the few projects that can avoid the bear market, which makes it a worthy addition to any portfolio.</p>
<p><strong>You can participate in the MCADE presale&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong><u>here</u></strong></a><strong>.</strong></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/can-metacade-avoid-the-great-cryptocurrency-crash/">Can Metacade Avoid The Great Cryptocurrency Crash?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/can-metacade-avoid-the-great-cryptocurrency-crash/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
