<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 16:17:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Gary Gensler on crypto regulations: ‘there’s been clarity for years’</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/sec-chair-gary-gensler-on-crypto-regulation/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wajeeh Khan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 16:17:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Interview]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=142175</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SEC sued Coinbase for violating U.S. securities laws today. Chair Gary Gensler discussed on CNBC&#8217;s &#8220;Squawk on the Street&#8221;. Coinbase stock opened nearly 20% down on Tuesday. Coinbase Global Inc opened nearly 20% down on Tuesday after the SEC sued the crypto exchange for violating the U.S. securities laws. Gensler discussed the lawsuit on CNBC [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sec-chair-gary-gensler-on-crypto-regulation/">Gary Gensler on crypto regulations: ‘there’s been clarity for years’</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>SEC sued Coinbase for violating U.S. securities laws today.</li>
<li>Chair Gary Gensler discussed on CNBC&rsquo;s &ldquo;Squawk on the Street&rdquo;.</li>
<li>Coinbase stock opened nearly 20% down on Tuesday.</li>
</ul>
<p>Coinbase Global Inc opened nearly 20% down on Tuesday after the SEC <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-sec-strikes-again-first-binance-now-coinbase/">sued</a> the crypto exchange for violating the U.S. securities laws.</p>
<h2>Gensler discussed the lawsuit on CNBC</h2>
<p>Crypto companies including Coinbase have been <a href="https://www.coinbase.com/blog/coinbase-takes-another-formal-step-to-seek-regulatory-clarity-from-sec-for" target="_blank" rel="noopener">demanding</a> more clarity from the U.S. regulator for the longest time.</p>
<p>Interestingly, though, Gary Gensler &ndash; Chair of the Securities and Exchange Commission denied today that there&rsquo;s been a lack of clarity in the first place.</p>
<blockquote><p>There&rsquo;s been clarity for years. The investing public has benefit of securities laws. Crypto shouldn&rsquo;t be different. These platforms need to come into compliance and protect investing public.</p></blockquote>
<p><a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/coinbase/">Coinbase</a> is still up roughly 45% for the year. A day earlier, the U.S. SEC had filed a similar complaint against Binance and its CEO Changpeng Zhao as well.</p>
<h2>Gensler says USD is already a digital currency</h2>
<p>On CNBC&rsquo;s &ldquo;<a href="https://www.cnbc.com/video/2023/06/06/sec-chair-gensler-whole-crypto-business-model-built-on-non-compliance-with-u-s-securities-laws.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Squawk on the Street</a>&rdquo;, Chair Gensler also contested the need for more digital currencies especially since about 16,000 of them are already tradable via Coinbase.</p>
<blockquote><p>We already have digital currency, the U.S. dollar, the Euro, the Yen. They&rsquo;re all digital. We have digital investments. So, what&rsquo;s the real underlying value of these tokens?</p></blockquote>
<p>He also confirmed that going after Coinbase and Binance wasn&rsquo;t an abrupt decision. The regulator has had discussions with these companies that have a business model based entirely on non-compliance with the securities laws, Gensler added.</p>
<p>Remember that the SEC has so far <a href="https://dailyhodl.com/2023/04/10/the-sec-has-failed-to-prove-xrp-is-a-security-in-ripple-lawsuit-says-attorney-jeremy-hogan/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">failed to prove</a> that XRP is a security in a lawsuit it filed way back in December 2020.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sec-chair-gary-gensler-on-crypto-regulation/">Gary Gensler on crypto regulations: ‘there’s been clarity for years’</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kraken probing funding Gateways amid deposit and withdrawal delays</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/kraken-probing-funding-gateways-amid-deposit-and-withdrawal-delays/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/kraken-probing-funding-gateways-amid-deposit-and-withdrawal-delays/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 13:49:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kraken]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/kraken-probing-funding-gateways-amid-deposit-and-withdrawal-delays/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Kraken recently suffered operational delays due to technical issues with crypto funding gateways. The exchange was however able to quickly resolve the problem although the exact cause hasn&#8217;t been disclosed. The delays caused panic since they came at a time when crypto exchanges in the US are under scrutiny by the SEC. Kraken crypto exchange [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/kraken-probing-funding-gateways-amid-deposit-and-withdrawal-delays/">Kraken probing funding Gateways amid deposit and withdrawal delays</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Kraken recently suffered operational delays due to technical issues with crypto funding gateways.</li>
<li>The exchange was however able to quickly resolve the problem although the exact cause hasn&rsquo;t been disclosed.</li>
<li>The delays caused panic since they came at a time when crypto exchanges in the US are under scrutiny by the SEC.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/kraken/">Kraken </a>crypto exchange recently suffered a technical glitch that impacted several crypto funding gateways. Among the affected crypto funding, channels included Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH), and ERC-20 tokens.</p>
<p>Users from various places complained of deposit and withdrawal delays drawing attention to the delicate infrastructure supporting the transactions.</p>
<h2>Swift response by Kraken</h2>
<p>After customers raised the issue, Kraken earlier today (7:15 am UTC) announced on its status page that deposits and withdrawals were facing challenges. The crypto exchange then immediately embarked on rectifying the issues and by 8:55 am UTC, the delays were resolved according to an update given by the exchange on their status page.</p>
<p>At around 10:30 am UTC, Kraken&rsquo;s futures trading platform was temporarily suspended for about 10 minutes for scheduled maintenance, which was separate from the earlier delay issues.</p>
<p>Kraken is one of the oldest cryptocurrency exchanges and it supports more than 200 cryptocurrencies and six fiat currencies.</p>
<h2>Uncertainty caused by SEC&rsquo;s legal action against crypto exchanges</h2>
<p>Against the backdrop of the brief technical glitch, Kraken and other cryptocurrency exchanges are coping with the uncertainty caused by SEC&rsquo;s legal action against <a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/binance/">Binance </a>and <a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/coinbase/">Coinbase</a>. The US SEC <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-sec-strikes-again-first-binance-now-coinbase/">first sued Binance before later announcing that it had also sued Coinbase </a>today.</p>
<p>Arcra&rsquo;s Chief Investment Officer pointed out that the measures taken by the SEC against Binance indirectly impact tokens listed on Coinbase, Kraken, and other crypto exchanges with a presence in the US.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/kraken-probing-funding-gateways-amid-deposit-and-withdrawal-delays/">Kraken probing funding Gateways amid deposit and withdrawal delays</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/kraken-probing-funding-gateways-amid-deposit-and-withdrawal-delays/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The SEC strikes again: First Binance, now Coinbase</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/the-sec-strikes-again-first-binance-now-coinbase/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 12:51:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Policy and Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/the-sec-strikes-again-first-binance-now-coinbase/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways The US SEC has sued crypto exchange Coinbase for acting as an unregistered broker. This latest development comes a few hours after the regulatory agency sued Binance. SEC sues Coinbase for acting as an unregistered broker The United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has filed a lawsuit against Coinbase, one of the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-sec-strikes-again-first-binance-now-coinbase/">The SEC strikes again: First Binance, now Coinbase</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The US SEC has sued crypto exchange Coinbase for acting as an unregistered broker.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">This latest development comes a few hours after the regulatory agency sued Binance.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr">SEC sues Coinbase for acting as an unregistered broker</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has <a href="https://twitter.com/News_Of_Alpha/status/1666055053625401344" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">filed a lawsuit against Coinbase</a>, one of the leading crypto exchanges in the world.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>latest cryptocurrency news</u></a> comes barely 24 hours after the SEC slapped a lawsuit against rival exchange Binance.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">SEC filed the lawsuit a few minutes ago, alleging that Coinbase has never registered as a broker, national securities exchange or clearing agency. Thus, the SEC claims that Coinbase has been evading the disclosure scheme for securities markets.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The regulatory agency alleged that several tokens offered by the crypto exchange are securities. SEC filed the lawsuit in a New York Federal court.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Coinbase is yet to respond to the lawsuit. This latest development comes as the SEC and Coinbase have been battling a legal case over the past few months.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Earlier this year, the SEC issued Coinbase a Wells Notice, indicating that it is looking into the affairs of the cryptocurrency exchange.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The crypto exchange now&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-sues-sec-ark-invest-buys-8-6m-in-coinbase-stock/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>filed a lawsuit against the SEC</u></a> in April, asking the securities regulator to provide a yes or no to its request for the commission to draft and approve a digital asset-specific rule.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">US SEC is coming after exchanges</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The lawsuit against Coinbase comes barely 24 hours after the&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sec-sues-binance-and-cz-for-breaking-us-securities-rules/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>SEC went after Binance</u></a>, the world&rsquo;s largest cryptocurrency exchange by daily trading volume.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The SEC alleged that Binance was offering services to high-valued US customers on its platform, which is in violation of U.S. securities laws.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The regulatory agency also claimed that Binance CEO exercised control over customer assets, adding that he combined them with personal and company holdings.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The SEC has been coming after crypto exchanges in recent months, including Kraken.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Coinbase&rsquo;s stock price has dipped by more than 15% during Tuesday&rsquo;s pre-market trading session following this latest development. COIN is now trading at $49.44 per share.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-sec-strikes-again-first-binance-now-coinbase/">The SEC strikes again: First Binance, now Coinbase</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Opinion: Binance sued by SEC, an inevitable but ominous day for crypto</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/opinion-binance-sued-by-sec-an-inevitable-but-ominous-day-for-crypto/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/opinion-binance-sued-by-sec-an-inevitable-but-ominous-day-for-crypto/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dan Ashmore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 12:38:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Opinion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/opinion-binance-sued-by-sec-an-inevitable-but-ominous-day-for-crypto/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key Takeaways The world&#8217;s biggest cryptocurrency exchange was sued by the SEC Monday Binance and its CEO Changpeng Zhao have fired back, denying any wrongdoing Our Head of Research, Dan Ashmore, looks into what it all means for crypto, and who is to blame In a development that surprises precisely nobody, the SEC is suing [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/opinion-binance-sued-by-sec-an-inevitable-but-ominous-day-for-crypto/">Opinion: Binance sued by SEC, an inevitable but ominous day for crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2 dir="ltr">Key Takeaways</h2>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">The world&rsquo;s biggest cryptocurrency exchange was sued by the SEC Monday</li>
<li dir="ltr">Binance and its CEO Changpeng Zhao have fired back, denying any wrongdoing</li>
<li dir="ltr">Our Head of Research, Dan Ashmore, looks into what it all means for crypto, and who is to blame</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p dir="ltr">In a development that surprises precisely nobody, the SEC is suing Binance and its CEO, Changpeng Zhao.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Before we get into what it all means for crypto, let&rsquo;s quickly surmise what the lawsuit entails. The SEC outlined in a <a href="https://www.sec.gov/files/litigation/complaints/2023/comp-pr2023-101.pdf"><u>complaint</u></a> filed Monday that the &ldquo;defendants have enriched themselves by billions of US dollars while placing investors&rsquo; assets at significant risk&rdquo;.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The charges are plenty, but among the most glaring is the SEC allegation that Binance knowingly operated in the US, despite repeated claims from Zhao and Binance that American consumers could not transact on the exchange (instead, a Binance.US subsidiary was launched for US customers in September 2019 after parent company Binance.com claimed they were leaving the US).</p>
<p dir="ltr">The SEC alleges that &nbsp;&ldquo;Zhao and Binance in reality subverted their own controls to secretly allow high-value US customers to continue trading on the Binance.com platform&rdquo;, adding that &ldquo;Zhao and Binance secretly controlled the Binance.US platform&rsquo;s operations behind the scenes&rdquo;. A selection of entities and subsidiaries are named as Binance-affiliated and accused of further transgressions in the suit. One of these entities is the Zhao-controlled Sigma Chain, accused of engaging in &ldquo;manipulative trading&rdquo; to boost volume on Binance.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The SEC also accuses Binance of commingling customer funds and moving them around as they please: &ldquo;Lacking regulatory oversight, Defendants were free to and did transfer investors&rsquo; crypto and fiat assets as Defendants pleased, at times commingling and diverting them in ways that properly registered brokers, dealers, exchanges, and clearing agencies would not have been able to do&rdquo;.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Then there is the heart of the issue, a question that has dogged crypto for a while now: what constitutes a security? While there are certainly grey areas within crypto, most notably stablecoins, there is the reality that a massive chunk of the tokens on the market will inevitably be seen as securities in the eyes of the law.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">At the end of the day, that is really all that matters. It appears Binance was more aware of this than anyone. One quote mentioned in the lawsuit is from (unnamed) Binance chief compliance officer in 2018, who messaged a colleague saying, &ldquo;we are operating as a fking unlicensed securities exchange in the USA bro.&rdquo; It seems the SEC agrees.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Binance avoided regulation&nbsp;</h2>
<p dir="ltr">That same CCO is also quoted elsewhere in the lawsuit as maintaining that &ldquo;we do not want (Binance).com to be regulated ever&rdquo;. To this day, Binance.com still claims to have no headquarters, and has been involved in repeated skirmishes with regulators.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">In May, the Commodities Futures Trading Commission <a href="https://www.cftc.gov/PressRoom/PressReleases/8680-23"><u>charged</u></a> Binance with the &ldquo;willful evasion of federal law and operating an illegal digital asset derivatives exchange&rdquo;. The complaint went on to accuse Binance of &ldquo;(failing) to implement basic compliance procedures designed to prevent and detect terrorist financing and money laundering&rdquo;.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This was a month after the SEC sued Paxos, the New York-based issuer of the Binance-branded stablecoin, BUSD. I wrote a deep dive on what that meant for crypto <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/what-does-busd-shutting-down-mean-for-the-crypto-industry-a-deep-dive/"><u>here</u></a>, but again, a violation of securities laws was the trigger for the SEC.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/13992872">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">There is more. According to Bloomberg, the U.S. Department of Justice&rsquo;s national security division is also conducting an inquiry into whether Binance allowed Russian customers to access the exchange, which would have been in violation of U.S. sanctions following the invasion of Ukraine.</p>
<p dir="ltr">All these cases and allegations mean the SEC lawsuit cannot be a surprise, particularly amid what is a wider regulatory clampdown in the US on the industry &ndash; SEC chair Gary Gensler last month slammed the industry for &ldquo;mass non-compliance&rdquo;, summing up the enforcement agency&rsquo;s views on the space.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Is Binance to blame?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Many crypto fans are automatically taking the side of Binance. To me, this misses the point. Binance has operated in an intentionally opaque manner for years, one which I have argued repeatedly is damaging for the entire crypto industry. Not only that, but it goes against one of the pillars of cryptocurrency: transparency and reducing the need to trust centralised third parties blindly. Those are two of the core reasons why Satoshi Nakamoto developed the blockchain as we know it.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Look no further than the issue around proof of reserves, which exploded onto the scene following the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ftx-insolvent-what-next-for-crypto/"><u>collapse of FTX</u></a> in November. Binance claimed to be leading the way in an industry-wide move to be more open with customers. However, their proof of reserves reports made no reference to liabilities whatsoever. Instead, CEO Zhao said on <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1600596763404079124?lang=en"><u>Twitter</u></a> that &ldquo;liabilities are harder&rdquo; before promising that &ldquo;we don&rsquo;t owe loans to anyone. You can ask around&rdquo;.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Only in crypto would you see a CEO assuring his customers on Twitter that there was no need for a proper audit to prove funds were safe. Not to mention, this came a few weeks after FTX CEO Sam Bankman-Fried did the same, promising that &ldquo;FTX is fine. Assets are fine&rdquo; and &ldquo;FTX has enough to cover all client holdings. We don&rsquo;t invest client assets, even in treasuries&rdquo;. Both tweets have since been deleted.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;Centralised crypto companies &ndash; like Binance &ndash; don&rsquo;t demonstrate any meaningful proof of reserves, so there&rsquo;s an implied trust that assets are custodied appropriately&rdquo;, says Mona El Isa, founder of Enzyme, the decentralised asset management protocol. &nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">And that is the issue &ndash; nobody knows what is going on behind the scenes at Binance. This truth was hammered home when Mazaars, the audit firm which had overseen Binance&rsquo;s proof-of-reserves report, announced it was suspending work with the exchange due to &ldquo;the way these reports are understood by the public.&rdquo; Mazars also summed up how futile these reports were when liabilities were not included. Proof-of-reserves reports &ldquo;do not constitute either an assurance or an audit opinion on subject matter. Instead they report limited findings based on the agreed procedures performed on the subject matter at a historical point in time.&rdquo;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What next for crypto?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The markets fell on the news. Bitcoin fell 5.1% to $25,600, currently trading at $25.800. Ether sold off 3.6%, while Binance&rsquo;s native token, BNB, fell 8%. Coinbase stock dropped 10%.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The news may not be overly surprising, but amounts to another body blow for an industry that is getting rattled by regulators thus far this year. It appears increasingly clear that crypto in the US will be forced offshore, which is a big problem for the industry, given the US remains the financial centre of the world.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The crypto world may claim to be decentralised, and parts of it are, but the reality is that people still need these centralised platforms to onboard into the blockchain world. The possibility that a lot of these firms will be pushed abroad therefore amounts to a real concern, as those rails to crossover from the fiat realm will become more inaccessible.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">While it will certainly still be possible to use crypto, it will be a lot more inconvenient &ndash; and that is just for retail. The biggest problem regards institutional investors, where crypto is fighting a battle for legitimacy following a torrid year last year, where it was laced with scandals. Whether you agree with regulators or not, the reality is that institutional capital needs to comply, and lawsuits like this push crypto further away from attracting Wall Street and trad-fi capital on the regular.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">I wrote <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/is-binances-dominance-falling/"><u>last week</u></a> about how Binance&rsquo;s dominance was falling in response to all these issues. However, despite this dropoff, it remains an absolute juggernaut and the biggest company in the space by far, with a colossal 48% share of trading volume. Cryptocurrency was brought to its knees by Luna, Celsius and FTX. Were something to happen Binance, it would be catastrophic.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">For now, Binance will continue fighting back against regulators. Zhao posted a poll on Twitter Tuesday where he asked the Internet, &ldquo;who protects you more?&rdquo;, with answers supplied as SEC and Binance. At time of writing, the responses were 85% in the favour of Binance.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In response to a tweet from Gary Gensler, where he said that &ldquo;through thirteen charges, we allege that Zhao and Binance entities engaged in an extensive web of deception, conflicts of interest, lack of disclosure, and calculated evasion of the law&rdquo;, Zhao wondered aloud whether &ldquo;(Gensler) ever reads the comments under his post, from the consumers he is supposed to protect&rdquo;.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">While I think some of the regulatory clampdown may be somewhat heavy-handed, I am having a hard time feeling sympathy for Binance. I have lamented many a time about how Binance&rsquo;s refusal to be transparent holds the entire crypto industry back. Its proof of reserves report, mentioned above, was absolutely pitiful and as far away from a formal audit as can be imagined. Why don&rsquo;t they just publicise their liabilities if they owe nobody any money?</p>
<p dir="ltr">Then they were forced to apologise in January when they accidentally mixed collateral and customer assets. &nbsp;&ldquo;Collateral assets have previously been moved into this wallet in error and referenced accordingly on the B-Token Proof of Collateral page,&rdquo; the spokesperson told Bloomberg. &ldquo;Binance is aware of this mistake and is in the process of transferring these assets to dedicated collateral wallets&rdquo; the spokesperson added. The story went away and appeared to have been a mistake, but this is the exact kind of thing that regulators are there to protect against.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">This is a company which has an approximate 67% market share and saw $5.29 trillion of trading volume in 2022! It must do better, and this day was coming. Because, in slightly more polite terms than their compliance officer put it above, this is an unregulated securities exchange in the eyes of the law. And they know it, even if they disagree with it.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">For crypto, this a blow, and despite Binance and Zhao&rsquo;s tweets and statements denying any wrongdoing, the lawsuits are mounting. The company continues to operate with minimal transparency, a web of subsidiaries and offshore entities without any physical location. No amount of tweets will change that, no passionate poll blaming lawmakers.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Crypto is hurting, and the missteps of these big centralised firms are a contributing factor.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/opinion-binance-sued-by-sec-an-inevitable-but-ominous-day-for-crypto/">Opinion: Binance sued by SEC, an inevitable but ominous day for crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/opinion-binance-sued-by-sec-an-inevitable-but-ominous-day-for-crypto/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>BNB price prediction: Is it safe to buy Binance Coin now?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bnb-price-prediction-is-it-safe-to-buy-binance-coin-now/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/bnb-price-prediction-is-it-safe-to-buy-binance-coin-now/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 12:27:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance Coin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bnb-price-prediction-is-it-safe-to-buy-binance-coin-now/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The SEC delivered the biggest lawsuit in the crypto industry. It sued Binance and Changpeng Zhao in the United States. Binance Coin price has been in a freefall after the SEC filed a major lawsuit against Binance and its CEO. BNB coin retreated to a low of $272.6, the lowest level since March 11. It [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bnb-price-prediction-is-it-safe-to-buy-binance-coin-now/">BNB price prediction: Is it safe to buy Binance Coin now?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The SEC delivered the biggest lawsuit in the crypto industry.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">It sued Binance and Changpeng Zhao in the United States.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/binance-coin/"><u>Binance Coin</u></a> price has been in a freefall after the SEC filed a major lawsuit against Binance and its CEO. BNB coin retreated to a low of $272.6, the lowest level since March 11. It has plunged by more than 20% from the highest level this year.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">SEC sues Binance and Changpeng Zhao</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Binance Coin and other cryptocurrencies plunged hard on Monday and Tuesday after the SEC filed one of the most consequential lawsuits in the crypto industry. In a statement, as we wrote&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-response-to-sec-lawsuit/"><u>here</u></a><strong>,&nbsp;</strong>the agency sued Binance, alleging that it had defrauded customers and offered regulated products to American customers without following the law.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As expected, in most periods, cryptocurrencies tend to underperform when there is a major announcement such as this. We saw most of them plunge after the collapse of FTX and Terra and its ecosystem. Most importantly, XRP and other coins plunged after the SEC launched a lawsuit against Ripple.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">There are also concerns about the state of regulations in the industry with the US using enforcement instead of engaging the crypto industry. Analysts believe that the agency will continue being tough against digital currency companies after the collapse of FTX.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Still, this is not to say that BNB coin price will continue falling. Instead, the most recent data shows that Binance is doing well. For example, data by DeFi Llama shows that Binance has had over $1.47 billion in outflows in the past 24 hours. While this is a huge number, the company still has over $51 billion in assets.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Further, historically, many investors tend to buy the dip in crypto after big events. For example, most coins jumped this year despite the collapse of FTX.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">BNB price forecast</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/05/06/1686054285625-13247c08-cb15-4508-9cc0-1e6d7bcf25f4.png" style="width: 691px;height: 336.287px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="691" height="336.287"></p>
<p dir="ltr">The daily chart shows that the Binance Coin price has been in a slow bearish trend in the past few days. This sell-off intensified after the SEC lawsuit. As it plunged, the coin crashed below the key support level at $298.4, the lowest point on May 12th.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/binance/"><u>Binance</u></a> Coin retreated below all moving averages and is slightly above the key point at $265.6. Therefore, I suspect that the coin will remain under pressure this week and then bounce back as the lawsuit fades. As we have seen with XRP, it is possible for a coin to rise despite the lawsuit. The initial level to watch will be at $265.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy Binance Coin</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>

    <p>eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=MTQyMTMw&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy BNB with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    Swapzone</h3>

    <p>Swapzone is a crypto exchange aggregator that operates as a gateway between the cryptocurrency community and exchange services. Swapzone aims to provide a convenient interface, safe user flow, and crystal-clear data for users to find the best exchange rates among the whole cryptocurrency market.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/swapzone-crypto?guid=MTQyMTMw&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy BNB with Swapzone today            </a>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bnb-price-prediction-is-it-safe-to-buy-binance-coin-now/">BNB price prediction: Is it safe to buy Binance Coin now?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/bnb-price-prediction-is-it-safe-to-buy-binance-coin-now/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>OKX Partners with Komainu, Enabling 24/7 Secure Trading of Segregated Assets Under Custody for Institutions</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/okx-partners-with-komainu-enabling-24-7-secure-trading-of-segregated-assets-under-custody-for-institutions/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/okx-partners-with-komainu-enabling-24-7-secure-trading-of-segregated-assets-under-custody-for-institutions/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire &#160;]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 08:36:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=142085</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>ST HELLIER, Jersey, June 6th, 2023, Chainwire OKX, the world&#8217;s second-largest cryptocurrency exchange by trading volume and a leading Web3 technology company, and regulated digital asset custody service provider Komainu, today announced that OKX has joined collateral management platform Komainu Connect, enabling institutional customers to conduct secure 24/7 trading of segregated assets under custody through [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/okx-partners-with-komainu-enabling-24-7-secure-trading-of-segregated-assets-under-custody-for-institutions/">OKX Partners with Komainu, Enabling 24/7 Secure Trading of Segregated Assets Under Custody for Institutions</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>ST HELLIER, Jersey, June 6th, 2023, Chainwire</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://www.okx.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">OKX</a>, the world&rsquo;s second-largest cryptocurrency exchange by trading volume and a leading Web3 technology company, and regulated digital asset custody service provider <a href="https://www.komainu.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Komainu</a>, today announced that OKX has joined collateral management platform Komainu Connect, enabling institutional customers to conduct secure 24/7 trading of segregated assets under custody through the OKX platform.</p>
<p>Launched in April of 2023, Komainu Connect reduces client counterparty risk by removing the need to store collateral with trading counterparties, and offering the ability to keep assets in safe custody instead.</p>
<blockquote><p>Nicolas Bertrand, CEO at Komainu, said: &ldquo;This strategic partnership marks a milestone in our mission to provide secure and compliant digital asset custody solutions. OKX&rsquo;s reputation as a leading cryptocurrency exchange, combined with our expertise in institutional-grade custody services is paving the way for a new era of trust and innovation in the industry.&rdquo;</p></blockquote>
<blockquote><p>Sebastian Widmann, Head of Strategy at Komainu, said: &ldquo;Komainu Connect is rapidly emerging as the leading collateral management solution. Partnering with one of the world&rsquo;s largest crypto exchanges is a testament to the infrastructure and expertise committed to this service and our focus remains on seamless execution for all parties.&rdquo;</p></blockquote>
<blockquote><p>Lennix Lai, Global Chief Commercial Officer at OKX, said: &ldquo;Institutions need the peace of mind that comes with knowing their assets are being kept safe with a leading custodian, while retaining their ability to capitalize when investment opportunities arise. That is why we are delighted to partner with Komainu to allow investors a way to keep their assets secure while not compromising on returns.&rdquo;</p></blockquote>
<p>The off-exchange settlement and tripartite mirroring solution is a significant step forward for large-scale institutional crypto traders requiring immediate access to OKX&rsquo;s market-leading portfolio margin account mode and liquid markets.</p>
<p>Komainu was established in 2018 to provide institutions with a secure and compliant custody service for investment in digital assets. Launched in June 2020, Komainu currently custodies assets for exchanges, financial institutions, asset managers, corporations, and government agencies.</p>
<p>Find out more about why institutions choose OKX <a href="https://www.okx.com/institutions" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">here</a>.</p>
<h3><strong>About OKX</strong></h3>
<p>OKX is a world-leading technology company building the future of Web3. Known as the most reliable crypto trading platform for traders, OKX&rsquo;s crypto exchange is the second largest globally by trading volume.</p>
<p>OKX&rsquo;s leading self-custody solutions include the Web3-compatible OKX Wallet, which allows users greater control of their assets while expanding access to DEXs, NFT marketplaces, DeFi, GameFi and thousands of dApps.</p>
<p>OKX partners with a number of the world&rsquo;s top brands and athletes, including English Premier League champions Manchester City F.C., McLaren Formula 1, The Tribeca Festival, golfer Ian Poulter, Olympian Scotty James, and F1 driver Daniel Ricciardo.</p>
<p>OKX is committed to transparency and security and publishes its Proof of Reserves on a monthly basis.</p>
<p>To learn more about OKX, download OKX&rsquo;s app or visit: <a href="http://okx.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">okx.com</a></p>
<h3><strong>About Komainu</strong></h3>
<p>Komainu is a regulated digital asset custodian built by institutions for institutions and created as a joint venture between Nomura, digital asset manager CoinShares, and digital asset security company Ledger. Offering multi-asset support with regulatory compliance, Komainu is merging traditional financial services with leading security standards for the next generation of institutional custody. Headquartered in Jersey and with offices in London, Dublin, Dubai, and Singapore, Komainu is regulated by the Jersey Financial Services Commission (JFSC) and Dubai Virtual Assets Regulatory Authority (VARA). For more information, visit <a href="https://www.komainu.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.komainu.com</a></p>
<p>Media Contact: Armel Leslie, Peaks Strategies, +1 (914) 320-7620, <a href="mailto:aleslie@peaksstrategies.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">aleslie@peaksstrategies.com</a></p>
<h3><strong>DISCLAIMER</strong></h3>
<p>This announcement is provided for informational purposes only. It is not intended to provide any investment, tax, or legal advice, nor should it be considered an offer to purchase, sell, or hold digital assets. Digital assets, including stablecoins, involve a high degree of risk, can fluctuate greatly, and can even become worthless. You should carefully consider whether trading or holding digital assets is suitable for you in light of your financial condition. Please consult your legal/tax/investment professional for questions about your specific circumstances.</p>
<h3>Contact</h3>
<p>Media, OKX, media@okx.com</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/okx-partners-with-komainu-enabling-24-7-secure-trading-of-segregated-assets-under-custody-for-institutions/">OKX Partners with Komainu, Enabling 24/7 Secure Trading of Segregated Assets Under Custody for Institutions</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/okx-partners-with-komainu-enabling-24-7-secure-trading-of-segregated-assets-under-custody-for-institutions/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance on SEC’s lawsuit on Monday: ‘we will vigorously defend’</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-response-to-sec-lawsuit/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wajeeh Khan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 20:55:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=142081</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SEC sued Binance for violating securities laws on Monday. Here&#8217;s what Binance said in its response to the regulator. Coinbase Global ended 10% down on today&#8217;s development. Binance is in focus on Monday after the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) sued the world&#8217;s leading crypto exchange. Here&#8217;s what Binance said in its response to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-response-to-sec-lawsuit/">Binance on SEC’s lawsuit on Monday: ‘we will vigorously defend’</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>SEC sued Binance for violating securities laws on Monday.</li>
<li>Here&rsquo;s what Binance said in its response to the regulator.</li>
<li>Coinbase Global ended 10% down on today&rsquo;s development.</li>
</ul>
<p>Binance is in focus on Monday after the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) sued the world&rsquo;s leading crypto exchange.</p>
<h2>Here&rsquo;s what Binance said in its response to SEC</h2>
<p>In its lawsuit, the regulator <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/sec-sues-crypto-exchange-binance-over-u-s-rule-violations-6918ed0f" target="_blank" rel="noopener">accused</a> Binance as well as its CEO Changpeng Zhao for failing to comply with the U.S. securities laws. The CFTC had previously filed such charges against the crypto company as well.</p>
<p>SEC also alleged that Binance commingled user funds worth billions of dollars with Merit Peak Limited &ndash; a CZ-controlled European company. Only hours later, though, Binance declined claims of wrongdoing and said in its <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/blog/ecosystem/sec-complaint-aims-to-unilaterally-define-crypto-market-structure-8707489117122437402" target="_blank" rel="noopener">official response</a> to the regulator:</p>
<blockquote><p>Any allegations that user assets on the Binance.US platform have ever been at risk are simply wrong. We will vigorously defend against any allegations to the contrary.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Crypto community stood with Binance on Twitter</h2>
<p>On Twitter, the crypto community demonstrated support for Binance and CEO Changpeng Zhao. Many found the SEC unfair in the way it was dealing with crypto assets in the United States.</p>
<p>In its response, Binance also said that the regulator&rsquo;s overreach was hurting the U.S. reputation as a global hub for financial innovation. Still, it added:</p>
<blockquote><p>We&rsquo;ll continue to cooperate with regulators and policymakers across the globe. We remain committed to productive engagement to ensure next-gen of crypto regulation fosters innovation.</p></blockquote>
<p>SEC&rsquo;s lawsuit against Binance saw shares of peer <a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/coinbase/">Coinbase Global Inc</a> lose about 10% today.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-response-to-sec-lawsuit/">Binance on SEC’s lawsuit on Monday: ‘we will vigorously defend’</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>JPMorgan teams up with six Indian banks to build a blockchain-based platform</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/jpmorgan-teams-up-with-six-indian-banks-to-build-a-blockchain-based-platform/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/jpmorgan-teams-up-with-six-indian-banks-to-build-a-blockchain-based-platform/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 18:17:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/jpmorgan-teams-up-with-six-indian-banks-to-build-a-blockchain-based-platform/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The blockchain-based platform is aimed at settling interbank dollar transactions. The move is part of the Indian government&#8217;s strategy to elevate GIFT City to the League of Cities like Singapore. The parties will launch a pilot project over the next few months in order to analyze the banks&#8217; experience. American multinational financial behemoth JPMorgan Chase [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/jpmorgan-teams-up-with-six-indian-banks-to-build-a-blockchain-based-platform/">JPMorgan teams up with six Indian banks to build a blockchain-based platform</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>The blockchain-based platform is aimed at settling interbank dollar transactions.</li>
<li>The move is part of the Indian government&rsquo;s strategy to elevate GIFT City to the League of Cities like Singapore.</li>
<li>The parties will launch a pilot project over the next few months in order to analyze the banks&rsquo; experience.</li>
</ul>
<p>American multinational financial behemoth JPMorgan Chase &amp; Co. has partnered with Indian banks to build a <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/blockchain/">blockchain</a>-based platform to settle interbank dollar transactions.</p>
<p>The Indian banks involved are based in the Gujarat International Finance Tec-City (GIFT) City and include HDFC Bank Ltd., ICICI Bank Ltd., Axis Bank Ltd., Yes Bank Ltd., and IndusInd Bank Ltd.</p>
<h2>Elevating GIFT City status</h2>
<p>Although it is a partnership within the private sector, the move is part of the Indian government&rsquo;s strategy of elevating GIFT City to a level where it can compete with the likes of Hong Kong, Singapore, the International Financial Centre (IFC) in Dubai, and the Abu Dhabi Global Market (ADGM).</p>
<p>Kaustubh Kulkarni, a senior Indian officer, and vice chairman of Asia Pacific, at JPMorgan, have stated that the institution would be launching a pilot project in the coming months to examine banks&rsquo; experience.</p>
<h2>JPMorgan and blockchain technology</h2>
<p>JPMorgan also plans to use blockchain technology to restructure dollar transactions between financial institutions so that the transactions can be completed in a matter of seconds.</p>
<p>According to Kulkarni, GIFT City banks would be able to maintain their own time zone and business hours once JPMorgan creates the blockchain infrastructure enabling instant transactions around the clock.</p>
<p>JPMorgan&rsquo;s pilot project using the Onyx blockchain technology is already expected to start on Monday after receiving clearance from the International Financial Services Centre Authority. Onyx, which is a blockchain-based platform for wholesale payment transactions was <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/jpmorgan-launches-its-own-stablecoin/">launched by JPMorgan in 2020</a>.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/jpmorgan-teams-up-with-six-indian-banks-to-build-a-blockchain-based-platform/">JPMorgan teams up with six Indian banks to build a blockchain-based platform</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/jpmorgan-teams-up-with-six-indian-banks-to-build-a-blockchain-based-platform/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>SEC sues Binance and CZ for breaking US Securities Rules</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/sec-sues-binance-and-cz-for-breaking-us-securities-rules/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 15:34:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Policy and Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/sec-sues-binance-and-cz-for-breaking-us-securities-rules/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways The US SEC has sued Binance for breaking securities rules. The regulatory agency has also sued Changpeng Zhao (CZ), the CEO of the cryptocurrency exchange. SEC sues Binance and CZ The United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has filed a lawsuit against Binance, the world&#8217;s leading cryptocurrency exchange, and Changpeng Zhao, the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sec-sues-binance-and-cz-for-breaking-us-securities-rules/">SEC sues Binance and CZ for breaking US Securities Rules</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The US SEC has sued Binance for breaking securities rules.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The regulatory agency has also sued Changpeng Zhao (CZ), the CEO of the cryptocurrency exchange.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr">SEC sues Binance and CZ</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has filed a lawsuit against Binance, the world&rsquo;s leading cryptocurrency exchange, and Changpeng Zhao, the CEO of the company.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This is according to a <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/sec-sues-crypto-exchange-binance-over-u-s-rule-violations-6918ed0f" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>report by The Wall Street Journal</u></a> a few minutes ago. According to the Wall Street Journal, the regulatory agency has sued Binance and its CEO for breaking US securities rules.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>latest cryptocurrency news</u></a> doesn&rsquo;t come as a surprise to some experts in the industry, as the regulatory agency has been going after cryptocurrency exchanges in recent months.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Binance faces 13 charges from the SEC</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The regulatory agency alleges that Binance secretly allow[ed] high-value U.S. customers&rdquo; to trade on the platform in violation of U.S. securities laws which prohibits unregistered exchanges from servicing U.S. customers.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The lawsuit also alleges that CZ exercised control over customer assets, adding that he commingled them with personal and company holdings. SEC Chairman Gary Gensler stated that;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;Through thirteen charges, we allege that Zhao and Binance entities engaged in an extensive web of deception, conflicts of interest, lack of disclosure, and calculated evasion of the law. As alleged, Zhao and Binance misled investors about their risk controls and corrupted trading volumes while actively concealing who was operating the platform, the manipulative trading of its affiliated market maker, and even where and with whom investor funds and crypto assets were custodied.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p dir="ltr">This latest development comes two weeks after the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sec-sues-crypto-exchange-bittrex-and-its-ex-ceo/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>SEC sued Bittrex</u></a>, one of the world&rsquo;s largest and oldest cryptocurrency exchanges, and co-founder and ex-CEO William Shihara for violating securities laws.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The regulatory agency had also come after several other crypto exchanges in recent months, including Kraken and Coinbase.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin has lost more than 2% of its value so far today and could fall below the $26k level soon following this latest development. At press time, the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">price of Bitcoin</a> stands at $26,682 per coin.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sec-sues-binance-and-cz-for-breaking-us-securities-rules/">SEC sues Binance and CZ for breaking US Securities Rules</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
