<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 19:17:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>XRP price outlook: a tinge of frustration but bulls have $1 in sight</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/xrp-price-outlook-a-tinge-of-frustration-but-bulls-have-1-in-sight/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/xrp-price-outlook-a-tinge-of-frustration-but-bulls-have-1-in-sight/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 19:17:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/xrp-price-outlook-a-tinge-of-frustration-but-bulls-have-1-in-sight/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>XRP&#8217;s explosive gain on the day Ripple scored a big one against the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) did not help bulls cross the psychologically important $1 level. And with ranged trading amid a flip in the Fear &#38; Greed Index this week, the struggle beneath $0.80 has hinted at a slight frustration across [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/xrp-price-outlook-a-tinge-of-frustration-but-bulls-have-1-in-sight/">XRP price outlook: a tinge of frustration but bulls have $1 in sight</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/ripple/">XRP</a>&rsquo;s explosive gain on the day Ripple scored a big one against the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) did not help bulls cross the psychologically important $1 level. And with ranged trading amid a flip in the Fear &amp; Greed Index this week, the struggle beneath $0.80 has hinted at a slight frustration across the XRP market.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What&rsquo;s the XRP outlook?</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><span class="fr-img-caption fr-fic fr-dib fr-draggable" style="width: 700px"><span class="fr-img-wrap"></span></span></p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/21/1689966383667-0fc5b34b-f6bc-4b58-b59a-1e3345a993d0.png" style="width: 700px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="700" height="320"><span class="fr-inner">A weekly chart showing XRP/USD price performance. Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/wCrv9RG2/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">TradingView</a></span></p>
<p class="fr-img-space-wrap2">XRP&rsquo;s pullback below $0.80 (XRP/USD traded to highs above $0.93 last week) has come even as <a href="https://www.coinglass.com/BitcoinOpenInterest" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">open interest</a> in futures contracts continued to hover at its highest level since November 2021. According to OI data from Coinglass, that metric soared to $1.19 billion on Thursday July 20.</p>

<p dir="ltr">Rising open interest is indicative of inflows into the XRP futures contracts and typically confirms the recent trend&rsquo;s strength.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The XRP market has also been on a tear in terms of the global spot trading volumes. On-chain data showed XRP volumes, buoyed by massive interest in South Korea, topped that of Bitcoin.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">This is the largest volume on <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24XRP&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$XRP</a> measured in the last 1,5 years.</p>
<p>INSANE! <a href="https://t.co/paNyPJsCXm">pic.twitter.com/paNyPJsCXm</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Crypto Rover (@rovercrc) <a href="https://twitter.com/rovercrc/status/1679517125264785409?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 13, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">Positive sentiment has also been infused into the XRP market by recent developments around adoption of Ripple technology. After the partial win against the SEC, reports emerged that the US-based blockchain company was looking to recapture the interest of major financial players in its cross-border payments and remittances technology.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Ripple also made a major splash this week, committing to a <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ripple-invests-in-54m-round-for-ai-metaverse-firm-futureverse/">$54 million investment</a> in Futureverse, an artificial intelligence and metaverse-focused project. With more upside catalysts across the crypto market, it is possible XRP price could cap a great month with a burst above the key resistance level.</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, while a move higher is a more likely scenario given the highlighted factors, a negative flip in sentiment with prices still near current levels could risk a bearish retest. The primary support level below $0.70 is around $0.50.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/xrp-price-outlook-a-tinge-of-frustration-but-bulls-have-1-in-sight/">XRP price outlook: a tinge of frustration but bulls have $1 in sight</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/xrp-price-outlook-a-tinge-of-frustration-but-bulls-have-1-in-sight/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>DOJ accuses Bankman-Fried of leaking Ellison’s diary to “discredit her”</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/doj-accuses-bankman-fried-of-leaking-ellisons-diary-to-discredit-her/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/doj-accuses-bankman-fried-of-leaking-ellisons-diary-to-discredit-her/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 16:59:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/doj-accuses-bankman-fried-of-leaking-ellisons-diary-to-discredit-her/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The DOJ has filed a court complaint accusing former FTX CEO Sam Bankman-Fried of leaking Caroline Ellison&#8217;s diary. Bankman-Fried is alleged to have met a New York Times reporter and handed out the information. The government sees this as an attempt by SBF to discredit Ellison who is a key witness. The US Department of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/doj-accuses-bankman-fried-of-leaking-ellisons-diary-to-discredit-her/">DOJ accuses Bankman-Fried of leaking Ellison’s diary to “discredit her”</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">The DOJ has filed a court complaint accusing former FTX CEO Sam Bankman-Fried of leaking Caroline Ellison&rsquo;s diary.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Bankman-Fried is alleged to have met a New York Times reporter and handed out the information.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The government sees this as an attempt by SBF to discredit Ellison who is a key witness.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">The US Department of Justice (DOJ) says Sam Bankman-Fried, the former CEO of <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/ftx/">FTX</a>, leaked the contents of a private diary belonging to Caroline Ellison to a <em>New York Times</em> reporter.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">DOJ says Bankman-Fried wanted to &ldquo;discredit&rdquo; Ellison</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Ellison is a former colleague of Bankman-Fried, and headed Alameda Research, a sister company of the collapsed crypto exchange.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">She was also charged for her role in the implosion that befell the companies. However, Ellison agreed to cooperate with the prosecution and is seen as a key witness in the DOJ&rsquo;s case against the former FTX chief.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The government&rsquo;s complaint against SBF relates to an <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2023/07/20/technology/ftx-caroline-ellison-bankman-fried.html" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">article</a> in the NYT that feature information leaked from Ellison&rsquo;s private diary. In its <a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.nysd.590940/gov.uscourts.nysd.590940.176.0.pdf" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">filing</a>, the DOJ says that the former FTX CEO is behind the leak and that his action &ldquo;<em>sought to publicly discredit a government witness</em>.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>The defendant&rsquo;s purpose in sharing these materials is plain. &nbsp;Ellison has pleaded guilty to a cooperation agreement and is expected to testify at trial that she agreed with the defendant to defraud FTX&rsquo;s customers and investors, and Alameda&rsquo;s lenders. &nbsp;By selectively sharing certain private documents with the New York Times, the defendant is attempting to discredit a witness, cast Ellison in a poor light, and advance his defense through the press and outside the constraints of the courtroom and rules of evidence: that Ellison was a jilted lover who perpetrated these crimes alone</em>,&rdquo; reads part of the DOJ&rsquo;s complaint.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Additionally, the government sees this as an extrajudicial move by the defendant, and which could interfere not only with the jury but also with witnesses lined up to testify against him. It&rsquo;s not the first complaint the DOJ has filed against Bankman-Fried.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>The effect, if not the intent, of the defendant&rsquo;s conduct is not only to harass Ellison, but also to deter other potential trial witnesses from testifying</em>,&rdquo; the DOJ wrote.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In January, the prosecution <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/doj-says-bankman-fried-attempted-to-influence-witness/">said</a> he had tried to influence an FTX.US official.The government has therefore requested the court to issue orders limiting extrajudicial statements that could interfere with the jury and witnesses.</p>
<p dir="ltr">SBF, once lauded as a crypto prodigy and a darling around the Capitol, is under house arrest and faces a long prison sentence if convicted. His trial is set to begin in October.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/doj-accuses-bankman-fried-of-leaking-ellisons-diary-to-discredit-her/">DOJ accuses Bankman-Fried of leaking Ellison’s diary to “discredit her”</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/doj-accuses-bankman-fried-of-leaking-ellisons-diary-to-discredit-her/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP, XLM and LINK record huge gains: is the altcoins season here?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/xrp-xlm-and-link-record-huge-gains-is-the-altcoins-season-here/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/xrp-xlm-and-link-record-huge-gains-is-the-altcoins-season-here/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 16:23:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/xrp-xlm-and-link-record-huge-gains-is-the-altcoins-season-here/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways XRP, XLM and LINK added more than 20% to their values over the past seven days, outperforming Bitcoin.&#160; Shiba Memu has now raised more than $1 million in its presale. XRP, XLM and LINK have been the best performers amongst the top 50 cryptocurrencies by market cap over the past few days.&#160; Their [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/xrp-xlm-and-link-record-huge-gains-is-the-altcoins-season-here/">XRP, XLM and LINK record huge gains: is the altcoins season here?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">XRP, XLM and LINK added more than 20% to their values over the past seven days, outperforming Bitcoin.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu has now raised more than $1 million in its presale.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">XRP, XLM and LINK have been the best performers amongst the top 50 cryptocurrencies by market cap over the past few days.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Their performance has seen Bitcoin&rsquo;s dominance drop below the 50% mark. Investors are now speculating whether the altcoins season is here, with altcoins outperforming Bitcoin since the start of the month.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">XLM, XRP, and LINK lead the altcoins rally</h2>
<p dir="ltr">XRP, the native coin of the Ripple ecosystem, has been the biggest winner so far this month. XRP added more than 70% to its value since the start of the month, thanks to a <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ripple-wins-sec-case-xrp-not-a-security/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>favourable ruling</u></a> in the Ripple vs. SEC case.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Stellar Lumen&rsquo;s XLM also rallied by more than 50% this month, thanks to XRP&rsquo;s positive performance. With XRP not considered a security, <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/xlm-price-soars-as-stellar-rides-ripples-xrp-wave/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>XLM became bullish</u></a> as it is XRP&rsquo;s major competitor in the market.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">LINK, the native coin of the Chainlink blockchain, also rallied by more than 20% this week. The rally was fueled by <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/3-reasons-why-chainlink-link-price-just-surged/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Chainlink&rsquo;s release of its CCIP protocol</u></a> as it expanded its base within the ecosystem.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">With altcoins outperforming Bitcoin in recent weeks, market participants could be wondering whether the altcoins season is finally here.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu&rsquo;s presale also continues to set new records. The team has now raised more than $1 million, with only 36,406,652 tokens left in this presale round.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Shiba Memu?</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Shiba Memu</u></a> is a meme coin project that seeks to differ from the current crop of meme coins found in the cryptocurrency space by offering more value to users.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">While the project is still in its presale stage, its promised utility has seen investors grab more than $1 million worth of its native SHMU token.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to their whitepaper, Shiba Memu is a cryptocurrency that combines AI and blockchain technology to develop an unstoppable, entirely self-sufficient marketing powerhouse.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The team revealed that Shiba Memu has the capacity to execute the work of 100 marketing agencies. Furthermore, Shiba Memu is an active AI-based platform, providing users with the transparency of blockchain technology and the efficiency of AI.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">If deployed, the Shiba Memu platform actively engages to find the best work going on in creative advertising, consumes the work and churns out far better results.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Shiba Memu team decided to leverage the recent popularity of meme coins. Meme coins have become an important part of the cryptocurrency ecosystem. The total meme coin market cap grew from practically $0 to reach the $20 billion mark in 2022.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The <a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Shiba Memu</u></a> team revealed the platform has self-sufficient marketing capabilities powered by AI technology. When deployed, Shiba Memu will develop its own marketing strategies, write its own PR, and promote itself in relevant forums and various social media platforms. &nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">At the moment, Shiba Memu operates on Ethereum and BNB Chain, the two leading DeFi and smart contract blockchains.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Shiba Memu&rsquo;s presale tops $1 million</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Despite the current market conditions, Shiba Memu&rsquo;s presale event has been going excellently. Shiba Memu&rsquo;s presale investment has increased by more than $200k over the past few days, with more than $1 million raised so far.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu has been attracting interest from investors thanks to the latest rally by altcoins.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The team revealed that the funds generated from the presale would be used to develop some of their products. They have allocated most of the funds to the development of the Shiba Memum AI technology.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Click here</u></a> to find out more about Shiba Memu&rsquo;s presale event.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Should you invest in Shiba Memu today?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin&rsquo;s dominance in the market has decreased in recent days, with altcoins like XRP, XLM and LINK experiencing massive surges in prices.</p>
<p dir="ltr">With more interest in altcoins, investors could be looking for new exciting projects in the cryptocurrency space. Shiba Memu could be one of the projects investors look to.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">By combining the power of blockchain technology and AI, <a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Shiba Memu</a> promises to be a unique project. The platform will look to ease marketing strategies for companies and organisations.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">If the project gets the right level of adoption, its SHMU token could rally higher in the coming months and years.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/xrp-xlm-and-link-record-huge-gains-is-the-altcoins-season-here/">XRP, XLM and LINK record huge gains: is the altcoins season here?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/xrp-xlm-and-link-record-huge-gains-is-the-altcoins-season-here/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Wormhole launches a Cosmos appchain called Gateway</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/wormhole-launches-a-cosmos-appchain-called-gateway/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/wormhole-launches-a-cosmos-appchain-called-gateway/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 15:44:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cosmos News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/wormhole-launches-a-cosmos-appchain-called-gateway/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Gateway is a Cosmos-powered appchain. It is designed to allow for access to unified liquidity in the Cosmos ecosystem. Decentralized messaging protocol Wormhole has released its application-specific blockchain dubbed Wormhole Gateway. The appchain is powered by the Cosmos SDK, and aims at broadening access and liquidity with the blockchain platform&#8217;s ecosystem. Wormhole Foundation, which announced [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/wormhole-launches-a-cosmos-appchain-called-gateway/">Wormhole launches a Cosmos appchain called Gateway</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Gateway is a Cosmos-powered appchain.</li>
<li dir="ltr">It is designed to allow for access to unified liquidity in the Cosmos ecosystem.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Decentralized messaging protocol Wormhole has released its application-specific blockchain dubbed Wormhole Gateway. The appchain is powered by the Cosmos SDK, and aims at broadening access and liquidity with the blockchain platform&rsquo;s ecosystem.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Wormhole Foundation, which announced Gateway on Friday, said the appchain is &ldquo;compatible and complementary to IBC.&rdquo;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Wormhole to connect 23 blockchains in Cosmos</h2>
<p dir="ltr">According to details shared in a <a href="https://wormhole.com/wormhole-gateway-the-gateway-to-the-cosmos-ecosystem/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">blog post</a>, Gateway allows Wormhole to connect 23+ blockchains, including Osmosis, Evmos and Neutron, across six runtimes to <a href="https://coinjournal.net/cosmos/">Cosmos</a>. This is achieved through a liquidity router that allows users to bridge funds to any appchain within the Cosmos ecosystem at no extra bridging fees, the protocol noted.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Introducing &#10024;&#10024;Wormhole Gateway&#10024;&#10024; &ndash; an application-specific blockchain, powered by the <a href="https://twitter.com/cosmos?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@cosmos</a> SDK.</p>
<p>Gateway&rsquo;s purpose is to help broaden access (and bring liquidity) to the Cosmos ecosystem while also improving Wormhole&rsquo;s security and sovereignty. <a href="https://t.co/qG1kyvcnoY">pic.twitter.com/qG1kyvcnoY</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Wormhole&#127786; (@wormholecrypto) <a href="https://twitter.com/wormholecrypto/status/1682337664379531266?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 21, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">Gateway is also designed to improve Wormhole&rsquo;s security and sovereignty. Security is key to the protocol given the impact of a February 2022 hack on the Wormhole bridge that saw a hacker 120,000 wETH worth $325 million. The exploit on the Solana-Ethereum bridge saw the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/solana-price-drops-by-9-all-you-need-to-know-about-the-wormhole-bridge-hack/">price of SOL declined sharply</a> amid community reaction to the news.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As part of enhancing security across the Cosmos ecosystem, Wormhole introduced Governor, a module designed to limit cross-chain contagion in the event of a hack.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In June, Wormhole <a href="https://twitter.com/wormholecrypto/status/1680997071132950528" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">introduced</a> Automatic Relayers, a decentralised network of relayers that allows for cross-chain messaging that developers can tap into without having to develop, run or manage an off-chain component. With this developers can deploy a fully-functional cross-chain dApp via a single solidity contract.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/wormhole-launches-a-cosmos-appchain-called-gateway/">Wormhole launches a Cosmos appchain called Gateway</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/wormhole-launches-a-cosmos-appchain-called-gateway/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Zoomex X WSOT 2023: Unleash Your Trading Prowess and Race to $7 Million in Prizes!</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/zoomex-x-wsot-2023-unleash-your-trading-prowess-and-race-to-7-million-in-prizes/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ben Myers]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 15:23:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=147126</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Get ready for the most thrilling cryptocurrency trading competition of the year! The World Series of Trading (WSOT) is back, yet this time, it&#8217;s bigger and better than ever. In partnership with F2 Ferrari driver Oliver Bearman, WSOT 2023 promises to be an unforgettable experience for traders worldwide.&#160; The leading crypto exchange, Zoomex, is renowned [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/zoomex-x-wsot-2023-unleash-your-trading-prowess-and-race-to-7-million-in-prizes/">Zoomex X WSOT 2023: Unleash Your Trading Prowess and Race to $7 Million in Prizes!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Get ready for the most thrilling cryptocurrency trading competition of the year! </span><a href="https://partner.zoomex.com/WSOTPR" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400">The World Series of Trading</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> (WSOT) is back, yet this time, it&rsquo;s bigger and better than ever. In partnership with F2 Ferrari driver Oliver Bearman, WSOT 2023 promises to be an unforgettable experience for traders worldwide.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The leading crypto exchange, Zoomex, is renowned for its cutting-edge technology, superior liquidity, unwavering commitment to customer satisfaction, and dedication to preserving the spirit of anonymity by offering a no-KYC approach.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Now, in tandem with WSOT, Zoomex aims to take the excitement of trading to new heights, empowering traders from all corners of the globe. Additionally, Zoomex is set to create an unparalleled fusion of high-speed trading and racing by joining forces with Oliver Bearman, an exceptional talent in motorsport competitions.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400">About WSOT &ndash; The world&rsquo;s largest cryptocurrency trading conference</span></h2>
<figure id="attachment_147153" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-147153" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-147153" src="https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Zoomex-X-WSOT-2023.png" alt="Zoomex X WSOT 2023" width="1000" height="334"><figcaption id="caption-attachment-147153" class="wp-caption-text">Zoomex X WSOT 2023</figcaption></figure>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Prepare for the highly anticipated </span><a href="https://partner.zoomex.com/WSOTPR" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400">WSOT 2023</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">, featuring an incredible prize pool of $7 million. Traders can participate in both squad and individual competitions, with team participants vying for a share of up to $6 million in USDT prizes. For the individual competition, staggering prizes of </span><b>up to $400,000 in USDT</b><span style="font-weight: 400"> await the winners.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">New Zoomex users who register within 72 hours before the start of WSOT can receive a bonus reward of $50. Additionally, there&rsquo;s an exciting opportunity for lucky registration prizes. Every 100 lucky applicants, namely the 100th, 200th, and so on, will be selected to receive a generous prize of 100 USDT bonus rewards.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Moreover, exciting new features have been introduced in this year&rsquo;s edition, including the Copy Trading Fest and Lucky Draw. With </span><b>a total prize pool of $500,000 USDT</b><span style="font-weight: 400">, participants can win incredible rewards such as Signed Ferrari helmets, racing suits, and a </span><b>cash reward of $10,000.</b><span style="font-weight: 400">&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The event will kick off on </span><b>July 24</b><span style="font-weight: 400">, spanning </span><b>43 exciting days</b><span style="font-weight: 400">, concluding on September 7. WSOT is more than just a competition. It is a vibrant platform that fosters connections, learning, and growth among traders.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Engage with like-minded participants, exchange trading strategies, and expand your network within the dynamic crypto community! Take advantage of this extraordinary opportunity to collaborate with </span><b>F2 Ferrari driver Oliver Bearman</b><span style="font-weight: 400"> and showcase your trading prowess on the world stage.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Join WSOT 2023 today and embark on an exhilarating journey that could transform your trading career!&nbsp;</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400">Zoomex | Your Trusted Partner for the Most Exciting Adventures</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">At Zoomex, integrity and long-term development principles are paramount as we strive to deliver a high-quality trading experience. Our key pillars include transparency, regulatory compliance, fund security, and reliable services, all of which contribute to creating value for our users.&nbsp;</span></p>
<h3><span style="font-weight: 400">Join the USDT Treasure Hunt and Get Rewarded</span></h3>
<figure id="attachment_147154" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-147154" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-147154" src="https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Zoomex-X-WSOT-2023-1.png" alt="Zoomex X WSOT 2023" width="1053" height="360"><figcaption id="caption-attachment-147154" class="wp-caption-text">Zoomex X WSOT 2023</figcaption></figure>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Currently, Zoomex hosts thrilling activities alongside the World Series of Trading (WSOT), including the highly anticipated </span><a href="https://partner.zoomex.com/1USDTPR" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><b>1 USDT Treasure Hunt</b></a><b>.</b><span style="font-weight: 400"> This engaging activity features three treasure zones, each with its enticing prize pool.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">For 3 hours, traders can win a 10 USDT prize, while a 0.1 ETH prize awaits winners over four days. The pinnacle of the hunt is the </span><b>0.1 BTC prize</b><span style="font-weight: 400">, awarded every eight days.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">To add even more excitement, during the WSOT campaign, from </span><b>July 13 to August 27, 2023</b><span style="font-weight: 400">, participants who continuously engage in the 1 USDT Treasure Hunt at least 50 times without winning any rewards will receive a full refund of their entry fees. The refunded amount will be promptly credited to your assets within ten business days after the conclusion of this unique campaign.&nbsp;</span></p>
<h3><span style="font-weight: 400">Race Guessing Campaign | Featuring the F2 Ferrari Driver&nbsp;</span></h3>
<figure id="attachment_147155" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-147155" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-147155" src="https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Zoomex-X-WSOT-2023-2.png" alt="Zoomex X WSOT 2023 - 2" width="1053" height="360"><figcaption id="caption-attachment-147155" class="wp-caption-text">Zoomex X WSOT 2023 = 2</figcaption></figure>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">As a unique celebration of our partnership with Oliver Bearman, the F2 Ferrari driver, Zoomex has introduced the </span><a href="https://partner.zoomex.com/F2PR" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400">Race Guessing Campaign</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">. Predict Oliver Bearman&rsquo;s ranking in the F2 race, and stand a chance to win a share of the 10,000 bonus pool. Every participant is guaranteed a prize and will receive 200 treasure coupons. Join us in the exhilarating Race Prediction Challenge and seize the opportunity to win 0.1 BTC using treasure coupons.&nbsp;</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400">About Zoomex | The Most Trusted Partner for Trading Strategies</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Zoomex, a cryptocurrency trading platform established in 2021 in Singapore, has gained significant recognition in the industry. Zoomex holds US MSB License and Canada MSB License.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The primary goal of Zoomex is to offer a superior online cryptocurrency trading environment, catering to an expanding customer base and fostering a wise investment atmosphere.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">With an unwavering focus on customers, Zoomex aims to emerge as a cryptocurrency leader built on security, customer trust, and innovative thinking. Adapting to the swiftly evolving cryptocurrency market, they pride themselves on delivering top-notch online trading services while safeguarding our customers&rsquo; assets.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Currently, Zoomex ranks </span><b>31st on CoinMarketCap</b><span style="font-weight: 400">, attesting to its growing prominence. With a remarkable </span><b>trading volume of $1,683,023,181 </b><span style="font-weight: 400">within 24 hours, Zoomex demonstrates its ability to facilitate substantial transactions.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400">Stay in the Game, and Keep On Racing</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">To join the Zoomex community, you can access </span><a href="https://t.me/zoomex_com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400">the official Zoomex Telegram</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">. Also, you can visit the </span><a href="https://partner.zoomex.com/OfficialPR" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400">official website</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">, and by clicking </span><a href="https://partner.zoomex.com/OfficialPR" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400">here</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">, a </span><b>$30 bonus and coupon rewards</b><span style="font-weight: 400"> are waiting for you.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/zoomex-x-wsot-2023-unleash-your-trading-prowess-and-race-to-7-million-in-prizes/">Zoomex X WSOT 2023: Unleash Your Trading Prowess and Race to $7 Million in Prizes!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Neon EVM Launches on Solana Mainnet</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/neon-evm-launches-on-solana-mainnet/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ben Myers]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 14:54:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=147120</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>[PARIS] &#8211; July 17, 2023 &#8211; During ETHCC23, Neon EVM launched on the Solana Mainnet to help close the gap between the different programming, computing, and memory models of Ethereum and Solana, bringing a low-friction solution to allow EVM dApps to settle to Solana. The Neon EVM program is a smart contract on the Solana [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/neon-evm-launches-on-solana-mainnet/">Neon EVM Launches on Solana Mainnet</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>[PARIS] &ndash; July 17, 2023 &ndash;</b><span style="font-weight: 400"> During ETHCC23,</span><a href="https://neonevm.org/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"> <b>Neon EVM</b></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> launched on the Solana Mainnet to help close the gap between the different programming, computing, and memory models of Ethereum and Solana, bringing a low-friction solution to allow EVM dApps to settle to Solana.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The Neon EVM program is a smart contract on the Solana blockchain. It accepts wrapped Ethereum-like transactions and processes them on Solana.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Previously, when EVM dApps wanted to leverage low-cost solutions, they had to use a rollup or sidechain. By using Solana as the settlement layer, an EVM is well-placed to outcompete such L2 solutions. The average transaction fee for sending ETH on the Ethereum network is ~$2. The L2s offer between</span><a href="https://l2fees.info/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"> <span style="font-weight: 400">$0.5&ndash;$0.1</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">, a saving of 4&ndash;20 times. In comparison, Solana&rsquo;s average transaction fees are ~0.00001 SOL ($0.0002) per transaction, 10,000 times saving. Initial tests of Neon EVM in Devnet demonstrate that the protocol</span><a href="https://medium.com/neon-labs/neon-synthetic-load-test-report-d53212711556" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"> <span style="font-weight: 400">translates these optimizations in practice</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">&ldquo;We are very excited to see Neon EVM live on Solana Mainnet,&rdquo; says </span><b>Marina Guryeva, Director of Neon Foundation</b><span style="font-weight: 400">. &ldquo;Once we repeat these tests in production, we will present the figures based on real-world data.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">With the launch of Neon EVM on the Solana Mainnet, the Neon DAO is activated to begin participating in, and influencing the future development of, Neon EVM.</span></p>
<p><b>About Neon EVM</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Neon EVM is an Ethereum Virtual Machine operating as a smart contract on Solana. It gives developers the power to directly deploy Ethereum dApps with minimal reconfiguration to the code, while benefiting from Solana&rsquo;s technical advantages. It is built with security, decentralization, and sustainability as core tenants. For more information about Neon EVM and future updates, visit</span><a rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"> <span style="font-weight: 400">NeonEVM.org</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> and connect with the community on</span><a href="https://twitter.com/Neon_EVM" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"> <span style="font-weight: 400">Twitter</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> or</span><a href="https://discord.gg/neonevm" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"> <span style="font-weight: 400">Discord</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">&nbsp;</span><b>Links and resources:</b></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400">Find the Neon EVM community on</span><a href="https://twitter.com/Neon_EVM" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"> <span style="font-weight: 400">Twitter</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> or</span><a href="https://discord.gg/neonevm" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"> <span style="font-weight: 400">Discord</span></a></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400">To choose a public RPC endpoint, see</span><a href="https://chainlist.org/?chain=245022926&amp;testnets=true&amp;search=Neon+EVM" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"> <span style="font-weight: 400">ChainList</span></a></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400">For a high-level overview of the technical architecture and features of Neon EVM, the whitepaper is available at</span><a href="https://neonevm.org/whitepaper.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"> <span style="font-weight: 400">NeonEVM.org/whitepaper.pdf</span></a></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400">View Neon </span><span style="font-weight: 400">EVM</span><span style="font-weight: 400"> transactions settled to Solana with the</span><a href="https://neonscan.org" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"> <span style="font-weight: 400">NeonScan</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> or</span><a href="https://neon-mainnet.blockscout.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"> <span style="font-weight: 400">BlockScout</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> explorers.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400">IRL: Epic Layer 2 Day, an event for researchers, developers, and enthusiasts dedicated to Ethereum L2 Scaling, see:</span> <a href="https://lu.ma/l2paris" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"> <span style="font-weight: 400">lu.ma/l2paris</span></a></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">&nbsp;</span></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/neon-evm-launches-on-solana-mainnet/">Neon EVM Launches on Solana Mainnet</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto price prediction: XDC Network, Polkadot, dYdX</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-xdc-network-polkadot-dydx/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-xdc-network-polkadot-dydx/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 12:02:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polkadot News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-xdc-network-polkadot-dydx/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrencies remained in a tight range this week as Bitcoin continued to ping pong around the $30,000 support level. The crypto fear and greed index consolidated at the neutral point at 52 while volumes remained low. This article will provide predictions of some of the top performers during the week, including XDC Network, Polkadot, and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-xdc-network-polkadot-dydx/">Crypto price prediction: XDC Network, Polkadot, dYdX</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/cryptocurrencies/"><u>Cryptocurrencies</u></a> remained in a tight range this week as Bitcoin continued to ping pong around the $30,000 support level. The crypto fear and greed index consolidated at the neutral point at 52 while volumes remained low. This article will provide predictions of some of the top performers during the week, including XDC Network, Polkadot, and dYdX.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">XDC Network price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr">XDC Network is a small layer-1 and EVM-compatible network with enterprise grade features. It has higher transaction speeds and lower costs. Some of the players in its ecosystem are Copper, Vinter, Fireblocks, and Fluent, among others.</p>
<p dir="ltr">XDC Network price has been in the green in the past five straight days and is now hovering at the highest level since April 2022. At its peak, the token was up by more than 41% from the lowest level this month.</p>
<p dir="ltr">On the daily chart, the coin has moved above the 50-day and 25-day moving averages, which is a bullish sign. Most importantly, XDC is hovering at an important resistance point since this price was the highest level on June 1st. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) has moved to the overbought level.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, XDC network&rsquo;s rally will likely take a breather in the coming days. If this happens, the next level to watch will be at $0.035.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/21/1689940841076-a5213bf7-9c77-40f4-af89-b78d23005b52.jpg" style="width: 623px;height: 282.427px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="623" height="282.427"></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">DYDX price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The DYDX token price has done well in the past few days even as exchange volume has eased. This performance happened even as volume in the ecosystem dropped slightly. It also coincided with the strong performance of other DeFi tokens like&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/maker/"><u>Maker</u></a> and Compound.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The daily chart shows that the DYDX token rose from June&rsquo;s low of $1.3653 in June to $2.14. It has moved above the 50-day moving average while the Relative Strength Index (RSI) rose above the neutral point. Volume has been a bit low. Therefore, the token will likely remain in this range during the weekend.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/21/1689940841274-cbb68339-a1a3-45f3-b7fb-4444970d18ab.jpg" style="width: 627px;height: 282.562px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="627" height="282.562"></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Polkadot price forecast</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/polkadot"><u>Polkadot</u></a> has been in a tight range this week since there was no ecosystem news. It has remained above the support at $5.15, the important support point at $5.15, the lowest level on March 10th.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Polkadot price has also remained slightly above the 50-day moving average while the Relative Strength Index (RSI) has moved above the neutral at 50. It is a few points below the support at $5.72, the highest point last week.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, the outlook for the coin is neutral, with the next level to watch being at $5.72. A move above that level in a high-volume environment will confirm a bullish breakout.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/21/1689940840751-711c7f7e-93be-45db-befe-9c897fe8b8bc.jpg" style="width: 668px;height: 302.314px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="668" height="302.314"></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy Polkadot</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>

    <p>eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=MTQ3MTE3&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy DOT with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    OKX</h3>

    <p>OKX is a world-leading cryptocurrency exchange, providing advanced financial services to traders globally by using blockchain technology.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/okx-crypto?guid=MTQ3MTE3&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy DOT with OKX today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Trading in digital assets is considered high risk. Digital assets are NOT backed by any government or central bank. The risk of loss in trading or holding digital assets can be substantial. You should carefully consider whether interacting, holding, or trading digital assets is suitable for you in light of your financial condition." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-xdc-network-polkadot-dydx/">Crypto price prediction: XDC Network, Polkadot, dYdX</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-xdc-network-polkadot-dydx/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Countdown to the 2nd phase of the Chancer presale amid strong demand for token</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/countdown-to-the-2nd-phase-of-the-chancer-presale-amid-strong-demand-for-token/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/countdown-to-the-2nd-phase-of-the-chancer-presale-amid-strong-demand-for-token/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Motiur Rahman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 10:53:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technical Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/countdown-to-the-2nd-phase-of-the-chancer-presale-amid-strong-demand-for-token/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Chancer presale has seen strong demand as investors bet on blockchain-based betting. Less than 10% of Chancer tokens remain before the first stage presale concludes. The value of Chancer could rise strongly after listing on Uniswap in Q3 2023 and after the mainnet launch in early 2024. Chancer, a blockchain-based predictive markets application, opened the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/countdown-to-the-2nd-phase-of-the-chancer-presale-amid-strong-demand-for-token/">Countdown to the 2nd phase of the Chancer presale amid strong demand for token</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Chancer presale has seen strong demand as investors bet on blockchain-based betting.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Less than 10% of Chancer tokens remain before the first stage presale concludes.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The value of Chancer could rise strongly after listing on Uniswap in Q3 2023 and after the mainnet launch in early 2024.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer, a blockchain-based predictive markets application, opened the presale on June 13th, 2023. Five weeks later, investors bought almost $905,000 in tokens in the first phase. The amount suggests that Chancer is imminently sold out at the current price of $0.01 since the first stage targets $1 million. Investors seeking to buy the token can do so via the company&rsquo;s&nbsp;<a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>website</u></a> before the price rises in the second stage.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Why is Chancer in high demand?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Raising funds quickly through a presale suggests investors see value in Chancer. So, what does the token offer?</p>
<p dir="ltr">$CHANCER is the native token that will power a blockchain-enabled platform Chancer. It is the world&rsquo;s first blockchain betting platform that allows users to bet against each other through a peer-to-peer (P2P) model.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The opportunity lies in tapping into the fast-growing online gambling and bringing it to blockchain. According to&nbsp;<a href="https://www.acumenresearchandconsulting.com/online-gambling-market" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>market reports</u></a>, online gambling will grow by 11.6% CAGR in this decade to hit $172 billion by 2030. Investors are betting on Chancer to revolutionise betting, given the growing application of blockchain in several other sectors.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>What is the value proposition of Chancer and its P2P model?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer carries a value proposition in that it lets users bet on numerous events, outcomes, and situations. This happens as users create their own Chancer P2P markets and determine what to predict in those markets. They can then invite friends or join Chancer markets created by others.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The exciting bit of P2P betting is that it allows flexibility. Users can bet on their preferred events, replacing the existing model where the bookmaker creates betting markets. Users can also determine the rules and odds for each bet via Chancer.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Besides rewards on successful bets, Chancer lets users earn from market-making activities or creating P2P markets. That makes Chancer more than just a betting platform. The Chancer token can also be staked, allowing investors to earn passive incomes and improve their bottom lines.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Chancer roadmap and predictions in 2023, 2024</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer is in the presale phase, but the demand for the project is already high. While the value of Chancer is increasing at each presale phase, the potential value of the token will be unlocked in the third and fourth quarters of 2023. This is when the token will be listed on exchanges. The token&rsquo;s roadmap points to the first listing on Uniswap in the third quarter. The team eyes at least two CEX listings in Q3.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">In the fourth quarter, product development will begin. It will start with the testnet, aiming to pave the way for the full mainnet launch in the first quarter of 2024.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The launch of the mainnet will be influential for Chancer as it actualizes the dream of bringing forth P2P betting. While our prediction is that the value of the Chancer token could start to rise in the third quarter of 2023, 2024 will be the most influential. This is when sustainable gains could be realised, allowing Chancer to go mainstream and become more acceptable.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">With the above roadmap, the value of Chancer could rise initially by double or triple-digit percentages in 2023. In 2024, the value could skyrocket by more than 10x heading into the future, where Chancer&rsquo;s future acceptance will allow more gains.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Should you buy Chancer this week?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Only 10% of Chancer tokens remain before the first stage of the presale concludes. After that, the price will increase by 10% in the second phase.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">With the demand for the token showing little signs of slowing down, chances are that the first phase will conclude in a few days. Thus, it could be the right time to grab the remaining tokens before the price increases to $0.011.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/countdown-to-the-2nd-phase-of-the-chancer-presale-amid-strong-demand-for-token/">Countdown to the 2nd phase of the Chancer presale amid strong demand for token</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/countdown-to-the-2nd-phase-of-the-chancer-presale-amid-strong-demand-for-token/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chancer underscores future of online betting with epic presale</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-underscores-future-of-online-betting-with-epic-presale/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 09:30:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-underscores-future-of-online-betting-with-epic-presale/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Chancer presale sees strong investor interest with over $835k raised just weeks into the token sale. Chancer could disrupt the online betting industry via a revolutionary P2P betting model. Early buyers of $CHANCER can now do so with ETH, USDT, BUSD and BNB. A recent&#160;report from K33 Research revealed that the global crypto industry currently [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-underscores-future-of-online-betting-with-epic-presale/">Chancer underscores future of online betting with epic presale</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Chancer presale sees strong investor interest with over $835k raised just weeks into the token sale.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Chancer could disrupt the online betting industry via a revolutionary P2P betting model.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Early buyers of $CHANCER can now do so with ETH, USDT, BUSD and BNB.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">A recent<a href="https://k33.com/research/articles/the-global-crypto-industry" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">&nbsp;<u>report</u></a> from K33 Research revealed that the global crypto industry currently stands at $180 billion.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Meanwhile, the global online betting and gambling market is worth over $60 billion. Growth projections for these sectors point to an average of 11% CAGR to 2030. It is a scenario that alludes to the unprecedented growth investors anticipate for both crypto and online betting.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Tucked in between and out to underscore this future is <a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Chancer</a>, one of the most exciting crypto project for the betting industry whose presale has seen incredible interest and investment.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Chancer&rsquo;s unique approach to the online betting</h2>
<p dir="ltr">According to its<a href="https://chancer.com/whitepaper.pdf">&nbsp;<u>whitepaper</u></a>, Chancer is building the &ldquo;<em>world&rsquo;s first decentralized social predictive markets platform</em>.&rdquo; The goal is to redefine the online betting market with a new peer-to-peer (P2P) model that puts control over market making into the hands of the user.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The project leverages blockchain technology to allow users be in charge of their markets, odds and rules &ndash; simply play your game at your own rules.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">No centralised power as is the case with current market where bookmaker have the biggest say in what bettors can access and how they do it. On Chancer, users can create a predictive market on any event, right from the local market&rsquo;s most mundane occurences, to the world&rsquo;s biggest sports and entertainment events.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer is also not just another betting platform &ndash; it is designed to grow into a robust community spanning the global market. Its core features of blockchain and <a href="https://coinjournal.net/cryptocurrencies/">cryptocurrency</a> support enhance the outlook of a project set to revolutionise the predictive markets space, likely attracting more and more users as all that is deficient with the traditional online betting platforms is essentially removed.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Powering Chancer&rsquo;s P2P betting model is its native token $CHANCER. Apart from handing control to the user, $CHANCER opens up the platform to true decentralisation. It also promises to democratise social betting with integration of bet sharing and livestreaming features.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">$CHANCER&rsquo;s blockbuster presale</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The crypto space currently has numerous token presales for projects looking to raise funds from prospective early backers. At any given time, these projects see varying degrees of success, including reaching targeted amounts to support roadmap milestones.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer&rsquo;s presale is proving to be one of the success stories already, less than six weeks into the event. After surpassing the $750k mark last week, the amount of $CHANCER sold has topped $835k and is poised to hit the landmark $1 million in record time.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The total supply for $CHANCER is 1.5 billion tokens, 65% of which will be available throughout the 12 stage presale phase. Investors can buy tokens using ETH, USDT, BUSD and BNB, the first two buy options recently added in a step that could see more people easily buy $CHANCER.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Buy $CHANCER <a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">here</a>.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Will $CHANCER price reach $1 in 2024?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">At present, the Chancer presale price is $0.01 and will jump to $0.011 in the next stage. The token&rsquo;s price at the end of the presale is set to be $0.021.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Crypto investors might view these prices as an ideal entry point, particularly for a project that&rsquo;s projected to take a big bite from a market expected to see significant growth all through to 2030.</p>
<p dir="ltr">With interest so high and crypto flying following Ripple&rsquo;s recent victory against the SEC, it&rsquo;s likely the token will sell out faster than anticipated. This even as investors eye a position in what could be the biggest investment opportunity of 2023.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As for price, its difficult to pinpoint future performance due to the factors that can be at play during given market scenarios. A confluence of factors could help catapult Chancer price higher, including a raging bull market fueled by approval for first US spot Bitcoin ETF, regulatory clarity and the mainnet launch.</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, while a token launching in a bull market phase &ndash; as $CHANCER is likely when it goes live in Q1, 2024 &ndash; opposite market conditions could hinder the would be price discovery. </p>
<p dir="ltr">Interested in buying $CHANCER? <a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Join the presale</a>.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-underscores-future-of-online-betting-with-epic-presale/">Chancer underscores future of online betting with epic presale</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
