<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 14:51:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>PayPal Reports Data Breach Information for Nearly 35,000 Accounts Worldwide</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-data-breach-35k-accounts/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-data-breach-35k-accounts/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 14:51:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cybersecurity News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FinTech News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[paypal]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=233391</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-data-breach-35k-accounts/">PayPal Reports Data Breach Information for Nearly 35,000 Accounts Worldwide</a></p>
<p>PayPal sent notifications to all the affected accounts asking them to change their passwords. PayPal said that there had been no breach in their systems. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-data-breach-35k-accounts/">PayPal Reports Data Breach Information for Nearly 35,000 Accounts Worldwide</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-data-breach-35k-accounts/">PayPal Reports Data Breach Information for Nearly 35,000 Accounts Worldwide</a></p>
<p>One of the world&#8217;s largest online payment services platforms <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">PayPal</a> faced a major breach of data last month between December 6 and December 8, 2022. As per reports, the hackers got away with the sensitive information of 34,942 accounts.</p>
<p>PayPal noted that the data included the Name, address, personal tax identification numbers, social security number, and date of birth, of the compromised accounts. The company has already started sending notifications to all the compromised accounts while blaming a credential-stuffing attack for the breach.</p>
<p>In a recent <a href="https://s3.documentcloud.org/documents/23578067/paypal-notice.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">notification</a> sent this Wednesday, PayPal noted:</p>
<blockquote><p>“On December 20, 2022, we confirmed that unauthorized parties were able to access your Paypal customer account using your login credentials”.</p></blockquote>
<p>After learning about the new data breach on December 8, PayPal stopped the unauthorized access and started an investigation immediately. PayPal quickly reset the passwords of the affected accounts and “implemented enhanced security controls” that would require the affected accounts to set up a new password.</p>
<p>“We have no information suggesting that any of your personal information was misused due to this incident or that there are any unauthorized transactions on your account. There is also no evidence that your login credentials were obtained from any PayPal systems,&#8221; noted PayPal.</p>
<h2>PayPal Claims No Breach In Systems</h2>
<p>As the hackers gained unauthorized access to user accounts and their valid credentials, PayPal said that there was no breach in their systems. It noted that there&#8217;s no evidence that suggests that the users&#8217; credentials were directly bought from them.</p>
<p>Instead, the hackers were able to access the accounts using credentials stuffing. This method involves trying several pairs of usernames and passwords sourced from data leaks, on various websites. Using bots, the list of credentials is inserted into their login portals of different services.</p>
<p>Users that use the same password for different online accounts are most-prone to becoming the victim of credential-stuffing attacks. As said, payments giant PayPal claims to have taken quick action in order to limit the hacker&#8217;s access to the platform and reset the passwords of the affected accounts. Besides, all the impacted users shall receive a two-year identity-monitoring service from Equifax for free.</p>
<p>PayPal also mentioned that the attackers didn&#8217;t manage to perform any transactions from the breached accounts. To prevent from becoming the victims of future hacks, users are advised to implement two-factor authentication (2FA) security features at their end.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nexo-sec-security-sales-45m-fines/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-data-breach-35k-accounts/">PayPal Reports Data Breach Information for Nearly 35,000 Accounts Worldwide</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-data-breach-35k-accounts/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Lender Nexo Charged by SEC Over Unregistered Security Sales, Will Pay $45M in Fines</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nexo-sec-security-sales-45m-fines/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nexo-sec-security-sales-45m-fines/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 14:48:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gary gensler]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nexo]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=233398</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nexo-sec-security-sales-45m-fines/">Crypto Lender Nexo Charged by SEC Over Unregistered Security Sales, Will Pay $45M in Fines</a></p>
<p>In addition to paying fines, Nexo will reportedly cease its unregistered lending product to all US investors. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nexo-sec-security-sales-45m-fines/">Crypto Lender Nexo Charged by SEC Over Unregistered Security Sales, Will Pay $45M in Fines</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nexo-sec-security-sales-45m-fines/">Crypto Lender Nexo Charged by SEC Over Unregistered Security Sales, Will Pay $45M in Fines</a></p>
<p>Crypto-lending firm Nexo has <a href="https://www.sec.gov/news/press-release/2023-11" target="_blank" rel="noopener">agreed to pay</a> fines of $45 million to the Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) for violating federal securities law. According to the regulatory agency, Nexo failed to register its crypto asset lending product. The SEC further stated that the crypto platform initiated this unregistered security in 2020, allowing US customers to earn.</p>
<p>Addressing the situation in a statement, SEC Chair Gary Gensler explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We charged Nexo with failing to register its retail crypto lending product before offering it to the public, bypassing essential disclosure requirements designed to protect investors. Compliance with our time-tested public policies isn&#8217;t a choice.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>In addition, Gensler suggested that the SEC would remain relentless in holding crypto-operating firms accountable. He concluded that Nexo would cease its unregistered lending product to all US investors.</p>
<p>The Director of the SEC&#8217;s Division of Enforcement, Gurbir S. Grewal, echoed some of Gensler&#8217;s statements. He also stressed that the SEC is after compliance with federal securities laws regardless of any pre-stated product &#8220;labels.&#8221; As the Division of Enforcement Director put it:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;If you&#8217;re offering or selling products that constitute securities under well-established laws and legal precedent, then no matter what you call those products, you&#8217;re subject to those laws, and we expect compliance.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>In other words, Grewal suggested that crypto assets pose the same economic realities as other assets that fall under federal securities laws.</p>
<h2>Nexo Agrees to Pay Fines Without Affirming or Denying SEC Allegations</h2>
<p>Nexo agreed to pay the fines without admitting any wrongdoing. The crypto lender will remit $22.5 million to the SEC and another $22.5 million penalty fee to state regulators. According to the SEC, the latter payment is in relation to the Earn Interest Product to US investors.</p>
<p>Nexo expressed contentment with the SEC resolution and looked forward to more structured oversight within the crypto industry. According to the crypto lender&#8217;s co-founder Kosta Kantchev, they &#8220;are confident that a clearer regulatory landscape will emerge soon, and companies like Nexo will be able to offer value-creating products in the United States in a compliant manner.&#8221;</p>
<p>Allaying the SEC&#8217;s grievances also sees Nexo &#8220;focus on what we do best&#8221; and develop &#8220;seamless financial solutions&#8221; for global audiences.</p>
<p>The Nexo-SEC penalty development comes amid increasing efforts by US regulators to crack down on infractions in the crypto space. These scrutiny efforts intensified following the sudden and dramatic collapse of crypto exchange <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a> last November.</p>
<p>Other <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-genesis-gemini-securities/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">similar SEC-driven crackdowns</a> include lawsuits against <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/gemini/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Gemini Trust Company LLC</a> and Genesis Global Capital LLC. According to the securities regulator, both crypto-centric platforms also illegally sold products to countless investors via their crypto lending program.</p>
<h2>Bulgarian Development</h2>
<p>Nexo is also butting heads with authorities elsewhere amid its recently-concluded SEC case. According to a <a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/four-accused-bulgarian-probe-crypto-lender-nexo-investigators-2023-01-13/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Reuters report</a>, Bulgarian authorities charged four people as part of an ongoing investigation into the crypto lender. On January 12th, these authorities <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nexo-money-laundering-probe/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">raided</a> more than 15 Nexo sites for a string of reported financial crimes.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alphabet-layoff-12000-employees/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nexo-sec-security-sales-45m-fines/">Crypto Lender Nexo Charged by SEC Over Unregistered Security Sales, Will Pay $45M in Fines</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nexo-sec-security-sales-45m-fines/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alphabet Reportedly Set to Layoff 12,000 Employees</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/alphabet-layoff-12000-employees/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/alphabet-layoff-12000-employees/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 13:09:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alphabet inc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Meta]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meta platforms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[microsoft]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=233381</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alphabet-layoff-12000-employees/">Alphabet Reportedly Set to Layoff 12,000 Employees</a></p>
<p>The layoff will affect every aspect of its business operation and teams from corporate services, recruitment, and engineering are affected.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alphabet-layoff-12000-employees/">Alphabet Reportedly Set to Layoff 12,000 Employees</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alphabet-layoff-12000-employees/">Alphabet Reportedly Set to Layoff 12,000 Employees</a></p>
<p>American multinational technology company <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/alphabet-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Alphabet Inc</a> (NASDAQ: GOOGL) may be crumbling under the weight of its own staff size and is considering a 12,000 workers layoff. As <a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/google-parent-lay-off-12000-workers-memo-2023-01-20/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reported</a> by Reuters, citing a company’s memo it reviewed, the layoff will cut across its global operations, however, the impact will be immediately felt in the United States.</p>
<p>The retrenchment will represent some 6% of the company’s workforce and Chief Executive Officer <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/sundar-pichai/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Sundar Pichai</a> said he takes full responsibility for the decisions that lead the company to its current state. According to the CEO, Alphabet Inc had gone on a hiring spree in preparation &#8220;for a different economic reality than the one we face today.&#8221;</p>
<p>The global economy was tested remarkably throughout 2022 as the lingering effect of the coronavirus pandemic was further compounded by the outbreak of a war between the duo of Russia and Ukraine. The war has lasted for more than 10 months and its impact on the global supply chain has been quite massive.</p>
<p>The broader sentiment in the tech sector affected Alphabet’s share price and general business outlook as the expenditure on advertising was significantly slashed by firms across the board. The culmination of these economic realities comes off as what is fueling its decision to let some of its staff go.</p>
<p>The layoff will affect every aspect of its business operation and teams from corporate services, recruitment, and engineering are affected. Alphabet said the impact of the layoff may be slower in other countries due to local labor laws.</p>
<p>Despite the outlook of the layoff, Pichai rained accolades on the company’s investments in Artificial Intelligence (AI).</p>
<p>&#8220;I am confident about the huge opportunity in front of us thanks to the strength of our mission, the value of our products and services, and our early investments in AI,&#8221; He said in the note.</p>
<h2>Alphabet Layoff: a Trend among Tech Giants</h2>
<p>That the Google parent company is laying off its workforce is not coming as a surprise as other major tech giants including <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/meta/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Meta Platforms Inc</a> (NASDAQ: META), <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/amazon/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Amazon.com Inc</a> (NASDAQ: AMZN), and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/microsoft-corporation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Microsoft Corporation</a> (NASDAQ: MSFT) amongst others have also trailed this path.</p>
<p>Meta started the bold move last year in November when it announced it will be laying off 11,000 or 13% of its global staff at the time. The Meta blow was complimented when Amazon said it will ax 18,000 of its workers in what became apparent that the tech sector was battered beyond normal.</p>
<p>Microsoft is also planning a 10,000-staff cut <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/01/18/apple-had-slower-headcount-growth-than-tech-peers-no-layoffs-yet.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">leaving</a> only <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/apple-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Apple Inc</a> (NASDAQ: AAPL) as the only tech giant that is yet to announce plans to send some of its workers away.</p>
<p>The tech workers&#8217; layoff justifies the strain that crypto companies like <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase Global Inc</a> (NASDAQ: COIN) and Gemini faced when they announced their own job cuts earlier in 2022.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ericsson-q4-2022-earnings/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alphabet-layoff-12000-employees/">Alphabet Reportedly Set to Layoff 12,000 Employees</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/alphabet-layoff-12000-employees/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ericsson Q4 2022 Earnings Report Sees Income Slide on Waning 5G Equipment Sales in Key Markets</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ericsson-q4-2022-earnings/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ericsson-q4-2022-earnings/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 12:32:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ericsson]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=233379</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ericsson-q4-2022-earnings/">Ericsson Q4 2022 Earnings Report Sees Income Slide on Waning 5G Equipment Sales in Key Markets</a></p>
<p>Swedish telecoms giant Ericsson says despite its poor Q4 2022 earnings, it sees significant patent revenue growth in the next 24 months. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ericsson-q4-2022-earnings/">Ericsson Q4 2022 Earnings Report Sees Income Slide on Waning 5G Equipment Sales in Key Markets</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ericsson-q4-2022-earnings/">Ericsson Q4 2022 Earnings Report Sees Income Slide on Waning 5G Equipment Sales in Key Markets</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ericsson/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ericsson</a> recently reported a larger-than-anticipated decline in its <a href="https://www.ericsson.com/en/press-releases/2023/1/ericsson-reports-fourth-quarter-and-full-year-results-2022" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Q4 2022 earnings statement</a>. The Swedish telecommunications giant said its underwhelming fourth-quarter earnings are due to a slowdown in sales of 5G equipment in high-margin markets. The pullback in spending on 5G networks by some customers, most notably in the US, saw Ericsson shares decline to a four-year low. Furthermore, the multinational networking and telecommunications company&#8217;s latest report comes amid an uncertain economic environment. Global tech stocks have experienced massive selloffs as customers exercise caution in the face of a looming recession.</p>
<p>Ericsson shares dipped 8% on Friday following news of its latest quarterly report. Furthermore, the company&#8217;s stock is now at a 50% drawdown since February last year.</p>
<p>According to Ericsson, its adjusted earnings before interest and taxes for Q4 2022 came in at 8.1 billion Swedish kronor ($785 million). This figure fell well below the consensus estimate of 10.74 billion kronor for the same period. Ericsson also reported a rise in net sales for the fourth quarter of last year. Net sales surged 21% to 86 billion crowns, surpassing the 84.2 billion crown estimate. However, the company&#8217;s margins, net income, and core earnings declined. Gross margin, in particular, for the period ended December 31st dropped from 43.2% to 41.4%. Ericsson&#8217;s Q4 adjusted operating earnings, minus restructuring charges, fell to 9.3 billion Swedish crowns from 12.8 billion a year earlier. This development also represented a significant drawdown from the 11.22 billion analysts expected for the same period.</p>
<h2>Ericsson Foresaw Weak Q4 2022 Report Looks to Deploy Cost-Saving Measures</h2>
<p>Ericsson foresees its core 2023 first-quarter earnings being lower year-over-year (YoY) than last year&#8217;s. In addition, the Stockholm-based telecoms giant also forecasts lower margins on its networks business in the first six months of 2023. Furthermore, Ericsson explained in the earnings statement that cost-saving initiatives would come into effect in the year&#8217;s second quarter. Elaborating further on its operational development for 2023, Ericsson chief executive officer Borje Ekholm said:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;There are near-term uncertainties, however, we are still in the early phase of global 5G rollout and widespread enterprise digitalization.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Ericsson previously indicated plans to reduce its costs by 9 billion crowns ($880 million) by the end of 2023. According to chief financial officer Carl Mellander, such an agenda would entail cutting down on consultants, real estate, and staff headcount. Also commenting further on the projected cuts, Mellander added:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;It&#8217;s different from geography to geography, some are starting now, and we&#8217;ll take it unit by unit, considering the labor laws of different countries.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Despite Ericsson&#8217;s demonstrated clear outlook regarding cost-cutting measures, the company&#8217;s CFO declined to add any perspectivism. Mellander did not state whether the projected headcount downsizing would be similar to 2017, when Ericsson axed thousands of workers. When the company took such drastic measures, it sought to return its bottom line to a profitable state.</p>
<p>As it stands, Ericsson expects significant patent revenue growth across the coming 18-24 months.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cameron-winklevoss-lawsuit-genesis/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ericsson-q4-2022-earnings/">Ericsson Q4 2022 Earnings Report Sees Income Slide on Waning 5G Equipment Sales in Key Markets</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ericsson-q4-2022-earnings/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cameron Winklevoss Threatens Lawsuit after Genesis Filed for Bankruptcy</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/cameron-winklevoss-lawsuit-genesis/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/cameron-winklevoss-lawsuit-genesis/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 11:34:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cameron winklevoss]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dcg]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gemini]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[genesis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tyler winklevoss]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=233341</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cameron-winklevoss-lawsuit-genesis/">Cameron Winklevoss Threatens Lawsuit after Genesis Filed for Bankruptcy</a></p>
<p>Winklevoss said this move will afford the firm to recoup its funds as the Barry Silbert-led  DCG has continued to refuse to offer its creditors a fair deal.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cameron-winklevoss-lawsuit-genesis/">Cameron Winklevoss Threatens Lawsuit after Genesis Filed for Bankruptcy</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cameron-winklevoss-lawsuit-genesis/">Cameron Winklevoss Threatens Lawsuit after Genesis Filed for Bankruptcy</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/cameron-winklevoss/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Cameron Winklevoss</a>, the co-founder and Chief Executive Officer (CEO) of the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/gemini/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Gemini</a> trading platform has <a href="https://twitter.com/cameron/status/1616302998736756737" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">threatened</a> to sue Genesis Global and its parent company, the Digital Currency Group. Cameron took to Twitter to share the update following the bankruptcy filing lodged by Genesis involving two of its other subsidiaries.</p>
<p>Cameron has been very vocal on social media about the complacency of Genesis and the Digital Currency Group, owned by Barry Silbert with regard to settling Gemini Earn customers. On more than one occasion, Cameron, who co-owns the Gemini exchange with his twin, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/tyler-winklevoss/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tyler Winklevoss</a> has <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cameron-winklevoss-accuses-barry-silbert/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">claimed</a> Silbert and Genesis are using stall tactics to avoid paying the $900 million owed to its Earn customers.</p>
<p>The Gemini Earn program pays out a reward to users who subscribe to the product. Unfortunately, the Earn customers could not gain access to their funds as Genesis closed withdrawals following the implosion of the FTX Derivatives Exchange back in November last year. With the gloominess surrounding the future of the product, Gemini has <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gemini-ends-earn-program-genesis/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">closed its Earn program</a> to all clients.</p>
<p>According to Cameron, the bankruptcy filing has been tagged a good one for Gemini Earn customers. He said this move will afford the firm to recoup its funds as the Barry Silbert-led  DCG has continued to refuse to offer its creditors a fair deal.</p>
<p>“The good news is that, by seeking the protection of the bankruptcy court, Genesis will be subject to judicial oversight and be required to provide discovery into the machinations that brought us to this point,” Cameron said in the tweet, adding that “the decision to put Genesis into bankruptcy does not insulate Barry, DCG, and any other wrongdoers from accountability.”</p>
<h2>Lawsuit against Genesis Inevitable, Cameron Insists</h2>
<p>The Gemini executive said despite the chances it has to recoup its Earn funds via the bankruptcy proceedings, he will still not hesitate to sue all parties involved if Silbert and DCG do not “come to their senses and make a fair offer to creditors.”</p>
<p>While the lawsuit option is very much on the table, Cameron said the firm will use every tool available in its power in the bankruptcy court to “maximize recovery for Earn users and any other parties within the bankruptcy court’s jurisdiction.”</p>
<p>As <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/genesis-files-bankruptcy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a> earlier by Coinspeaker, Genesis Global said its credit and liabilities are within the $1 billion and $10 billion range and that it has as many as 100,000 creditors. Of the funds, $900 million belongs to more than 340,000 Gemini Earn customers, making the situation one of great concern for the crypto trading platform.</p>
<p>The bankruptcy filing of Genesis itself is a function of the aftermath of the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-exchange-files-for-bankruptcy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">implosion</a> of the FTX Derivatives Exchange. While the deep contagion may still have more firms it will impact, Cameron maintained that DCG and Barry Silbert also have serious explanations to give besides the repayment that creditors expect.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cardano-hoskinson-coindesk/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cameron-winklevoss-lawsuit-genesis/">Cameron Winklevoss Threatens Lawsuit after Genesis Filed for Bankruptcy</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/cameron-winklevoss-lawsuit-genesis/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano Co-Founder Hoskinson Considering Acquiring CoinDesk</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/cardano-hoskinson-coindesk/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/cardano-hoskinson-coindesk/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sanaa Sharma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 11:21:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[charles hoskinson]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coindesk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dcg]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[genesis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=233289</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cardano-hoskinson-coindesk/">Cardano Co-Founder Hoskinson Considering Acquiring CoinDesk</a></p>
<p>Hoskinson predicted that the purchase would cost him around two hundred million USD and that he will examine the financial details before taking concrete action.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cardano-hoskinson-coindesk/">Cardano Co-Founder Hoskinson Considering Acquiring CoinDesk</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cardano-hoskinson-coindesk/">Cardano Co-Founder Hoskinson Considering Acquiring CoinDesk</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/cardano/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Cardano</a> Co-founder Charles Hoskinson has <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-01-19/cardano-founder-expresses-interest-in-coindesk-crypto-service" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a> that he is mulling over acquiring CoinDesk, the media wing of the now-struggling Digital Currency Group. According to Hoskinson, the virtue of journalism needs to be rehabilitated on cryptocurrencies and blockchain. CoinDesk, on the other hand, is also contemplating the chances of a sale.</p>
<p>Hoskinson, in a Youtube live stream in the United States, said that his involvement with the media angle is intense. Cardano&#8217;s ADA cryptocurrency is one of the top ten assets, according to CoinMarketCap rankings, with a market capitalization of approximately $11.7 billion.</p>
<p>Hoskinson predicted that the purchase would cost him around two hundred million USD and that he will examine the financial details before taking concrete action. CoinDesk has also employed Lazard Ltd as a financial advisor to investigate options for a sale, according to the Wall Street Journal.</p>
<p>The Cardano founder went on to describe the biased treatment employed by the media in the past, arguing that a few particular shops would have a particular agenda to propagate. The crypto tycoon, who also leads the Cardano development firm Input Output, has proposed changing several news articles into <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NFTs</a>, eventually making it possible for people to communicate with each other. He suggests that it would be extremely interesting to present and watch every individual story as a living entity.</p>
<p>Hoskinson also suggests offering financial incentives to customers while the blockchain community could be a decentralized way of making crypto media more accountable. Moreover, financial incentives like these will contain Cardano&#8217;s impact over independent reporting, which will pull readers to persistently confirm, examine and interact with the reporting.</p>
<p>Genesis Global Capital, which is the crypto brokerage wing of Digital Currency Group, filed for bankruptcy last Thursday in New York following the collapse of the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a> which left the firm buried under debt.</p>
<p>Hoskinson, apparently, heard from sources that Coindesk for seeking money or trying desperately to get acquired by some other firms. This news comes after Barry Silbert&#8217;s Digital Currency Group, which is also the main unit, sunk into crypto trouble. Genesis filed for bankruptcy after suspending all withdrawals for users in mid-November.</p>
<p>Coindesk was initially acquired by DCG for around $500,000 back in January 2016. The website was previously inaugurated in 2013 when the cryptocurrency space was rather in its nascent stage.</p>
<p>On the topic of Coindesk hiring Lazard to weigh in on moves that would dissociate it from Barry Silbert&#8217;s Digital Currency Group, CEO Kevin Worth said that the company has received several inbound proposals of interest in CoinDesk.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/netflix-subscribers-q4-2022-ceo-steps-down/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cardano-hoskinson-coindesk/">Cardano Co-Founder Hoskinson Considering Acquiring CoinDesk</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/cardano-hoskinson-coindesk/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Netflix Overthrows Expectation on Subscribers in Q4, CEO Steps Down</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/netflix-subscribers-q4-2022-ceo-steps-down/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/netflix-subscribers-q4-2022-ceo-steps-down/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 11:17:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wall Street]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[netflix]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[netflix stock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nflx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nflx stock]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=233354</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/netflix-subscribers-q4-2022-ceo-steps-down/">Netflix Overthrows Expectation on Subscribers in Q4, CEO Steps Down</a></p>
<p>Co-founder Reed Hastings is stepping down as the CEO.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/netflix-subscribers-q4-2022-ceo-steps-down/">Netflix Overthrows Expectation on Subscribers in Q4, CEO Steps Down</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/netflix-subscribers-q4-2022-ceo-steps-down/">Netflix Overthrows Expectation on Subscribers in Q4, CEO Steps Down</a></p>
<p>Production company <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/netflix/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Netflix</a> (NASDAQ: NFLX) saw a massive addition to its subscribers in Q4, exceeding Wall Street&#8217;s expectations. According to the fourth quarter financial results, the company gained 7.66 million paid subscribers, over the predicted 4.57 million. The significant additional Netflix subscribers in Q4 increased the company&#8217;s shares by 6%. At the time of writing, the company&#8217;s stock is up 7.12% in after-hours trading to $338.27. NFLX has popped more than 7% since the year started and gained 9.05% in the last three months. Over the past month, the company has increased by 7.06%.</p>
<h2>Netflix Subscribers Spike</h2>
<p>Although Netflix surpassed analysts&#8217; expectations in its quarterly subscribers, the company missed its earnings. Its earnings per share (EPS) came in at 12 cents, nearly X4 less than the 45 cents prediction. This is the first time Netflix&#8217;s latest tier is added to its earnings result, the ad-supported service. <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/netflix-basic-with-ads-plan-month/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tagged &#8220;Basic with Ads</a>,&#8221; the new service rolled out in the US last year at $6.99 per month. Unlike all Netflix tiers, Basic with Ads subscribers are exposed to 15 to 30 seconds long commercials before and during their Netflix content.</p>
<p>Notably, Netflix did not specify the number of Basic with Ads users contributing to the new subscribers&#8217; growth. However, the company explained that it saw significant engagement from both new and regular service users. There was no notable record of users dialing down from the premium service to the ads-included tier. Chief financial officer Spencer Neumann <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/01/19/netflix-nflx-earnings-q4-2022.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">stated</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We wouldn&#8217;t be getting into this business if it couldn&#8217;t be a meaningful portion of our business. We&#8217;re over $30 billion in revenue, almost $32 billion revenue, in 2022 and we wouldn&#8217;t get into a business like this if we didn&#8217;t believe it could be bigger than at least 10% of our revenue.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>At the same time, co-founder Reed Hastings is stepping down as the CEO for co-CEO Ted Sarandos and COO Greg Peters to take over. As Hastings exits his role, he will now become the company&#8217;s executive chairman. He acknowledged that the new co-CEOs have been able to help Netflix through challenging times within the business.</p>
<p>The company added in a statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;2022 was a tough year, with a bumpy start but a brighter finish. We believe we have a clear path to reaccelerate our revenue growth: continuing to improve all aspects of Netflix, launching paid sharing and building our ads offering. As always, our north stars remain pleasing our members and building even greater profitability over time.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Read other <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/business/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">business news</a> on Coinspeaker.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/playtika-acquisition-rovio/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/netflix-subscribers-q4-2022-ceo-steps-down/">Netflix Overthrows Expectation on Subscribers in Q4, CEO Steps Down</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/netflix-subscribers-q4-2022-ceo-steps-down/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Israel-Based Game Developer Playtika Sends Acquisition Proposal to Angry Birds Creator Rovio</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/playtika-acquisition-rovio/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/playtika-acquisition-rovio/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Darya Rudz]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 11:12:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Deals News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gaming News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[playtika]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[playtika rovio]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[playtika rovio acquisition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[rove angry birds]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[rovio]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=233266</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/playtika-acquisition-rovio/">Israel-Based Game Developer Playtika Sends Acquisition Proposal to Angry Birds Creator Rovio</a></p>
<p>This is the second offer made by Playtika to Rovio. No agreements have been made between the companies, and there is no assurance that any transaction will materialize or eventually be completed.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/playtika-acquisition-rovio/">Israel-Based Game Developer Playtika Sends Acquisition Proposal to Angry Birds Creator Rovio</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/playtika-acquisition-rovio/">Israel-Based Game Developer Playtika Sends Acquisition Proposal to Angry Birds Creator Rovio</a></p>
<p>Israel-based mobile games developer Playtika Holding Corp (NASDAQ: PLTK) has sent a proposal to buy Finnish video game developer Rovio Entertainment Corporation (HEL: ROVIO). The price of the acquisition deal would be as much as 683 million euros ($737.50 million), or 9.05 euros per share, paid in cash.</p>
<h2>Playtika Interested in Acquiring Rovio</h2>
<p>Notably, this is the second acquisition offer from Playtika to Rovio. On November 16, 2022, Rovio submitted an 8.50 euros per share proposal to the Rovio Board of Directors. Now, the new offer values each share of Rovio at 9.05 euros, or about 60% higher than the company&#8217;s closing price on January 19.</p>
<p>Apparently, Playtika is extremely interested in acquiring Rovio company which is best known for the Angry Birds franchise.</p>
<p>Playtika CEO Robert Antokol commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We firmly believe the combination of Rovio’s renowned IP and scale of its user base, together with our best-in-class monetization and game operations capabilities, will create tremendous value for our shareholders.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>In September 2017, Rovio went public via an <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-initial-public-offering-ipo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">initial public offering</a> (IPO) on the main list of NASDAQ’s Helsinki stock exchange, which valued the company at $1 billion. However, the company is now trading 50% below its public offering price. To improve its results, Rovio announced it had 10 new games in development last year. However, it is still having some setbacks. Therefore, the deal with Playtika could revitalize its business.</p>
<p>No agreements have been made between the companies, and Playtika&#8217;s <a href="https://playtika.gcs-web.com/news-releases/news-release-details/playtika-announces-premium-all-cash-proposal-acquire-rovio" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">press release</a> mentions that &#8216;there is no assurance that any transaction will materialize or eventually be completed.&#8217; Rovio declined to comment.</p>
<h2>About Playtika</h2>
<p>Playtika is an Israel-based digital entertainment company that focuses on the development and publication of mobile games. Founded in 2010, Playtika was among the first to offer free-to-play social games on social networks and, shortly after, on mobile platforms.</p>
<p>Currently, the company is under a restructuring process. In December, Playtika <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/playtika-15-layoff-workforce/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">confirmed</a> a 15% layoff of its entire workforce or 610 employees across Europe, Israel, and the US. Besides, it is closing some of its studios, including the Helsinki-based team Seriously, as a result of a global economic slowdown. As many as three games have been also shut, including strategy battler &#8220;Merge Stories&#8221;, farming sim &#8220;Dice Life&#8221;, and hidden object title &#8220;Ghost Detective&#8221;.</p>
<p>Last year, Playtika shared lost half in value. When it went public in 2021, its valuation totaled over $11 billion at a per-share price of $27. However, in the summer of 2022, its market cap was standing at $3.1 billion, with a share price of just around $8.61.</p>
<p>In 2022, Playtika was actively looking for a merger. It appointed financial advisor The Raine Group and law firm Latham &amp; Watkins to pursue &#8220;a full range of strategic alternatives&#8221; which could include a sale or a merger. It almost got a deal with Joffre Capital, but the latter pulled out of the agreement citing management issues.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/procter-gamble-fiscal-q2-2023/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/playtika-acquisition-rovio/">Israel-Based Game Developer Playtika Sends Acquisition Proposal to Angry Birds Creator Rovio</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/playtika-acquisition-rovio/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Procter &amp; Gamble Reveals Underwhelming Revenue Impacted by Higher Product Prices in Fiscal Q2 2023 Statement</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/procter-gamble-fiscal-q2-2023/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/procter-gamble-fiscal-q2-2023/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 11:05:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wall Street]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pg]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[procter gamble]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=233303</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/procter-gamble-fiscal-q2-2023/">Procter &#038; Gamble Reveals Underwhelming Revenue Impacted by Higher Product Prices in Fiscal Q2 2023 Statement</a></p>
<p>Consumer goods heavyweight Procter &#038; Gamble saw its fiscal Q2 2023 earnings slip but maintained a higher organic fiscal sales growth. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/procter-gamble-fiscal-q2-2023/">Procter &#038; Gamble Reveals Underwhelming Revenue Impacted by Higher Product Prices in Fiscal Q2 2023 Statement</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/procter-gamble-fiscal-q2-2023/">Procter &#038; Gamble Reveals Underwhelming Revenue Impacted by Higher Product Prices in Fiscal Q2 2023 Statement</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/procter-and-gamble/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Procter &amp; Gamble</a> (NYSE: PG) recently reported declining revenue and profit in its fiscal Q2 2023 <a href="https://www.pginvestor.com/financial-reporting/press-releases/news-details/2023/PG-Announces-Fiscal-Year-2023-Second-Quarter-Results/default.aspx" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">earnings statement</a>. On Thursday, the American multinational consumer goods corporation reported total revenue of $20.77 billion. This figure came slightly lower than the consensus estimates of $20.73 billion in P&amp;G&#8217;s fiscal second quarter. The company also realized adjusted earnings per share of $1.59, which is on par with analysts&#8217; expectations. A year earlier, P&amp;G gained $1.66 in adjusted earnings per share.</p>
<p>The latest Procter &amp; Gamble fiscal Q2 2023 earnings report also saw the consumer goods giant rake in a net income of $3.9 billion, excluding items. This is less than the $4.22 billion the company made in the fiscal second quarter of last year.</p>
<h2>Higher Costs Drive Down Sales Volumes</h2>
<p>P&amp;G&#8217;s latest year-over-year (YoY) decline in earnings comes as the organization hoped to rely on higher prices to offset declining sales. However, this strategy turned out differently than expected, with P&amp;G&#8217;s reported December 10% product price increase cutting sales volumes instead. P&amp;G&#8217;s sales volumes slumped 6%, the most significant quarterly drop in years. In addition, the leading consumer goods company also experienced substantial foreign exchange headwinds for the given period.</p>
<p>All of Procter &amp; Gamble&#8217;s divisions reported waning sales volumes in the 2023 fiscal second quarter. This unsavory development came about despite experiencing increases in organic sales due to the higher pricing.</p>
<p>Despite fiscal Q2&#8217;s gloomy sales volume, P&amp;G slightly raised its outlook for organic fiscal 2023 sales growth to between 4% and 5%. This range previously stood at 3% to 5%.</p>
<h2>Procter &amp; Gamble Executives Reflect on Company Approach Following Fiscal Q2 2023 Results</h2>
<p>Procter &amp; Gamble&#8217;s chief executive officer, Jon Moeller, believes that against all odds, the company &#8220;delivered solid results in the second quarter of the fiscal year 2023 in what continues to be a very difficult cost and operating environment.&#8221; In addition, Moeller suggested that P&amp;G continues to take a grounded approach to all its operational decisions for 2023. As he put it:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The world seems to want everything to be better, as do I. That&#8217;s really not the reality&#8230; It&#8217;s not the time to be taking guidance to the top range of possibility.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>P&amp;G finance chief Andre Schulten also echoed some of Moeller&#8217;s sentiments, explaining that the company remains on track. Schulten touched on the company&#8217;s sales volume declines, revealing that P&amp;G had anticipated the drop. Furthermore, he explained that half of this decline was due to a combination of factors. These factors include P&amp;G halting sales of most items in Russia and retailer inventory cutbacks in the US, Europe, and China.</p>
<p>P&amp;G executives maintain their goal of performing a few percentage points better than the market. In addition, Schulten said that shoppers remain willing to pay more for high-end items. He further stated that a significant number of shoppers also seek out deals, and demand is up for both small and large products. According to Schulten, people do not stop doing their laundry or washing their hair.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/moonpay-web3-nightshift/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/procter-gamble-fiscal-q2-2023/">Procter &#038; Gamble Reveals Underwhelming Revenue Impacted by Higher Product Prices in Fiscal Q2 2023 Statement</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/procter-gamble-fiscal-q2-2023/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Infrastructure Firm MoonPay Acquires Web3 Creative Agency Nightshift</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/moonpay-web3-nightshift/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/moonpay-web3-nightshift/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 10:51:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Deals News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[moonpay]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nightshift]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=233267</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/moonpay-web3-nightshift/">Crypto Infrastructure Firm MoonPay Acquires Web3 Creative Agency Nightshift</a></p>
<p>This partnership will allow MoonPay to expand the shared expertise and provide an easy gateway for brands to enter Web3. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/moonpay-web3-nightshift/">Crypto Infrastructure Firm MoonPay Acquires Web3 Creative Agency Nightshift</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/moonpay-web3-nightshift/">Crypto Infrastructure Firm MoonPay Acquires Web3 Creative Agency Nightshift</a></p>
<p>On Thursday, January 19, crypto infrastructure firm MoonPay announced its first acquisition while scooping up Web3 creative studio Nightshift. The latest acquisition will help MoonPay expand its footprint and services in the world of Web3.</p>
<h2>MoonPay and Nightshift</h2>
<p>The details of the acquisition amount, however, remain undisclosed. As part of the acquisition, MoonPay will rebrand Nightshift to Otherlife. As Nightshift, the company handled creatives for Web3 native clients such as Adam Bomb Squad, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase</a>, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/opensea/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">OpenSea</a>, and others. Along with services in Web3, the agency has been offering design, branding and Web3 product strategy for big clients such as Shopify, Playboy, Arsenal Football Club, etc.</p>
<p>Initially, MoonPay started its journey as a fintech player allowing users to buy crypto products by using fiat currencies. Over the last year, MoonPay has been making a move in the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NFT</a> space. In June 2022, MoonPay launched Hypermint which allows brands to mint 100 million digital assets all at once. Speaking on the matter, MoonPay CEO Ivan Soto-Wright <a href="https://www.adweek.com/commerce/crypto-payments-startup-moonpay-buys-web3-agency-nightshift/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“With the addition of Otherlife, we can provide companies, brands, and creative agencies with world-class, end-to-end support to unlock new revenue through groundbreaking Web3-based products, experiences and ideas. I’ve been a great admirer of everything Perrow, Moodie and the team at Otherlife have created. And I’m excited about what we’ll build together.”</p></blockquote>
<p>“There was a big opportunity for us to come together and now be able to offer the end-to-end lifecycle support for big brands. Now we can go to any brand that has an idea or wants to enter Web3, and we can help them execute a full end-to-end strategy,” added he.</p>
<h2>What&#8217;s Next for MoonPay</h2>
<p>With the combined expertise of this new pairing, MoonPay will offer an easy gateway for legacy brands to venture into Web3. Throughout the last year, MoonPay has been rapidly expanding its suite of products to ensure that they provide an easy gateway for brands to expand into Web3.</p>
<p>Along with launching Hypermint, MoonPay partnered with entertainment giant Universal Pictures to unveil their NFT-based scavenger hunt for parkgoers at Universal Studios. Otherlife Creative Director and Co-Founder Michael Moodie <a href="https://nftnow.com/news/moonpay-expands-its-web3-offerings-with-nightshift-acquisition/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Reflecting our continued focus on innovation and creativity, Otherlife’s brand is a renewal of our commitment to providing cutting-edge creative solutions and our dedication to staying at the forefront of the web3 industry. We will continue to push the boundaries of what’s possible while staying true to our genesis values&#8221;.</p></blockquote>
<p>Read other <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/business/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">business news</a> on our website.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/digital-yuan-smart-contract-meituan/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/moonpay-web3-nightshift/">Crypto Infrastructure Firm MoonPay Acquires Web3 Creative Agency Nightshift</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/moonpay-web3-nightshift/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>