<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 08:03:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Microsoft Calls for Revised AI Regulation, Proposes Streamlined Five-Point Guidelines</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-ai-regulation/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-ai-regulation/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 08:03:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[microsoft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[openai]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sam altman]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=256558</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-ai-regulation/">Microsoft Calls for Revised AI Regulation, Proposes Streamlined Five-Point Guidelines</a></p>
<p>Yesterday, Microsoft VC and President Brad Smith called for a new supervisory agency and proposed guidelines for effective AI regulation.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-ai-regulation/">Microsoft Calls for Revised AI Regulation, Proposes Streamlined Five-Point Guidelines</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-ai-regulation/">Microsoft Calls for Revised AI Regulation, Proposes Streamlined Five-Point Guidelines</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/microsoft-corporation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Microsoft Corporation</a> (NASDAQ: MSFT) has joined the discussion on artificial intelligence (AI) regulation, calling for oversight from a new federal agency. In addition to a proposed supervisory fed agency, Microsoft also stressed the need for “safety brakes” and licensing to avoid pitfalls in the sector. Furthermore, the Washington-based company called for an executive order that approves new restrictions on how the US government deploys AI tools.</p>
<p>In a speech in Washington on Thursday, Microsoft President Brad Smith branded AI regulation the challenge of the 21st century. He also compared the emerging tech with the transformative eras of the printing press and elevators. With this comparison, he stressed the need for proper oversight to avoid potential harm. Before Congress members and civil society groups, Smith <a href="https://query.prod.cms.rt.microsoft.com/cms/api/am/binary/RW14Gtw" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">outlined</a> a <a href="https://blogs.microsoft.com/on-the-issues/2023/05/25/how-do-we-best-govern-ai/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">five-point agenda</a> for how governments, including the US, could address AI risks without stifling the tech’s transformative potential.</p>
<h2>Five-Point Agenda</h2>
<p>Smith’s five-point outline begins with implementing and building upon new government-led AI safety frameworks. The Microsoft Vice Chair and President opined that building on existing good ideas is the best route to success. The business executive further referenced the US National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST) framework as a credible foundation to build upon.</p>
<p>The next proposed step calls for “effective safety brakes for AI systems that control critical infrastructure”. Smith said these measures would ensure human oversight and accountability within the AI space as the technology becomes more powerful. He also stressed that the safety brakes could act as emergency tools to stop potentially hazardous incidents. As Smith put it:</p>
<blockquote><p>“These fail-safe systems would be part of a comprehensive approach to system safety that would keep effective human oversight, resilience, and robustness top of mind. In spirit, they would resemble the braking systems engineers have long built into other technologies such as elevators, school buses, and high-speed trains.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Smith’s third key point proposes developing a broad legal and regulatory framework based on AI’s technology architecture. This includes implementing various regulations and licensing that specifically cater to the “different actors” within the AI infrastructure ecosystem.</p>
<p>Smith also advocated for transparent, academic, and non-profit access to AI tools and resources. According to him, doing this would make the systems more responsible. Finally, the Microsoft executive suggested new public-private partnerships geared toward deploying AI to address accompanying societal challenges effectively. These include protecting democracy and rights and fostering all-inclusive growth.</p>
<h2>Microsoft President Fields Lawmakers’ Concerns Regarding AI Regulation</h2>
<p>In his hour-long appearance, Smith also fielded questions from the lawmaker attendees who voiced concerns. Smith said the reason could eventually prevail when asked about OpenAI CEO Sam Altman’s recent threat to pull products from Europe over compliance differences. When asked how Congress should balance regulation with innovation to overtake China, the Microsoft executive suggested Western governments work together to set a global AI regulatory standard.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-hire-15000-2023/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-ai-regulation/">Microsoft Calls for Revised AI Regulation, Proposes Streamlined Five-Point Guidelines</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-ai-regulation/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alibaba Rebuts Layoff Reports, Plans to Hire 15,000 People in 2023</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-hire-15000-2023/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-hire-15000-2023/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 08:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cloud Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alibaba]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alibaba cloud]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cainiao network technology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=256551</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-hire-15000-2023/">Alibaba Rebuts Layoff Reports, Plans to Hire 15,000 People in 2023</a></p>
<p>Amid reports of layoffs, Alibaba surprised the market by announcing plans to hire 15,000 people in 2023. It is pursuing a six-way split of its operations and preparing for the spinoff of Alibaba Cloud.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-hire-15000-2023/">Alibaba Rebuts Layoff Reports, Plans to Hire 15,000 People in 2023</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-hire-15000-2023/">Alibaba Rebuts Layoff Reports, Plans to Hire 15,000 People in 2023</a></p>
<p>Amid the uncertainty in the global jobs market and major job losses over the last few months, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/alibaba-group/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Alibaba</a> is taking a turn for the good. Amid reports that the Alibaba Group Holding is planning a fresh round of layoffs, the Chinese tech giant surprised everyone by announcing its plans to hire 15,000 people this year in 2023.</p>
<h2>Alibaba to Hire New People This Year</h2>
<p>On Thursday, May 25, the Chinese e-commerce giant released a statement on the social media platform Weibo stating that its “six major business divisions will need to hire 15,000 new recruits in total&#8221;. Additionally, the company <a href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/alibaba-hiring-15-000-people-pushes-back-on-job-cut-reports-1.1924868" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a> that it plans to recruit 3,000 university graduates. It also referred to the report of layoffs as &#8220;rumors&#8221; while adding that employee departures are part of the “normal flow”.</p>
<p>Earlier this week, reports emerged that Alibaba&#8217;s cloud division has started a round of job cuts that would reduce its staff by nearly 7%. Alibaba is providing severance packages and transfer opportunities within the company to its employees in the fast-growing cloud unit, as it prepares for the unit&#8217;s spinoff and future initial public offering.</p>
<p>Alibaba CEO Daniel Zhang has announced the restructuring of the company&#8217;s cloud division, revealing plans to completely divest control of Alibaba Cloud. Zhang believes that relinquishing control will unlock the potential of the cloud venture, enabling it to experience greater growth as an independent entity without any constraints imposed by Alibaba&#8217;s ownership.</p>
<p>Some analysts have valued Alibaba&#8217;s Cloud business to be above $30 billion. Amid the explosive popularity of AI platforms like ChatGPT, the cloud business sector seems primed for substantial growth. Also, ChatGPT&#8217;s tech relies largely on cloud-based resources to train next-gen artificial intelligence models.</p>
<h2>Alibaba Pursues Six-Way Split of Operations</h2>
<p>The Chinese e-commerce giant noted that it is pursuing a six-way split of its operations as it plans to adapt to slower growth amid the rising regulatory scrutiny in China&#8217;s technology industry. Alibaba Cloud, one of the prominent divisions, has decided to pursue independent fundraising and explore potential listings, along with the Cainiao logistics division and international commerce.</p>
<p>As per <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-logistics-ipo-2024/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reports</a> earlier this month, Cainiao Network Technology is also seeking an IPO by early 2024. The company is looking forward to raising between $1 billion and $2 billion. Cainiao has consistently achieved significant gains. The company, known for its software and data sharing with logistics firms, carriers, and warehouses, generated 42 billion yuan ($6.07 billion) in revenue during the nine months ending in December. This marked a 22% year-on-year increase and accounted for 6% of the Group&#8217;s total revenue during that period.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-sam-altman-115m-worldcoin-project/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-hire-15000-2023/">Alibaba Rebuts Layoff Reports, Plans to Hire 15,000 People in 2023</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-hire-15000-2023/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>OpenAI’s Sam Altman Secures $115M in Funding for Worldcoin Project</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-sam-altman-115m-worldcoin-project/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-sam-altman-115m-worldcoin-project/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 07:58:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investors News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[openai]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sam altman]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[toos for humanity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[worldcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[worldcoin project]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=256547</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-sam-altman-115m-worldcoin-project/">OpenAI&#8217;s Sam Altman Secures $115M in Funding for Worldcoin Project</a></p>
<p>Tools of Humanity, the company behind the Worldcoin project, said that the capital raised shall go towards boosting research, growth and other development efforts for the project. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-sam-altman-115m-worldcoin-project/">OpenAI&#8217;s Sam Altman Secures $115M in Funding for Worldcoin Project</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-sam-altman-115m-worldcoin-project/">OpenAI&#8217;s Sam Altman Secures $115M in Funding for Worldcoin Project</a></p>
<p>Sam Altman, the chief executive of has recently secured $115 million in fresh Series C funding for the Worldcoin project. Blockchain Capital led the recent funding round along with other investors such as <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/a16z/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">a16z</a>, Bain Capital Crypto, and Distributed Global.</p>
<p>Back in 2019, Sam Altman co-founded Worldcoin with the goal of offering digital ID to everyone on the planet. Worldcoin is a decentralized open-source protocol. The project uses a device to scan the iris to confirm user identity. After this, the users receive tokens for free &#8220;just for being a unique individual&#8221;.</p>
<p>The project is currently in the beta phase and is developed around the Worldcoin token. Also, the Worldcoin project is gaining fast traction while already attracting more than 2 million people.</p>
<p>Sam Altman said that the capital raised shall go towards boosting research, growth and other development efforts for the Worldcoin project. The project also has its first cryptocurrency wallet dubbed World App, which will be useful for the Worldcoin ecosystem.</p>
<p>Tools of Humanity, the company behind the Worldcoin project made the official announcement on Thursday, May 25. Alex Blania, the CEO and co-founder of Tools for Humanity said:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;As we embark on the age of AI, it is imperative that individuals are able to maintain personal privacy while proving their humanness. In doing so we can help ensure that everyone can realize the financial benefits that AI is poised to deliver&#8221;.</p></blockquote>
<p>Blania further added that the funding round signals the seriousness of the venture. “When we started talking about it three years ago, people really made jokes about us, like we read too many sci-fi books, and that’s now changed,” he said.</p>
<h2>Controversies around Worldcoin Project</h2>
<p>The Worldcoin Project has recently faced some criticism for perceived privacy risks. Back in 2021, former U.S. intelligence contractor Edward Snowden tweeted:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Don&#8217;t catalogue eyeballs.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Additionally, the project has faced other setbacks as well. Due to concerns over privacy and data, the Worldcoin Project had to halt operations in at least seven countries. There have also been reports that a black market has been spotted in Chinese social media and e-commerce platforms wherein sellers offered interested parties access to KYC verifications for World App.</p>
<p>Worldcoin has clarified the matter adding that there were many instances of such activities on online platforms. They assured that there&#8217;s no sensitive data ever accessed by unauthorized parties. Blockchain Capital general partner Spencer Bogart said that WorldCoin has been a widely misunderstood project. Bogart added World ID has a &#8220;unique opportunity to establish and scale a new privacy-preserving primitive&#8221;. this would allow any application to distinguish between humans and bots.</p>
<p>&#8220;With an ability to easily distinguish between machines and humans, we can improve the UX of the internet, enable myriad new features and applications, and help restore trust in digital communities (knowingly conversing with real humans instead of bot armies),&#8221; <a href="https://twitter.com/CremeDeLaCrypto/status/1661724483479281666" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">wrote</a> Bogart.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gap-shares-q1-2023-results/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-sam-altman-115m-worldcoin-project/">OpenAI&#8217;s Sam Altman Secures $115M in Funding for Worldcoin Project</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-sam-altman-115m-worldcoin-project/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>GPS Shares Gain 14% after Gap Reports Q1 2023 Results In-line with Analysts’ Expectations</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/gap-shares-q1-2023-results/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/gap-shares-q1-2023-results/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 07:35:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wall Street]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gap]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gap stock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gps stock]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=256548</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gap-shares-q1-2023-results/">GPS Shares Gain 14% after Gap Reports Q1 2023 Results In-line with Analysts’ Expectations</a></p>
<p>As Gap increased layoffs during the first quarter, online sales declined 9 percent YoY but accounted for about 37% of net sales.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gap-shares-q1-2023-results/">GPS Shares Gain 14% after Gap Reports Q1 2023 Results In-line with Analysts’ Expectations</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gap-shares-q1-2023-results/">GPS Shares Gain 14% after Gap Reports Q1 2023 Results In-line with Analysts’ Expectations</a></p>
<p>After starting the year with a bearish sentiment, Gap Inc (NYSE: GPS) &#8211; an American apparel company &#8211; saw its shares rise approximately 14 percent during Thursday’s after-market hours to trade around $8.44. The $2.79 billion valued company reported its first quarter earnings result on May 25, which was largely in line with analysts’ expectations. For Q1 2023 which ended on April 29, 2023, Gap reported revenue of $3.28 billion, whereas analysts surveyed by REFINITIV expected $3.29 billion.</p>
<p>As a result, the company posted an adjusted earnings per share of 1 cents while analysts surveyed by REFINITIV expected a loss of 16 cents during the quarter. Notably, the first quarter results marked the last days of Bob Martin, Executive Chairman and Gap Interim CEO, as the board of directors searches for a new head.</p>
<p>“The Gap Inc. Board of Directors and I have a deep appreciation for and confidence in the work that has taken hold under Bobby Martin and the Leadership Team, with results already showing progress, and more importantly, a collective focus on continued improvement still ahead. As we are engaged toward the appointment of a new Gap Inc. CEO to carry this work into the future, we look forward to the time when we will introduce this great company’s next leader &#8211; one who will bring passion, vision and an unwavering focus on the customer,” <a href="https://s24.q4cdn.com/508879282/files/doc_financials/2023/q1/1Q23-EPR-with-Tables-FINAL.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a> Mayo Shattuck, Gap’s Lead Independent Director.</p>
<h2>Closer Look at Gap Q1 2023 Results and Market Outlook</h2>
<p>The company announced that it closed the first quarter with 3,453 store locations in more than 40 global countries, out of which 2,601 are Gap operated. The company’s net sales declined approximately 6 percent during the first quarter compared to the same time last year. As the company focuses more on online sales, internet sales declined about 9 percent during the first quarter compared to the same time last year. Reportedly, online sales accounted for about 37 percent of the total sales during the first quarter.</p>
<p>Last month, the company announced it plans to send home another 1,800 employees, where 25 percent of headquarters staff will be affected. Earlier, the company had notified investors that only 500 employees would lose their jobs.</p>
<p>As for the specific brands, Gap reported that Old Navy posted net sales of about $1.8 billion, down 1 percent YoY. The GAP segment reported net sales of about $692 million, a decline of approximately 13 percent compared to the same time last year. The company’s Banana Republic posted net sales of about $432 million during the first quarter, down 10 percent YoY. The Athleta section posted net sales of about $321 million during the first quarter, down 11 percent YoY.</p>
<p>Read other <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/business/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">business news</a> on Coinspeaker.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/virgin-galactic-final-flight-test-space-travel/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gap-shares-q1-2023-results/">GPS Shares Gain 14% after Gap Reports Q1 2023 Results In-line with Analysts’ Expectations</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/gap-shares-q1-2023-results/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Virgin Galactic to Conduct Final Flight Test as It Eyes Full Space Travel Launch</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/virgin-galactic-final-flight-test-space-travel/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/virgin-galactic-final-flight-test-space-travel/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 15:55:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blue origin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[richard branson]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[spacex]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[unity 25]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[virgin galactic]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=256518</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/virgin-galactic-final-flight-test-space-travel/">Virgin Galactic to Conduct Final Flight Test as It Eyes Full Space Travel Launch</a></p>
<p>American spaceflight company Virgin Galactic has announced preparation for a highly anticipated milestone as it prepares to launch its first spaceflight in nearly two years.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/virgin-galactic-final-flight-test-space-travel/">Virgin Galactic to Conduct Final Flight Test as It Eyes Full Space Travel Launch</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/virgin-galactic-final-flight-test-space-travel/">Virgin Galactic to Conduct Final Flight Test as It Eyes Full Space Travel Launch</a></p>
<p>This crucial flight serves as the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/virgin-galactic/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Virgin Galactic Holdings</a>&#8216; (NYSE: SPCE) final test before the company begins flying commercial passengers, marking a significant step forward in the realization of its space tourism vision.</p>
<p>The mission called ‘Unity 25’ represents the company&#8217;s fifth space voyage and is expected to launch from Spaceport America in New Mexico. According to <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/25/virgin-galactic-unity-25-spaceflight-final-test-before-commercial-service.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reports</a>, six Virgin Galactic staffers will be traveling on this mission for a brief voyage to the edge of space.</p>
<p>Notably, VSS Unity will be piloted by Virgin Galactic’s Mike Masucci and CJ Sturckow, while carrier aircraft VMS Eve will be flown by Jameel Janjua and Nicola Pecile. Notably, the firm has 600 bookings for tickets for upcoming flights, priced between $200,000 and $250,000 each.</p>
<p>Unlike its previous mission, which <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/branson-space-virgin-galactic-flight/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">carried</a> founder <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/richard-branson/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Sir Richard Branson</a>, in July 2021, Virgin Galactic said it will not publicly broadcast the flight. Instead, the corporation intends to provide updates on Unity 25′s progress via social media platforms.</p>
<p>According to the details provided, the carrier aircraft VMS Eve is scheduled to take off at 10 a.m. ET. This significant flight will see the aircraft carrying Virgin Galactic&#8217;s VSS Unity spacecraft to an altitude of around 40,000 feet, before releasing the rocket-powered vehicle to continue its journey.</p>
<p>Once released from the carrier aircraft, the VSS Unity will ignite its engine, propelling itself further into the heavens. The aim of this flight is to surpass an altitude of 80 kilometers, which is the internationally recognized boundary of space in the United States.</p>
<p>At this altitude, passengers on board the VSS Unity will experience the incredible sensation of weightlessness and gaze upon the Earth from the awe-inspiring perspective of space. Depending on the results and data from Unity 25, the company hopes to fly its first commercial flight in &#8220;late June&#8221;.</p>
<p>By reaching the boundary of space, Virgin Galactic aims to push the boundaries of what is possible and inspire generations to come. This flight represents the culmination of years of meticulous planning, engineering advancements, and rigorous testing.</p>
<h2>Potential Impact of the Virgin Galactic Flight</h2>
<p>Virgin Galactic&#8217;s attempt to break through this barrier is both a show of its technological capabilities and a step toward its eventual aim of making space travel available to the general population. The lessons learned from these flights will be used to enhance and improve systems and processes, assuring the safety and comfort of future passengers.</p>
<p>The success of Virgin Galactic goes beyond tourism. The data and knowledge that will be gained during this flight will help to progress scientific research and technology. It will provide essential insights into the impacts of microgravity, spacecraft behavior, and prospective uses in a variety of sectors.</p>
<p>Furthermore, Virgin Galactic&#8217;s determination and dedication will serve as a key challenge to other firms including <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/spacex/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SpaceX</a> and Blue Origin that are working towards similar goals.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/circle-euroc-stablecoin-avalanche-blockchain/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/virgin-galactic-final-flight-test-space-travel/">Virgin Galactic to Conduct Final Flight Test as It Eyes Full Space Travel Launch</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/virgin-galactic-final-flight-test-space-travel/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Euro Coin: Circle Launches Stablecoin on Avalanche Blockchain to Facilitate Fast &amp; Efficient Payment Systems</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/circle-euroc-stablecoin-avalanche-blockchain/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/circle-euroc-stablecoin-avalanche-blockchain/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 15:48:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ava labs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[avalanche]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[avax]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[circle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Euro Coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[euroc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jeremy allaire]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=256512</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/circle-euroc-stablecoin-avalanche-blockchain/">Euro Coin: Circle Launches Stablecoin on Avalanche Blockchain to Facilitate Fast &#038; Efficient Payment Systems</a></p>
<p>USDC stablecoin issuer Circle recently launched Euro Coin on the Avalanche protocol to exploit the network’s blazing transaction speed. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/circle-euroc-stablecoin-avalanche-blockchain/">Euro Coin: Circle Launches Stablecoin on Avalanche Blockchain to Facilitate Fast &#038; Efficient Payment Systems</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/circle-euroc-stablecoin-avalanche-blockchain/">Euro Coin: Circle Launches Stablecoin on Avalanche Blockchain to Facilitate Fast &#038; Efficient Payment Systems</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/circle/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Circle</a> has <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/circle-takes-euro-coin-multi-chain-with-launch-on-avalanche-301834001.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">launched</a> a euro-based stablecoin on the Avalanche blockchain to deliver prompt and efficient payments and financial services. The <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/euro-coin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Euro Coin</a> (EUROC) launch is the first of a series of anticipated multi-chain launches to aid developers and users. According to Circle’s team, Euro Coin availability on Avalanche increases liquidity and provides users an additional transactional option alongside USD Coin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/usd-coin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">USDC</a>). Last year, Circle launched EUROC as a regulated stablecoin backed 100% by euro reserves. Each Euro Coin has an equivalent euro held in custody at financial institutions regulated by the US government.</p>
<h2>Execs Weigh In on Circle Euro Stablecoin</h2>
<p>VP of Product at Circle, Joao Reginatto, commented on benefits of the Euro stablecoin. According to Reginatto, Avalanche developers with apps that support USDC can easily integrate EUROC because both stablecoins have similar contract designs. The Circle senior executive also said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“When we first introduced Euro Coin on Ethereum last year, we wanted anyone with an internet connection to have access to the euro across borders and time zones. By launching Euro Coin on Avalanche’s fast and efficient platform, we can help developers and their users experience near-instant, more cost-effective financial transactions and unlock new possibilities for payments, remittances, and 24/7 FX.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Meanwhile, John Nahas, Vice President of Business Development at Avalanche developer Ava Labs also discussed the possibilities of Euro Coin. Describing the arrival EUROC on Avalanche as a “pivotal moment” that unlocks “new possibilities for our developers and end users,” Nahas said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“We continue to see great adoption and volume behind Circle’s USDC and expect great feedback and usage of Euro Coin on Avalanche.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Furthermore, the Ava Labs Business Development VP added that the “trusted and fully reserved” EUROC token would accelerate decentralized finance (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-decentralized-finance-defi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">DeFi</a>) adoption. Nahas opined that DeFi continues to make inroads into a “multi-currency, cross-border environment” via instant payments and remittances, and Euro Coin would be an additional boon.</p>
<p>Several popular wallets and apps would support Euro Coin on the Avalanche blockchain. These include Coinbase Wallet, Core, MetaMask, Curve, Dexalot, BENQI, Cables, GMX, NFT-TiX, Pangolin, Shift Markets, Trader Joe, and Platypus.</p>
<h2>Avalanche &#8211; The New Euro Stablecoin’s Host</h2>
<p>Avalanche is a decentralized open-source proof-of-stake network that can finalize transactions in less than a second. The blockchain uses smart contract functionality to aid Web3 development and has comprehensive toolkits to create robust, custom blockchain solutions. Avalanche’s native digital currency is <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/avalanche/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">AVAX</a>.</p>
<h2>Ava Labs</h2>
<p>Ava Labs is the developer behind Avalanche and seeks to facilitate the seamless digitization of disparate assets on a single open-source blockchain. Since its 2018 inception, the company has received funding from several established investors, including <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/a16z/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Andreessen Horowitz</a> (a16z) and Polychain Capital.</p>
<h2>Circle</h2>
<p>Founded in 2013 by <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/jeremy-allaire/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Jeremy Allaire</a> and Sean Neville as a peer-to-peer payments technology company, Circle created and began issuing USDC. The Boston-based global fintech also assists various kinds of business scales in tapping into the power of digital currencies. In addition, Circle aids businesses in leveraging public blockchains for transactional, commercial, and financial applications.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bnb-chain-hard-fork-luban-june-12/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/circle-euroc-stablecoin-avalanche-blockchain/">Euro Coin: Circle Launches Stablecoin on Avalanche Blockchain to Facilitate Fast &#038; Efficient Payment Systems</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/circle-euroc-stablecoin-avalanche-blockchain/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>BNB Chain Developers Schedule Hard Fork Dubbed Luban on June 12</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bnb-chain-hard-fork-luban-june-12/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bnb-chain-hard-fork-luban-june-12/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 14:55:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alameda research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bnb]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bnb coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=256499</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bnb-chain-hard-fork-luban-june-12/">BNB Chain Developers Schedule Hard Fork Dubbed Luban on June 12</a></p>
<p>The growth of BNB and the underlying chain is largely connected with the ongoing regulatory scrutiny, especially in the United States</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bnb-chain-hard-fork-luban-june-12/">BNB Chain Developers Schedule Hard Fork Dubbed Luban on June 12</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bnb-chain-hard-fork-luban-june-12/">BNB Chain Developers Schedule Hard Fork Dubbed Luban on June 12</a></p>
<p>The BNB Smart Chain (BSC), a leading smart contract blockchain developed by the leading centralized exchange <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a> with about $4.45 billion in total value locked, is expected to have a hard fork on its mainnet at block height 29,020,050. Through the current block generation speed, Binance Chain core developers expect the Luban hard fork to take place on June 12, 2023. As a result, the BNB Smart Chain validators and full node operators have been advised to switch their software version to v1.2.4 before the hard fork takes place in seventeen days.</p>
<p>According to GitHub documentation, the Luban hard fork on the BNB Smart Chain is expected to introduce three BEPs. The first is called BEP-126 and is expected to introduce a fast finality mechanism. With BEP-126, the BNB Smart Chain can handle much more complicated transactions much faster without compromising security.</p>
<p>The second one is BEP-174, which is cross-chain-related management.</p>
<p>“This BEP introduces a new governance proposal type to manage the set of whitelisted Relayers…This BEP will improve the management of the relayer whitelist by introducing Relayer Managers, where a Relayer Manager can manage the registration of a single Relayer. Managers will be elected and ejected via governance,” the BSC core developers <a href="https://github.com/bnb-chain/bsc/releases/tag/v1.2.4" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">noted</a>.</p>
<p>The third one is the BEP-221, which introduces a new precompiled contract to validate the CometBFT light blocks.</p>
<h2>BNB Smart Chain (BSC) and Market Outlook</h2>
<p>The BNB Smart Chain has been developed over the years to compete with other smart contract-oriented blockchains like <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a> and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/tron/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tron</a>. According to on-chain data provided by BscScan, the BNB  chain had a market capitalization of about $7,413,623,726. Worth noting, the Smart Chain has a total voting power of about 22,447,545 BNB coins.</p>
<p>Moreover, the BNB chain was developed with the goal to embrace large-scale applications &#8211; including GameFi, SocialFi, and the metaverse. In this regard, BNB coin is expected to gain value as the underlying chain gets much-needed updates.</p>
<p>According to the latest market data provided by Coingecko and Tradingview, BNB coin traded around $306 on Thursday, up approximately 25 percent YTD. As a result, the BNB market has a market capitalization of about $48,315,168,651, with a circulating supply of 157,900,174 units. Nevertheless, BNB price has dropped approximately 55 percent from its ATH, around $686.</p>
<p>The growth of BNB and the underlying chain is largely connected with the ongoing regulatory scrutiny, especially in the United States. Notably, Binance has been losing significant ground in the United States since the collapse of FTX and Alameda Research late last year.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/starling-bank-ceo-step-down/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bnb-chain-hard-fork-luban-june-12/">BNB Chain Developers Schedule Hard Fork Dubbed Luban on June 12</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bnb-chain-hard-fork-luban-june-12/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Starling Bank CEO to Step Down on June 30th after 10 Years in Charge</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/starling-bank-ceo-step-down/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/starling-bank-ceo-step-down/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 14:46:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FinTech News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[anne boden]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[goldman sachs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[starling]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[starling bank]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=256427</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/starling-bank-ceo-step-down/">Starling Bank CEO to Step Down on June 30th after 10 Years in Charge</a></p>
<p>Starling CEO Anne Boden agrees to step down from the role at the British neobank next month over 'conflict of interest' concerns. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/starling-bank-ceo-step-down/">Starling Bank CEO to Step Down on June 30th after 10 Years in Charge</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/starling-bank-ceo-step-down/">Starling Bank CEO to Step Down on June 30th after 10 Years in Charge</a></p>
<p>According to reports, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/starling-bank/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Starling Bank</a> co-founder and CEO Anne Boden <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/25/boss-of-goldman-backed-digital-bank-starling-to-step-down-next-month.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">will step down</a> at the end of next month. Chief operating officer John Mountain is replacing Boden at the helm of the British digital bank. The CFO has been with Starling since 2015.</p>
<p>Boden co-founded Starling in 2014 and grew the neobank&#8217;s profile and business visibility to become a leading UK financial player. The Starling CEO agreed to step down over concerns that her stake in the firm could create a conflict of interest. According to Boden, who owns 4% of the company, the initial decision to quit the CEO role was hers and not Starling&#8217;s board. In a statement released Thursday, the outgoing chief executive reflected on her time as leader of the digital bank and embraced the necessary shakeups. Boden wrote:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;I have spent almost a decade here as both the founder and CEO, a dual role which is unique in UK banking. It&#8217;s been all-consuming, and I&#8217;ve loved every minute of it. Now that we have grown from being an aspiring challenger to an established bank, it is clear the roles and priorities of a CEO and a large shareholder ultimately differ and require distinct approaches. As Starling continues to evolve and grow, separating my two roles is in the bank&#8217;s best interests.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>As Starling&#8217;s CEO, Boden has been pivotal in making the digital banking platform an established fintech hub under the British government. The outspoken chief executive is also staunchly critical of social media facilitating online fraud and remains <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/starling-anne-boden-dangerous/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">skeptical of digital currencies</a>.</p>
<h2>Starling CEO Announced Plans to Step Down &amp; Weighed in On Company&#8217;s IPO Outlook</h2>
<p>On Thursday, Boden touched on Starling&#8217;s operability, prospects, and mass market appeal. The CEO opined that the neobank was in a strong position and capable of raising capital today without sustaining a share price decrease. On how her exit could impact Starling&#8217;s <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/starling-ipo-within-two-years-ceo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">initial public offering (IPO) plans</a>, Boden suggested the company would address those concerns when due. According to her, the IPO market is closed, and Starling is in no immediate rush to pursue a public listing. Boden further added that there was no decision regarding a listing venue, but Starling could likely list domestically.</p>
<p>Boden said although options are open, the decision on a listing venue may not be a food one at this time. However, she mentioned that since Starling is a UK bank that has found success in the, the &#8220;default situation&#8221; would be that the company lists in the UK.</p>
<p>Starling <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/goldman-sachs-invests-starling-bank/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">enjoys the backing</a> of the US banking powerhouse <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/goldman-sachs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Goldman Sachs</a> (NYSE: GS) and is one of the UK&#8217;s most prominent neobanks. The digital bank boasts a user base of 3.6 million customers and has raised a total of £946.5 billion to date from investors. Starling Bank&#8217;s last valuation in April 2022 was £2.5 billion.</p>
<p>The bank has its headquarters in London but operates offices in Southampton, Dublin, and Cardiff.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-earnings-ai-rally/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/starling-bank-ceo-step-down/">Starling Bank CEO to Step Down on June 30th after 10 Years in Charge</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/starling-bank-ceo-step-down/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nvidia Earnings Outlook for Current Quarter Induces AI Rally as Company Boosts Production</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-earnings-ai-rally/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-earnings-ai-rally/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 14:39:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alphabet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[amd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[micron]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[microsoft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nvidia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nvidia stock]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=256489</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-earnings-ai-rally/">Nvidia Earnings Outlook for Current Quarter Induces AI Rally as Company Boosts Production</a></p>
<p>Nvidia recently increased its quarterly earnings guidance on the back of solid demand, also sparking a rally in AI stocks. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-earnings-ai-rally/">Nvidia Earnings Outlook for Current Quarter Induces AI Rally as Company Boosts Production</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-earnings-ai-rally/">Nvidia Earnings Outlook for Current Quarter Induces AI Rally as Company Boosts Production</a></p>
<p>The latest earnings outlook of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/nvidia/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Nvidia Corporation</a> (NASDAQ: NVDA) has triggered a substantial rally in artificial intelligence (AI) stocks. Early Thursday, the chip maker&#8217;s stock soared, pulling other AI-exposed companies higher on a better-than-expected sales forecast. Nvidia&#8217;s bullish sales forecast originated from surging demand for its AI chips, which has also seen the company boost production.</p>
<p>Weighing in on increased production, Nvidia chief executive officer Jensen Huang explained in a <a href="http://nvidianews.nvidia.com/news/nvidia-announces-financial-results-for-first-quarter-fiscal-2024" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">statement</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The computer industry is going through two simultaneous transitions &#8211; accelerated computing and generative AI. Our entire data center family of products &#8211; H100, Grace CPU, Grace Hopper Superchip, NVLink, Quantum 400 InfiniBand, and BlueField-3 DPU &#8211; is in production. We are significantly increasing our supply to meet surging demand for them.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Nvidia Projected Earnings See AI Stocks Rally to Combined $300 Billion in Market Value Since Wednesday</h2>
<p>Since yesterday&#8217;s extended trading session, AI stocks have increased by a combined $300 billion in market capitalization from the Nvidia development. Furthermore, KeyBanc Capital Markets analysts described Nvidia&#8217;s earnings outlook as &#8220;[living] up to the generative hype.&#8221; The analysts increased their NVDA price target from $375 to $500, adding that the semiconductor player is in prime position to benefit from &#8220;AI/machine-learning secular data-center growth&#8221;.</p>
<p>Although Nvidia&#8217;s fiscal Q1 2023 earnings surpassed expectations, the firm&#8217;s Q2 outlook primarily stoked the AI rally. The Santa Clara-based multinational tech company expects a revenue haul of $11 billion for its fiscal second quarter. This figure is substantially higher than the $7.2 billion income that analysts expect.</p>
<p>Nvidia&#8217;s stock shot up 28% after the opening bell to trade at its highest-ever level of $391.50. This substantial upswing raised the company&#8217;s stock market value by roughly $200 billion to its current perch of $960 billion. Currently valued at almost a trillion dollars, Nvidia solidified its status as the world&#8217;s most valuable chipmaker. Additionally, the software and fabless computer component designer is currently Wall Street&#8217;s fifth most valuable company.</p>
<p>Nvidia&#8217;s good fortune boosted the valuation profile of several other tech-rooted entities in premarket trade. These include C3.ai Inc (NYSE: AI), Palantir Technologies (NYSE: PLTR), and Arista Networks (NYSE: ANET), which rose 9%, 7.5%, and 7%, respectively. <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/microsoft-corporation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Microsoft</a> (NASDAQ: MSFT) and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/alphabet-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Alphabet</a> (NASDAQ: GOOGL) were also up 2%. Furthermore, Nvidia chip-manufacturing rivals, including Advanced Micro Devices (NASDAQ: AMD) and Micron Technology (NASDAQ: MU), were 8.5% and 4.5% higher, respectively.</p>
<p>Synovus Trust senior portfolio manager Daniel Morgan commented on the Nvidia earnings-triggered AI rally, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;With all the enthusiasm around AI and the fact Nvidia delivered a huge beat for first-quarter results and second-quarter estimates, this gives some actual evidence AI is for real.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Morgan also revealed that Synovus Trust owns shares in Nvidia.</p>
<h2>Will the Nvidia Rally Stand The Test of Time?</h2>
<p>With the Nvidia play in full swing, analysts ponder how long the AI rally would last and if the gains would hold. Although some analysts have faith in the staying power of AI, others point out that emerging technologies typically run in distinct cycles. These more pragmatically-inclined analysts reference blockchain, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-decentralized-finance-defi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">DeFi</a>, and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NFTs</a> as recent examples of technologies that experienced a price slump soon after a rally. According to this group of analysts, the prices dropped when the news cycle &#8220;was played up&#8221;. By contrast, the same group stated that more established fields like streaming and e-commerce have more sustained lasting impacts on investments and the economy.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/eu-regulator-crypto-trading-activities/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-earnings-ai-rally/">Nvidia Earnings Outlook for Current Quarter Induces AI Rally as Company Boosts Production</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-earnings-ai-rally/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>EU Regulator Proposes to Curb Leverage in Crypto Trading Activities</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/eu-regulator-crypto-trading-activities/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/eu-regulator-crypto-trading-activities/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 13:45:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[esrb]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mica]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=256446</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/eu-regulator-crypto-trading-activities/">EU Regulator Proposes to Curb Leverage in Crypto Trading Activities</a></p>
<p>The ESRB recommended restrictions on crypto firms' lending to clients, especially for leveraged bets, and suggested higher collateral requirements for distributed finance products and stablecoins.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/eu-regulator-crypto-trading-activities/">EU Regulator Proposes to Curb Leverage in Crypto Trading Activities</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/eu-regulator-crypto-trading-activities/">EU Regulator Proposes to Curb Leverage in Crypto Trading Activities</a></p>
<p>On Thursday, May 25, an EU watchdog &#8211; the European Systemic Risk Board &#8211; recommended that European authorities should curb leveraged bets on digital assets by introducing limits for investment funds and exchanges. Over the last few years, with the growing number of market participants, crypto trading is getting quite popular among retail investors. As a result of this, leveraged bets have been in high demand. The EU watchdog wants to prevent shocks in the crypto industry caused by leverage bets and prevent further jeopardy to financial stability.</p>
<p>The European Systemic Risk Board (ESRB) has made a few recommendations demanding regular reports from companies involved with the crypto sector along with introducing specific rules for some of the largest players in the space. In its <a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/eu-watchdog-calls-curbing-leverage-crypto-trading-2023-05-25/#:~:text=FRANKFURT%2C%20May%2025%20(Reuters),EU%20watchdog%20said%20on%20Thursday." target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a> accessed by Reuters, the ESRB noted:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Systemic risks could arise quickly and suddenly. If the rapid growth trends observed in recent years were to continue, crypto-assets could pose risks to financial stability.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The development comes at a time when regulators across the world have been taking measures to protect investors&#8217; interest in the crypto space. The last 18 months have been absolutely tumultuous for the crypto industry and marred with high-profile scams and bankruptcies.</p>
<p>During the crypto winter of 2022, the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> price tanked by more than 70% leaving investors dry of their money. Also, major incidents like the Terra ecosystem crash and the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a> exchange crash wiped out billions of dollars of investors&#8217; money.</p>
<h2>Making Tweaks to the MiCA Framework</h2>
<p>Earlier this month, in a landmark decision, the EU <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/eu-parliament-passes-mica/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">passed</a> the much-awaited Markets in Crypto Assets (MiCA) legislation. The MiCA has been adopted by EU member states and the European Parliament. Under the MiCA legislative framework, cryptocurrency businesses must get EU authorization to serve customers in the EU. They must comply with protections against money laundering and financing extremist organizations.</p>
<p>Thus, the ESRB has recently proposed a change in the recently passed EU regulation for &#8220;introducing leverage limits for investment funds exposed to crypto-assets&#8221;. These recommendations from ESRB are not bindings but a proposal to consider in the EU&#8217;s future work and new versions of MiCA.</p>
<p>The ESRB recommended restrictions on crypto firms&#8217; lending to clients, especially for leveraged bets, and suggested higher collateral requirements for distributed finance products and stablecoins.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-175m-startup-fund/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/eu-regulator-crypto-trading-activities/">EU Regulator Proposes to Curb Leverage in Crypto Trading Activities</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/eu-regulator-crypto-trading-activities/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4603 metric#misses=43 metric#hit-ratio=99.1 metric#bytes=1233682 metric#prefetches=197 metric#store-reads=22 metric#store-writes=13 metric#store-hits=204 metric#store-misses=4 metric#sql-queries=34 metric#ms-total=97.29 metric#ms-cache=6.32 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.1859 metric#ms-cache-ratio=6.5 -->