<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 18:24:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Grayscale Bitcoin Fund up 25% this year, but discount still killing investors</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/grayscale-bitcoin-fund-up-25-this-year-but-discount-still-killing-investors/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/grayscale-bitcoin-fund-up-25-this-year-but-discount-still-killing-investors/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dan Ashmore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 18:24:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Grayscale]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/grayscale-bitcoin-fund-up-25-this-year-but-discount-still-killing-investors/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key Takeaways GBTC Fund is up 25% since the start of the year, compared to a 4% rise in the underlying asset, Bitcoin The discount is now back to where it was prior to the FTX collapse, at 37% The discount had hit an all-time high of 50% only four weeks ago &#160; The largest [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/grayscale-bitcoin-fund-up-25-this-year-but-discount-still-killing-investors/">Grayscale Bitcoin Fund up 25% this year, but discount still killing investors</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2><strong>Key Takeaways</strong></h2>
<ul>
<li>GBTC Fund is up 25% since the start of the year, compared to a 4% rise in the underlying asset, Bitcoin</li>
<li>The discount is now back to where it was prior to the FTX collapse, at 37%</li>
<li>The discount had hit an all-time high of 50% only four weeks ago</li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The largest <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> fund in the world, the Grayscale Bitcoin Trust, has seen its value jump by 25% since the start of the year. Bitcoin, on the other hand, is only up about 4% on the year.</p>
<p>This means that the discount to the underlying asset, Bitcoin, is at its smallest level in months. I had analysed the divergence in December, only four weeks ago, when the discount hit an <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/why-has-the-grayscale-bitcoin-trust-discount-hit-an-all-time-high/">all-time high of 50%</a>.</p>
<p>Today, the discount sits at 37%, back to where it was before the ignominious <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ftx-insolvent-what-next-for-crypto/">collapse of FTX</a>.</p>
        <div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/12400257">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<h2><strong>What is the Grayscale discount?</strong></h2>
<p>Grayscale is a trust which provides an avenue for investors to gain exposure to Bitcoin without physically buying Bitcoin. This can be convenient for institutions or other entities who may not be able to participate I the Bitcoin market directly for regulatory or legal reasons.</p>
<p>But Grayscale has rarely traded at the same price as its net asset value. Previously, it had traded at a premium to the underlying Bitcoin as shares surged with investors desperate to get exposure to the high-flying cryptocurrency.</p>
<p>Today, however, it is the opposite &ndash; a steep discount. While there is a chunky fee of 2% that explains some of the discount, this does not come close enough to bridging a discount of 30%+ that we have seen consistently in this crypto winter.</p>
<p>The SEC recently denied Grayscale&rsquo;s application to convert the trust into an exchange-traded fund, spelling bearish action around the fund. There has also been the rise of more competition, with similar funds being launched, especially in Europe, and filings for Bitcoin ETFs.</p>
<p>But the most significant worry was surrounding the safety of reserves. This issue grew legs after the FTX collapse, as speculation mounted that Grayscale&rsquo;s parent company, Digital Currency Group (DCG), may file for bankruptcy.</p>
<p>DCG is also the parent company to Genesis, which recently laid off 30% of its staff and is reportedly considering bankruptcy. Concern grew when Grayscale refused to publish a proof of reserves report, suddenly in vogue following the nefarious actions behind the scenes at FTX.</p>
<p>It cited &ldquo;security concerns&rdquo; as the reason that this would not be possible, but analysts decried this, with it very unclear what security concerns could be ignited by the publishing of public records on the blockchain.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">6) Coinbase frequently performs on-chain validation. Due to security concerns, we do not make such on-chain wallet information and confirmation information publicly available through a cryptographic Proof-of-Reserve, or other advanced cryptographic accounting procedure.</p>
<p>&mdash; Grayscale (@Grayscale) <a href="https://twitter.com/Grayscale/status/1593737746413244417?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">November 18, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2> <strong>Why has the discount closed?</strong></h2>
<p>While the discount is still enormous at 37%, this has narrowed from the staggering 50% it reached in the aftermath of the FTX implosion.</p>
<p>There has been increasing pressure on DCG to address this discount, with calls from within the industry that the trust should allow investors to redeem their holdings, which would allow them to realise the full value of the Bitcoin they hold. This clamour may have helped narrow the gap somewhat.</p>
<p>One hedge fund, Fir Tree, even launched a lawsuit against Grayscale, demanding that the company either lower its fees or allow redemptions such that the discount can be closed.</p>
<p>But like everything in crypto right now, macro also has a part to play. The year has begun with <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/why-are-crypto-prices-rising-2023-off-to-hot-start/">crypto prices rising</a> off increased optimism that inflation may have peaked. This follows a relatively serene month or so in crypto markets.</p>
<p>The discount widened to a large degree in the aftermath of the FTX crash because people feared contagion and the chips were still falling. Similar to the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/im-sick-of-talking-about-tether-but-heres-an-article-about-tether/">peg on Tether slipping</a> when the UST crisis occurred.</p>
<p>Now that normal service <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/normalcy-returning-to-crypto-markets-on-chain-data-shows/">has somewhat resumed</a>, the discount has narrowed. Unfortunately for investors, it is still a staggering 37% off the net asset value. In a year where Bitcoin itself has plummeted, layering in a discount on top of that torrid price action is the last thing investors needed&hellip;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/grayscale-bitcoin-fund-up-25-this-year-but-discount-still-killing-investors/">Grayscale Bitcoin Fund up 25% this year, but discount still killing investors</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/grayscale-bitcoin-fund-up-25-this-year-but-discount-still-killing-investors/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase lays off 950 employees, CEO says the exchange is well capitalized</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-lays-off-950-employees-ceo-says-the-exchange-is-well-capitalized/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-lays-off-950-employees-ceo-says-the-exchange-is-well-capitalized/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 17:48:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Huobi]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-lays-off-950-employees-ceo-says-the-exchange-is-well-capitalized/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The exchange wants to reduce operating costs by 25%. It is the second crypto exchange after Huobi to confirm layoffs in 2023. Coinbase CEO has however confirmed that the exchange is well capitalized. The American-based cryptocurrency exchange, Coinbase has announced through its website that it is cutting down on its operating expenses by 25%. The [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-lays-off-950-employees-ceo-says-the-exchange-is-well-capitalized/">Coinbase lays off 950 employees, CEO says the exchange is well capitalized</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>The exchange wants to reduce operating costs by 25%.</li>
<li>It is the second crypto exchange after Huobi to confirm layoffs in 2023.</li>
<li>Coinbase CEO has however confirmed that the exchange is well capitalized.</li>
</ul>
<p>The American-based cryptocurrency exchange, <a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/coinbase/">Coinbase</a> has announced through its website that it is cutting down on its operating expenses by 25%. The move includes laying off 950 employees, which accounts for about 20% of the company&rsquo;s workforce.</p>
<p>The exchange&rsquo;s CEO, Brian Armstrong, has listed the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-winter-may-not-end-anytime-soon/">ongoing bear crypto market</a> and the broader macroeconomy as the main reasons to reduce the company&rsquo;s expenses.</p>
<h2>Hard times for the exchange</h2>
<p>While announcing the laying off, the CEO also assured the public that the crypto exchange is well capitalized and added that crypto is not going anywhere.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, the CEO noted that while the exchange has gone through multiple crypto bear markets, the current bear market is proving to be a real struggle for Coinbase. He said that it is the first time a global economic meltdown has aligned with a bear crypto market. He said:</p>
<p><em>&ldquo;As we examined our 2023 scenarios, it became clear that we would need to reduce expenses to increase our chances of doing well in every scenario. While it is always painful to part ways with our colleagues, there was no way to reduce our expenses significantly enough without considering changes to headcount.&rdquo;</em></p>
<h2>2023 has already seen several layoffs</h2>
<p>Coinbase joins several other companies that started the year 2023 by announcing layoffs. Huobi exchange also <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/is-huobi-safe-why-customers-should-be-withdrawing-funds/">recently confirmed 20% layoffs</a>.</p>
<p>For example, Salesforce announced it is planning to reduce its workforce by 10%, which would translate to laying off about 8,000 people. Amazon also confirmed that it is carrying out its second round of layoffs that will see it lay off about 18,000 people from its workforce.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-lays-off-950-employees-ceo-says-the-exchange-is-well-capitalized/">Coinbase lays off 950 employees, CEO says the exchange is well capitalized</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-lays-off-950-employees-ceo-says-the-exchange-is-well-capitalized/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>BONK price action spells trouble after becoming an overnight crypto sensation</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bonk-price-action-spells-trouble-after-becoming-an-overnight-crypto-sensation/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/bonk-price-action-spells-trouble-after-becoming-an-overnight-crypto-sensation/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Motiur Rahman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 16:34:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bonk-price-action-spells-trouble-after-becoming-an-overnight-crypto-sensation/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bonk token launched on December 25, 2022 The cryptocurrency rose by four-digit percentages after the launch BONK price has cooled and trades on a descent and could claim lower levels Crypto has always treated its fans with twists, turns, and surprises. The crypto community loves it this way, for it becomes a time to make [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bonk-price-action-spells-trouble-after-becoming-an-overnight-crypto-sensation/">BONK price action spells trouble after becoming an overnight crypto sensation</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Bonk token launched on December 25, 2022</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The cryptocurrency rose by four-digit percentages after the launch</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">BONK price has cooled and trades on a descent and could claim lower levels</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Crypto has always treated its fans with twists, turns, and surprises. The crypto community loves it this way, for it becomes a time to make quick bucks as the rest of the market sleeps. In 2022, we were treated to a wild launch of the ApeCoin. Before the dust settled, Optimism airdrop came with a thud! The year couldn&rsquo;t end in a better way for crypto fans than it did with the&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bonk-price-has-soared-prepare-for-a-major-dive/#:~:text=Bonk%20is%20a%20new%20meme,exposure%20to%20FTX%20and%20Alameda." rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Bonk token</u></a> (BONK/USD).</p>
<p dir="ltr">If you are a fan of&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/a-brief-history-of-dogecoin-and-other-meme-coins/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>meme tokens</u></a>, then BONK does not miss your watchlist after a heroic entry into the crypto space. Launched on December 25, 2022, BONK has been a sensation, jumping by four digits percentage in price. The token also dominated social trading platforms. Analysts credited the popularity of the newly dog-themed token to the Solana community. The former is based on the Solana network.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Nonetheless, if history is indeed a good teacher, then we should learn that the gains may not last forever. We have seen highly hyped launches boosting token prices, only for them to crash thereafter. BONK may not be an exception. As of press time, the meme cryptocurrency had lost at least 50% of its value from its all-time high. Typical of the phrase, if you didn&rsquo;t board early, don&rsquo;t do it now. Technical pointers show BONK could fall further.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>BONK on a decline as price finds minor support</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/00/10/1673368409614-a491c771-3e2a-4c0e-b442-8697a559f1f5.png" style="width: 600px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="600" height="266"></p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BONKUSDT/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>BONK/USDT Chart by TradingView</u></a></p>
<p dir="ltr">From the 4-hour chart outlook, BONK trades nervously at a support zone. The highs to the upside have been lower, coinciding with a declining price. Buy-side volumes have improved slightly at the support, but not sufficient to boost BONK&rsquo;s price.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>BONK price prediction</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">As the hype around the BONK launch dies, the price could continue falling. Investors may look at BONK as an overvalued asset. Profit-taking and panic selling may also be at play and force a bearish breakout.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Where to buy BONK</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bonk-price-action-spells-trouble-after-becoming-an-overnight-crypto-sensation/">BONK price action spells trouble after becoming an overnight crypto sensation</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/bonk-price-action-spells-trouble-after-becoming-an-overnight-crypto-sensation/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Polkadot prediction as price embarks on a relief rally from the $4.2 bottom</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/polkadot-prediction-as-price-embarks-on-a-relief-rally-from-the-4-2-bottom/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/polkadot-prediction-as-price-embarks-on-a-relief-rally-from-the-4-2-bottom/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Motiur Rahman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 16:27:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polkadot News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/polkadot-prediction-as-price-embarks-on-a-relief-rally-from-the-4-2-bottom/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Polkadot had the second-highest development activity in 2022 DOT price has heavily disappointed since the 2021 ATH but has recovered lately DOT faces resistance at $5 and may correct downwards Polkadot (DOT/USD) buyers are struggling to break above $5. A technical outlook shows the cryptocurrency has been rejected at the building resistance for the second [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/polkadot-prediction-as-price-embarks-on-a-relief-rally-from-the-4-2-bottom/">Polkadot prediction as price embarks on a relief rally from the $4.2 bottom</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Polkadot had the second-highest development activity in 2022</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">DOT price has heavily disappointed since the 2021 ATH but has recovered lately</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">DOT faces resistance at $5 and may correct downwards</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Polkadot (DOT/USD) buyers are struggling to break above $5. A technical outlook shows the cryptocurrency has been rejected at the building resistance for the second day. However, Polkadot fans should be at least excited by a relief rally that has seen the price recover from the $4.2 bottom.</p>
<p dir="ltr">If time is a true judge, then the Polkadot price has disappointed heavily. The cryptocurrency touched a high of nearly $56 in November 2021 and has since come crumbling. With a single-digit price now, DOT is a shell of its former self.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Although 2022 may have ended on a low note for DOT buyers, enthusiasts should be happy with the blockchain&rsquo;s activity. Santiment data indicates that the blockchain had the highest development activity in the year after Cardano. Polkadot was followed by Cosmos blockchain, Ethereum, and Internet Computer in the top 5. That shows that the decline in the price of the native token wasn&rsquo;t in any way signalling a falling popularity of the protocol. Rather, it was due to a sustained bearish market that has hit every cryptocurrency.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">If you are considering&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/polkadot/buy/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>buying DOT</u></a>, you may have to wait until the throat clears. For short-term investors, a break above $5 is the needed confirmation.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>DOT price facing resistance at $5 and 50-day MA</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/00/10/1673368020387-eeade7e4-076c-4c55-a1d3-915498d6a000.png" style="width: 600px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="600" height="270"></p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/DOTUSD/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>DOT/USD Chart by TradingView</u></a></p>
<p dir="ltr">Based on the price action, DOT&rsquo;s long-term momentum is still bearish. The short-term is bullish, with the RSI now in the bullish zone. However, DOT is facing resistance at the 50-day MA. The moving average coincides with the $5 resistance level.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>What happens next for DOT?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">A potential correction is looming for the&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/polkadot/#:~:text=The%20price%20of%20DOT%20today,trading%20volume%20of%20%2490.58M." rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>DOT price</u></a> at the current level if bulls do not recover above $5. If a breakout occurs, DOT could set the next target above $7, with minor corrections at $5.6 and $6.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Where to buy DOT</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>

    <p>eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=OTkzMzM&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=TX&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy DOT with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    Binance</h3>

    <p>Binance is one of the largest cryptocurrency exchanges in the world. It is better suited to more experienced investors and it offers a large number of cryptocurrencies to choose from, at over 600.

Binance is also known for having low trading fees and a multiple of trading options that its users can benefit from, such as; peer-to-peer trading, margin trading and spot trading.
</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/binance-crypto?guid=OTkzMzM&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=TX&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy DOT with Binance today            </a>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/polkadot-prediction-as-price-embarks-on-a-relief-rally-from-the-4-2-bottom/">Polkadot prediction as price embarks on a relief rally from the $4.2 bottom</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/polkadot-prediction-as-price-embarks-on-a-relief-rally-from-the-4-2-bottom/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin could tank further but you might be excited by this Bloomberg prediction</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-could-tank-further-but-you-might-be-excited-by-this-bloomberg-prediction/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-could-tank-further-but-you-might-be-excited-by-this-bloomberg-prediction/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Motiur Rahman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 16:20:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-could-tank-further-but-you-might-be-excited-by-this-bloomberg-prediction/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bloomberg report projects bullish Bitcoin in 2023 Analysts bank on recession dynamics and central banks&#8217; actions as bull triggers BTC trades on a short-term recovery, with $19,000 in sight Investors may hold their breath, hoping that 2023 will turn out to be a good year for crypto and stocks alike. But even with these hoped-for [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-could-tank-further-but-you-might-be-excited-by-this-bloomberg-prediction/">Bitcoin could tank further but you might be excited by this Bloomberg prediction</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Bloomberg report projects bullish Bitcoin in 2023</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Analysts bank on recession dynamics and central banks&rsquo; actions as bull triggers</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">BTC trades on a short-term recovery, with $19,000 in sight</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Investors may hold their breath, hoping that 2023 will turn out to be a good year for crypto and stocks alike. But even with these hoped-for expectations, market analysts have warned that 2023 could be the year of a global recession. With the economic depression, notable recoveries may be hard to come by. But Blomberg analysts think a recession would be a bullish trigger for <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/#:~:text=The%20price%20of%20BTC%20today,trading%20volume%20of%20%2413.67B." rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Bitcoin price</u></a> (BTC/USD). How?</p>
<p dir="ltr">In its cryptocurrency outlook, analysts say Bitcoin will come out ahead in a potential economic shutdown in 2023. Even so, the prediction is not outright. According to the report, Bitcoin could slide to $12,000 or even $10,000. From there, it will stage a strong comeback.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Additionally, the Bloomberg report highlights policy easing in 2023 as a key bullish trigger for Bitcoin and cryptocurrencies. The analysts say central banks could be forced to ease policy on the back of deflationary outcomes. If this happens, the use case of Bitcoin as a digital version of gold will strengthen. The analysts point out that Bitcoin will start performing like the US long-dated treasury bonds and metal. The scenario will be bullish for the digital asset.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Bitcoin price movement as moving averages join the support</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/00/10/1673367549133-a2c2b36d-aad8-408b-9311-04e04052f034.png" style="width: 600px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="600" height="276"></p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>BTC/USD Chart by TradingView</u></a></p>
<p dir="ltr">Technically, BTC is mildly bullish and trades along a short-term ascending trendline. The price has, for the first time since November, moved above the 50-day moving average. A potential 20-day MA crossover of the 50-day MA could heighten the recoveries. The RSI reading has safely surpassed the midpoint reading of 50, indicating that buyers are in control.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>What is the likely target for BTC?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">With the upside,&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Bitcoin</u></a> now trades below an overhead and crucial resistance at $19,000. Should the current upside continue, the level is the target zone for buyers. Accelerated recoveries will depend on the prevailing crypto sentiment.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Where to buy BTC</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>

    <p>eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=OTkzMzI&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=TX&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy BTC with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    Binance</h3>

    <p>Binance is one of the largest cryptocurrency exchanges in the world. It is better suited to more experienced investors and it offers a large number of cryptocurrencies to choose from, at over 600.

Binance is also known for having low trading fees and a multiple of trading options that its users can benefit from, such as; peer-to-peer trading, margin trading and spot trading.
</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/binance-crypto?guid=OTkzMzI&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=TX&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy BTC with Binance today            </a>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-could-tank-further-but-you-might-be-excited-by-this-bloomberg-prediction/">Bitcoin could tank further but you might be excited by this Bloomberg prediction</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-could-tank-further-but-you-might-be-excited-by-this-bloomberg-prediction/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>NFT sales rose 26% in the first week of 2023</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/nft-sales-rose-26-in-the-first-week-of-2023/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/nft-sales-rose-26-in-the-first-week-of-2023/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 16:10:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/nft-sales-rose-26-in-the-first-week-of-2023/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NFT sales jumped 26% as trading volume rose across major blockchains. Ethereum accounted for the most NFT sales, while Bored Ape Yacht Club dominated among collections. The broader crypto industry has started 2023 slightly higher, with notable rallies for coins such as Cardano, Solana and Ziliqa. The NFT market size is expected to grow over [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/nft-sales-rose-26-in-the-first-week-of-2023/">NFT sales rose 26% in the first week of 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>NFT sales jumped 26% as trading volume rose across major blockchains.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>Ethereum accounted for the most NFT sales, while Bored Ape Yacht Club dominated among collections.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><strong><em>The broader crypto industry has started 2023 slightly higher, with notable rallies for coins such as Cardano, Solana and Ziliqa.</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">The NFT market size is expected to grow over the next several years, and 2023 has begun with a significant jump in sales on <a href="https://coinjournal.net/compare/best-nft-marketplaces/">top NFT marketplaces</a>. It is one of the interesting <a href="https://coinjournal.net/research/nft-statistics/">NFT statistics</a> for the year.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to data from <a href="https://www.cryptoslam.io/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Cryptoslam.io</a>, NFT sales increased by 26% in the first week of the year. The platform showed the metric rose by the margin as 1.2 million NFT transactions registered across 400,740 NFT buyers.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As for the NFT collection with the highest transaction volume, the honour fell to the Bored Ape Yacht Club (BAYC). The collection registered $19,052,102 in sales, with trading volume rising by 53% in the week.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">BNB Chain records 71% spike in NFT sales</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Per the data, the most sales occurred on the Ethereum blockchain &ndash; where NFT sales accounted for $164 million of $209 million. Overall, the sales rose across all major blockchain networks. BNB Chain saw the largest jump in sales, with a 71% spike just higher than the 70% growth on Theta grew.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Solana remains a top NFT ecosystem despite recent upheaval following the collapse of FTX and saw its NFT sales increase by 28.8% last week.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Crypto prices up early in 2023</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/cryptocurrencies/">Cryptocurrencies</a> entered 2023 on the back of major losses in the previous year, with Bitcoin and the rest of the crypto market having recorded massive dips from their all-time highs.</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, the first week of the year has seen crypto mirror broader market movements with gains pushing BTC above $17,000 and Ethereum to $1,340. While Bitcoin is up more than 4% in the past week, Ethereum has notched double figures with over 10%.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Among the most impressive performers include Cardano that&rsquo;s up 28% and Solana that has rallied by more than 45% this past week. SOL&rsquo;s surge came after the BONK &nbsp;meme coin airdrop to the Solana NFT community. Ziliqa has soared over 50% amid major network upgrades and integrations &ndash; including with esports loyalty programs.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/nft-sales-rose-26-in-the-first-week-of-2023/">NFT sales rose 26% in the first week of 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/nft-sales-rose-26-in-the-first-week-of-2023/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance coin back to safety as buyers now aim for $295</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-coin-back-to-safety-as-buyers-now-aim-for-295/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-coin-back-to-safety-as-buyers-now-aim-for-295/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Motiur Rahman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 15:50:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance Coin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNB]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-coin-back-to-safety-as-buyers-now-aim-for-295/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Binance coin has recaptured crucial support at $266 after the latest crash The cryptocurrency was previously weighed by adverse publicity A recovery above $266 sets BNB to the next resistance at $295 Binance (BNB/USD) traded at $274 on Tuesday, slowing from a monthly high of $282 the previous day. BNB buyers would be delighted about [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-coin-back-to-safety-as-buyers-now-aim-for-295/">Binance coin back to safety as buyers now aim for $295</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Binance coin has recaptured crucial support at $266 after the latest crash</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The cryptocurrency was previously weighed by adverse publicity</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">A recovery above $266 sets BNB to the next resistance at $295</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Binance (BNB/USD) traded at $274 on Tuesday, slowing from a monthly high of $282 the previous day. BNB buyers would be delighted about how far the cryptocurrency has come since Binance began to be adversely mentioned.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Touching a low of $220 in mid-Dec, there were fears of further downside for BNB after the collapse of FTX. That&rsquo;s particularly because, at the price level, BNB had lost crucial support at $266, which kept it stable. However, relentless buying has seen BNB recover to the level which now supports the price.</p>
<p dir="ltr">BNB price is at least now back to safety above $266. However, Binance&rsquo;s woes seem to be far from over. The latest&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>cryptocurrency news</u></a> suggests that US federal prosecutors have started to investigate the crypto exchange. According to reports, several American firms have been issued subpoenas for their communications with Binance. The exchange is reportedly being probed for violations of the US Bank Secrecy Act. The regulations mandate financial entities to verify their clients in a bid to curb money laundering. BNB price is yet to react to the potential litigation.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>BNB recovers above $266 support as price turns mildly bullish</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/00/10/1673365796836-1091b14b-0411-4564-8c6a-3b44220ec2aa.png" style="width: 600px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="600" height="272"></p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BNBUSD/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>BNB/USD Chart by TradingView</u></a></p>
<p dir="ltr">A technical outlook gives BNB $295 as the likely price target. This is the next resistance zone, and BNB has in the past hit the target each time price has recovered above $266. The MACD indicator is shifting above the neutral zone, underlining a bullish momentum. Similarly, BNB trades above the moving averages. The 50-day MA could hold as the dynamic support, coinciding with the $266 level.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Is investing in BNB now a good idea?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">A retest of the $266 support would open buy trades on the cryptocurrency. Investors should watch for bullish price action signals at the support to&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/binance-coin/buy/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>buy BNB</u></a> and ride to the $295 resistance.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Where to buy BNB</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>

    <p>eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=OTkzMjU&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=TX&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy BNB with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    Binance</h3>

    <p>Binance is one of the largest cryptocurrency exchanges in the world. It is better suited to more experienced investors and it offers a large number of cryptocurrencies to choose from, at over 600.

Binance is also known for having low trading fees and a multiple of trading options that its users can benefit from, such as; peer-to-peer trading, margin trading and spot trading.
</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/binance-crypto?guid=OTkzMjU&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=TX&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy BNB with Binance today            </a>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-coin-back-to-safety-as-buyers-now-aim-for-295/">Binance coin back to safety as buyers now aim for $295</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-coin-back-to-safety-as-buyers-now-aim-for-295/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP witnessing increased institutional inflows. Here is the most important level now</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/xrp-witnessing-increased-institutional-inflows-here-is-the-most-important-level-now/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/xrp-witnessing-increased-institutional-inflows-here-is-the-most-important-level-now/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Motiur Rahman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 15:23:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/xrp-witnessing-increased-institutional-inflows-here-is-the-most-important-level-now/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>XRP accumulation intensified in the first week of the year Investors bank on Ripple&#8217;s win against the SEC XRP has gained stability above $0.31, and the price could surge from here If you have been following&#160;Ripple (XRP/USD), you already know its case with the SEC continues to be important. Investors have priced XRP depending on [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/xrp-witnessing-increased-institutional-inflows-here-is-the-most-important-level-now/">XRP witnessing increased institutional inflows. Here is the most important level now</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">XRP accumulation intensified in the first week of the year</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Investors bank on Ripple&rsquo;s win against the SEC</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">XRP has gained stability above $0.31, and the price could surge from here</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">If you have been following&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/ripple/what-is-ripple/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Ripple</u></a> (XRP/USD), you already know its case with the SEC continues to be important. Investors have priced XRP depending on the direction of the case. However, the latest CoinShares report shows that institutional investors are banking heavily on a Ripple win.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to CoinShares, the first week of 2023 saw $3 million in inflows into XRP. On the other hand, investors exited $6.5 million and $3 million from Bitcoin and Ethereum, respectively. This could be positive news as it shows how much trust the market has developed in XRP. According to CoinShares, the inflows reflected improved clarity on Ripple&rsquo;s case with the SEC. But despite this positive development, XRP-associated investment products recorded $9.7 million worth of outflows.</p>
<p dir="ltr">From a fundamental perspective, we could argue that it is still a double-edged sword for XRP as the case drags on. There are positives to pick from the latest institutional inflow, with the settlement expected in the current first quarter. The technical outlook also supports a potential XRP accumulation of around $0.31.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>XRP gains stability above support at $0.31</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/00/10/1673364130356-b8df0d67-e49b-4750-9a47-18cb0da6d02d.png" style="width: 600px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="600" height="269"></p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XRPUSD/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>XRP/USD Chart by TradingView</u></a></p>
<p dir="ltr">A price outlook shows XRP is pushing higher after settling and consolidating above $0.31. The momentum has improved but remains weak. The MACD indicator is yet to cross above the neutral zone.</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, the volume indicators would be a little bit exciting. A spike in buy-side volumes suggests that buying is ongoing for XRP above $0.31. The previous bullish pin bar acts as the buffer against the bear pressure for XRP.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Will XRP become bullish?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">XRP has a chance to become bullish if the price holds steady at the current level. The upside is likely to continue in the short and medium term to the $0.4 resistance. The ongoing case with the SEC will determine if&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/ripple/#:~:text=The%20price%20of%20XRP%20today,in%20the%20last%2024%20hours." rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>XRP price</u></a> sustains the recoveries.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Where to buy XRP</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>

    <p>eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=OTkzMjI&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=TX&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy XRP with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    Binance</h3>

    <p>Binance is one of the largest cryptocurrency exchanges in the world. It is better suited to more experienced investors and it offers a large number of cryptocurrencies to choose from, at over 600.

Binance is also known for having low trading fees and a multiple of trading options that its users can benefit from, such as; peer-to-peer trading, margin trading and spot trading.
</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/binance-crypto?guid=OTkzMjI&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=TX&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy XRP with Binance today            </a>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/xrp-witnessing-increased-institutional-inflows-here-is-the-most-important-level-now/">XRP witnessing increased institutional inflows. Here is the most important level now</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/xrp-witnessing-increased-institutional-inflows-here-is-the-most-important-level-now/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Best ICOs to Invest in February 2023 According to Reddit</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/best-icos-to-invest-in-february-2023-according-to-reddit/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/best-icos-to-invest-in-february-2023-according-to-reddit/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice Davies]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 13:53:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/best-icos-to-invest-in-february-2023-according-to-reddit/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An initial coin offering (ICO) is a way for projects to generate funds to help get themselves up and running. These are regularly used in the crypto world, allowing companies to help generate publicity, which in turn attracts further investment and new users to their platforms. ICOs are usually released with a white paper outlining [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/best-icos-to-invest-in-february-2023-according-to-reddit/">Best ICOs to Invest in February 2023 According to Reddit</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">An initial coin offering (ICO) is a way for projects to generate funds to help get themselves up and running. These are regularly used in the crypto world, allowing companies to help generate publicity, which in turn attracts further investment and new users to their platforms. ICOs are usually released with a white paper outlining the platform&rsquo;s future, and early investors can often look forward to realizing profits on their initial investment as the project progresses.</p>
<p dir="ltr">These are the best ICOs to add to your crypto portfolio in February 2023:</p>
<ol>
<li dir="ltr">Metacade (MCADE)</li>
<li dir="ltr">VisaMetaFi (VISA)</li>
<li dir="ltr">Heroes of Mavia (MAVIA</li>
<li dir="ltr">Wombat Exchange (WOM)</li>
<li dir="ltr">CryptoCitizen (CCASH)</li>
<li dir="ltr">ByePix (EPIX)</li>
<li dir="ltr">WeSendIt (WSI)</li>
<li dir="ltr">Kryptview (KVT)</li>
</ol>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>1.&nbsp;</strong><strong>Metacade &ndash; A Revolutionary Gaming Platform for the Metaverse</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade</u></a> is a new blockchain-based platform that has already gained huge popularity during its presale stage. This community gaming hub is aiming to become a virtual gaming hub that recreates the excitement and community of real-world video arcades, all from the comfort of gamers&rsquo; homes. The platform will offer a vast array of play-to-earn (P2E) games to attract both casual and hardcore gamers alike, with a compelling play-to-earn mechanic at its core.</p>
<p dir="ltr">P2E looks to be just one of many earning opportunities Metacade&rsquo;s community will have to create income for themselves. Players can also earn through sharing gaming alpha, writing reviews and staking the MCADE token. Other ground-breaking features include the Metacade Create2Earn scheme, which features the Metagrants initiative where developers can access crypto-funding to support the creation of new games. In addition, a jobs board aims to match the best Web3 creative talent with exciting career opportunities within the industry.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr"><strong>Why buy MCADE?</strong></h3>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade&rsquo;s native token, MCADE, recently launched in presale and sold out its beta phase in just over three weeks, with $1 million raised. With nine presale rounds that will see the value of MCADE rise from its beta price of $0.008 to $0.02 by the conclusion of the presale, expectations are that the price of MCADE could surge once it hits decentralized exchanges.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This scope for profit during the current bear market and the long-term growth potential of Metacade&rsquo;s ground-breaking GameFi platform makes Metacade one of the best ICOs for investors looking to expand their crypto portfolio.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>&gt;&gt;&gt; You can participate in the Metacade presale&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong><u>here</u></strong></a><strong>&nbsp;&lt;&lt;&lt;</strong></p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>2.&nbsp;</strong><strong>VisaMetaFi (VISA) &ndash; Outstanding new simple to use crypto payment system</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">VisaMetaFi&rsquo;s platform features a new decentralized crypto payment system that can be used across different online merchants and blockchain platforms. It incorporates Web3, DeFi, DAO, metaverse, and MetaFi payment capabilities, making it one of the best ICOs to invest in.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The platform allows users to transfer stablecoins anywhere in the world without transaction fees, as well as eradicate the need for users to swap digital coins or convert crypto to fiat to make transfers. Big names making use of VisaMetaFi include the holiday booking website Booking.com.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr"><strong>Why buy VISA?</strong></h3>
<p dir="ltr">VisaMetaFi has successfully undergone the opening phases of the project, reaching tens of thousands of global users, including the release of a native VISA coin.</p>
<p dir="ltr">With its simple and accessible framework for enabling online and crypto payments worldwide, VISA looks set to capture the attention of investors in the long term. Consequently, VISA is among the best ICOs to invest in February 2023.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>3. Heroes of Mavia (MAVIA) &ndash; Attractive P2E battle-builder game</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Heroes of Mavia is one of the best blockchain-based gaming ICOs currently available thanks to its exciting base-building and player2player battle features. Gamers create their own armies to capture enemy bases within the Heroes of Mavia ecosystem earning Ruby tokens as they progress.</p>
<p dir="ltr">These tokens can be used to upgrade their bases, equip their armies, and fortify defences. The game has several attractive features, including an NFT marketplace, live battle streaming and a partnership manager for users to collaborate through military-style alliances while earning passive income.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr"><strong>Why buy MAVIA?</strong></h3>
<p dir="ltr">The native MAVIA token has already attracted a vast and loyal following on social media from investors wanting to get on board this new and exciting P2E gaming platform ahead of the NFT launch due in Q1 of 2023 and free2play launch in Q2.</p>
<p dir="ltr">With backing from crypto big guns Binance Labs, crypto.com, and Genblock Capital, MAVIA is an excellent crypto portfolio investment in February 2023.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>4.&nbsp;</strong><strong>WombatExchange (WOM) &ndash; Exciting stableswap currency exchange</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Defined by its white paper as a &ldquo;multi-chain stableswap&rdquo; hosted on the Binance Chain, WombatExchange is a new crypto exchange that allows market players to swap stablecoins while generating a yield through coin staking and benefiting from minimal levels of slippage.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The user-friendly interface makes WombatExchange an excellent entry point for traders new to crypto exchanges. In addition, the available liquidity pool means that users aren&rsquo;t required to hold multiple stable currencies.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr"><strong>Why buy WOM?</strong></h3>
<p dir="ltr">WombatExchange&rsquo;s native currency coin, WOM, is an enticing ICO that will give holders access to voting rights on the platform&rsquo;s governance proposals and stablecoin liquidity. The exchange has already captured the imagination and investment of several large companies, including Hailstone Ventures and Shima Capital.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Meanwhile, Wombat Exchange&rsquo;s Twitter account is approaching 70,000 followers and growing fast, making it one of the best ICOs for investors looking for new possibilities in the world of crypto exchanges.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>5.&nbsp;</strong><strong>CryptoCitizen (CCASH) &ndash; Addictive MMORPG metaverse gaming platform</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">CryptoCitizen is another metaverse gaming offering that offers free-to-play and P2E capabilities in a world with a supporting storyline. The platform has a vast potential audience as a massively multiplayer online role-playing game (MMORPG) with a diverse range of gaming opportunities, including shoot-&lsquo;em-up, racing, and classic 1v1 fighting elements.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Users can earn the native CCASH token through success in challenges and improving their &lsquo;Citizen Ranking,&rsquo; which in turn also opens opportunities to access exclusive NFTs.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr"><strong>Why buy CCASH?</strong></h3>
<p dir="ltr">CryptoCitizen has already caused a storm within the gaming world, with more than 200,000 pre-registering for its Alpha Test phase. It was presented at Gamescom 2022 to huge acclaim and has already fully allocated three presale allocations of CCASH through Polkastarter, Firestarter, and Seedify.</p>
<p dir="ltr">With a maximum supply of 1 billion CCASH tokens and only 1.2% being released when CCASH is listed on exchanges, the furore already whipped up and the scarcity of tokens on open exchanges makes CCASH one of the best ICOs for early investors to purchase.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>6.&nbsp;</strong><strong>ByePix (EPIX) &ndash; Social2Earn platform looking to challenge Facebook</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">ByePix is a Web3-based platform that combines multiple exciting elements in one easy-to-use hub. Attractions include DeFi apps, NFTs, P2E titles, and a fully-functioning ecosystem that caters to players&rsquo; every need. For example, gamers can receive tokenized rewards for completing tasks in &lsquo;Gem Hunters&rsquo;, one of the platform&rsquo;s first P2E titles.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Additional features of the platform include virtual plots of land which can be bought using the EPIX coin, cultivated and developed, before being sold for a neat profit. Other earning potential comes from completing social tasks through the platform&rsquo;s Social2Earn initiative and investing in EPIX to produce returns.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr"><strong>Why buy EPIX?</strong></h3>
<p dir="ltr">ByePix has generated a massive buzz with significant investment from prominent venture capital firms. Their ultimate goal is to challenge social media giants like Facebook and Instagram. While that might appear a tall order, there is an opportunity for ByePix to improve the social media landscape in the longer term by compensating users for their content.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This innovative approach makes EPIX one of the best ICOs worth considering for investors looking for an exciting and potentially game-changing crypto opportunity.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>7.&nbsp;</strong><strong>WeSendIt (WSI) &ndash; Exciting new decentralized storage and file-sharing platform</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">A new crypto service that provides decentralized cloud storage and file-sharing options, WeSendit has recently announced its new WeSendIt 3.0 release, allowing users to earn tokenized rewards every time they send data.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This BEP-20 token can then be exchanged for advertising, scalable data storage, and subscription discounts, with further rewards available through customer referrals to the platform.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr"><strong>Why buy WSI?</strong></h3>
<p dir="ltr">Designed as a low-cost alternative to the centralized file-sharing and data storage options offered by tech giants such as Amazon, Google, and Microsoft, WeSendIt&rsquo;s move into the crypto world is backed by more than a decade&rsquo;s experience in the sector. Over this time, they&rsquo;ve gained more than three million customers across 150 countries making WSI among the best ICOs to purchase in February 2023.</p>
<p dir="ltr">WSI tokens have already successfully undergone private sale in September 2022. With the demand for decentralized data storage facilities only going to increase over the coming years, WSI is an ICO worth investing in to receive potentially rich profits.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>8.</strong> <strong>Kryptview (KVT) &ndash; Interactive Research2Earn platform to help inform crypto investors</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Kryptview&rsquo;s new interactive &lsquo;Research-to-Earn&rsquo; platform is dedicated to producing and sharing research on cryptocurrencies, tokens, and platforms. Users are encouraged to interact with the community by earning rewards for evaluating, analyzing, and reviewing crypto projects.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In addition, users can offer &lsquo;research bounties&rsquo; to assets as an enticement for other platform members to research said asset, provide information and thus potential value. The native KVT coin is used to distribute rewards and underpins the entire ecosystem.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr"><strong>Why buy KVT?</strong></h3>
<p dir="ltr">Aiming to become the first platform of its kind to break through into the crypto mainstream, several big crypto backers, including The Blox and Matters, have lent their backing to the project.</p>
<p dir="ltr">With demand expected to be high when KVT hits the exchanges, getting in early will help investors exploit potential long-term gains. This makes it one of the best ICOs currently available, with potential rewards available in the future with its innovative and potentially market-leading offering.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>In Summary &ndash; Metacade is the Best ICO For Investing In 2023&nbsp;</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">ICOs are an excellent way for investors to make early and significant profits, provided they can back the correct projects before they hit the open market. With many presales offering similar staged increases in value over their presales, understanding where value can be found is vital.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade&rsquo;s rich and multi-dimensional roadmap offers a host of exciting earning potential for users in addition to its incredible upcoming scope of P2E titles and the Metagrants scheme that will help it lead GameFi development. These factors combine to make it the best ICO investment opportunity in February 2023. With the quick sell-out of the beta phase, and more than $2 million already raised, MCADE looks set to skyrocket as the roadmap reaches fruition with the release of new features in 2023 and 2024.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>You can buy the best ICO tokens at eToro&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://coinjournal.net/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=OTkzMTQ" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong><u>here</u></strong></a><strong>.</strong></p>
<p><strong>You can participate in the Metacade presale&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong><u>here</u></strong></a><strong>.</strong></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/best-icos-to-invest-in-february-2023-according-to-reddit/">Best ICOs to Invest in February 2023 According to Reddit</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/best-icos-to-invest-in-february-2023-according-to-reddit/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
