<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 21:20:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Stablecoin legislation may come this year, Bitwise exec says</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/stablecoin-legislation-may-come-this-year-bitwise-exec-says/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/stablecoin-legislation-may-come-this-year-bitwise-exec-says/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 21:20:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/stablecoin-legislation-may-come-this-year-bitwise-exec-says/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitwise Chief Compliance Officer Kathrine Dowling is optimistic on stablecoin regulation in the US in 2023. According to Dowling, stablecoins will the first to be regulatory as what needs to be done is mostly straightforward. The US is looking to align with the global regulatory community. Stablecoins are likely to be the first to get [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/stablecoin-legislation-may-come-this-year-bitwise-exec-says/">Stablecoin legislation may come this year, Bitwise exec says</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>Bitwise Chief Compliance Officer Kathrine Dowling is optimistic on stablecoin regulation in the US in 2023.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>According to Dowling, stablecoins will the first to be regulatory as what needs to be done is mostly straightforward.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><strong><em>The US is looking to align with the global regulatory community.</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/glossary/stablecoin/">Stablecoins</a> are likely to be the first to get regulated in the US in 2023, according to Katherine Dowling, the general counsel and chief compliance officer at cryptocurrency investment firm Bitwise.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Easier to work out stablecoin regulations</h2>
<p dir="ltr">In an <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/video/bitwise-general-counsel-on-crypto-regulation/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">interview</a> with CoinDesk TV on Monday, Dowling said the move towards a stablecoin legislation this year is more likely because the sub-industry represents a sector that&rsquo;s not so complex. Stablecoin regulation is a &ldquo;<em>narrower issue,</em>&rdquo; she said.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Speaking during an appearance on the crypto media outlet&rsquo;s &lsquo;<em>First Mover</em>&rsquo;, the Bitwise compliance officer said regulators can easily get hold of issues around stablecoins &ldquo;a little bit better&rdquo; than what the broader crypto market represented.</p>
<p dir="ltr">While the events of the past few months, and whose effects continue to be felt across crypto &ndash;including the collapse of FTX &ndash;derailed the sector. However, with regulatory spotlight on the broader industry, the aftermath could have offered a platform for a rebuilding.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to Dowling, the issue of proper legislation is an outcome that Congress is keen on.</p>
<p dir="ltr">And legislation, not just for the stablecoin market but also for the broader digital assets space, would entail clarity. This will in turn help rebuild trust in and across the ecosystem, with clear rules key to the US&rsquo; plans to keep up with the global regulatory landscape.</p>
<p dir="ltr">While some experts have warned about the potential impact of regulation to crypto innovation, Dowling says having the laws in place is critical. For the United States, these could even see it become a global regulatory standard, a scenario likely to provide the foundation for dialogue on crypto regulation on a global level.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">As <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/eu-postpones-final-vote-on-its-mica-regulation/">reported</a> last week, the European Union is looking to finally ratify its comprehensive crypto regulations, the Markets in Crypto-Assets (MiCA). A final vote on the regulation was recently delayed to April.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/stablecoin-legislation-may-come-this-year-bitwise-exec-says/">Stablecoin legislation may come this year, Bitwise exec says</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/stablecoin-legislation-may-come-this-year-bitwise-exec-says/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum launches first &#8216;shadow fork&#8217; for the Shanghai upgrade</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-launches-first-shadow-fork-for-the-shanghai-upgrade/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-launches-first-shadow-fork-for-the-shanghai-upgrade/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 17:30:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-launches-first-shadow-fork-for-the-shanghai-upgrade/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Developers will follow up with more shadow forks ahead of the Shanghai upgrade. The Shanghai upgrade will allow for withdrawal of staked ETH Over 16 million ETH have been locked since Ethereum began the transition from proof of work to proof of stake chain. Ethereum developers have managed to deploy the first &#8220;shadow fork&#8221; of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-launches-first-shadow-fork-for-the-shanghai-upgrade/">Ethereum launches first &#8216;shadow fork&#8217; for the Shanghai upgrade</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>Developers will follow up with more shadow forks ahead of the Shanghai upgrade.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>The Shanghai upgrade will allow for withdrawal of staked ETH</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><strong><em>Over 16 million ETH have been locked since Ethereum began the transition from proof of work to proof of stake chain.</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/">Ethereum</a> developers have managed to deploy the first &ldquo;shadow fork&rdquo; of the upcoming network upgrade Shanghai.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to an <a href="https://twitter.com/vdWijden/status/1617530244302532615" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">update</a> from one of the developers, the shadow fork for the highly anticipated upgrade executed at around 5:40 am ET on Monday 23 January 2023. As a copy of Ethereum&rsquo;s mainnet, the fork is a feature that offers an environment in which developers can test code before it deploys on the public blockchain.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Withdrawal-Mainnet-Shadow-Fork-1 is finalizing &#128640;&#128640;&#128640;</p>
<p>It started out with a few issues because the config wasn't correctly applied on geth (we disallow overriding the mainnet config). The config is applied correctly and all nodes are in agreement. We will start some evil nodes,.</p>
<p>&mdash; MariusVanDerWijden (@vdWijden) <a href="https://twitter.com/vdWijden/status/1617530244302532615?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 23, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">While commenting on the fork this morning, Ethereum Foundation developer Marius Van Der Wijden noted there had been some minor technical glitches with nodes using Geth clients.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, the software developer highlighted that developers managed to fix the hitches, with all nodes being in agreement at the time of his update.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to him, the next step now involves testing with &ldquo;evil nodes&rdquo; on both the execution and consensus layers. Evil nodes are those designed to spam invalid blocks as they attempt to trick other nodes into joining the bad chain, Van Der Wijden explained.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Ethereum&rsquo;s Shanghai upgrade to unlock staked ETH</h2>
<p dir="ltr">As highly anticipated, the Shanghai upgrade will enable withdrawals of staked Ether (ETH) tokens, which remain locked following Ethereum&rsquo;s &ldquo;Merge&rdquo; in September last year. Ethereum&rsquo;s Beacon Chain went live in December 2020 and investors have deposited millions of ETH since.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to on-chain data from Glassnode, more than 16.16 million ETH is currently staked, accounting for just over 13% of the total supply of Ether.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The data also <a href="https://twitter.com/glassnode/status/1617294398613749761" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">shows</a> that more than 11.4 million of the staked ETH was deposited via staking services, including Lido, Coinbase, and Kraken.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">A total of 16.101M <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24ETH&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$ETH</a> is staked on the <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Ethereum?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Ethereum</a> Proof-of-Stake beacon chain (13.4% of circulating).</p>
<p>Of this, 11.408M <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24ETH&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$ETH</a> is via staking service providers, representing 70.86% of the total:</p>
<p>Staking Service Dominance<br>&ndash; Lido: 29.3%<br>&ndash; Coinbase 12.8%<br>&ndash; Kraken 7.6%<br>&ndash; Binance 6.3% <a href="https://t.co/5KAymd56tg">pic.twitter.com/5KAymd56tg</a></p>
<p>&mdash; glassnode (@glassnode) <a href="https://twitter.com/glassnode/status/1617294398613749761?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 22, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-launches-first-shadow-fork-for-the-shanghai-upgrade/">Ethereum launches first &#8216;shadow fork&#8217; for the Shanghai upgrade</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-launches-first-shadow-fork-for-the-shanghai-upgrade/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu (SHIB) Price Prediction &#8211; Metacade Could Surpass SHIB in the Upcoming Months</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-shib-price-prediction-metacade-could-surpass-shib-in-the-upcoming-months/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-shib-price-prediction-metacade-could-surpass-shib-in-the-upcoming-months/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice Davies]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 17:22:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-shib-price-prediction-metacade-could-surpass-shib-in-the-upcoming-months/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>There has been a great deal of criticism of top meme coin projects such as Dogecoin (DOGE) and Shiba Inu since their high-energy communities built up so much momentum and rocketed the projects up the crypto charts. However, both projects have been able to weather the bear market of 2022. So holders will be looking [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-shib-price-prediction-metacade-could-surpass-shib-in-the-upcoming-months/">Shiba Inu (SHIB) Price Prediction &#8211; Metacade Could Surpass SHIB in the Upcoming Months</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">There has been a great deal of criticism of top meme coin projects such as Dogecoin (DOGE) and Shiba Inu since their high-energy communities built up so much momentum and rocketed the projects up the crypto charts.</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, both projects have been able to weather the bear market of 2022. So holders will be looking at Shiba Inu price predictions for 2023 to come to a conclusion about the investment potential of the token.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Many SHIB investors are being drawn to a new and exciting project, <a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade</u></a>, that looks set to deliver much more dramatic gains in 2023. With the challenges that face SHIB and the high potential of the Metacade project, we&rsquo;re likely to see more and more SHIB holders look to capitalize on MCADE&rsquo;s likely rise above SHIB over the coming months.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Metacade?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade is an innovative new project that is planning to provide its users with an incredible and diverse play-to-earn (P2E) arcade. By building around this flagship P2E arcade, Metacade is set to redefine GameFi by creating a community hub that puts gamers first.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Although the P2E arcade is already attracting a lot of attention from savvy investors who can see its potential, the Metacade ecosystem is supported by a host of other complementary features.</p>
<p dir="ltr">An ingenious rewards system is in place throughout the project, with rewards for playing games and winning competitive tournaments hosted on the Metacade platform, and contributing to the community through actions like writing game reviews. This incentivizes users to contribute to the project and is a strategic masterstroke in ensuring the project can build huge momentum.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How does it work?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The project uses a utility and governance token, MCADE, to power the rewards system and as a medium of exchange across the platform. MCADE tokens can also be staked, allowing token holders to earn a passive income, with rewards even provided in stablecoins so as not to increase the circulating supply of MCADE.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade has another innovative mechanism that furthers the success of the platform &mdash; Metagrants. Metagrants will allow game developers to pitch ideas within the Metacade ecosystem, with MCADE token holders able to decide where funding should be allocated. This will help drive engagement and adoption of the platform, as the community gets to give the funds to the projects they are most excited about. &nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Metacade team has understood the importance of the project becoming self-sustaining, so there are a number of different revenue streams set up to support the project on an ongoing basis. This includes on-platform advertising, a gaming launchpad, and competitive tournaments, to name but a few.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Metacade (MCADE) Price Prediction: The sky is the limit</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade boasts a&nbsp;<a href="https://metacade.co/whitepaper.pdf" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>clear strategic plan</u></a> that has considered all elements of ensuring the success of the project. With the GameFi space already showing its robustness, it&rsquo;s well understood that it&rsquo;s a part of Web3 that is set to explode. There&rsquo;s no surprise, then, that the outlook for Metacade is much brighter than the Shiba Inu price prediction.</p>
<p dir="ltr">With the MCADE token selling out fast during its red-hot presale, there&rsquo;s no doubt that the price of MCADE looks very likely to see some dramatic increases over the coming months. With GameFi predicted by many to see a surge in adoption, MCADE could reach as much as $0.50 in 2023 and seems likely to get to $5 before 2025.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Shiba Inu Price Prediction: Can it hold on?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">A challenge that meme coins face is that they rely heavily on the hype built by the community and need momentum to keep rising. While SHIB undoubtedly still has a <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-nears-a-demand-zone-as-the-shib-army-guesses-shibarium-in-countdown/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>significant community of supporters</u></a>, with little real-world utility from the project, it seems unlikely that the project will be able to see the levels of hype it achieved back in 2021.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Shiba Inu price prediction takes this into account, with SHIB needing to focus on holding on to its current price, meaning that if SHIB were to hold $0.000008 by the end of 2023, it would be considered a successful year for the project. Barring any dramatic changes in utility, the token seems likely to begin a slow decline over the next year while the community desperately tries to generate more interest.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Metacade (MCADE) v Shiba Inu (SHIB): Which is better?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">There can be no doubt that MCADE represents a significant opportunity to all investors, and this is likely the driver of huge interest seen thus far in the presale. While SHIB might be able to hang on for a while longer, any serious investor looking for big returns on their investment should be jumping into MCADE and leaving the Shiba Inu community well alone. With this in mind, Metacade seems very likely to surpass SHIB over the coming months.</p>
<p><strong>You can participate in the Metacade presale&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong><u>here</u></strong></a><strong>.</strong></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-shib-price-prediction-metacade-could-surpass-shib-in-the-upcoming-months/">Shiba Inu (SHIB) Price Prediction &#8211; Metacade Could Surpass SHIB in the Upcoming Months</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-shib-price-prediction-metacade-could-surpass-shib-in-the-upcoming-months/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is 2023 A Revamping Year For Crypto Gaming?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/is-2023-a-revamping-year-for-crypto-gaming/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 16:30:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gaming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/is-2023-a-revamping-year-for-crypto-gaming/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto gaming saw robust financing despite the significant decline in blockchain game token prices. Venture capitalists &#8211; the &#8216;real OGs&#8217; &#8211; continue to bet big on leading game studios, with experience and end product key factors. The Web3 game industry is in the &#8220;build&#8221; stage as the hype cycle fades and only the best will [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/is-2023-a-revamping-year-for-crypto-gaming/">Is 2023 A Revamping Year For Crypto Gaming?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>Crypto gaming saw robust financing despite the significant decline in blockchain game token prices.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>Venture capitalists &ndash; the &lsquo;real OGs&rsquo; &ndash; continue to bet big on leading game studios, with experience and end product key factors.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><strong><em>The Web3 game industry is in the &ldquo;build&rdquo; stage as the hype cycle fades and only the best will make it.</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">The history of <a href="https://coinjournal.net/glossary/play-to-earn-play2earn/">play-to-earn games</a> has seen an affirmative change, especially in 2022. The marketplace is still reeling from the sudden rush of capital as well as users, which was followed by a significant decline in the pricing of blockchain game tokens and a fall in the number of players.&nbsp;</p>
<p>And with the aftermath of the FTX debacle spreading to every part of the industry, the prospects for play-to-earn appear to be gloomy at first glance. But if you go under the bonnet, the data paint a different story: robust financing this year has laid the groundwork for significant &ldquo;building&rdquo; in 2023.</p>
<p>For a number of months, the market has been receiving cash thanks to a steady stream of significant fundraisers that have been conducted by Web3 gaming firms. UnCaged studios were able to raise $24 million in the month of August, contributing to the approximately $750 million that was collected by Web3 gaming developers in just that one month.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The momentum carried on through September, when Revolving Games successfully raised $25 million, and into October, when Odyssey Interactive, Stardust, and SkyWeaver, respectively, raised $19 million, $30 million, and $40 million. In November, Thirdverse was successful in raising $15 million in funding for Web3 plus virtual reality (VR) games;</p>
<p>The plummeting asset prices and the player enthusiasm in the Web3 gaming area are completely contradicted by these numbers. Despite the fact that both players and tokens are struggling, venture investors continue to place large bets on <a href="https://coinjournal.net/research-center/blockchain-gaming-statistics/">the potential of blockchain gaming</a>. Who of the studios will emerge victorious in the coming year? To what end?</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Venture capitalists: the real OG has all the power&nbsp;</h2>
<p dir="ltr">It is important to note that the bulk of companies that have been granted money is required to hold seed or pre-seed offerings. This is a requirement that has been consistent across the bulk of the fundraisers that have gone place over the past few months. They are, on the other hand, holding the Series As.</p>
<p>Without a shadow of a doubt, there are a few significant departures from the standard. A number of studios have finished their seed or pre-seed stages with great success. Despite this, the founding teams of these companies have significant gaming experience.&nbsp;</p>
<p>As an illustration, Ruckus Games is a video game development studio that was recently able to secure early funding in the amount of $5.5 million.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This suggests that venture capitalists are shifting their attention to studios that already have experience in the game industry, which is a divergence from the initial periods of Web3 gaming.</p>
<p>During that early stage, a great number of Web3 gaming companies were given substantial money despite the fact that they lacked either a distinct plan for the launching of their goods or founding teams that have the demonstrated experience necessary to make it happen.</p>
<p>In point of fact, the YOLO times of late 2021, as well as early 2022, are a distant memory at this point. The game development studios that are currently receiving financing have already demonstrated some amount of success in the creation of Web3 games.&nbsp;</p>
<p>These days, venture capitalists are looking even further into the future, anywhere from 5 to 10 years down the line.</p>
<p>Simultaneously, there are other AI-supporting <a href="https://coinjournal.net/compare/best-crypto-trading-bots/">trading bots</a> like immediate edge which have widened the investing scope for venture capitalists alongwith giving investors a variety of investing options in terms of purchasing different digital currencies.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Crypto gaming: the advances to witness&nbsp;</h2>
<p dir="ltr">When we consider these increases in conjunction with the longer-term tendencies shown in Web3 gaming, investors can begin to see that certain patterns are emerging to influence the future of the industry.</p>
<p>The question now is, what kind of an effect will all of the pay increases have in the coming years?</p>
<p>Mobile gaming is almost certain to receive a significant amount of attention. According to a report published by DappRadar in September, hyper-casual smartphone blockchain games successfully transitioned over 1.7 million gamers from Web2 gaming to Web3 gaming in just one week.</p>
<p>It does seem probable that Web3 gameplay will gain entry into the &ldquo;mainstream&rdquo; as a result of the changes that are currently taking place, and that over the next 5 years, the global score of the 100 best gaming studios will include studios that have powerful blockchain elements.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This forecast is founded on the observation that the aforementioned transformations are taking place right now.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In addition to that, there are a number of reliable trade assistance bots like <a href="https://immediateedgepro.com" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">immediate edge</a> which are allowing traders to redeem their earned game points into crypto and utilize it for versatile usage.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What&rsquo;s coming next?&nbsp;</h2>
<p dir="ltr">There is a good chance that we haven&rsquo;t seen the conclusion of the large-scale funding rounds that have been taking place in the Web3 gaming industry over the past few months.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The hype cycle surrounding Web 3 gaming has finally come to an end, and the market is currently in the &ldquo;build&rdquo; period. This time around, investors are searching for companies that have a perspective on their operations that is more long-term focused.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This shift in emphasis, when coupled with the enormous shifts that have been taking place in the blockchain technology industry as a whole, is going to produce new dynamics and chances for developers in the P2E market in the year 2023.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The expectations of the players as well as the funders will need to be raised in order to sort the wheat from the chaff.&nbsp;</p>
<p>When it comes to determining priorities after the year 2023, the quality of the work will be given more weight than the quantity. Those who are able to develop the most remarkable games will emerge victorious in the end. The real game has just begun NOW.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/is-2023-a-revamping-year-for-crypto-gaming/">Is 2023 A Revamping Year For Crypto Gaming?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Revolution of DeFi Ecosystem: The Wave of Decentralised Identity Solutions Is Here to Stay!</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/revolution-of-defi-ecosystem-the-wave-of-decentralised-identity-solutions-is-here-to-stay/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/revolution-of-defi-ecosystem-the-wave-of-decentralised-identity-solutions-is-here-to-stay/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 15:37:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/revolution-of-defi-ecosystem-the-wave-of-decentralised-identity-solutions-is-here-to-stay/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Introduction to decentralised identities, or DIDs and the non-fungible token (NFTs) space. Decentralised identity and use of zero-knowledge proof (ZKP) innovation. Other benefits, including protection for the regular user. There is still a lot of &#8220;wild west&#8221; in decentralised finance (DeFi) today. There is no clear rule of law since there are so many competing [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/revolution-of-defi-ecosystem-the-wave-of-decentralised-identity-solutions-is-here-to-stay/">Revolution of DeFi Ecosystem: The Wave of Decentralised Identity Solutions Is Here to Stay!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>Introduction to decentralised identities, or DIDs and the non-fungible token (NFTs) space.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>Decentralised identity and use of zero-knowledge proof (ZKP) innovation.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><strong><em>Other benefits, including protection for the regular user.</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">There is still a lot of &ldquo;wild west&rdquo; in decentralised finance (<a href="https://coinjournal.net/glossary/defi/">DeFi</a>) today. There is no clear rule of law since there are so many competing factions, each with its own set of claims and goals.</p>
<p>As a result, some users have had unfavourable experiences after venturing into the ecosystem for the first time. Users&rsquo; faith is shaken when they hear accounts of scams and &ldquo;rug pulls,&rdquo; and when algorithmic processes fail due to unfavourable market conditions. In spite of the best efforts of the people working on DeFi projects, many users still find the technology intimidating and <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-problem-of-identity-theft-and-blockchain-era-ways-to-address-it/">risky</a>.</p>
<p>Many people are still wary of the cryptocurrency world due to the dangerous services and unregulated atmosphere. Individual and institutional investors alike are frightened of and confused by <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/defi/">DeFi</a>. The burning question now is how and when non-Degens will be able to fully embrace DeFi.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Ingress of decentralised IDs</h2>
<p dir="ltr">DeFi&rsquo;s foundational technology also happens to be the key to bypassing the problem at hand. Decentralised identities, or DIDs, are the answer. DIDs can provide reliable data to legislators by utilising blockchains, smart contracts, plus <a href="https://coinjournal.net/glossary/non-fungible-token-nft/">non-fungible tokens</a> (NFTs), all while protecting users&rsquo; independence and anonymity.</p>
<p>The cryptographic infrastructure allows for this, and NFTs in particular, is vital to making this a reality. In its role as an asset, an NFT is verifiably distinct from all other commodities and comes with its own history, which can contain any kind of information. No one can forge or change an NFT because of the underpinning decentralised protocols.</p>
<p>As expected, more is required for a fully realised digital persona. In addition, there must be transparency and clarity regarding who owns which DIDs. To this end, a person&rsquo;s DID can be connected to their physical identity verification processes.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This could be accomplished in a variety of methods, for as by using biometric data, real-world papers, or other confirmations that can be independently verified. A profile that cannot be faked has been developed by combining all these data in an NFT.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">The usage authority&nbsp;</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Privacy activists might reject the notion on the grounds that it is overly stringent and comprehensive. When all is said and done, an accurate account of a person&rsquo;s data being stored on a bitcoin ledger for all of eternity does not sound particularly private, does it? The next advantage of DIDs comes into play in this context, in tandem with using <a href="https://coinjournal.net/glossary/zero-knowledge-proof/">zero-knowledge proof</a> (ZKP) innovation.</p>
<p>Using ZKP technology, information can be validated once by a third party that is not involved in the verification process, and then it can be used to verify someone&rsquo;s credentials.&nbsp;</p>
<p>As a consequence of this, an individual will be able to demonstrate their access, records, or background without necessarily disclosing their name or any other personally identifiable information to the person conducting the verification.</p>
<p>In this paradigm, individuals would have full control over their own information and would be able to provide rights to verifiers over what can be viewed and when it may be seen.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The information included on IDs would no longer have to be a free-for-all for companies and governments to exploit whenever they see fit.&nbsp;</p>
<p>These objectives not only contribute to the preservation of individual rights, but they also bring with them a variety of potential applications in the real world.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In addition to that, <a href="https://the-etherum-code.com" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">click here</a> and get further details regarding trade assistance bots to further get enlightened about advanced trading rights. &nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">The paragon of trust </h2>
<p dir="ltr">This method may make the DeFi revolution accessible to everyone, from first-time investors to multinational conglomerates. A DID could be crafted in such a way that it is always compliant with the law in a particular jurisdiction, so satisfying the authorities and preventing any violations.&nbsp;</p>
<p>As a result, all types of financial and commercial transactions might be conducted more efficiently, with a corresponding decrease in fraud.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The best part is that regular people might be able to take charge of their data and safeguard themselves from harm.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Instant realisation&nbsp;</h3>
<p dir="ltr">What needs to be acknowledged is the fact that this is not merely an interesting concept; rather, it is already a reality. Decentralised mechanisms have been created to cater to exactly such types of IDs, and people are already being utilised in several businesses.&nbsp;</p>
<p>These IDs are becoming increasingly common. Soon, more companies will begin using comparable solutions for their consumers, which will ultimately result in increased safety and tranquillity for everyone.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Role of regulators&nbsp;</h3>
<p dir="ltr">Although it is true that the acts of regulators will play a part in assisting risk-averse investors in taking the plunge into this new arena, it is also true that the actions of regulators alone will not be sufficient.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This is due to the fact that freedom and responsibility both need to be balanced. Decentralised Identification offers what is required now and will continue to offer for a significant amount of time into the future of DeFi, regardless of where this fascinating new business takes us.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Conclusion: Is the DeFi usage spectrum broadened?&nbsp;</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Bringing this discussion back around to DeFi, it is becoming more apparent how DIDs might be used to introduce transparency and confidence into this sphere without compromising decentralisation or privacy.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Customers and service providers are both able to make use of these profiles, which creates knowable entities on decentralised platforms without necessarily revealing the identity of the consumer.&nbsp;</p>
<p>For instance, certain functionalities or dApps may require the use of DIDs that have been appropriately verified in order to gain access to them. Nevertheless, the necessary service might not be necessary in order to validate the identity of the holder.</p>
<p>The DeFi services themselves may have their very own DIDs, which operate in a manner analogous to that described above. These DIDs serve as an instant and irreversible history and evidence of repute.&nbsp;</p>
<p>When put into place, a system like this would serve to deter harmful actions by producing consequences that have real-world significance for people who take part in them. All of this might be carried out without the holder being subjected to intrusive surveillance or having their full knowledge.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/revolution-of-defi-ecosystem-the-wave-of-decentralised-identity-solutions-is-here-to-stay/">Revolution of DeFi Ecosystem: The Wave of Decentralised Identity Solutions Is Here to Stay!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/revolution-of-defi-ecosystem-the-wave-of-decentralised-identity-solutions-is-here-to-stay/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Sandbox (SAND) Price Forecast &#8211; Why Metacade (MCADE) Will Outperform SAND in 2023</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/the-sandbox-sand-price-forecast-why-metacade-mcade-will-outperform-sand-in-2023/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/the-sandbox-sand-price-forecast-why-metacade-mcade-will-outperform-sand-in-2023/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice Davies]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 15:02:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/the-sandbox-sand-price-forecast-why-metacade-mcade-will-outperform-sand-in-2023/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Sandbox is one of crypto&#8217;s metaverse first-movers, but its epic decline during the 2022 bear market has left some investors dismayed. Are you wondering what&#8217;s in store for this leading metaverse token? Below, you&#8217;ll find a The Sandbox price forecast for 2023 and learn about Metacade &#8211; a project that many have predicted could [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-sandbox-sand-price-forecast-why-metacade-mcade-will-outperform-sand-in-2023/">The Sandbox (SAND) Price Forecast &#8211; Why Metacade (MCADE) Will Outperform SAND in 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">The Sandbox is one of crypto&rsquo;s metaverse first-movers, but its epic decline during the 2022 bear market has left some investors dismayed. Are you wondering what&rsquo;s in store for this leading metaverse token? Below, you&rsquo;ll find a The Sandbox price forecast for 2023 and learn about Metacade &ndash; a project that many have predicted could significantly outperform SAND this year.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">The Sandbox (SAND) has failed to attract players</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://www.sandbox.game/en/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>The Sandbox</u></a> is an Ethereum-based virtual world where users can truly own and monetize their creations. Set in an open-world sandbox, the platform lets players explore their creativity and use a selection of tools to generate immersive experiences for others to play.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Sandbox utilizes NFTs to represent in-game assets, like LAND and ASSETS, enabling them to be bought and sold on the open market. It&rsquo;s one of the leading metaverse crypto projects, alongside Decentraland, which saw its SAND token spike in price after Facebook, now Meta, announced its foray into the metaverse.</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, the hype fizzled out during 2022&rsquo;s bear market, sending the price of SAND plummeting. After reaching a high of $8.48 in November 2021, SAND has recently made a low of $0.37 &ndash; an approximate 95.6% decline.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">This is partly down to a lack of adoption by regular players. Since the start of 2021, The Sandbox has struggled to attract more than 1,000 users per day for a sustained period of time, often clocking in just hundreds of users (DappRadar). Compare that to traditional metaverse games like Roblox and Fortnite, which have millions of daily active users, and The Sandbox seems a little overvalued.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">The Sandbox (SAND) Price Forecast</h2>
<p dir="ltr">SAND has seen somewhat of a resurgence in January. After hitting its $0.37 low, SAND has rallied to make a high of $0.71 in around two weeks. However, this area is expected to pose significant resistance, according to The Sandbox price forecasts. In the short term, many experts The Sandbox price forecasts have set targets for as low as $0.54. Over the longer term, some analysts predict that SAND could collapse to $0.24 if its user count doesn&rsquo;t pick up soon.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Metacade (MCADE) is setting the standard for gaming communities</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade</u></a> is a play-to-earn (P2E) community hub that, like The Sandbox, is aiming to revolutionize ownership in gaming. Instead of giving players ownership of their in-game assets, however, Metacade empowers them to truly own the community they call home.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Fundamentally speaking, Metacade has everything you&rsquo;d expect from a social gaming platform, like forums, reviews, game leaderboards, and tournaments. But, by harnessing the benefits of crypto and decentralization, it&rsquo;s expected to kickstart a new paradigm in the way social platforms are operated.</p>
<p dir="ltr">For instance, it&rsquo;s launching the Metagrants scheme late this year. Metagrants give MCADE holders voting rights to determine which game developers should be awarded funding from the Metacade treasury. Dozens of developers will go head-to-head to battle it out and earn the most votes in each Metagrant competition, with the winner being given financing to build their vision. They even have the opportunity to use Metacade&rsquo;s native testing environment to receive feedback on their games from its most avid supporters.</p>
<p dir="ltr">These community-backed titles are then added to Metacade&rsquo;s virtual arcade for anyone to play. With the potential to be responsible for creating some of the best P2E games the world has ever seen, Metacade could soon be in the spotlight if just one game takes off.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">In 2024, Metacade will become a <a href="https://www.investopedia.com/tech/what-dao/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>decentralized autonomous organization (DAO)</u></a> and complete its final step toward becoming the world&rsquo;s first player-owned virtual arcade. From here, the direction of the project will be determined by the community, with members of the collective stepping up to take leadership roles. They&rsquo;ll be able to decide which upgrades are implemented, whether to accept new partnerships, and even set the token supply burn rate &ndash; a move that could steadily increase the price of MCADE over time.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Metacade (MCADE) Price Forecast</h2>
<p dir="ltr">In comparison to The Sandbox&rsquo;s price forecast, Metacade is expected to outperform SAND this year. Its MCADE token presale has been a roaring success, selling over $1.12 million in the beta sale. Currently, in phase 2 of its presale, Metacade has raised over $3.2 million while the MCADE token has increased 50%, as planned, &nbsp;to $0.012 from its initial price of $0.008. By the time the presale is over, it&rsquo;s predicted to climb as high as $0.02, meaning the earliest investors could be up 150%!&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">With the GameFi industry likely to make significant steps in 2023, Metacade could be the hottest P2E token out there. Analysts have begun to forecast prices of $0.20 by the end of the year, with some even predicting it could reach $0.50 &ndash; up 2,400% from its projected final presale price.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Metacade (MCADE) seems certain to outperform The Sandbox</h2>
<p dir="ltr">By now, it&rsquo;s clear to see that MCADE is a better investment choice than SAND. While The Sandbox has certainly pioneered crypto-based metaverses, its lack of adoption is unlikely to change anytime soon. This is why so many The Sandbox price forecasts predict that reclaiming the $8 zone is an almost impossible target over the next few years; there&rsquo;s simply not enough demand.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Meanwhile, Metacade has everything to gain and virtually nothing to lose. Its MCADE token presale has already attracted thousands of investors and plenty of media attention, and it seems like the current $3.2 million raised is only the beginning. If you&rsquo;re thinking of investing in SAND &ndash; stop. Take a moment to flick through <a href="https://metacade.co/whitepaper.pdf" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade&rsquo;s whitepaper</u></a> and see why some are calling it the best P2E token of 2023.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>You can buy The Sandbox (SAND) at eToro&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://coinjournal.net/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=OTk5MDM" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong><u>here</u></strong></a><strong>.</strong></p>
<p><strong>You can participate in the Metacade presale&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong><u>here</u></strong></a><strong>.</strong></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-sandbox-sand-price-forecast-why-metacade-mcade-will-outperform-sand-in-2023/">The Sandbox (SAND) Price Forecast &#8211; Why Metacade (MCADE) Will Outperform SAND in 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/the-sandbox-sand-price-forecast-why-metacade-mcade-will-outperform-sand-in-2023/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Proposal to deploy Uniswap v3 on BNB Chain gets 80% support</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/proposal-to-deploy-uniswap-v3-on-bnb-chain-gets-80-support/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/proposal-to-deploy-uniswap-v3-on-bnb-chain-gets-80-support/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 14:58:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[UNI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uniswap News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/proposal-to-deploy-uniswap-v3-on-bnb-chain-gets-80-support/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>0xPlasma Labs&#8217;s proposal seeks to have Uniswap v3 deployed on the BNB Chain. Uniswap could benefit from an ecosystem with nearly $1.2 billion in TVL and a large, growing user base. The proposal is expected to go to a final governance vote in coming weeks. Decentralised exchange Uniswap&#8216;s v3 protocol could be deployed on the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/proposal-to-deploy-uniswap-v3-on-bnb-chain-gets-80-support/">Proposal to deploy Uniswap v3 on BNB Chain gets 80% support</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr"><strong>0xPlasma Labs&rsquo;s proposal seeks to have Uniswap v3 deployed on the BNB Chain.</strong></li>
<li dir="ltr"><strong>Uniswap could benefit from an ecosystem with nearly $1.2 billion in TVL and a large, growing user base.</strong></li>
<li dir="ltr"><strong>The proposal is expected to go to a final governance vote in coming weeks.</strong></li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Decentralised exchange <a href="https://coinjournal.net/uniswap/">Uniswap</a>&lsquo;s v3 protocol could be deployed on the BNB Chain after a majority of participants in a community vote on the proposal gave the move a thumbs up.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">0xPlasma Labs proposal for Uniswap v3 approved by community</h2>
<p dir="ltr">According to 0xPlasma Labs, a decentralised finance (DeFi) and Metaverse NFTs platform, an initial vote on the proposal saw 80.28% of participants approve it. 0xPlasma Labs introduced the Uniswap proposal on 12 December 2022, with an announcement it shared on 22 January 2023 showing that 6,495 holders of Uniswap native token UNI voted in favour.</p>
<p dir="ltr">About 20 million tokens were locked as part of the process, with this &ldquo;temperature check&rdquo; representing &ldquo;the biggest number for the whole Uniswap Governance History.&rdquo; About 4.9 million UNI tokens, or roughly 19.72% of the holders were against the move.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">&#129412; We&rsquo;re excited to share that our <a href="https://twitter.com/0xPlasma?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@0xPlasma</a> proposal to deploy <a href="https://twitter.com/Uniswap?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@Uniswap</a> v3 on <a href="https://twitter.com/BNBCHAIN?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@BNBCHAIN</a> has passed the "Temperature Check" with 20M votes "YES" and 6,495 <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24UNI&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$UNI</a> voters (the biggest number for the whole Uniswap Governance History). <br>Moving forward to the final "Governance Proposal" <a href="https://t.co/HoIJgY8mX1">pic.twitter.com/HoIJgY8mX1</a></p>
<p>&mdash; 0xPlasma Labs: DeFi &amp; NFT Metaverse &#129415; &#128266; (@0xPlasma) <a href="https://twitter.com/0xPlasma/status/1617022128414687232?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 22, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Benefits to the Unswap ecosystem</h2>
<p dir="ltr">0xPlasma Labs noted in their <a href="https://snapshot.org/#/uniswap/proposal/0xa3c7247632d3a08e4e73a63867908d0cd4402f48fa673945f93e3197dee5450a" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">proposal</a> that deploying Uniswap v3 on the BNB Chain could bring several benefits to the DEX ecosystem. For one, the BNB Chain has a huge user base that&rsquo;s still growing, something that could see Uniswap benefit from a potential new market.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Additionally, BNB Chain&rsquo;s high transaction speeds and low fees are key features that will benefit Uniswap&rsquo;s decentralised exchange services and DeFi (BNB Chain has a total value locked, or TVL, of about $1.2 billion.)</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>BNB Chain&rsquo;s strong governance model and active community could provide valuable support and feedback for the development of Uniswap v3</em>,&rdquo; the 0xPlasma Labs team wrote.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The approval means the proposal is set for the final governance vote expected within coming weeks.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/proposal-to-deploy-uniswap-v3-on-bnb-chain-gets-80-support/">Proposal to deploy Uniswap v3 on BNB Chain gets 80% support</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/proposal-to-deploy-uniswap-v3-on-bnb-chain-gets-80-support/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoins hedge narrative is dead, as speculative price action continues</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoins-hedge-narrative-is-dead-as-speculative-price-action-continues/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoins-hedge-narrative-is-dead-as-speculative-price-action-continues/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dan Ashmore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 13:50:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoins-hedge-narrative-is-dead-as-speculative-price-action-continues/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key Takeaways Crypto has risen to start the year off the back of expectations that interest rates may be cut sooner than anticipated This contrasts with the view that crypto is uncorrelated, proving it false Assessing the price action of crypto through the pandemic and subsequent rate-raising cycle shows an extremely risky asset class that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoins-hedge-narrative-is-dead-as-speculative-price-action-continues/">Bitcoins hedge narrative is dead, as speculative price action continues</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2><strong>Key Takeaways</strong></h2>
<ul>
<li>Crypto has risen to start the year off the back of expectations that interest rates may be cut sooner than anticipated</li>
<li>This contrasts with the view that crypto is uncorrelated, proving it false</li>
<li>Assessing the price action of crypto through the pandemic and subsequent rate-raising cycle shows an extremely risky asset class that moves in line with other speculative asset classes</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p>Over the last couple of months, markets have turned green off the back of <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/what-to-expect-in-crypto-ahead-of-inflation-report-as-bitcoin-banks-eight-straight-days-of-gains/">inflation data softening</a> around the globe. Crypto hasn&rsquo;t been left off the invite list, with digital assets surging to their strongest <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-prices-surge-via-strongest-rally-in-9-months-but-why/">rally in 9 months</a>.</p>
<p>If there was ever any doubt (and by now, there really shouldn&rsquo;t be), this proves once and for all that any narrative around crypto being an uncorrelated asset is dead.</p>
        <div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/12520344">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<h2><strong>Pandemic bull run</strong></h2>
<p>To quickly recap on the last few years in cryptoland, the asset class initially moved violently upward as central banks worldwide pursued ultra-low interest rate policy.</p>
<p>As economies ground to a halt for the ultimate black swan, the COVID-19 pandemic, nations faced a highly uncertain outlook in Q1 of 2020. With lockdowns sweeping the world, central banks were forced to do what they could to stimulate these abruptly-shut societies.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Out came stimulus packages of an unprecedented scale.&nbsp;</p>
        <div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/12520480">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p>With all this stimulus and generationally cheap money, risk assets went bananas. The biggest leader of all was cryptocurrency. Some argued that the assets were rising as a result of the inevitable inflation that would result from all this expansionary monetary policy, as crypto was a hedge against the fiat system. The argument wouldn&rsquo;t hold.</p>
<h2><strong>The transition to a new interest rate paradigm</strong></h2>
<p>The year 2022 did indeed bring a spike in inflation, and this time central banks were forced to do the opposite &ndash; aggressively hike rates as the cost of living spiralled relentlessly.</p>
<p>This has reined in risk assets, as per the playbook. Liquidity is sucked out of the system, suppressing demand. Investors now have alternate vehicles in which to park their wealth and earn a yield, with government-guaranteed T-bills now offering reasonable alternatives, as opposed to the zero rates previously (or negative in some nations).</p>
        <div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/12432907">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p>But cryptocurrency followed the rest of the world&rsquo;s risk assets down. Not only that, but the scale of the meltdown in the sector was unlike anything we have seen in a major asset class in a long time. <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> shaved over three-quarters of its market cap, and it came out favourably compared to altcoins, many of which were decimated.</p>
<p>And now, the last couple of months have brought more optimistic readings regarding inflation. The numbers are still scary, but just a little bit of positivity has crept in that the worst may have passed. Of course, there is still a war ongoing in Europe and now fear has elevated that a recession may be imminent (if not here already), but hey &ndash; let&rsquo;s celebrate whatever wins we can. &nbsp;</p>
<p>The stock market has cautiously crept upwards, as the market moves to the expectation that high interest rates will cease sooner than previously expected.</p>
<p>The only thing is, crypto has also risen. Not only that, but it has printed gains which blow the moves in equity markets out of the water.</p>
<p>Which, you know, kind of suggests that this may not be an inflation hedge at all. As inflation comes back down and the likelihood of lower rates and another expansionary period grows, crypto rises. Go figure.</p>
        <div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/12521888">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<h2><strong>Correlation vs stock market remains high</strong></h2>
<p>The proof is in the pudding. It is pretty clear by simply looking at the price chart of S&amp;P 500 vs Bitcoin that the correlation here is stark &ndash; with the key lurking variable being interest rates.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Quite literally, crypto is the opposite of an uncorrelated asset &ndash; it has moved in lockstep with the stock market for the last few years.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Interestingly, there have been periods of decoupling, however. Unfortunately, they have come amid crypto-specific crashes. To show this, I plotted the Bitcoin/S&amp;P 500 correlation against the Bitcoin price over the last couple of years.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The correlation has been high, aside from a few noticeable periods &ndash; all occurring when the Bitcoin price plummeted. The most recent example was November 2022, when crypto wobbled amid the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ftx-insolvent-what-next-for-crypto/">FTX crash</a>.&nbsp;</p>
        <div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/12521914">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p>There really is no debate here. Crypto is a highly correlated, extreme-risk asset. The only question is whether it can shed this moniker in the long term. But any thought contesting that it is not currently wildly speculative is wide of the mark.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoins-hedge-narrative-is-dead-as-speculative-price-action-continues/">Bitcoins hedge narrative is dead, as speculative price action continues</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoins-hedge-narrative-is-dead-as-speculative-price-action-continues/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Axie Infinity price shoots up 40% today: todays top gainer</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/axie-infinity-price-shoots-up-40-today-todays-top-gainer/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 12:43:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/axie-infinity-price-shoots-up-40-today-todays-top-gainer/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Axie Infinity (AXS) has hit a high of $13.83 today. AXS is today&#8217;s top gainer followed by STEPN coin. Here is a deep dive into what is causing today&#8217;s price surge. After a calm weekend with most cryptocurrencies consolidating their previous gains, Axie Infinity has started the week with a bang after climbing to a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/axie-infinity-price-shoots-up-40-today-todays-top-gainer/">Axie Infinity price shoots up 40% today: todays top gainer</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul class="decimal_type">
<li>Axie Infinity (AXS) has hit a high of $13.83 today.</li>
<li>AXS is today&rsquo;s top gainer followed by STEPN coin.</li>
<li>Here is a deep dive into what is causing today&rsquo;s price surge.</li>
</ul>
<p>After a calm weekend with most cryptocurrencies consolidating their previous gains, <a href="https://axieinfinity.com/">Axie Infinity</a> has started the week with a bang after climbing to a four-month high of $13.83.</p>
<p>AXS has traded below $12 since mid-September and dropped to as low as $6 towards the end of 2022. The token has however turned the tables and staged a steady recovery since the start of 2023 with today being one of the greatest days for the token in recent history.&nbsp;</p>
<p>At press time, the token was trading at $12.86 after a slight pullback from a high of $13.83.</p>
<p>But what is pushing the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/axie-infinity/">price of AXS&nbsp;</a>up and how far will it go? Here are the forces behind today&rsquo;s AXS rally.</p>
<h2>What is pushing Axie Infinity price up?</h2>
<p>Although the crypto winter brought the price of the Axie Infinity token down from its all-time high (ATH) of $165.37 to trading below $10, the increased gaming activity on the Axie Infinity blockchain is largely behind the ongoing bullish price action.</p>
<p>Axie Infinity is branded as a blockchain-based battling game owned and operated by players around the world. Inspired by such games as Tamagotchi and Pok&eacute;mon, and the ability of players to collect, breed, raise, battle, and trade token-based creatures the Axie Infinity ecosystem has seen increased growth since the start of 2023.</p>
<p>Axie Infinity currently ranks as the most successful <a href="https://coinjournal.net/glossary/play-to-earn-play2earn/">play-to-earn (P2E)</a> game within the blockchain industry and the booming sentiment among gaming tokens has also boosted AXS performance with many investors now anxious to see what the future holds for the token.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/axie-infinity-price-shoots-up-40-today-todays-top-gainer/">Axie Infinity price shoots up 40% today: todays top gainer</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
