<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 14:50:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>PAWSWAP price plunge as trillions of PAW are staked</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/pawswap-price-plunge-as-trillions-of-paw-are-staked/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/pawswap-price-plunge-as-trillions-of-paw-are-staked/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 14:50:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/pawswap-price-plunge-as-trillions-of-paw-are-staked/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>At press time, the PAW token had dropped 10.90%. PawSwap team yesterday launched its PAW Staking Mainnet. So far about 200 trillion PAW tokens have been staked on the mainnet. Contrary to the expectations of many, the PAWSWAP (PAW) price has plunged after about 200 trillion PAW tokens are staked on the PAW Staking Mainnet [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/pawswap-price-plunge-as-trillions-of-paw-are-staked/">PAWSWAP price plunge as trillions of PAW are staked</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>At press time, the PAW token had dropped 10.90%.</li>
<li>PawSwap team yesterday launched its PAW Staking Mainnet.</li>
<li>So far about 200 trillion PAW tokens have been staked on the mainnet.</li>
</ul>
<p>Contrary to the expectations of many, the <a href="https://pawecosystem.com/">PAWSWAP (PAW)</a> price has plunged after about 200 trillion PAW tokens are staked on the PAW Staking Mainnet which was launched on April 30, 2023. Interestingly, it has taken less than 24 hours for so many PAW tokens to be staked.</p>
<p>Normally, such a great reduction of token supply would result in a significant price surge but that has not been the case for PAWSWAP, whose price had rather dropped by 10.68% at press time. The staked PAW tokens account for 0.2% of the total PAW token supply.</p>
<h2>PawSwap roadmap</h2>
<p>The launch of the mainnet for staking is the first major product to be launched for the PAW ecosystem. The project has a robust roadmap including PawChain blockchain and cross-chain decentralized exchange (PawSwap), focusing on security, speed, and a user-friendly experience for trading crypto assets.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">The PAW Staking Mainnet is Live! </p>
<p>We are happy to report our staking platform, which is our first major PAW Ecosystem product delivery, has been deployed.</p>
<p>You can visit <a href="https://t.co/VVNxUpRThp">https://t.co/VVNxUpRThp</a> to get started and get staking!</p>
<p>In the next few days, the PAW team will provide the&hellip; <a href="https://t.co/LjsGxfiC7w">pic.twitter.com/LjsGxfiC7w</a></p>
<p>&mdash; PAWChain (@PawChain) <a href="https://twitter.com/PawChain/status/1652720641408114691?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">April 30, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>CertiK has already confirmed that the newly launched mainnet &ldquo;meets their standards.&rdquo; In addition, the PawSwap team also said that it will be chairing a report on the audit status of the mainnet with its community.</p>
<p>The PawSwap team started with the launch of the PAW token on the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/what-is-ethereum/">Ethereum network</a> and has now launched the PAW Staking Mainnet.</p>
<p>While the launch of the staking mainnet and the subsequent token staking seem not to have stirred a bullish PAWSWAP price movement, the launch of the PawChain blockchain and cross-chain decentralized exchange (PawSwap) is expected to increase PAW token demand which could, in turn, result in a price surge for the PAW token.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/pawswap-price-plunge-as-trillions-of-paw-are-staked/">PAWSWAP price plunge as trillions of PAW are staked</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/pawswap-price-plunge-as-trillions-of-paw-are-staked/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>MCADE tops $0.027 as analysts turn bullish on First Republic Bank saga</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/mcade-tops-0-027-as-analysts-turn-bullish-on-first-republic-sage/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 13:45:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/mcade-tops-0-027-as-analysts-turn-bullish-on-first-republic-sage/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways MCADE has topped the $0.027 mark as the cryptocurrency market begins to recover. First Republic Bank has been acquired by JPMorgan Chase as the banking woes in the United States banking sector continue. The banking woes have boosted Bitcoin&#8217;s position as a safe haven asset.&#160; Analysts are becoming bullish on Bitcoin and the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/mcade-tops-0-027-as-analysts-turn-bullish-on-first-republic-sage/">MCADE tops $0.027 as analysts turn bullish on First Republic Bank saga</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">MCADE has topped the $0.027 mark as the cryptocurrency market begins to recover.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">First Republic Bank has been acquired by JPMorgan Chase as the banking woes in the United States banking sector continue.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The banking woes have boosted Bitcoin&rsquo;s position as a safe haven asset.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Analysts are becoming bullish on Bitcoin and the broader cryptocurrency market thanks to the recent banking woes in the United States. MCADE is up by more than 2% in the last 24 hours and could rally higher as the broader crypto market looks to embark on a recovery.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">JPMorgan acquires First Republic Bank</h2>
<p dir="ltr">JPMorgan Chase, one of the leading banks in the United States, has acquired the troubled First Republic Bank.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">This&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">latest cryptocurrency news</a> comes after the First Republic Bank was seized by the California Department of Financial Protection and Innovation.</p>
<p dir="ltr">JPMorgan Chase will assume all assets of the embattled bank ding uninsured deposits. First Republic Bank currently has $229.1 billion in assets and $103.9 billion in deposits.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Following the acquisition, 84 locations of First Republic Bank in eight states will now reopen as JPMorgan Chase. Furthermore, all depositors of the troubled bank will become a part of JPMorgan and have access to their total deposits insured by FDIC.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">First Republic Bank&rsquo;s collapse is the third major one in the United States since the start of the year, a cause for concern amongst investors in the country,&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Crypto experts are predicting a bullish run for Bitcoin</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The recent banking woes have been favourable to the cryptocurrency sector. According to Standard Chartered analyst Geoff Kendrick, the recent events could see <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/04/24/bitcoin-btc-price-could-hit-100000-by-end-2024-standard-chartered.html" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Bitcoin rally to $100,000 by 2024</u></a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In a note following First Republic Bank&rsquo;s woes, Kendrick said;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;We see the potential for Bitcoin (BTC) to reach the USD 100,000 level by end-2024, as we believe the much-touted &lsquo;crypto winter&rsquo; is finally over. The current stress in the traditional banking sector is highly conducive to BTC outperformance &ndash; and validates the original premise for Bitcoin as a decentralised, trustless and scarce digital asset,&rdquo;</em></p>
<p dir="ltr">Bloomberg Intelligence&rsquo;s <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-04-30/bitcoin-s-btc-four-month-winning-run-brings-100-000-in-view-if-history-right#xj4y7vzkg" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Jamie Douglas Coutts also pointed out</u></a> that Bitcoin could be on course for the longest streak of monthly gains since 2021. He stipulated that if 1% of global bond-market value moved toward Bitcoin, that would take BTC&rsquo;s price to $185,000.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The FOMC meeting this week could see the Federal Reserve increase interest rates by 25 basis points as it continues to fight against inflation.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">MCADE could rally higher in line with Bitcoin</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The continued banking crisis in the United States could boost cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin, Ether, and Metacade in the short and medium term. More investors could see assets like BTC and MCADE as safe havens compared to the traditional financial ecosystem.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In addition to that, if the Federal Reserve adopts a more dovish approach to its interest rate hikes later this week, Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies could greatly benefit.</p>
<p dir="ltr">MCADE is currently trading at $0.0275 per coin and is close to the $0.034 all-time high price it set roughly two weeks ago.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">With MCADE set to list on the MEXC cryptocurrency exchange in a few days, the token will become available to millions of people globally, and this could boost its value in the near term.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">MCADE listed on Uniswap and BitMart last month and is set to list on MEXC this week. The token could also launch on several other cryptocurrency exchanges over the next few weeks and months.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Is Metacade a good investment?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">MCADE could be one of the tokens to watch out for as an investor in the cryptocurrency space. The token has been performing well since the pre-sale event was concluded, and Metacade raised $16 million.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As the Metacade team works on its GameFi platform and also listing on other exchanges, MCADE&rsquo;s value could experience a massive surge over the next few weeks and months.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Experts believe that the GameFi industry could experience a surge in value over the next few years, and Metacade could be one of the biggest winners.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/mcade-tops-0-027-as-analysts-turn-bullish-on-first-republic-sage/">MCADE tops $0.027 as analysts turn bullish on First Republic Bank saga</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Metacade Releases on Multiple Exchanges as ApeCoin Price Enjoys Rally. Which Token is the Better Investment?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-releases-on-multiple-exchanges-as-apecoin-price-enjoys-rally-which-token-is-the-better-investment/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-releases-on-multiple-exchanges-as-apecoin-price-enjoys-rally-which-token-is-the-better-investment/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice Davies]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 13:33:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-releases-on-multiple-exchanges-as-apecoin-price-enjoys-rally-which-token-is-the-better-investment/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>ApeCoin is home to one of the most valuable NFTs, with the Bored Ape Yacht Club (BAYC) continuing to attract fans and be one of the most sought-after meme coins. After a recent slump, ApeCoin&#8217;s price has surged in recent weeks. While this price action is impressive, the new crypto gaming platform Metacade is going [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-releases-on-multiple-exchanges-as-apecoin-price-enjoys-rally-which-token-is-the-better-investment/">Metacade Releases on Multiple Exchanges as ApeCoin Price Enjoys Rally. Which Token is the Better Investment?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">ApeCoin is home to one of the most valuable NFTs, with the Bored Ape Yacht Club (BAYC) continuing to attract fans and be one of the most sought-after meme coins. After a recent slump, ApeCoin&rsquo;s price has surged in recent weeks. While this price action is impressive, the new crypto gaming platform Metacade is going from strength to strength after selling out its presale, snowballing now that it has hit decentralized exchanges (DEX).</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Metacade thrives after Uniswap listing.</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">After the presale event sold out of its total token allocation, raising $16.4 million, Metacade listed its native MCADE token on leading DEX Uniswap in the first week of April and the CEX Bitmart on the 20th of April. MCADE&rsquo;s momentum continues; investors who reserved their tokens during the presale round for between $0.008 and $0.02 have seen excellent returns during the early stages of its public listing.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Meanwhile, Metacade recently announced an exciting partnership with MetaStudio, an innovative team of developers with extensive experience. More good news for the new MCADE token was that&nbsp;<a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/metacade/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>CoinMarketCap</u></a> listed it within hours of the presale concluding. All of this positivity underlines the platform&rsquo;s potential to become one of the leading crypto opportunities of 2023, with potentially vast returns on the horizon.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>ApeCoin price rallies after setbacks</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">APE, the native token of ApeCoin, suffered losses in early 2023 after community members voted against releasing two new NFT collections. Yuga Labs wanted to capitalize on the overwhelming success of its Bored Ape Yacht Cat (BAYC) with the release of the ApeCoin Armory Club and ApeCoin Pet Club. Members voted decisively against the proposals, with more than 83% of the community voting against them.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In addition, a recent release of 7.3 million APE tokens caused a 10% drop in the ApeCoin price, while a further 15.6 million tokens are due to drop in mid-April, dropping even more tokens onto the market. However, there is some good news for those that hold ApeCoin coins with the news that the ApeCoin price has recovered from dropping below $4 at the end of March to its current value above $4.50.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>ApeCoin (APE) price prediction 2023</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">All signs point to the ApeCoin price beginning to move after being stuck in the $4 to $4.20 range for several weeks. Many believe this is the beginning of a return to bullish price action for APE, with $8 achievable this year.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Even the more pessimistic ApeCoin price predictions that see the token struggling to surpass $7 would return plenty for ApeCoin investors. Even then, these gains could be dwarfed by those possible with crypto gaming newbie Metacade. Here&rsquo;s why.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>What is Metacade?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=58" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade</u></a> is a ground-breaking new play-to-earn (P2E) crypto gaming platform developed to provide gaming fans, crypto enthusiasts, and developers with a thriving community to hang out and collaborate. Blockchain technology will set the standard of what&rsquo;s possible for future crypto-gaming platforms, particularly with its multi-faceted and comprehensive rewards system that goes beyond the usual GameFi norm of P2E.</p>
<p dir="ltr">For example, the Create2Earn scheme rewards users for contributions to community building. Each time a user posts a piece of social content such as game reviews, alpha, or contributions to live chats and Reddit-style sub-forums.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As well as giving crypto gaming enthusiasts the wherewithal to make the most of their gaming experience, thus maximizing the platform&rsquo;s total addressable market (TAM), Metacade looks set to drive innovation in the wider GameFi sector with the introduction of the pioneering Metagrants scheme.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Developers can submit their concepts to create new P2E games exclusively for Metacade in return for crypto funding to support their ventures. Each submission goes into a pool, which the MCADE community votes on, with the most popular ideas receiving funding from the central treasury to support the development journey.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This community-led approach will likely drive user retention and engage an ever-growing number of new users to the platform, and form a vital part of the platform&rsquo;s devolution to becoming a decentralized autonomous organization, which will empower users to take control of Metacade&rsquo;s future direction and create the platform they want to use.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>How high can Metacade (MCADE) go?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">After launching at $0.008 during the beta phase of the presale event, MCADE launched at the beginning of April on Uniswap at $0.022. With other listings to come in the coming weeks and months likely to increase buying pressure on MCADE, that could push the price to $0.50 by the end of the year, depending on the broader economic outlook. This would represent gains of more than 20x for those that purchased their MCADE tokens on the exchanges early.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Is MCADE a good investment?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade has the potential to be a strong investment opportunity in isolation, given the platform&rsquo;s many merits that look likely to push the price forward, particularly with the impending releases on Bitmart and MEXC in the next few weeks and the announcement of the partnership with MetaStudio.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Compared with returns available for buying ApeCoin, which looks to be about to crest the wave of bullish performance, MCADE still looks like the better investment opportunity as it intends to promote innovation in the crypto gaming market over the coming months and years.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>You can find more information, including how to buy MCADE,&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=58" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong><u>here</u></strong></a><strong>.</strong></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-releases-on-multiple-exchanges-as-apecoin-price-enjoys-rally-which-token-is-the-better-investment/">Metacade Releases on Multiple Exchanges as ApeCoin Price Enjoys Rally. Which Token is the Better Investment?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-releases-on-multiple-exchanges-as-apecoin-price-enjoys-rally-which-token-is-the-better-investment/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum price prediction: Here’s why FRC collapse matters</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-price-prediction-heres-why-frc-collapse-matters/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-price-prediction-heres-why-frc-collapse-matters/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 12:28:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-price-prediction-heres-why-frc-collapse-matters/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>ETH price remained under pressure in the past few days. The collapse of First Republic Bank matters for cryptocurrencies. Ethereum price came under pressure on Monday after the collapse of First Republic Bank (FRC). ETH pulled back to a low of $1,827 as investors also waited for the upcoming interest rate decision by the Federal [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-price-prediction-heres-why-frc-collapse-matters/">Ethereum price prediction: Here’s why FRC collapse matters</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">ETH price remained under pressure in the past few days.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The collapse of First Republic Bank matters for cryptocurrencies.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/"><u>Ethereum</u></a> price came under pressure on Monday after the collapse of First Republic Bank (FRC). ETH pulled back to a low of $1,827 as investors also waited for the upcoming interest rate decision by the Federal Reserve. It remains about 107% above the lowest level in 2022.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">First Republic Bank collapse</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The biggest financial news on Monday was the&nbsp;<a href="https://invezz.com/news/2023/04/29/first-republic-bank-frc-collapse-is-underway-as-fdic-seeks-rescue/"><u>collapse of First Republic Bank</u></a>, the second-biggest bank to fall in the US. This collapse happened a week after the company announced that it lost over $100 billion in the first quarter. In a statement, FDIC said that the company will be acquired by JP Morgan, the biggest company in the US.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The collapse of First Republic makes 2023 the worst year for banks since the 2008 financial crisis. We have seen banks like Signature, Silicon Valley Bank, Credit Suisse, and Silvergate Bank collapse.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">These collapses are positive for Ethereum and other cryptocurrency prices for two reasons. First, the collapse could mean that many people will move to cryptocurrencies like&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/"><u>Bitcoin</u></a> and ETH. While Bitcoin will benefit more in this transition, other&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/altcoins/"><u>altcoins</u></a> like Ethereum will also benefit since cryptocurrencies have a positive correlation.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Second, the collapse means that the Federal Reserve will likely consider the health of the banking sector when it starts its meeting on Tuesday. Minutes published last month showed that several officials were concerned about the banking crisis.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, there is a likelihood that the Fed will consider pausing its interest rates in this meeting. The alternative is that the bank will decide to hike rates by 0.25% &nbsp;and then point to a strategic pause in the near term.</p>
<p dir="ltr">A change of tune by the Federal Reserve will be bullish for Bitcoin and Ethereum prices. Historically, cryptocurrencies tend to do well when the Fed is pivoting.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Ethereum price prediction</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/04/01/1682944077208-2c173a05-6deb-4576-aab3-0a901a1beb0b.png" style="width: 643px;height: 312.927px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="643" height="312.927"></p>
<p dir="ltr">The daily chart shows that the ETH price has been in a bullish trend in the past few weeks. The coin has moved above the 50-day and 25-day exponential moving averages. This is a bullish sign. It has moved above the ascending trendline shown in green.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">It has also moved slightly below the key resistance level at $2,032, which was the highest point on August 12 last year. It is at the 23.6% Fibonacci Retracement level. Therefore, there is a likelihood that Ethereum will have a bullish breakout as buyers target the key resistance point at $2,500.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy Ethereum</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>

    <p>eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=MTM4MDg4&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy ETH with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    Public</h3>

    <p>Public is an investing platform that allows you to invest stocks, ETFs, crypto, and alternative assets like fine art and collectibles&mdash;all in one place.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/public-crypto?guid=MTM4MDg4&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy ETH with Public today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptocurrency execution and custody services are provided by Apex Crypto LLC (NMLS ID 1828849) through a software licensing agreement between Apex Crypto LLC and Public Crypto LLC. Crypto trading on Public platforms is served by Public Crypto LLC and offered through APEX Crypto. Please ensure that you fully understand the risks involved before trading." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-price-prediction-heres-why-frc-collapse-matters/">Ethereum price prediction: Here’s why FRC collapse matters</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-price-prediction-heres-why-frc-collapse-matters/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Meme coins surge as market dips: WSB and PEPE lead the way</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/meme-coins-surge-as-market-dips-wsb-and-pepe-lead-the-way/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/meme-coins-surge-as-market-dips-wsb-and-pepe-lead-the-way/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 10:50:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/meme-coins-surge-as-market-dips-wsb-and-pepe-lead-the-way/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The global crypto market cap has dropped by 2.16%. Bitcoin has dropped by 2.60% while Ethereum has dropped by 3.26%. WSB is today&#8217;s top gainer after a 400% price surge. Meme coins are today&#8217;s top gainers as the majority of big cryptocurrencies plunge. WALL STREET BABY (WSB), a little-known meme coin, for example, has surged [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/meme-coins-surge-as-market-dips-wsb-and-pepe-lead-the-way/">Meme coins surge as market dips: WSB and PEPE lead the way</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul class="decimal_type">
<li>The global crypto market cap has dropped by 2.16%.</li>
<li>Bitcoin has dropped by 2.60% while Ethereum has dropped by 3.26%.</li>
<li>WSB is today&rsquo;s top gainer after a 400% price surge.</li>
</ul>
<p>Meme coins are today&rsquo;s top gainers as the majority of big cryptocurrencies plunge. WALL STREET BABY (WSB), a little-known meme coin, for example, has <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/wall-street-bet/">surged by 400.14%</a> to become today&rsquo;s top gainer.</p>
<p>Other meme coins that have seen tremendous price gains include AiShiba (shibai), which at press time had surged by 171.21%, and PEPE which had surged by 128.14%.</p>
<h2>Crypto market dropping</h2>
<p>It is interesting to see little-known coins take on major cryptocurrencies like <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/what-is-bitcoin/">Bitcoin (BTC)</a> and <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/what-is-ethereum/">Ethereum (ETH)</a>. While the above-mentioned meme coins saw a triple-digit percentage rise, BTC saw a 2.60% decrease and Ethereum saw a 3.26% drop.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinlore.com/crypto/meme-tokens">Popular meme coins</a><a href="https://www.coinlore.com/crypto/meme-tokens"></a> seem to follow the major cryptocurrencies as <a href="https://coinjournal.net/shiba-inu/what-is-shiba-inu/">Shiba Inu (SHIB)</a> and <a href="https://coinjournal.net/dogecoin/what-is-dogecoin/">Dogecoin (DOGE)</a> dropped by 2.48% and 2.97% respectively. So why are the little-known meme coins rising?</p>
<h2>Why are little-known meme coins surging?</h2>
<p>Well, the PEPE coin seems to be leading the way after <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/okx-review-a-one-stop-platform-for-crypto-defi-dapps-nfts-and-gamefi/">OKX </a>announced listing the PEPE/USDT trading pair starting today with PEPE withdrawals starting tomorrow. There is no major crypto news affecting the rest of the meme coins meaning they are riding on PEPE&rsquo;s hype.</p>
<p>PEPE has surged by 305% while the WALL STREET BABY (WSB) has raised by a whopping 1878.13% in the last seven days.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/meme-coins-surge-as-market-dips-wsb-and-pepe-lead-the-way/">Meme coins surge as market dips: WSB and PEPE lead the way</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/meme-coins-surge-as-market-dips-wsb-and-pepe-lead-the-way/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu (SHIB) and Aptos (APT) price outlook as Bitcoin (BTC) tests resistance near $30k</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-shib-and-aptos-apt-price-outlook-as-bitcoin-btc-tests-resistance-near-30k/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-shib-and-aptos-apt-price-outlook-as-bitcoin-btc-tests-resistance-near-30k/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 18:58:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-shib-and-aptos-apt-price-outlook-as-bitcoin-btc-tests-resistance-near-30k/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s dip below $30,000 and subsequent retest of resistance above$29k highlights the past week&#8217;s top coins outlook. Shiba Inu (SHIB) price is below its 50 and 200 MA but analysts are bullish on SHIB given overall sentiment and network growth. Aptos (APT) price has formed a massive bull flag pattern that could see APT explode [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-shib-and-aptos-apt-price-outlook-as-bitcoin-btc-tests-resistance-near-30k/">Shiba Inu (SHIB) and Aptos (APT) price outlook as Bitcoin (BTC) tests resistance near $30k</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Bitcoin&rsquo;s dip below $30,000 and subsequent retest of resistance above$29k highlights the past week&rsquo;s top coins outlook.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Shiba Inu (SHIB) price is below its 50 and 200 MA but analysts are bullish on SHIB given overall sentiment and network growth.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Aptos (APT) price has formed a massive bull flag pattern that could see APT explode to new highs in 2023.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">The cryptocurrency market continues to see significant volatility as <a href="https://coinjournal.net/price/"><u>prices</u></a> of various tokens fluctuate near key levels. <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/"><u>Bitcoin (BTC)</u></a> price fell to around $27,200 this past week and saw the global cryptocurrency market cap drop from above $1.34 trillion to $1.25 trillion amid broader sell-off pressure.</p>
<p dir="ltr">BTC price is however back above $29,000 and has retested resistance near the psychological $30k level this weekend.</p>
<p dir="ltr">At the same time, several altcoins that have recently seen dramatic declines look positioned for fresh moves, with cryptocurrency bulls buoyed by fresh turmoil in the banking sector with troubles for US bank First Republic.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Here&rsquo;s the price prediction for <a href="https://coinjournal.net/shiba-inu/"><u>Shiba Inu (SHIB)</u></a> and Aptos (APT).</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Shiba Inu (SHIB) price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Inu price is down nearly 10% in the past two weeks, having traded lower from highs above $0.000011 recently.</p>
<p dir="ltr">SHIB currently trades below its 50 MA and 200 MA, while the daily RSI is below 40 to suggest bears might have a slight advantage. &nbsp;</p>
<div class="fr-img-space-wrap"><span class="fr-img-caption fr-fic fr-dib fr-draggable" style="width: 700px"><span class="fr-img-wrap">
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/03/30/1682880841687-6468b8e1-f602-40cc-997c-ced14021d08b.png" style="width: 700px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="700" height="242"><span class="fr-inner"></span></p>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Inu (SHIB) daily price chart. Source:<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/gnVjZG9y/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">&nbsp;<u>TradingView</u></a></p>
<p></p></span>
<p></p></span>
<p class="fr-img-space-wrap2">But the 16th ranked cryptocurrency, which remains one of the top memecoins with a market of $6.1 billion, has a growing community buoyed by the success of the testnet for layer 2 protocol Shibarium.&nbsp;</p>
<p class="fr-img-space-wrap2">On-chain data shows the protocol has enabled over 194,000 transactions and seen over 100,000 wallet interactions.</p>
</div>
<p dir="ltr">If an upside flip in the price amid new <a href="https://coinjournal.net/shiba-inu/buy/"><u>buy Shiba Inu</u></a> pressure, the main short term target will be the $0.000035 level. The 2021 all-time high provides another key level and a move to $0.01 could be the Holy Grail of the upcoming bull cycle.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Aptos (APT) price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/aptos/"><u>Aptos (APT)</u></a> is a new layer 1 blockchain network that&rsquo;s benefitted from massive investment by venture capitals. The Aptos mainnet went live recently and the demand for the native APT token saw the price rally to the YTD peak of $19.92 in January.</p>
<div class="fr-img-space-wrap"><span class="fr-img-caption fr-fic fr-dib fr-draggable" style="width: 700px"><span class="fr-img-wrap">
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/03/30/1682880773725-8c3e544a-a17f-4a66-884a-624c418a5f7a.png" style="width: 700px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="700" height="270"><span class="fr-inner"></span></p>
<p dir="ltr">Aptos (APT) price daily chart. Source:<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/8s52Wcng/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">&nbsp;<u>TradingView</u></a></p>
<p></p></span>
<p></p></span>
<p class="fr-img-space-wrap2">Currently trading around $10 has the APT/USD pair roughly 46% off the January highs. However, analysts remain bullish on the Aptos price.</p>
</div>
<p>Crypto analyst Captain Faibik recently<a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoFaibik/status/1650014295412076546" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">&nbsp;<u>highlighted</u></a> Aptos bullish flag pattern. If a breakout follows, a move to $20 in the short term could be one of the main targets.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Meanwhile, this <a href="https://coinjournal.net/aptos/price-prediction/"><u>Aptos price prediction</u></a> for the medium term sees a potential burst to a new all-time high.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-shib-and-aptos-apt-price-outlook-as-bitcoin-btc-tests-resistance-near-30k/">Shiba Inu (SHIB) and Aptos (APT) price outlook as Bitcoin (BTC) tests resistance near $30k</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-shib-and-aptos-apt-price-outlook-as-bitcoin-btc-tests-resistance-near-30k/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Litecoin price prediction: can bulls pick up new momentum for LTC?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/litecoin-price-prediction-can-bulls-pick-up-new-momentum-for-ltc/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/litecoin-price-prediction-can-bulls-pick-up-new-momentum-for-ltc/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 18:43:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/litecoin-price-prediction-can-bulls-pick-up-new-momentum-for-ltc/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Litecoin price traded above $90 on Sunday, with LTC hitting intraday highs of $91.60. While price has rejected twice above $100, the area remains a key target for bulls as Bitcoin retests the $30k level. If it breaks above the hurdle, fresh momentum heading into the Litecoin halving in August could catapult LTC price towards [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/litecoin-price-prediction-can-bulls-pick-up-new-momentum-for-ltc/">Litecoin price prediction: can bulls pick up new momentum for LTC?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Litecoin price traded above $90 on Sunday, with LTC hitting intraday highs of $91.60.</li>
<li dir="ltr">While price has rejected twice above $100, the area remains a key target for bulls as Bitcoin retests the $30k level.</li>
<li dir="ltr">If it breaks above the hurdle, fresh momentum heading into the Litecoin halving in August could catapult LTC price towards its all-time peak.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/litecoin/"><u>Litecoin (LTC)</u></a> is trading around the $90 level after bulls battled to regain some control following the sharp sell-off to lows of $84 this past week. The weakness in the price of LTC came after another dip in March that saw the price rejected at year-to-date highs of $106 in February.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The decline occurred at a key horizontal resistance area at the $100 zone, which remains the main hurdle as Litecoin enters the last few months before its halving in August.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Litecoin price: are bulls taking control?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The LTC price rejection in the past weeks at $100 meant a double top pattern appeared, which signals bearish strength and highlights the potential for downward continuation. As it happened, LTC price broke below an ascending trendline support after hitting $103 on 18 April and a significant drop a few days later had LTC/USD hugging lows of $84.</p>
<p dir="ltr">But despite the previous gains being wiped out by the decline, LTC is currently trying to maintain the $90 area after a critical daily close above it. &nbsp;Bulls will need to confirm they are getting in control by pushing higher even as a potential rising channel appears on the daily chart.</p>
<p dir="ltr">A look at the Relative Strength Index (RSI) shows the momentum indicator is just below the 50 line. However, the indicator is looking to cross above the signal line to suggest further possible accumulation of the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/altcoin/"><u>altcoin</u></a>.</p>
<div class="fr-img-space-wrap"><span class="fr-img-caption fr-fic fr-dib fr-draggable" style="width: 615px"><span class="fr-img-wrap">
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/03/30/1682879352906-6e0675e7-51e6-4d55-b130-270e099500f3.png" style="width: 700px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="700" height="270"><span class="fr-inner"></span></p>
<p dir="ltr">Litecoin price LTC/USD daily chart outlook. Source:<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/4jdMW8TY/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">&nbsp;<u>TradingView</u></a></p>
<p></p></span>
<p></p></span>
<h2 class="fr-img-space-wrap2">Litecoin price prediction ahead of halving</h2>
</div>
<p dir="ltr">With approximately 100 days left before halving, the Litecoin price prediction for 2023 is bullish. The network has continued to see greater miner confidence, with the total hashrate for the blockchain recently hitting 760 terahashes per second(TH/s).</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">760,745,039,240,513 beautiful hashes = today's combined computational strength, and security, of the <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Litecoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Litecoin</a> blockchain! &#9889; <a href="https://t.co/lWoO4eUqTC">pic.twitter.com/lWoO4eUqTC</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Litecoin (@litecoin) <a href="https://twitter.com/litecoin/status/1649439109646286848?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">April 21, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">If the expected halving rally kicks in amid a broader market uptick, the two main targets above $100 will lie around $180 and then $300. The all-time high for LTC is around $410 reached in May 2021.</p>
<p dir="ltr">On the flipside, a bearish reversal could see the long term resistance-turned support area of $65 come into play. Below that, the main buffer for Litecoin price remains the multi-year base around $40.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/litecoin-price-prediction-can-bulls-pick-up-new-momentum-for-ltc/">Litecoin price prediction: can bulls pick up new momentum for LTC?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/litecoin-price-prediction-can-bulls-pick-up-new-momentum-for-ltc/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Casper price prediction: what next for CSPR after 60% rally in April?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/casper-price-prediction-what-next-for-cspr-after-60-rally-in-april/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/casper-price-prediction-what-next-for-cspr-after-60-rally-in-april/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 18:16:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[smart contracts]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/casper-price-prediction-what-next-for-cspr-after-60-rally-in-april/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Casper Network price rose over 60% in April, hitting a high of $0.060. CSPR traded at around $0.059 at the time of writing, about 6% up in the past 24 hours. While CSPR price is above key support level, here&#8217;s the price outlook for Casper Network going into May. Casper Network price rose more than [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/casper-price-prediction-what-next-for-cspr-after-60-rally-in-april/">Casper price prediction: what next for CSPR after 60% rally in April?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Casper Network price rose over 60% in April, hitting a high of $0.060.</li>
<li dir="ltr">CSPR traded at around $0.059 at the time of writing, about 6% up in the past 24 hours.</li>
<li dir="ltr">While CSPR price is above key support level, here&rsquo;s the price outlook for Casper Network going into May.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Casper Network price rose more than 60% in April as the value of the native CSPR rallied to above $0.060. The cryptocurrency&rsquo;s <a href="https://coinjournal.net/price/">price</a> currently sits around $0.059, up 6% in the past 24 hours and nearly 16% higher in the past seven days.</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, while the Casper token is one of the standout performers of the last month, it remains off its peak of $1.33 by some huge distance. According to data from CoinGecko, CSPR reached its all-time low of $0.022 in June 2022, meaning traders who took positions at these levels are 164% up on their investment.</p>
<p dir="ltr">CSPR at current levels is -95% from the all-time high reached in May 2021.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Casper Network (CSPR)?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Casper Network, a layer 1 blockchain network targeted for enterprise adoption of the blockchain technology. CSPR is the governance token of the Casper blockchain, whose mainnet launched in 2021.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As a native token, CSPR has multiple roles in the Casper ecosystem, including network fees, staking rewards and payments as a medium of exchange.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Casper Network has seen multiple projects built on top of its proof-of-stake blockchain. One of the projects on the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/smart-contracts/">smart contracts</a> platform is layer 2 protocol Metis that migrated from <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/ethereum/">Ethereum</a> to Casper. Metis looks to boost development of Decentralized Autonomous Companies (DACs).</p>
<p dir="ltr">Another project is patent encryption platform IPwe, which targets the creation of a decentralised database system for patent management and licensing. There&rsquo;s also ACDX, a digital assets exchange for structured products and derivatives trading.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Casper price prediction: What next for CSPR?</h2>
<div class="fr-img-space-wrap"><span class="fr-img-caption fr-fic fr-dib fr-draggable" style="width: 615px"><span class="fr-img-wrap">
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/03/30/1682877625460-9b438569-3f9f-43ea-b473-997e6a8b9401.png" style="width: 700px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="700" height="242"><span class="fr-inner"></span></p>
<p dir="ltr">CSPR price 4-hour chart. Source:<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/tc90nz2D/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">&nbsp;<u>TradingView</u></a></p>
<p></p></span>
<p></p></span>
<p class="fr-img-space-wrap2">Casper&rsquo;s price could continue to rise into May and potentially break above $0.1. This outlook will materialise if CSPR price consolidates above $0.065, building new momentum for a breakout above $0.080.&nbsp;</p>
</div>
<p dir="ltr">Above the $0.10 level, significant resistance will be around $0.13, with a bullish <a href="https://coinjournal.net/casper/price-prediction/"><u>Casper price prediction</u></a> of $0.20 in May.</p>
<p dir="ltr">On the downside, CSPR&rsquo;s outperformance over the past month could see traders eye profit taking deals. Such a scenario will definitely dent the bullish momentum and result in downward action, with a potential slump to $0.025.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/casper-price-prediction-what-next-for-cspr-after-60-rally-in-april/">Casper price prediction: what next for CSPR after 60% rally in April?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/casper-price-prediction-what-next-for-cspr-after-60-rally-in-april/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto price predictions: Chainlink, Filecoin, Pepe</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-predictions-chainlink-filecoin-pepe/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-predictions-chainlink-filecoin-pepe/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 10:30:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chainlink News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FIL]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Filecoin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-predictions-chainlink-filecoin-pepe/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrency prices had a mixed performance last week as investors focused &#160;on the impending collapse of First Republic Bank (FRC). After falling to a low of $27,100, the coin jumped to about $30,000, where it has been in the past few days. Here is a crypto price prediction for some of the top coins like [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-predictions-chainlink-filecoin-pepe/">Crypto price predictions: Chainlink, Filecoin, Pepe</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/price/"><u>Cryptocurrency prices</u></a> had a mixed performance last week as investors focused &nbsp;on the impending collapse of First Republic Bank (FRC). After falling to a low of $27,100, the coin jumped to about $30,000, where it has been in the past few days. Here is a crypto price prediction for some of the top coins like Chainlink (LINK), Filecoin (FIL), and Pepe.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Chainlink price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr">On the daily chart, we see that the LINK has been in a consolidation phase in the past few days. The coin remains slightly below the important resistance point at $9.510, the highest point on November 8, August 13, and June 9.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">It is also below the key resistance level at $8.82, the highest point on April 19. The coin is also trading slightly below the 25-day moving average. Therefore, there is a likelihood that <a href="https://coinjournal.net/chainlink/"><u>Chainlink</u></a> will have a bearish breakout as sellers target the green ascending trendline at $6. A break above the key resistance at $8 will see it jump to $9.51.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/03/30/1682850553386-4d881e88-ccd7-4d9e-9c5d-48392de25c28.png" style="width: 590px;height: 287.133px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="590" height="287.133"></p>
<h3 dir="ltr">How to buy Chainlink</h3>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>

    <p>eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=MTM4MDc0&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy LINK with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    Public</h3>

    <p>Public is an investing platform that allows you to invest stocks, ETFs, crypto, and alternative assets like fine art and collectibles&mdash;all in one place.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/public-crypto?guid=MTM4MDc0&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy LINK with Public today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptocurrency execution and custody services are provided by Apex Crypto LLC (NMLS ID 1828849) through a software licensing agreement between Apex Crypto LLC and Public Crypto LLC. Crypto trading on Public platforms is served by Public Crypto LLC and offered through APEX Crypto. Please ensure that you fully understand the risks involved before trading." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Filecoin price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/filecoin"><u>Filecoin</u></a> price has been in a tight range in the past few days. The coin is trading at $5.9, where it has been recently. It has moved above the ascending trendline shown in green. FIL has moved slightly below the important resistance point at $6.60, the highest level on November 5 last year. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) has moved slightly below the neutral point at 50.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, the Filecoin price will likely remain in this range in the next few days. More downside will be confirmed if the price moves below the ascending trendline. If this happens, the next key level to watch will be at $4.0.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/03/30/1682850553799-2765858b-76e0-42b6-9ba9-34ab893f07b9.png" style="width: 520px;height: 253.067px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="520" height="253.067"></p>
<h3 dir="ltr">How to buy Filecoin</h3>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>

    <p>eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=MTM4MDc0&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy FIL with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    Binance.US</h3>

    <p>Binance.US provides secure and reliable access to the world&rsquo;s most popular cryptocurrencies, with some of the lowest fees in the industry.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/binance-us-crypto?guid=MTM4MDc0&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy FIL with Binance.US today            </a>
    </p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Pepe price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The hourly chart shows that the Pepe crypto price has been in a strong bullish trend in the past few days. It has dropped to a low of $0.00000013 to about $0.00000061. This means that the token has jumped by over 300% from the lowest level this year. It has moved above all moving averages.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, it seems like the Pepe token is having a bullish momentum. If this happens, the next key level to watch will be at $0.00000070. A move below the support level at $0.00000044 will invalidate the bullish view.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/03/30/1682850553536-89c0da97-0784-4045-a64e-eeaf0d7bcec1.png" style="width: 603px;height: 293.46px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="603" height="293.46"></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-predictions-chainlink-filecoin-pepe/">Crypto price predictions: Chainlink, Filecoin, Pepe</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-predictions-chainlink-filecoin-pepe/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
