<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 20:41:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Euro Bullish Sentiments Abound as Region Appears Set to Hold Off Recession</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/euro-bullish-sentiments/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/euro-bullish-sentiments/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 13:10:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Currencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ecb]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[euro]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jerome powell]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[us dollar]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=232193</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/euro-bullish-sentiments/">Euro Bullish Sentiments Abound as Region Appears Set to Hold Off Recession</a></p>
<p>More observers are growing bullish on the euro this year despite its relative slump against the US dollar in 2022.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/euro-bullish-sentiments/">Euro Bullish Sentiments Abound as Region Appears Set to Hold Off Recession</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/euro-bullish-sentiments/">Euro Bullish Sentiments Abound as Region Appears Set to Hold Off Recession</a></p>
<p>Currency analysts and experts are <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/01/11/experts-bullish-on-euro-as-europe-looks-to-hold-off-a-recession.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">turning bullish</a> on the euro as the continent tries to withstand a recession. With 2023 well underway, the markets head into uncertainty amid shifting economic data and fiscal policy. However, currency experts maintain that this trend could spell positive news for the euro.</p>
<p>According to Steve Englander, head of global G-10 FX research at <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/standard-chartered/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Standard Chartered</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The euro is trading within its late December range, but incoming data since the beginning of 2023 suggest to us that it should be stronger.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Although the euro slumped against the US dollar in the second half of last year, it recovered in recent months. As it stands, the common currency is trading within a tight range of just over $1.07.</p>
<p>Last year, the euro&#8217;s weakness came mainly due to the US Federal Reserve&#8217;s aggressive monetary policy tightening. At the same time, the European Central Bank had run out of leeway to increase interest rates to curtail inflation. However, recent developments now suggest a policy reverse between both regions. For example, incoming data trends state there is a need for sustained hawkishness in Frankfurt with a potential easing off of rates in Washington. It is the perceived closing of the interest rate gap that several analysts highlight as a positive development for the euro. As Englander put it:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Both euro area core inflation and economic surprises have continued to strengthen, making it easier for the European Central Bank to maintain a hawkish tone. Energy concerns that loomed large as a EUR-negative in mid-2022 are beginning to ebb.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Lessening of Economic Threat from Excessive Eurozone Energy Prices also Fuels Euro Bullish Sentiments</h2>
<p>Also feeding into the recent euro bullish sentiments is the reduction of the economic threat from the eurozone&#8217;s excessively high energy prices. This trend has also been helped by the fact that much of northern Europe experienced mild undemanding winters.</p>
<p>According to recent Eurostat preliminary figures, the annual headline inflation in the eurozone dropped to 9.2% from 10.1% last November. However, core inflation, excluding volatile energy, food, alcohol, and tobacco prices, surged beyond general anticipation. This figure eventually attained a new all-time high of 5.2%.</p>
<p>Despite the hawkish stance taken by the US Fed and ECB, Englander noted that US data surprises have been weaker in Europe. This development has subsequently resulted in less upward pressure on interest rates.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Fed Chair <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/jerome-powell/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Jerome Powell</a> repeatedly emphasizes the role of wages in reducing core services inflation. Furthermore, Powell points to wage growth as a risk factor in the US apex bank&#8217;s quest to reduce it. Should the Fed eventually bring down core services inflation, it would have wiggle room to slash its aggressive rate hiking cycle substantially. In addition, the central bank might even be in a prime position to embark on a reversal later in the year.</p>
<p>FX Research head George Saravelos also pointed to the Chinese economy factor as an added impetus for the euro. According to him, China&#8217;s reopening could boost the euro since it is a pro-cyclical currency.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/suzuki-motor-electric-suv-concept-evx/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/euro-bullish-sentiments/">Euro Bullish Sentiments Abound as Region Appears Set to Hold Off Recession</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/euro-bullish-sentiments/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Suzuki Motor Unveils Electric SUV Concept eVX</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/suzuki-motor-electric-suv-concept-evx/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/suzuki-motor-electric-suv-concept-evx/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 12:43:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Transportation News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[evx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[maruti suzuki]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[suzuki]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=232181</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/suzuki-motor-electric-suv-concept-evx/">Suzuki Motor Unveils Electric SUV Concept eVX</a></p>
<p>The company displays a range of eco-friendly products, emphasizing its vision of committing to “bring new products, technologies, investments and set up new facilities in India.”</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/suzuki-motor-electric-suv-concept-evx/">Suzuki Motor Unveils Electric SUV Concept eVX</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/suzuki-motor-electric-suv-concept-evx/">Suzuki Motor Unveils Electric SUV Concept eVX</a></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Japanese multinational corporation Suzuki Motor Corporation’s Indian Unit has unveiled a concept electric SUV called ‘eVX&#8217;. The company announced the new EV at the Auto Expo 2023, which began on Wednesday. The show has returned after three years, and Maruti Suzuki, Suzuki Motor’s Indian arm, is one of the major manufacturers participating in the event. </span></p>
<h2>Suzuki Unveils Concept eVX</h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Concept eVX is developed by Suzuki Motor Corporation, Japan, and designed on an all-electric SUV platform. The SUV boasts a driving range of up to 550 km and will be powered by a 60kWh battery pack and what the company calls “safe battery technology.” While unveiling Concept eVX at the Expo, the Suzuki Motor Corporation Representative Director and President Toshihiro Suzuki talked about the company’s plans for the new product. He revealed that the new electric SUC will hit the market by 2025. The executive <a href="https://www.outlookindia.com/business/auto-expo-2023-opens-suzuki-motor-unveils-concept-electric-suv-news-252598" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">continued</a>:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">“We are promoting a range of global measures to reduce greenhouse gas emissions generated from our business. One key measure is reducing CO2 emitted by using our products. Here in India, as announced in March last year, we will invest 100 billion rupees (Rs 10,000 core) in the production of BEVs (Battery Electric Vehicles) and their batteries.”</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Maruti Suzuki explained that the Concept eVX is 4,300mm in length and has a width of 1,800mm. In height, the product is 1,600mm tall. &#8216;</span></p>
<h2>Suzuki&#8217;s Eco-Friendly Products</h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Apart from Concept eVX, the company also displayed 15 other vehicles at the Expo, including Ertiga, Brezza, and Baleno. Others are Grand Vitara, Flex Fuel, XL6, Swift, Ciaz, WagonR, etc. Notably, the WagonR Flex Fuel Prototype is flex-fuel compliant, and the WagonR prototype can operate on E85 fuel. For the yet-to-be-launched Brezza S-CNG, the vehicle has the latest factory-fitted s-CNG vehicles</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The company displays a range of eco-friendly products, emphasizing its vision of committing to “bring new products, technologies, investments and set up new facilities in India.” Maruti Suzuki Managing Director &amp; CEO Hisashi Takeuch commented on the new development.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">“We believe in exploring a full spectrum of technologies like hybrids, CNG, bio-CNG, ethanol and electric to support Government of India’s twin objective of reducing oil-import bill and Carbon New Zero by 2070.”</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The CEO added that the EV is the first global strategy of its kind and is debuting in India. According to him, the language design and being a battery electric SUV emphasized the company’s commitment to environmental friendliness and sustainability. </span></p>
<p>Read more <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/technology/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">technology news</a> on Coinspeaker.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-770m-texas-plant-expansion/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/suzuki-motor-electric-suv-concept-evx/">Suzuki Motor Unveils Electric SUV Concept eVX</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/suzuki-motor-electric-suv-concept-evx/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tesla to Spend Over $770M on Texas Plant Expansion for Battery Cells and Manufacturing</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-770m-texas-plant-expansion/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-770m-texas-plant-expansion/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 11:39:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Transportation News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tesla]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=232164</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-770m-texas-plant-expansion/">Tesla to Spend Over $770M on Texas Plant Expansion for Battery Cells and Manufacturing</a></p>
<p>EV maker Tesla has applied with the state of Texas regarding the expansion of its Austin-based gigafactory to accommodate more operations. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-770m-texas-plant-expansion/">Tesla to Spend Over $770M on Texas Plant Expansion for Battery Cells and Manufacturing</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-770m-texas-plant-expansion/">Tesla to Spend Over $770M on Texas Plant Expansion for Battery Cells and Manufacturing</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/tesla/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tesla</a> (NASDAQ: TSLA) plans to spend more than $770 million on the <a href="https://www.teslarati.com/tesla-giga-texas-expansion-cathode-battery-cell-plant/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">expansion</a> of its factory in Austin, Texas. January filings with the Texas Department of Licensing and Registration disclose the massive fund outlay. Per reports, Tesla plans to spend on constructing facilities geared towards testing battery cells and manufacturing. In addition, the prominent electric vehicle maker also intends to situate a drive unit manufacturing base, and a die shop, at the expanded site.</p>
<p>The planned Tesla Texas facility expansion would mark one of the company’s largest scale-ups since its German gigafactory move in 2022. Tesla officially opened its Texas EV and battery plant last April to a Cyber Rodeo opening grand party for stakeholders. The EV manufacturer currently produces its Model Y vehicles at the Austin gigafactory but is already experiencing some operational constraints. As it stands, the production lines at the facility command a small portion of its entire real estate. This predicament precipitated the need to expand, in addition to Tesla’s plans to manufacture Cybertrucks in the existing facility. Nonetheless, Tesla does not rule out onboarding more vehicle-line production initiatives at the Austin gigafactory down the stretch.</p>
<h2>Phase Breakdown of Tesla Texas Expansion Initiative</h2>
<p>The expansion would see an additional 1.4 million square feet of space added to the already imposing Texan site. The expansion scheme, broken down into four specific projects, should begin at the end of the month.</p>
<p>The largest of the four projects entails a 693,093-square-foot facility called Cell 1. This project is also the most expensive and would cost an estimated $368 million. According to reports, Cell 1 erection will begin on January 23rd and complete on February 12th next year.</p>
<p>The second-largest Texas expansion project is the Drive Unit planned to be 423,032 square feet. This initiative carries a price tag of $85 million and will begin on February 6th to end on January 15th, 2024.</p>
<p>The third-largest project by a square foot of 321,186 is “Cathode.” Although not as large as Cell 1 or Drive Unit, Cathode is the second most expensive at $260 million. Cathode has a start date of January 30th and will conclude at the end of the year on December 18th.</p>
<p>Cell Test Lab is the smallest of the expansion projects and has a run time of just six months. It will require an additional 2,560 square feet with an estimated cost of $3.7 million. Cell Test Lab will begin at the end of January and last till August 25th, 2023.</p>
<p>Despite the detailed project breakdown, some of these phases could supplement previous plans. For example, according to recent drone flyovers of the construction site, the Cathode plant’s construction is already underway.</p>
<h2>Expansion Scheme Follows Zhu Promotion</h2>
<p>Tesla’s Texas gigafactory expansion scheme comes on the heels of the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-china-highest-profile-executive/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">promotion</a> of its China boss. Last week, the EV company promoted Tom Zhu to the highest-profile executive role after <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/elon-musk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Elon Musk</a>. As Musk’s lieutenant, Zhu now has direct oversight over Tesla’s US assembly plants and sales operations in Europe and North America.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-korean-tax-authorities-bithumb/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-770m-texas-plant-expansion/">Tesla to Spend Over $770M on Texas Plant Expansion for Battery Cells and Manufacturing</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-770m-texas-plant-expansion/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>South Korean Tax Authorities Investigating Crypto Exchange Operator Bithumb Holdings</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-korean-tax-authorities-bithumb/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-korean-tax-authorities-bithumb/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mercy Tukiya Mutanya]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 11:37:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bithumb]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=232168</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-korean-tax-authorities-bithumb/">South Korean Tax Authorities Investigating Crypto Exchange Operator Bithumb Holdings</a></p>
<p>A local report states that the investigation will be conducted by a unit dedicated to “special tax investigations.”</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-korean-tax-authorities-bithumb/">South Korean Tax Authorities Investigating Crypto Exchange Operator Bithumb Holdings</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-korean-tax-authorities-bithumb/">South Korean Tax Authorities Investigating Crypto Exchange Operator Bithumb Holdings</a></p>
<p>South Korean tax authorities are investigating local crypto exchange operator Bithumb Holdings. This is according to a Tuesday report by Yonhap News which states that the National Tax Service is reportedly investigating possible tax evasion via domestic and international transactions of Bithumb Korea, Bithumb Holdings, and affiliates in Gangnam-gu, Seoul. A company official <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/01/10/crypto-exchange-operator-bithumb-investigated-by-south-korean-tax-authorities-report/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">confirmed</a> the news to CoinDesk Korea but could not share details.</p>
<p>A local report states that the investigation will be conducted by a unit dedicated to “special tax investigations.” This is not the first time <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/bithumb/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bithumb</a> has been at the center of such an investigation. The National Tax Service also conducted a special tax investigation on Bithumb Korea and collected 80 billion won in income tax in 2018. It was determined in that investigation that Bithumb was not guilty of tax evasion.</p>
<p>It is reported that authorities have questioned businessman Kang Jong-hyeon – a former chairman at Bithumb suspected to be the real owner of the company – and his younger sister, Kang Ji-yeon over an embezzlement case involving related companies.</p>
<p>The company was recently in the news over a case involving another former chairman Lee Jung-Hoon. The former exec was acquitted in the first hearing on fraud charges involving $100 million. Prosecutors were seeking an eight-year prison sentence for Jung-Hoon following his July 2021 indictment. It was alleged that he stole money from cosmetic surgeon Kim Byung-Gun during negotiations for an acquisition deal. This was in a matter where Lee proposed a joint management agreement with Kim in which the latter would take over Bithumb.</p>
<p>It was alleged that Lee embezzled the acquisition deposit in the name of the listing &#8220;BXA token.&#8221; The claim, however, could not be proven.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-coins-feature-stripe-payments/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-korean-tax-authorities-bithumb/">South Korean Tax Authorities Investigating Crypto Exchange Operator Bithumb Holdings</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-korean-tax-authorities-bithumb/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Twitter Launches Coins Feature with Stripe Payments</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-coins-feature-stripe-payments/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-coins-feature-stripe-payments/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sanaa Sharma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 11:15:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[doge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stripe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[twitter]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=232159</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-coins-feature-stripe-payments/">Twitter Launches Coins Feature with Stripe Payments</a></p>
<p>Along with the accommodation of this feature, traders will also be able to acquire on-time cryptocurrency market information on all the monetary tokens on the platform.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-coins-feature-stripe-payments/">Twitter Launches Coins Feature with Stripe Payments</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-coins-feature-stripe-payments/">Twitter Launches Coins Feature with Stripe Payments</a></p>
<p>Jane Manchun Wong, a prominent reverse engineering expert, has disclosed that the social media platform <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/twitter/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Twitter</a> is moving closer to inaugurating a new feature which is known as Coins.</p>
<p>The feature is all set to reward users for posting some specific tweets by entering Twitter&#8217;s internal token with fiat money. The feature will also engage in conducting transactions via Stripe, an internet technology platform that allows payments and other kinds of transactions in several nations around the world. Stripe dived into backing crypto payments last year, and Twitter examined <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/usd-coin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">USDC</a> payouts via Stripe for creators monetizing their content through social media platforms.</p>
<p>As initially <a href="https://u.today/twitter-preparing-to-launch-new-coins-feature" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reported</a> by the media, Twitter backtracked on its decision to launch a cryptocurrency wallet following the social media platform being bought by the much-criticized tech entrepreneur <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/elon-musk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Elon Musk</a>. <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/dogecoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Dogecoin</a> plunged to approximately ten percent showcasing how related its popularity is to news associated with Musk and his firms. Recently, Twitter also launched a novel crypto attribute that enabled users to search for updated price details. The brand-new modification allows users to search for price charts for both Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a>) and Ethereum (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ETH</a>) by easily typing their name or ticker symbol in the search tab.</p>
<p>Along with the accommodation of this feature, traders will also be able to acquire on-time cryptocurrency market information on all the monetary tokens on the platform. Twitter has recently picked up the pace and built on novel features to get a hold of its users after massive criticism from the community over Musk&#8217;s decisions.</p>
<p>The news also claims that Twitter&#8217;s monetization scheme persisted in building, even though the loss of its employees has impacted the company&#8217;s operations. It seems for now that those who will be awarded the Twitter prizes will have to be patient until they earn at least $50 worth to redeem, which is the same amount as the minimum payout amount for those monetizing Twitter&#8217;s existing Super Follows feature.</p>
<p>Developer and app researcher Nima Owji, who initially distributed leaks of Twitter Coin in December, said that he also did not find any indications that crypto will constitute the Coins and Awards giveaways. However, Owji did say that if Twitter had planned to enforce crypto, it would be keeping the rumors under wraps for now.</p>
<p>According to Owji, Twitter doesn&#8217;t forward any sensitive details about specific things when not ready. He added to his statement by claiming that if the company were to add it to the algorithm, they will plan to release it.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-com-delists-usdt-osc-ban/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-coins-feature-stripe-payments/">Twitter Launches Coins Feature with Stripe Payments</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-coins-feature-stripe-payments/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto.com Delists USDT for Canadians Following OSC Ban</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-com-delists-usdt-osc-ban/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-com-delists-usdt-osc-ban/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Darya Rudz]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 10:01:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto.com]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto.com canada]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto.com exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto.com tether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto.com usdt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tether usdt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[usdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=232051</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-com-delists-usdt-osc-ban/">Crypto.com Delists USDT for Canadians Following OSC Ban</a></p>
<p>In December, the Canadian Securities Administrators (CSA) announced strengthening its approach to oversight of crypto trading platforms by expanding existing requirements for platforms operating in Canada. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-com-delists-usdt-osc-ban/">Crypto.com Delists USDT for Canadians Following OSC Ban</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-com-delists-usdt-osc-ban/">Crypto.com Delists USDT for Canadians Following OSC Ban</a></p>
<p>One of the leading global exchanges Crypto.com has announced its decision to delist Tether&#8217;s <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/tether/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">USDT</a> stablecoin for Canadians in order to comply with instructions from the Ontario Securities Commission (OSC), an independent agency responsible for regulating the capital markets in Ontario. Starting from January 31, USDT will no longer be available for Canadian residents on Crypto.com, and all the transactions involving the stablecoin will be suspended. The remaining USDT balance will be converted to USDC.</p>
<p>The exchange announced its decision in an email to its users.</p>
<blockquote class="reddit-card" ><p>      <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/Crypto_com/comments/10842e5/usdt_is_getting_delisted/?ref_source=embed&amp;ref=share">USDT is getting delisted</a> from      <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/Crypto_com/">Crypto_com</a>    </p></blockquote>
<p>    <script async src="https://embed.redditmedia.com/widgets/platform.js" charset="UTF-8"></script></p>
<p>According to Crypto.com spokesperson, the action follows increasing the scrutiny of centralized exchanges around the world, and Canada is not an exception. In December, the Canadian Securities Administrators (CSA) <a href="https://www.osc.ca/en/news-events/news/csa-provides-update-crypto-trading-platforms-operating-canada" target="_blank" rel="noopener">announced</a> strengthening its approach to oversight of crypto trading platforms by expanding existing requirements for platforms operating in Canada.</p>
<p>The press release reads:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The CSA continues to monitor and assess the presence and role of stablecoins in Canadian capital markets. As a result of this ongoing work, the CSA is of the view that stablecoins, or stablecoin arrangements, may constitute securities and/or derivatives. Crypto trading platforms that are registered or that have entered into a pre-registration undertaking are reminded that they are prohibited from permitting Canadian clients to trade, or obtain exposure to, any crypto asset that is itself a security and/or a derivative.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>In addition, CSA reminded that crypto trading platforms are required to have &#8216;established policies and procedures to determine whether each crypto asset they provide exposure to is a security and/or derivative.&#8217;</p>
<p>In its <a href="https://www.securities-administrators.ca/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/2022_2025CSA_BusinessPlan.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">2022-2025 Business Plan</a>, CSA set out six strategic goals, and one of them is related to stablecoins. The CSA aims to monitor and assess the presence and role of stablecoins in Canadian capital markets and work collaboratively to identify and respond to regulatory implications and risks.</p>
<h2>Tether (USDT) Under Scrutiny</h2>
<p>Although Tether remains the largest stablecoin with $66.28 billion in market cap, it is still affected by the collapse of Terra/ Luna USD and the crash of FTX exchange that took place in 2022. Following the failures, regulators around the world agree that Tether needs to be given the right transparency.</p>
<p>Back in September 2022, we <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tether-proof-usdt-backing/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a> about the order by New York Judge Katherine Polk Failla for Tether to come forward with documents to prove its USDT backing. Those included balance sheets, general ledgers, cash-flow statements, income statements, and profit and loss statements. The order also required Tether to share details about the accounts it holds at crypto exchanges Bitfinex, Poloniex, and Bittrex.</p>
<p>Further, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase Inc</a> (NASDAQ: COIN) exchange called its users to the conversion of their USDT stablecoins to USD Coin. It even <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-fee-usdt-usdc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">waved</a> the conversion fees to zero.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/demand-usdc-stablecoin-ftx-collapse/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-com-delists-usdt-osc-ban/">Crypto.com Delists USDT for Canadians Following OSC Ban</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-com-delists-usdt-osc-ban/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Demand for USDC Stablecoin Skyrockets after FTX Collapse</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/demand-usdc-stablecoin-ftx-collapse/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/demand-usdc-stablecoin-ftx-collapse/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 09:58:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[circle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[circle usdc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx collapse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tether usdt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[usd coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[usdc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[usdc stablecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[usdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=232125</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/demand-usdc-stablecoin-ftx-collapse/">Demand for USDC Stablecoin Skyrockets after FTX Collapse</a></p>
<p>Despite the fact that customers may be shifting their focus to its competitor, Tether doesn't see a threat.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/demand-usdc-stablecoin-ftx-collapse/">Demand for USDC Stablecoin Skyrockets after FTX Collapse</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/demand-usdc-stablecoin-ftx-collapse/">Demand for USDC Stablecoin Skyrockets after FTX Collapse</a></p>
<p>Following a series of events that took place in 2022, it appears that the Circle-issued <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/usd-coin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">USDC</a> stablecoin has suddenly found itself to be a favorite option among crypto users. According to a data report by blockchain analytics firm Glassnode, the USDC now sees a daily transfer volume of up to four or five times that of major competitor Tether USDT. That’s despite the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/tether/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">USDT</a> maintaining its status as the largest stablecoin by market capitalization.</p>
<p>Per the data, USDC has a transfer volume of $15 billion as opposed to that of USDT which is $3 billion. Altogether, USDC&#8217;s total transfer volume is $7 trillion more than USDT’s.</p>
<h2>What Drives USDC Stablecoin Adoption?</h2>
<p>It might be important to note that stablecoins are generally the easy choice for crypto investors. Particularly at a time like this, when market volatility remains at its highest. For some reason, however, USDC seems to be enjoying most of the attention. So, it all boils down to the fact that investors perceive USDC as a safer option.</p>
<p>Many USDC loyalists are always eager to point to USDC’s assets being backed by real cash or short-term U.S. treasuries. They also speak about how Circle ensures to carry out monthly audits and is usually transparent with the entire process.</p>
<p>Tether, on the other hand, has been severally accused of being economical with the truth when it comes to its reserves. The company behind USDT was slammed with a $41 million fine in October 2021. That was when the Commodity Futures Trading Commission CFTC <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tether-bitfinex-42-5m-ctfc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">accused</a> it of not holding sufficient reserves for almost 72% of two years.</p>
<p>Additionally, many investors also had fears that USDT had exposure to FTX and Alameda. This was when it briefly depegged against the US dollar shortly after the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-exchange-files-for-bankruptcy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX collapse</a>. However, Tether has come out to put the fears to bed, saying there&#8217;s no such exposure.</p>
<p>Despite the fact that customers may be shifting their focus to its competitor, Tether doesn&#8217;t see a threat. The firm points to its consistent growth in terms of market capitalization, <a href="https://twitter.com/Tether_to/status/1427375297729531909?t=8iB-ubgsb3sNoX8tZC_SRw&amp;s=19" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">insisting</a> that it shows “the market’s continued trust and confidence in Tether.”</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/judge-binance-us-lender-voyager-digital/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/demand-usdc-stablecoin-ftx-collapse/">Demand for USDC Stablecoin Skyrockets after FTX Collapse</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/demand-usdc-stablecoin-ftx-collapse/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Judge Clears Binance.US Bid to Acquire Bankrupt Crypto Lender Voyager Digital</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/judge-binance-us-lender-voyager-digital/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/judge-binance-us-lender-voyager-digital/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 09:51:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Deals News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance us]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[voyager digital]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=232123</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/judge-binance-us-lender-voyager-digital/">Judge Clears Binance.US Bid to Acquire Bankrupt Crypto Lender Voyager Digital</a></p>
<p>Voyager attorney said that the Binance.US deal is in the best interest of Voyager's creditors and would help them get their crypto back much faster. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/judge-binance-us-lender-voyager-digital/">Judge Clears Binance.US Bid to Acquire Bankrupt Crypto Lender Voyager Digital</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/judge-binance-us-lender-voyager-digital/">Judge Clears Binance.US Bid to Acquire Bankrupt Crypto Lender Voyager Digital</a></p>
<p>On Tuesday, January 11, bankrupt crypto lender Voyager Digital received initial approval to sell its assets to Binance.US in a proposed $1 billion deal. In New York, US Bankruptcy Judge Michael Wiles gave a green flag to Voyager to proceed with its purchase agreement with Binance.US.</p>
<p>However, the judge has asked other attorneys working on the deal to revise the proposed order documents before approving them. The deal is currently subject to another hearing in March 2023 and would require approval from a majority of Voyager&#8217;s creditors.</p>
<p>Crypto lender Voyager Digital had initially agreed to sell itself to <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a>. But following the collapse of FTX in November 2022, they decided to reopen the bidding process after which Binance.US managed to grab the deal last month.</p>
<p>Joshua Sussberg, the attorney representing voyager Digital noted that the bankrupt crypto lender was cooperating with the US Committee on Foreign Investment in the United States (CFIUS), even during the holiday season. He also noted that Voyager is looking to address any issues so that CFIUS could approve the transaction. &#8220;We are coordinating with Binance and their attorneys to not only deal with that inquiry but to voluntarily submit an application to move this process along,&#8221; Sussberg <a href="https://www.euronews.com/next/2023/01/10/fintech-crypto-voyager-bankruptcy" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>.</p>
<p>In yesterday&#8217;s hearing speaking on behalf of Voyager, Kirkland &amp; Ellis partner Christine Okike added that lawyers had &#8220;resolved for the purposes of today&#8221; objections made by the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a> and the state of New Jersey. &#8220;The debtors submit that we have performed due diligence on Binance US, and Binance US&#8217;s financials show that it has ample cash on hand to pay the debtors up to $35 million in cash, the maximum amount that may be due,&#8221; she said.</p>
<h2>Binance.US Deal for Voyager Creditors</h2>
<p>Voyager attorney Joshua Sussberg believes that moving forward on the deal with Binance.US would be in the best interest of Voyager&#8217;s creditors. &#8220;We do not want to delay getting money getting crypto back into our customers&#8217; hands. Importantly &#8230; we also took a very hard look at a standalone self-liquidation &#8230; the self-liquidation auction is not an option that is going to put the most money in our customers&#8217; pockets,&#8221; Sussborg said.</p>
<p>The Binance transaction involves $20 million in cash payments and an agreement of transferring Voyager&#8217;s customers to Binance.US. As per Voyager&#8217;s estimates, the sale would allow customers to recover 51% of the value of their deposits at the time of bankruptcy filing.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/group-one-ownership-microstrategy/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/judge-binance-us-lender-voyager-digital/">Judge Clears Binance.US Bid to Acquire Bankrupt Crypto Lender Voyager Digital</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/judge-binance-us-lender-voyager-digital/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Group One Declares 13.5% Options Ownership in MicroStrategy</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/group-one-ownership-microstrategy/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/group-one-ownership-microstrategy/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 09:49:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[group one]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[microstrategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MSTR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mstr stock]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=232130</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/group-one-ownership-microstrategy/">Group One Declares 13.5% Options Ownership in MicroStrategy</a></p>
<p>With Bitcoin gathering some decent gains since the new year, MicroStrategy saw its shares climb 34.21%.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/group-one-ownership-microstrategy/">Group One Declares 13.5% Options Ownership in MicroStrategy</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/group-one-ownership-microstrategy/">Group One Declares 13.5% Options Ownership in MicroStrategy</a></p>
<p>According to a <a href="https://www.sec.gov/Archives/edgar/data/932540/000093254023000001/MSTR13G.txt" target="_blank" rel="noopener">filing</a> with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), proprietary trading firm Group One has acquired options to buy 1.3 million shares of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/microstrategy-incorporated/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">MicroStrategy</a> (NASDAQ: MSTR). Group One presents itself as a market maker in US equity opinions, providing liquidity over diverse securities. On the other hand, MicroStrategy is the largest independent publicly-traded business intelligence company, popular for its <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> holdings. The company was the first to acquire Bitcoin as a primary treasury reserve asset. Under the leadership of CEO and Bitcoin bull <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/michael-saylor/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Michael Saylor</a>, MicroStrategy made its first BTC purchase in 2020. The company continues to amass digital coins and owns more than 132,000 coins.</p>
<h2>Group One Has 13.5% Stake in MicroStrategy</h2>
<p>Per the SEC filing, the 1.3 million shares also mean that Group One has a 13.5% stake in MicroStrategy. Meanwhile, MSTR currently trades at $190 per share after closing up 8.57. The company’s stock suffered along with BTC in 2022 due to its strong ties with the cryptocurrency. It plunged more than 70% last year as Bitcoin dropped from about $48,000 around March to $16,500 as the year wrapped up. While MSTR dropped 13% in the last three months, it also fell over 6% over the past month. With Bitcoin gathering some decent gains since the new year, MicroStrategy also saw its shares climb 34.21%. Furthermore, the business intelligence company has become a proxy for investors seeking Bitcoin exposure due to its exposure to the crypto asset.</p>
<p>Since it began to adopt Bitcoin, MicroStrategy conducted its first-ever BTC sale on the 22nd of December. The company sold 704 BTC for about $11.8 million to generate tax benefits. MicroStrategy commented on the sale:</p>
<blockquote><p>“MicroStrategy plans to carry back the capital losses resulting from this transaction against previous capital gains, to the extent such carrybacks are available under the federal income tax laws currently in effect, which may generate a tax benefit.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Although MicroStrategy has a cogent reason to sell its BTC, the company broke a promise. CEO Saylor once said in an interview that the company is not a seller. He stated that the business intelligence company’s strategy is only to acquire and hold Bitcoin. Following the first-ever Bitcoin sale, MSTR fell to its lowest level since August 2022, losing 1.1% to $136.63. However, the company repurchased 810 coins a couple of days after the sale.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/web-3-0-beacon-crypto-startups/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/group-one-ownership-microstrategy/">Group One Declares 13.5% Options Ownership in MicroStrategy</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/group-one-ownership-microstrategy/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Web 3.0 Accelerator Beacon Graduates 13 Innovative Crypto Startups</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/web-3-0-beacon-crypto-startups/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/web-3-0-beacon-crypto-startups/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 09:46:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Startups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Beacon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Demo Day]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=232059</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/web-3-0-beacon-crypto-startups/">Web 3.0 Accelerator Beacon Graduates 13 Innovative Crypto Startups</a></p>
<p>Besides the funding, the handpicked projects will receive cross-industry mentorship from other Beacon contributors.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/web-3-0-beacon-crypto-startups/">Web 3.0 Accelerator Beacon Graduates 13 Innovative Crypto Startups</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/web-3-0-beacon-crypto-startups/">Web 3.0 Accelerator Beacon Graduates 13 Innovative Crypto Startups</a></p>
<p>Beacon, a Web 3.0 accelerator has completed its inaugural program with 13 innovative blockchain startups that were presented during its Demo Day event. As <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2023/01/10/web3-focused-beacon-launches-flagship-demo-day-with-13-crypto-startups/?guccounter=1" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reported</a> by TechCrunch, the first Cohort graduating from Beacon, known as Cohort 0 was selected from a multitude of applicants from different countries and continents.</p>
<p>Beacon remains the brainchild of Sandeep Nailwal, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/matic-network/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Polygon</a> co-founder with key contributions from top builders and executives in the broader Web3.0 ecosystem. The goal of Beacon is not far-fetched and it includes helping innovative minds get the exposure they need as well as financing.</p>
<p>Nailwal revealed that the startup was created when he remembered the struggles he faced along with his team while building out the Polygon Layer-2 blockchain protocol. Designed to graduate two Cohorts per year in Fall and Spring respectively, the first Cohort presented their ideas at the just concluded Demo Day.</p>
<p>“For Cohort 0, we spoke with over 1,000 projects to end up at 15 companies in Cohort 0 with 13 graduating at our Demo Day,” Nailwal said in an interview with TechCrunch. “With the current rate of applications for Cohort 1, we’re planning to land at a similar 1% acceptance rate.”</p>
<p>According to Nailwal, Cohort 0 is seen as the MVP of Beacon, implying that its growth and relevance may become a unique reference point for future Cohorts. The selected startups will be availed primary funding of about $250,000 at a post-money valuation of $8 million for future Cohorts according to Nailwal</p>
<p>Besides the funding, the handpicked projects will receive cross-industry mentorship from other Beacon contributors including but not limited to Jack Lu, CEO, and co-founder of Magic Eden; a handful of venture capitalists; Rob Behnke, co-founder of Halborn; Brendan Farmer, co-lead at Polygon Zero; Dan Kim, VP of business development and listing at <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase Global Inc</a> (NASDAQ: COIN); and Miles Anthony, CEO, and co-founder of Decentral Games.</p>
<h2>Insights into the 13 Web 3.0 Startups Graduated by Beacon</h2>
<p>The 13 startups that revealed their ideas at the Beacon Demo Day event represented different aspects and embodied varying solutions in Web 3.0. These startups include Arcana, Blinkmoon, ChapterX, Colexion, Community Gaming, FastLane, Cubist, Meta Apes, Mystic Moose, Nillion, Davos Protocol, TimeSwap, and Ylide.</p>
<p>Arcana for instance is branded as a complete Web3.0 toolkit for developers, Blinkmoon, a Vancouver-Canada-based startup is a new, independent game development studio founded by industry veterans bridging the stunning world of visual effects to the immersive world of games.</p>
<p>Of all the startups presented, only Community Gaming is at the Series A funding level while others are at the Seed stage. As an ESports platform, Community Gaming was founded by Chris Gonsalves and offers <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a> &#8211; and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/solana/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Solana</a>-based blockchain payment technologies and provides players, organizers, and game developers tools to create, facilitate and participate in esports tournaments.</p>
<p>According to Beacon, the protocols are Chain-Agnostic, meaning they can easily interact with two or more protocols to further showcase the interoperability feature of the Web 3.0 world.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-busd-peg/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/web-3-0-beacon-crypto-startups/">Web 3.0 Accelerator Beacon Graduates 13 Innovative Crypto Startups</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/web-3-0-beacon-crypto-startups/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>