<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 17:54:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>BBBY Shares Plunge 24% as Bed Bath &amp; Beyond Hints at Bankruptcy</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bbby-shares-plunge-bankruptcy/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bbby-shares-plunge-bankruptcy/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 17:54:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bbby stock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bed Bath & Beyond]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=231523</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bbby-shares-plunge-bankruptcy/">BBBY Shares Plunge 24% as Bed Bath &#038; Beyond Hints at Bankruptcy</a></p>
<p>Amid the growing concern in the shares of BBBY, the stock is down by as much as 23.23% after previously hitting an All-Time Low (ATL). </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bbby-shares-plunge-bankruptcy/">BBBY Shares Plunge 24% as Bed Bath &#038; Beyond Hints at Bankruptcy</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bbby-shares-plunge-bankruptcy/">BBBY Shares Plunge 24% as Bed Bath &#038; Beyond Hints at Bankruptcy</a></p>
<p>An American chain of domestic merchandise retail stores Bed Bath &amp; Beyond Inc (NASDAQ: BBBY) has finally given a more concerning insight into its distressed financial state and has <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/01/05/bed-bath-beyond-shares-plummet-as-company-warns-of-deeper-financial-troubles.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">hinted</a> at a potential bankruptcy as a way to move forward from its current woes. The company has been recording low sales, further fueling a liquidity crunch that has left the firm to consider other viable restructuring means to stabilize the brand. All this has had a negative impact on BBBY shares.</p>
<p>The company’s Chief Executive Officer Sue Gove, who took over when former CEO Mark Tritton hit a brick wall in performance back in June last year, said the focus remains to implore new ways to reposition its brands including Bed Bath &amp; Beyond, Buybuy Baby and Harmon to “remain destinations of choice for customers well into the future.”</p>
<p>With bankruptcy one of the firm’s extreme getaway options, it is also looking at reducing its store footprints and continuing with its aggressive cut in workforce. Earlier, Gove confirmed that the company had secured $500 million to pilot its transformation. However, slowing sales across the board as evidenced by the empty shelves across its active stores are giving a bitter glimpse of the tough times ahead.</p>
<p>“Transforming an organization of our size and scale requires time, and we anticipate that each coming quarter will build on our progress,” she said.</p>
<p>Bed Bath &amp; Beyond is in search of a new Chief Financial Officer following the suicide of its former executive Gustavo Arnal back in September last year as <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bed-bath-beyond-cfo-died-bbby/">reported</a> at the time by Coinspeaker.</p>
<p>Whether or not the demise of Gustavo added to the company’s dilemma is unclear, however, what remains obvious is the net loss of about $385.8 million incurred in the third quarter ended November 26, down 40% from the year-ago period.</p>
<p>Bed Bath &amp; Beyond has been battling rejections from its suppliers, a trend that has kept its competitors including Target in an advantaged position.</p>
<h2>BBBY Shares and the Bankruptcy Scare: Encompassing Norm</h2>
<p>Amid the growing concern in the shares of BBBY, the stock is down by as much as 24.69% after previously hitting an All-Time Low (ATL).</p>
<p>The company’s distress remains obvious but in the broader financial ecosystem, its bankruptcy will not necessarily come as a shock to many. In reality, Bed Bath &amp; Beyond Inc’s woes date back beyond last year, and judging by firms who displayed healthy financials, it is undoubtedly <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-exchange-files-for-bankruptcy/">not going to outdo</a> FTX Derivatives Exchange if it decides to file for bankruptcy.</p>
<p>While bankruptcy remains one of its likely lifelines, CEO Gove is optimistic the company can pull through its challenges. At the moment, she said the firm is using the funds earned during the holiday season to repay the vendor it owes so it can easily restock its shelves and place additional orders for new goods.</p>
<p>Bigger retailers like <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/amazon/">Amazon.com Inc</a> (NASDAQ: AMZN) are also showing signs of distress with more than 18,000 workers have been <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/amazon-record-layoff-economic-crisis/">reportedly</a> laid off.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/blackrock-bitcoin-global-allocation-fund/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bbby-shares-plunge-bankruptcy/">BBBY Shares Plunge 24% as Bed Bath &#038; Beyond Hints at Bankruptcy</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bbby-shares-plunge-bankruptcy/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>BlackRock Adds Bitcoin to Global Allocation Fund</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/blackrock-bitcoin-global-allocation-fund/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/blackrock-bitcoin-global-allocation-fund/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 17:39:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blackrock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=231510</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/blackrock-bitcoin-global-allocation-fund/">BlackRock Adds Bitcoin to Global Allocation Fund</a></p>
<p>BlackRock is now providing Bitcoin exposure to the ordinary and passive investors of its Global Allocation Fund. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/blackrock-bitcoin-global-allocation-fund/">BlackRock Adds Bitcoin to Global Allocation Fund</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/blackrock-bitcoin-global-allocation-fund/">BlackRock Adds Bitcoin to Global Allocation Fund</a></p>
<p>Globally-renowned asset manager <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/blackrock/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BlackRock</a> (NYSE: BLK) has added Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a>) to its global allocation fund. Reports state that ordinary and passive investors can now gain BTC exposure via the BlackRock Global Allocation Fund. The highly coveted fund invests globally in both corporate and government-issued equity, debt, and short-term securities.</p>
<p>BlackRock’s Global Allocation Fund executes these investments without any prescribed limits. In addition, the fund looks to invest no less than 70% of its total assets in these securities of corporate and government issuers. Yet still, the fund could also choose to invest in the equity securities of minor and emerging growth companies. However, the BlackRock Global Allocation Fund demonstrates diverseness by investing a portion of its high-yield fixed-income transferable securities in its debt portfolio. Moreover, currency exposure is also flexibly managed.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Addition Could Grow BlackRock Fund AUM Further</h2>
<p>The BlackRock Global Allocation Fund presently manages roughly $15 trillion in assets, and the addition of Bitcoin should see these numbers swell further. Furthermore, this BTC development should also see white-collared individuals such as nurses and teachers buy Bitcoin alongside other equities and assets. The fund is usually recommended to white-collar professionals that want to invest savings but lack time to track the market. The reason why it sees such high recommendation value is due to its diverse nature. In addition, the BlackRock global fund also tries to track global growth, thereby protecting it from unsavory events in one country.</p>
<p>In a filing, BlackRock said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“The Fund may invest in cash-settled bitcoin futures that are traded on commodity exchanges registered with the Commodity Futures Trading Commission.”</p></blockquote>
<p>The addition of Bitcoin to the BlackRock fund also speaks volumes about how far the leading crypto has come. The fund is one of the first general ones to add BTC to its package. Furthermore, it also suggests that Bitcoin is now a worthy addition to even a conservative portfolio.</p>
<p>While many other providers also issue global allocation funds, Vanguard’s chief investment officer Greg Davis said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Although we see merit in supporting the technology behind cryptocurrency, we feel it’s best to stick to the investing principles that have made Vanguard a reliable choice for investors. So when it comes to cryptocurrency, we take the same approach and steer our clients toward time-tested products.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Davis’ assertion hints at the well-documented volatility of Bitcoin and most crypto in general. In addition, several previous academic studies also explicitly show that Bitcoin increases risk-adjusted returns.</p>
<h2>BlackRock ‘Long-Haul’ Philosophy Plays Well to BTC Price Trajectory</h2>
<p>Despite the roller-coaster nature of the crypto price trajectory, the BlackRock fund might greatly benefit from the BTC addition. The reason is that the Global Allocation is for long-term investments, and Bitcoin returns over at least four years are usually good.</p>
<p>Assumptions abound within the traditional finance space that other funds may eventually follow BlackRock’s lead. The possibility of similar funds abounding increases if the BlackRock fund shows significant returns after two years.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/aag-flagship-product-metaone-wallet/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/blackrock-bitcoin-global-allocation-fund/">BlackRock Adds Bitcoin to Global Allocation Fund</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/blackrock-bitcoin-global-allocation-fund/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>AAG Launches Its Flagship Product, MetaOne Web 3.0 Wallet</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/aag-flagship-product-metaone-wallet/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/aag-flagship-product-metaone-wallet/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 16:03:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[aag]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MetaOne Wallet]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=231390</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/aag-flagship-product-metaone-wallet/">AAG Launches Its Flagship Product, MetaOne Web 3.0 Wallet</a></p>
<p>The security features of the MetaOne Wallet are hinged on the AAG scam detector software.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/aag-flagship-product-metaone-wallet/">AAG Launches Its Flagship Product, MetaOne Web 3.0 Wallet</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/aag-flagship-product-metaone-wallet/">AAG Launches Its Flagship Product, MetaOne Web 3.0 Wallet</a></p>
<p>AAG, a Web3.0 infrastructure service provider has <a href="https://getmeta.one" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">launched</a> its flagship product, the MetaOne Wallet as it seeks to drive an inclusive usage of Decentralized Applications (DApp) in the blockchain ecosystem. As contained in a Press Release shared with Coinspeaker, the launch of the MetaOne Wallet comes with a lot of allowances that make it a good choice for both experienced investors and those new to the space.</p>
<p>Decentralized non-custodial wallets such as the MetaOne are considered a major gateway into the Web 3.0 world. The wallets can be relied upon to connect to Decentralized Exchanges (DEXs), <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-decentralized-finance-defi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Decentralized Finance</a> (DeFi) platforms, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Non-Fungible Token</a> (NFT) protocols, and a host of others.</p>
<p>The MetaOne Wallet enables all of these connections in a simplified way. As an avenue to safeguard assets and interact with the emerging decentralized world, users are often tasked with keeping their seed phrases safe. These seed phrases are keys that can unlock a wallet and its content and it is the standard safety rule for most wallets.</p>
<p>The emergence of MetaOne is notably designed to help eliminate the need to remember seed phrases as the wallet enables users to log in or access their accounts through a variety of means. Some of these avenues include the use of email addresses and passwords or the biometric fingerprint scanners attached to most devices today. Users can easily choose and set up whichever option that best resonates with them.</p>
<p>“I truly believe MetaOne will be a game-changer for both consumers and businesses. When businesses are able to provide a more seamless onboarding experience and consumers can feel safe to enter and discover what they can do with Web 3.0, we will be able to take a giant leap toward mainstream adoption,” said Jack Vinijtrongjit, Co-Founder and CEO of AAG.</p>
<h2>MetaOne Wallet to Drive New Frontiers</h2>
<p>The MetaOne Wallet has a number of inbuilt features that make it a game-changing next-generation wallet for the Web 3.0 world. Besides its simple user interface, users can experience no hassle to fund or purchase any token of their choice. This is because the wallet supports on-ramp transactions with the help of Coinbase Pay and Simplex.</p>
<p>These allowance helps users buy cryptocurrencies using their bank cards just as they make payments at online stores. In addition, the MetaOne Wallet has a DApp Store that is built to harbor as many as 1,100 applications at launch. Each of these supported DApps has been vetted and thus, offers users a high level of safety.</p>
<p>The security features of the MetaOne Wallet are hinged on the AAG scam detector software. With exploits a common occurrence in the crypto world, suspicious transactions on the platform will be flagged by the wallet, nudging users into consciousness in case they are about to make an error.</p>
<p>In all, MetaOne will infuse a functional academy whose sole aim will be hinged on educating users on the potential of the product as an extension of the capabilities of the broader blockchain world. The MetaOne Wallet will support digital assets (crypto and NFTs) on <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a>, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a>, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/matic-network/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Polygon</a>, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/harmony/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Harmony</a>, and BNB Chain at launch and has plans to integrate more protocols in the near future.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/samsung-q4-operating-profit-slump/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/aag-flagship-product-metaone-wallet/">AAG Launches Its Flagship Product, MetaOne Web 3.0 Wallet</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/aag-flagship-product-metaone-wallet/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Samsung to Report Q4 Operating Profit Slump amid Global Market Downturn</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/samsung-q4-operating-profit-slump/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/samsung-q4-operating-profit-slump/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 15:01:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[samsung]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[samsung electronics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=231499</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/samsung-q4-operating-profit-slump/">Samsung to Report Q4 Operating Profit Slump amid Global Market Downturn</a></p>
<p>Samsung has had a relatively tough year, one that has seeped into its stock performance.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/samsung-q4-operating-profit-slump/">Samsung to Report Q4 Operating Profit Slump amid Global Market Downturn</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/samsung-q4-operating-profit-slump/">Samsung to Report Q4 Operating Profit Slump amid Global Market Downturn</a></p>
<p>South Korean multinational tech giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/samsung/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Samsung Electronics Co Ltd</a> (KRX: 005930) is set to report a significant slump in its fourth quarter (Q4) operating profit amid a broader plunge in the global economy. According to a Reuters <a href="https://money.usnews.com/investing/news/articles/2023-01-04/samsungs-quarterly-profit-set-to-hit-6-year-low-as-consumers-hunker-down" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a>, citing a Refinitiv SmartEstimate from 21 analysts, the company’s operating profit is bound to fall to 5.9 trillion won ($4.62 billion).</p>
<p>Samsung is set to release the preliminary report on Friday while the full report is billed for later this month. Should the analyst&#8217;s estimates come through, it will come off as the worst quarterly performance for the company since the third quarter of 2016. Amid the slow recovery from the COVID-19 pandemic in 2021, the company recorded an operating profit of 13.87 trillion won within the same quarter.</p>
<p>&#8220;The main reason for the performance&#8230; is a sharp drop in demand. Both shipments and prices of chips and smartphones are expected to fall short of previous expectations,&#8221; said Kim Roko, an analyst at Hana Financial Investment.</p>
<p>The slumped revenue expectation from Samsung showcases the frailty in the semiconductor industry which has taken quite a beating as consumer tapers down on spending for luxury phones. The prices of the DRAM memory chips which are the most important for use in laptops and PCs dropped 40% on a year-on-year basis.</p>
<p>Drawing on data from TrendForce, prices of NAND Flash chips used in data storage also fell by 14% year-on-year.</p>
<p>These drops were reflected in the reduced handset shipments which came in at 63 million for the quarter. Of these numbers, 62 million were smartphones as detailed by Counterpoint. The mobile phone shipment also directly contrasts with the 72 million handsets that Samsung sold out in the fourth quarter of 2021.</p>
<h2>Samsung to Sustain Investment Despite Reduced Operating Profit</h2>
<p>The South Korean giant, ranked as the fourth largest publicly traded company in Asia, is set to continue its projected investment in its business segments this year.</p>
<p>The company chose to maintain this strategy with the understanding that its investments at this period of market low can help it secure a significant market share. This it hopes will pay off when the broader financial ecosystem recovers.</p>
<p>Samsung’s top rivals including SK Hynix Inc (KRX: 000660) and Micron Technology Inc (NASDAQ: MU) have revealed plans to halt their investments until at least the second half of this year. Rather than trail this path, Samsung is not reducing the earmarked 128.82 trillion won ($100.83 billion) it plans to spend on research and development this year as it <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/samsung-advanced-chips-2027/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">unveiled</a> back in October 2022.</p>
<p>Samsung has had a relatively tough year, one that has seeped into its stock performance. While its shares are currently trading at 58,200 won, up 0.69%, it has fallen as much as 29% in the year-to-date period.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/silvergate-staff-layoff-asset-liquidation/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/samsung-q4-operating-profit-slump/">Samsung to Report Q4 Operating Profit Slump amid Global Market Downturn</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/samsung-q4-operating-profit-slump/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Silvergate Resorted to Staff Layoff, Asset Liquidation to Survive FTX-Triggered Crypto Meltdown</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/silvergate-staff-layoff-asset-liquidation/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/silvergate-staff-layoff-asset-liquidation/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 14:55:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[diem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sam bankman-fried]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sbf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[silvergate]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=231501</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/silvergate-staff-layoff-asset-liquidation/">Silvergate Resorted to Staff Layoff, Asset Liquidation to Survive FTX-Triggered Crypto Meltdown</a></p>
<p>Crypto bank Silvergate had to undertake a 200-employee layoff and take other drastic measures to facilitate a withdrawal bank run. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/silvergate-staff-layoff-asset-liquidation/">Silvergate Resorted to Staff Layoff, Asset Liquidation to Survive FTX-Triggered Crypto Meltdown</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/silvergate-staff-layoff-asset-liquidation/">Silvergate Resorted to Staff Layoff, Asset Liquidation to Survive FTX-Triggered Crypto Meltdown</a></p>
<p>During the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a>-triggered crypto meltdown, Silvergate Bank scrambled to cover a massive withdrawal spate and also embarked on a <a href="https://www.sec.gov/Archives/edgar/data/1312109/000131210923000011/si-20230105.htm" target="_blank" rel="noopener">substantial</a> staff layoff. According to the <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/silvergate-raced-to-cover-8-1-billion-in-withdrawals-during-crypto-meltdown-11672895207" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Wall Street Journal</a>, the crypto-focused bank offloaded assets at a loss to cover $8.1 billion in withdrawals. Silvergate also downsized its staff force by a whopping 40% to remain buoyant. Despite these extreme measures taken, the crypto bank says that it remains committed to digital assets.</p>
<h2>Silvergate Halts Digital Currency Plans in Addition to Staff Layoff</h2>
<p>In addition to its sizable staff layoff and emergency liquidity injection, Silvergate also halted plans to launch a digital currency. Furthermore, the California-based bank wrote off the $196 million linked to its acquisition of Diem Association from<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/meta/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"> Meta</a> (NASDAQ: META).</p>
<p>Silvergate’s shares were trading down 23% at $16.9 during the pre-market trading session after these developments.</p>
<p>According to Silvergate, crypto-related deposits plummeted 68% in the fourth quarter of last year. In order to satisfy the withdrawals, the crypto bank liquidated debt on its balance sheet. However, Silvergate incurred a $718 million loss selling the debt, which far surpasses its total profits since at least 2013.</p>
<p>At the end of 2022’s fourth quarter, Silvergate stated that it had more cash on hand at $4.6 billion than its remaining $3.8 billion deposits. In addition, the bank held another $5.6 billion in debt securities, such as US Treasurys, that were easy to liquidate. Silvergate, which saw a rise in daily average volume on its network in the fourth quarter, also said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“While Silvergate is taking decisive action to navigate the current environment, its mission has not changed. Silvergate believes in the digital asset industry.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>Silvergate Able to Survive Steep Deposit Decline</h2>
<p>Silvergate, which laid off more than 200 employees, could withstand a steep decline in deposits due to its internal structure. The crypto-centric platform is not structured like most other banks and sold off much of its traditional banking branches and operations. This move freed Silvergate to focus exclusively on providing crypto investors and exchanges bank accounts. As it stands, crypto-related deposits make up around 90% of Silvergate’s total. In addition, the bank retains almost all of its deposits in cash or easy-to-liquidate securities.</p>
<p>Despite the tumult brought about in the crypto space by FTX’s collapse, Silvergate pledged to remain committed. According to the bank, it has the funding to weather a sustained period of transformation.</p>
<p>Silvergate’s core service is to custody the deposits of crypto-minded companies. In addition, the platform also operates a network that facilitates business between investors and crypto exchanges. However, late last year, Silvegate came under intense scrutiny over its relationship with ex-FTX CEO <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/sam-bankman-fried/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Sam Bankman-Fried’</a>s companies. Furthermore, the sudden implosion of FTX in early November rattled the crypto space and sent Silvergate’s stock plummeting.</p>
<p>Since FTX’s bankruptcy, questions regarding the viability of Silvergate’s business model have grown louder. Furthermore, a few days ago, a group of federal regulators warned banks against too much exposure to the crypto market.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sony-honda-electric-car-afeela-2026/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/silvergate-staff-layoff-asset-liquidation/">Silvergate Resorted to Staff Layoff, Asset Liquidation to Survive FTX-Triggered Crypto Meltdown</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/silvergate-staff-layoff-asset-liquidation/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sony &amp; Honda Announce New Electric Car Brand Afeela for Shipping in 2026</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sony-honda-electric-car-afeela-2026/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sony-honda-electric-car-afeela-2026/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 13:01:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Transportation News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[afeela]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ces]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[honda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sony]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=231480</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sony-honda-electric-car-afeela-2026/">Sony &amp; Honda Announce New Electric Car Brand Afeela for Shipping in 2026</a></p>
<p>Electronics giant Sony and automobile company Honda recently revealed the prototype of their joint electric car initiative at 2023's CES.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sony-honda-electric-car-afeela-2026/">Sony &amp; Honda Announce New Electric Car Brand Afeela for Shipping in 2026</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sony-honda-electric-car-afeela-2026/">Sony &amp; Honda Announce New Electric Car Brand Afeela for Shipping in 2026</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sony/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Sony</a> and Honda have unveiled the prototype of their <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sony-honda-electric-car-2025-debut/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">joint electric car initiative</a> Afeela at this year&#8217;s Consumer Electronics Show (CES). On Wednesday, the four-door sedan drove onstage as Sony CEO Kenichiro Yoshida explained the company&#8217;s mobility outlook. According to Kenichiro, Sony looks to build vehicles that have autonomous functionality and can transform into &#8220;moving entertainment spaces.&#8221;</p>
<p>There is little-known information regarding Afeela. However, the Sony/Honda electric car will begin shipping to North America in 2026. Meanwhile, the first preorders of the Afeelas will happen in 2025, with sales also starting that same year.</p>
<h2>Deep Dive into Upcoming Sony-Honda Electric Car</h2>
<p>According to reports, production of the midsize-sedan-looking Afeela will take place at one of Honda&#8217;s manufacturing plants. Furthermore, the electric automobile will combine staple elements from both Sony and Honda in its functionality. For example, Afeela would leverage Sony&#8217;s experience with AI, virtual reality, entertainment, and augmented reality for a pleasurable and interactive driving experience. In addition, the car would incorporate grounded safety and driver assistance systems from Honda. According to Sony Honda Mobility CEO Yasuhide Mizuno, Afeela&#8217;s offerings will focus on sensing and interacting with people. In addition, Mizuno said that much production emphasis would also be placed on enhancing driving dynamics and performance. Summing these concepts up, the Sony Honda Mobility chief executive <a href="https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-11601385/Sony-unveils-prototype-EV-Afeela-Honda.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">explained</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Afeela represents our concept of an interactive relationship where people feel the sensation of interactive mobility and where mobility can detect and understand people and society by utilizing sensing and AI technologies.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The vehicle&#8217;s exterior will reportedly sport over 40 sensors, including cameras, ultrasonic, radar, and lidar. These sensors enhance Afeela&#8217;s ability to detect objects while driving autonomously. Among the aforementioned sensors is a narrow exterior display screen called the media bar, which runs along the car&#8217;s front bumper. In a nutshell, Mizuno said that the EV would embody three primary themes, namely autonomy, augmentation, and affinity.</p>
<h2>Epic Games Collaboration</h2>
<p>Sony and Honda are working with Unreal Engine graphics technology from <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/epic-games/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Epic Games</a> to design Afeela&#8217;s interface. Unreal Engine, which produces Fortnite, has also seen its technology deployed by other automobile brands, including <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/general-motors/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">General Motors.</a></p>
<p>Epic Games chief technology officer Kim Libreri commented on how the video game and software developer would enhance Afeela&#8217;s functionality. He says the most organic way to visualize critical data within the vehicle is via intuitive interactive photo real augmentation. Libreri further explained that this ability played to Epic Games&#8217; strengths. He also said:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;In the future, the automobile will become a next generation destination for social connectivity. Not only for the occupants, but also their network of friends and colleagues. It will become a continuum of our digital lives.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Afeela Pricing</h2>
<p>Pricing of Afeela, which currently resembles a mashup between a Porsche 911 and the Lucid Air, will be comparable to other premium automakers. These include <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/mercedes-benz/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Mercedes-Benz</a>, BMW, Audi, and Volvo. Furthermore, Sony expects the car&#8217;s software to offer subscription-based services. This implies that Afeela&#8217;s owners will likely have to pay a monthly fee to access certain features.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/amazon-record-layoff-economic-crisis/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sony-honda-electric-car-afeela-2026/">Sony &amp; Honda Announce New Electric Car Brand Afeela for Shipping in 2026</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sony-honda-electric-car-afeela-2026/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Retail Giant Amazon to Carry Out Record Layoff of 18,000 Employees amid Economic Crisis</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/amazon-record-layoff-economic-crisis/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/amazon-record-layoff-economic-crisis/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 12:42:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Amazon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[andy jassy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=231445</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/amazon-record-layoff-economic-crisis/">Retail Giant Amazon to Carry Out Record Layoff of 18,000 Employees amid Economic Crisis</a></p>
<p>Recently,  layoff decisions has somewhat become a trend among global firms.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/amazon-record-layoff-economic-crisis/">Retail Giant Amazon to Carry Out Record Layoff of 18,000 Employees amid Economic Crisis</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/amazon-record-layoff-economic-crisis/">Retail Giant Amazon to Carry Out Record Layoff of 18,000 Employees amid Economic Crisis</a></p>
<p>Online retail giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/amazon/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Amazon</a> has announced its decision to cut down its number of employees due to the global economic situation. The <a href="https://www.aboutamazon.com/news/company-news/update-from-ceo-andy-jassy-on-role-eliminations" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announcement</a>, which comes as a follow-up to a previous one, confirms that the layoffs will affect no less than 18,000 employees of the firm.</p>
<p>According to Amazon Chief Executive, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/andy-jassy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Andy Jassy</a>, full details of the layoffs will emerge by January 18. However, he can confirm that the company’s e-commerce and human resources departments will be largely affected.</p>
<h2>Amazon Rues Economic Situation, Continues Massive Layoffs</h2>
<p>Per the decision, Amazon will be cutting ties with nearly 6% of its 300,000-man corporate workforce.</p>
<p>Although this kind of decision has somewhat become a trend among global firms recently, it is particularly surprising for Amazon which recently doubled its base pay ceiling for employees.</p>
<p>Citing reasons for the decision to lay off their staff, Jassy says it is mostly as a result of the uncertain economy. He also added that the firm may have hired too rapidly over the past few years.</p>
<p>It might be worth mentioning that this is not the first time Amazon is letting go of its staff in recent times. The firm allegedly began its layoff spree last November, starting with staff from its devices division.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, concerns are being raised in some quarters regarding why Amazon chose to make such an announcement before officially informing the affected staff. Recall that an earlier report in the Wall Street Journal suggested that Amazon was planning to cut down 17,000 jobs. In a response memo to the company’s staff, Jassy wrote:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We don&#8217;t take these decisions lightly or underestimate how much they might affect the lives of those who are impacted.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The Chief Executive explained that the announcement was a response to the leak which is why the news is coming before officially reaching out to those affected.</p>
<p>Nonetheless, Amazon will ensure to file legal notices about the mass layoffs and include plans to pay severance.</p>
<h2>Tech Industry Layoffs</h2>
<p>For what it&#8217;s worth, Amazon is not an isolated case when it comes to layoffs. It is an industry-wide trend. According to tracking site Layoffs.fyi, the tech industry as a whole, released over 150,000 workers in total throughout 2022. And just yesterday, Salesforce Inc also <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/salesforce-workforce-pandemic/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">revealed</a> plans to axe nearly 10% of its staff as well. According to figures company staff figures available as of October 31, that will amount to about 8,000 jobs. Amazon&#8217;s layoffs have now surpassed that of Facebook-parent Meta Platforms. Meta <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/zuckerberg-meta-employee-layoffs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">announced</a> 11,000 job cuts in 2022.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/file-crypto-tax-reports-uk/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/amazon-record-layoff-economic-crisis/">Retail Giant Amazon to Carry Out Record Layoff of 18,000 Employees amid Economic Crisis</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/amazon-record-layoff-economic-crisis/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>File Crypto Tax Reports at Unbeatable Price in UK</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/file-crypto-tax-reports-uk/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/file-crypto-tax-reports-uk/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 12:34:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptiony]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto tax]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[regulation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=229243</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/file-crypto-tax-reports-uk/">File Crypto Tax Reports at Unbeatable Price in UK</a></p>
<p>Cryptiony was established to help solve one of the most fundamental challenges in the digital currency sector - filing tax reports.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/file-crypto-tax-reports-uk/">File Crypto Tax Reports at Unbeatable Price in UK</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/file-crypto-tax-reports-uk/">File Crypto Tax Reports at Unbeatable Price in UK</a></p>
<p>The bigger the crypto ecosystem, the more tax authorities in different jurisdictions will require active players to file their tax reports. While many countries have not gotten to the level at which they enforce their own tax rules, the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-crypto-tax-investments/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">United Kingdom is a notable exception</a>. Taxes are not just mandatory in the country, it is a criminal offense to evade crypto taxes or file its report either for losses or profits made.</p>
<p>Herein lies the complications, filing tax reports is a somewhat new requirement from regulators, one which most accounting agencies are not adequately equipped to handle. This has paved the way for innovative crypto tax automation platforms among which is <a href="https://cryptiony.com/?utm_source=article&amp;utm_medium=coinspeaker&amp;utm_campaign=launching" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Cryptiony</a>.</p>
<p>Cryptiony was established to help solve one of the most fundamental challenges in the digital currency sector &#8211; filing tax reports. Filing crypto tax returns is a very complicated affair as there is no guiding standard governing this aspect of the industry yet. With thousands of crypto exchanges now in the market for the growing number of crypto investors to choose from, the strain in computing crypto tax reports from this platform is so enormous.</p>
<p>Cryptiony resolves this with its crypto tax automation web application for individuals and tax professionals. The platform is driven by the mission to enable easy cryptocurrency tax calculation, fostering cheap and fast computations for beginners, professional traders, and accountants by using automation and encryption processes to make crypto tax compliance stressless.</p>
<p>The design of the Cryptiony platform will not just help every user of its crypto tax automation tool comply with extant regulations, but it will help place the broader industry in very good standing with authorities around the world. This assumption is based on the fact that the easier it is for regulators to track the crypto market for taxation and other purposes, the more comfortable they will be in enabling innovations in the industry to thrive.</p>
<h2>The Cryptiony Advantage in Crypto Tax Filing</h2>
<p>Cryptiony offers a lot of advantages to people adopting it to file their tax reports, especially in the UK. To begin with, the platform offers free tax report filing for up to 500 transactions, and its charges are friendly, and based on an annual subscription model.</p>
<p>Cryptiony offers the same model as other known crypto tax protocols but it is designed as a more user-friendly alternative with quick synchronizations with the exchanges, it is more convenient and quick.</p>
<p>The Cryptiony platform is the brainwork of Bartosz Milczarek serving as the platform’s Chief Executive Officer, Krzysztof Dworakowski serving as the CTO, and Hanna Milczarek who is the CMO. Each of these veterans has decades of experience building automation solutions in the digital and tech world and they decided to turn their passion into a business that morphed into Cryptiony.</p>
<p>Though cryptocurrency tax computations can be complicated and costly, the use of the Cryptiony app comes off as one easy getaway for crypto traders, investors, and accounting professionals alike.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/doj-465m-robinhood-shares-sbf/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/file-crypto-tax-reports-uk/">File Crypto Tax Reports at Unbeatable Price in UK</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/file-crypto-tax-reports-uk/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>US DOJ Prepares to Seize $465M in Robinhood Shares Belonging to SBF, HOOD Stock Up 3.4%</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/doj-465m-robinhood-shares-sbf/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/doj-465m-robinhood-shares-sbf/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 12:30:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Alameda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[doj]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hood stock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[robinhood]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[robinhood shares]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sam bankman-fried]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sbf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[us doj]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=231455</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/doj-465m-robinhood-shares-sbf/">US DOJ Prepares to Seize $465M in Robinhood Shares Belonging to SBF, HOOD Stock Up 3.4%</a></p>
<p>The DoJ believes SBF engaged in a year-long fraud business that cost investors and customers billions of dollars.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/doj-465m-robinhood-shares-sbf/">US DOJ Prepares to Seize $465M in Robinhood Shares Belonging to SBF, HOOD Stock Up 3.4%</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/doj-465m-robinhood-shares-sbf/">US DOJ Prepares to Seize $465M in Robinhood Shares Belonging to SBF, HOOD Stock Up 3.4%</a></p>
<p>The United States Department of Justice (DOJ) is, ostensibly, preparing to seize and liquidate Sam Bankman-Fried’s (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/sam-bankman-fried/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SBF</a>) 56 million <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/robinhood/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Robinhood Markets Inc</a> (NASDAQ: HOOD) shares valued at approximately $465 million. Notably, SBF purchased approximately 7.42 percent of HOOD stock via Emergent Fidelity Technologies Ltd, using funds borrowed from Alameda Research, according to an affidavit he filed in December in an Antigua court.</p>
<p>According to media outlet <a href="https://www.reuters.com/legal/bankman-fried-set-enter-not-guilty-plea-ftx-fraud-case-2023-01-03/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Reuters</a>, US attorney Seth Shapiro told US Bankruptcy Judge John Dorsey &#8211; who is overseeing the FTX bankruptcy &#8211; that SBF’s stake in Robinhood are proceeds of FTX. As such, the United States attorney thinks the $465 million should be seized and shared between FTX stakeholders including BlockFi.</p>
<p>SBF pleaded not guilty to fraud charges filed against him in a United State court and the hearing has been set for October.</p>
<p>However, experts say SBF will be fighting a steep legal battle after his close <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a> and Alameda counterparts Caroline Ellison and Gary Wang pleaded guilty to fraud charges.</p>
<p>Moreover, Ellison and Wang have agreed to fully cooperate with government prosecutors against SBF.</p>
<p>“It’s going to be a very tough task for Bankman-Fried to ultimately prevail at trial. And while Bankman-Fried could be hoping for leniency, he may end up with a more severe sentence than he originally bargained for,” Mark A. Kasten, a partner at law firm Buchanan Ingersoll &amp; Rooney PC Counsel, noted.</p>
<h2>SBF Threatens to Pull Down Crypto Market</h2>
<p>The cryptocurrency market has taken a nosedive since the collapse of FTX and its native token FTT. With billions of dollars vaporized from the FTX implosion, regulators are keen to pounce hard on predatory crypto projects.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="474" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">The entire industry’s credibility is cratering b/c of fraudsters like <a href="https://twitter.com/SBF_FTX?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@SBF_FTX</a> and other bad actors. We have members of Congress talking about banning crypto w/an SEC Chair ready to pounce on the good guys while conspiring w/the bad guys. Let’s not do this. How about a zoom call?</p>
<p>&mdash; John E Deaton (@JohnEDeaton1) <a href="https://twitter.com/JohnEDeaton1/status/1610019554951929859?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 2, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Several crypto companies that were exposed to FTX and Alameda have since collapsed or are on the verge of filing for bankruptcy. As such, SBF investigators have an uphill task to tackle a rogue FTX balance sheet that included FTT as assets. Furthermore, the DoJ believes SBF engaged in a year-long fraud business that cost investors and customers billions of dollars.</p>
<p>Following the FTX&#8217;s collapse, market strategists are worried the market may plummet further in the coming quarters before rebounding. A long crypto winter eventually reciprocates to job loss as trading volume decreases over time. Furthermore, Coinbase warned in its Q4 earnings results that crypto trading volume is expected to fall further in 2023. Additionally, SBF had indicated before the FTX collapse that most cryptocurrency exchanges are silently struggling to stay liquid.</p>
<p>According to our latest crypto price oracles, Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a>) is exchanging for around $16,813, up 1.7 percent in the past seven days.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/oorbit-lg-electronics-metaverse-games/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/doj-465m-robinhood-shares-sbf/">US DOJ Prepares to Seize $465M in Robinhood Shares Belonging to SBF, HOOD Stock Up 3.4%</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/doj-465m-robinhood-shares-sbf/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Oorbit Partners with LG Electronics to Bring Metaverse Games to Smart TVs</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/oorbit-lg-electronics-metaverse-games/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/oorbit-lg-electronics-metaverse-games/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 12:25:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[lg]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[oorbit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[samsung]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=231432</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/oorbit-lg-electronics-metaverse-games/">Oorbit Partners with LG Electronics to Bring Metaverse Games to Smart TVs</a></p>
<p>With the metaverse gaining immense momentum through NFTs and blockchain technology, LG and Oorbit are poised to disrupt the industry significantly.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/oorbit-lg-electronics-metaverse-games/">Oorbit Partners with LG Electronics to Bring Metaverse Games to Smart TVs</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/oorbit-lg-electronics-metaverse-games/">Oorbit Partners with LG Electronics to Bring Metaverse Games to Smart TVs</a></p>
<p>Oorbit, a 3D cloud-based technology platform, has announced a strategic partnership with LG Electronics to bring immersive gaming to smart TVs. Through the partnership, LG and Oorbit users can access virtual concerts on Elynxir from Pixelynx and AI generative multiplayer games in Auxworld from Auxuman.</p>
<p>In a note through the announcement, Pooya Koosha, CTO and Oorbit cofounder, noted that the company has been developing hardware and software for the last decade to meet immersive gaming needs.</p>
<p>“Our proprietary technology is the connective tissue that links virtual worlds together and makes it easy for developers and brands to bring their experiences into the metaverse. Scaling our technology for millions of LG TV customers is the next step in making the metaverse accessible for all,” Koosha added.</p>
<p>Jung Sung-hyun, head of the content service division at LG Electronics Home Entertainment Company noted that the partnership with Oorbit is in line with its mission to bring entertainment to every user. With the metaverse gaining immense momentum through NFTs and blockchain technology, LG and Oorbit are poised to disrupt the industry significantly.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the South Korean tech giant has been in existence for decades and sold millions of quality devices worldwide.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="474" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Announced just in time for <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/CES2023?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#CES2023</a>, we’re excited to announce that we have partnered with <a href="https://twitter.com/LGElectronics?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@LGElectronics</a> to bring interoperable gaming and social experiences directly to your LG Smart TVs.</p>
<p>READ: <a href="https://t.co/nppJZe650B">https://t.co/nppJZe650B</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Oorbit (@OorbitOnline) <a href="https://twitter.com/OorbitOnline/status/1610731239970902016?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 4, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Ash Koosha, CEO of Oorbit, <a href="https://www.venturebeat.com/games/oobit-partners-with-lg-to-bring-interoperable-metaverse-platform-to-tvs/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">noted</a> in a statement. “Imagine playing with a map you bought for one game and taking that same item into a concert where it becomes your backstage pass. Translatable digital ownership is possible with virtual worlds that are connected through Oorbit.….”</p>
<h2>LG and Oorbit Tap on Blockchain and Cryptocurrency Market</h2>
<p>The cryptocurrency market has grown into a trillion-dollar industry within a decade of existence. Global tech companies are tapping into the blockchain industry to diversify their revenue collection avenues. Furthermore, blockchain technology has indicated an immense potential to disrupt global markets with ease.</p>
<p>As such, LG has increased its focus on cryptocurrency and blockchain technology in the past few years. For instance, the South Korean tech company officially updated its business development goals to include cryptocurrency and blockchain-based software in March 2022.</p>
<p>As one of the largest electronics companies, LG unveiled a cryptocurrency wallet dubbed Wallypto built on top of the Hedera Hashgraph blockchain and currently supports Hedera’s HTS tokens.</p>
<p>Notably, LG will be competing with other companies in the metaverse market including <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/samsung/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Samsung</a> which announced similar intentions last year.</p>
<p>Oorbit, on the other hand, has attracted notable attention from several investors in the industry. For instance, Oorbit announced last year that it raised $5 million in funding for its metaverse platform from Mark Cuban, Deadmau5 company Pixelynx, and HOF Capital.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-400m-fine-dpc-eu-privacy-laws/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/oorbit-lg-electronics-metaverse-games/">Oorbit Partners with LG Electronics to Bring Metaverse Games to Smart TVs</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/oorbit-lg-electronics-metaverse-games/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>