<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 11:08:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>PayPal Unveils Cryptocurrencies Hub Following PYUSD Stablecoin Launch</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-cryptocurrencies-hub-pyusd/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-cryptocurrencies-hub-pyusd/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 11:08:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[paypal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[paypal usd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pyusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266803</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-cryptocurrencies-hub-pyusd/">PayPal Unveils Cryptocurrencies Hub Following PYUSD Stablecoin Launch</a></p>
<p>While PayPal's new crypto service allows users to explore the crypto industry, access to this innovative feature has been restricted in certain jurisdictions and for specific individuals.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-cryptocurrencies-hub-pyusd/">PayPal Unveils Cryptocurrencies Hub Following PYUSD Stablecoin Launch</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-cryptocurrencies-hub-pyusd/">PayPal Unveils Cryptocurrencies Hub Following PYUSD Stablecoin Launch</a></p>
<p>Leading American payment company <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">PayPal</a> has taken another step into the digital asset industry with the launch of its Cryptocurrencies Hub. This feature allows users to interact with different crypto assets such as Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a>) and Ethereum (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ETH</a>). The move comes just one week after introducing its native <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/stablecoins-how-manage-operate/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">stablecoin</a> dubbed PYUSD, which is backed 1:1 by the US dollar.</p>
<p>According to a <a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/paypal-cryptocurrencies-hub-launch" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a> by Cointelegraph, the payment giant updated its terms and conditions to offer insights into how users can leverage the newly introduced Cryptocurrencies Hub to explore the world of digital assets. This strategic maneuver demonstrates the company&#8217;s ambition to establish itself as a prominent crypto-friendly platform.</p>
<p>PayPal&#8217;s foray into the emerging economy began in October 2020 when the company expanded its services to allow users to buy, sell, and hold assets in their accounts. Shortly after that, in March 2021, the company extended its crypto services, enabling customers to checkout at other online businesses using cryptocurrency.</p>
<h2>PayPal Unveils Its Cryptocurrencies Hub</h2>
<p>The US-based payments company has now deepened its foothold in the industry with the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-paypal-usd-stablecoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">launch</a> of the controversial stablecoin and the subsequent introduction of the Cryptocurrencies Hub. This new feature aims to facilitate the seamless buying and selling of cryptocurrencies. Notably, it empowers users to use the proceeds from their crypto transactions to purchase through the PayPal platform.</p>
<p>Upon its official launch, the Cryptocurrencies Hub will be seamlessly integrated with users&#8217; existing PayPal accounts, accessible using their existing login credentials.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the new crypto offering is designed to enable swift conversions between PYUSD and a diverse range of other digital assets. According to the company, any balance shown in the Cryptocurrencies Hub represents the total amount of each asset displayed.</p>
<p>&#8220;Any balance in your Cryptocurrencies Hub represents your ownership of the amount of each Crypto Asset shown. You will not hold the digital Crypto Assets themselves in your Crypto Asset balance,&#8221; the company explained in the newly updated terms of service.</p>
<h2>Hawaii Users Are Exempted from Using PayPal&#8217;s New Service</h2>
<p>While PayPal&#8217;s new crypto service allows users to explore the crypto industry, access to this innovative feature has been restricted in certain jurisdictions and for specific individuals. The company has chosen a personalized approach to grant access to the newly introduced service.</p>
<p>According to the payment firm, to be eligible for the Cryptocurrencies Hub, new users must open a personal PayPal account and maintain a Balance Account in good standing. Additionally, users must provide key identification information, including their full name, physical address, date of birth, and taxpayer identification number.</p>
<p>However, these rules do not apply to Hawaii residents as the company has excluded them from using the new crypto service.</p>
<p>&#8220;Your access to the Cryptocurrencies Hub will be through your personal PayPal account&#8217;s Balance Account. If you are a Hawaii resident, you will not be permitted to set up a Cryptocurrencies Hub at this time,&#8221; the company said.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-mom-hester-peirce-gensler-sec/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-cryptocurrencies-hub-pyusd/">PayPal Unveils Cryptocurrencies Hub Following PYUSD Stablecoin Launch</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-cryptocurrencies-hub-pyusd/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Former SEC Official Predicts Crypto Mom Hester Peirce to Replace Gensler as SEC Chair</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-mom-hester-peirce-gensler-sec/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-mom-hester-peirce-gensler-sec/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 11:05:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gary gensler]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hester peirce]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266809</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-mom-hester-peirce-gensler-sec/">Former SEC Official Predicts Crypto Mom Hester Peirce to Replace Gensler as SEC Chair</a></p>
<p>The former SEC official said that if Hester Peirce chairs the SEC, several crypto-related enforcement actions would come to a sudden stop. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-mom-hester-peirce-gensler-sec/">Former SEC Official Predicts Crypto Mom Hester Peirce to Replace Gensler as SEC Chair</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-mom-hester-peirce-gensler-sec/">Former SEC Official Predicts Crypto Mom Hester Peirce to Replace Gensler as SEC Chair</a></p>
<p>Former <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a> official John Reed Stark has recently weighed on the state of the current spot Bitcoin ETF applications and why he doesn&#8217;t expect any approval this year. Earlier in June, the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) received several applications from giant financial players like <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/blackrock/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BlackRock</a>, Bitwise, and others.</p>
<p>However, Reed Stark predicts that the regulatory situation on crypto enforcement would take a u-turn if a Republican candidate takes over the US Presidency after the 2024 elections. In a tweet on August 13, the ex-SEC Office of Internet Enforcement head suggested that if a Republican becomes President, the crypto-regulatory landscape could undergo significant change. This might involve appointing crypto-friendly Commissioner Hester Peirce to take over as the agency&#8217;s chairman instead of Gary Gensler.</p>
<p>Several Republican candidates are currently in contention. Former President <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/donald-trump/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Donald Trump</a> leads among Republican voters, followed by Florida Governor Ron DeSantis and South Carolina Senator Tim Scott, albeit with a considerable gap.</p>
<p>However, he also reminds us that the SEC&#8217;s crackdown on cryptocurrencies began when Jay Clayton was in office. Just a few days before his resignation, Clayton had filed a lawsuit against Ripple for selling XRP as unregistered securities.</p>
<p>&#8220;Chair Clayton served as a fierce and relentless crypto critic and boasts a hefty multi-year track record of anti-crypto speeches and Congressional testimony, while also spearheading a broad range of groundbreaking crypto-related enforcement actions and aggressive/comprehensive SEC crypto-related regulatory pronouncements,&#8221; <a href="https://twitter.com/JohnReedStark/status/1690707913789112320" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">noted</a> Reed Stark.</p>
<h2>Hester Pierce as the New SEC Chair?</h2>
<p>For years, SEC Commissioner Hester Peirce has been a vocal critic of her administration and their tough stand on crypto. She is quite popular as the &#8216;crypto mom&#8217; within the crypto community for her crypto-friendly stand.</p>
<p>Stark highlighted Peirce&#8217;s track record of disagreement and resistance against numerous of the regulator&#8217;s crypto-related enforcement actions. He pointed out that if Peirce were to lead the SEC, it&#8217;s likely that most of the agency&#8217;s crypto-related enforcement efforts and disruptive actions in the crypto space would come to a sudden stop.</p>
<p>Stark also highlighted the growing divide in crypto regulation within the SEC and broader US politics. When Stark initially started discussing crypto in 2017, he noted that various politicians, including then-President Donald Trump, Secretary Hilary Clinton, and Congresswoman Maxine Waters, shared a common view that crypto was a &#8220;dangerous and horrific plague&#8221;.</p>
<p>However, the stance on crypto has become more contentious. Republican candidate Ron de Santis has expressed intentions to safeguard Bitcoin and pledged to prohibit central bank digital currencies (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-central-bank-digital-currency-cbdc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CBDCs</a>) if elected President.</p>
<p>On the opposing side, Democratic Senator Elizabeth Warren has been actively working to tighten regulations on all forms of crypto in the country. She has even formed an &#8220;anti-crypto army&#8221; as part of her Senate re-election campaign.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/zunami-protocol-manipulation-attack/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-mom-hester-peirce-gensler-sec/">Former SEC Official Predicts Crypto Mom Hester Peirce to Replace Gensler as SEC Chair</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-mom-hester-peirce-gensler-sec/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Zunami Protocol Loses $2.1M in Fresh Price Manipulation Attack</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/zunami-protocol-manipulation-attack/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/zunami-protocol-manipulation-attack/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 09:31:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cybersecurity News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[curve]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[curve finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[defi hack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[flash loan attack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[price manipulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[zunami]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266754</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/zunami-protocol-manipulation-attack/">Zunami Protocol Loses $2.1M in Fresh Price Manipulation Attack</a></p>
<p>Zunami may be the latest victim of a flash loan attack, a scheme that has gradually become the bane of existence for many DeFi protocols.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/zunami-protocol-manipulation-attack/">Zunami Protocol Loses $2.1M in Fresh Price Manipulation Attack</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/zunami-protocol-manipulation-attack/">Zunami Protocol Loses $2.1M in Fresh Price Manipulation Attack</a></p>
<p>Decentralized finance protocol Zunami Protocol has <a href="https://twitter.com/ZunamiProtocol/status/1690863406079696896?t=6BD7CxEQCNxt6Q2B4IXb9Q&amp;s=19" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">confirmed</a> to its clients that there has been an attack on its &#8220;zStables&#8221; pools on Curve Finance. Sharing the news on Twitter, Zunami assured clients that its collateral remains intact. However, the protocol also warned clients to avoid buying any of its Zunami Ether (zETH) or Zunami USD (UZD) stablecoins while it investigates the matter.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, blockchain security firm PeckShield has tied the exploit to price manipulation by attackers. And by its estimates, the attackers carted away no less than $2.1 million from Zunami’s Curve Pool. For what it&#8217;s worth, another blockchain security outfit Ironblocks has also estimated Zunami&#8217;s loss, pegging it at similar figures to that of PeckShield.</p>
<p>It might be worth mentioning that Zunami protocol did not catch wind of the attack until about 20 minutes after PeckShield discovered the exploit on Curve. Zunami later confirmed the attack on August 13, at around 11:07 UTC.</p>
<h2>Zunami Protocol Falls Victim to Flash Loan Attack</h2>
<p>By all means, Zunami may be the latest victim of a flash loan attack, a scheme that has gradually become the bane of existence for many DeFi protocols. According to Ironblocks, &#8220;the attacker took [a] flash loan from [the] balancer, then he added liquidity so he [would] be able to change the price significantly and started to trade in Zunami&#8217;s exchange.&#8221;</p>
<p>The attacker then removed the liquidity and changed the price, before trading back and returning the flash loan. In the end, the attacker made 1,152 ETH to himself in what was a classic case of price manipulation, <a href="https://twitter.com/Ironblocks_/status/1690869728204533760?t=csyQVY5zTrZvfi1IzAftJw&amp;s=19">claims</a> Ironblocks.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the attack immediately impacted the prices of both the Zunami USD stablecoin (UZD) and Zunami Ether (zEth). This follows after both plummeted shortly after the hack. UZD is the most impacted and has already lost over 99% of its value. zEth is also currently down 88% to $206.</p>
<p>Curve Finance, on the other hand, has also been having a very turbulent run recently. It has been hit by multiple attacks, losing as much as $19 million to a single hacker.  As Coinspeaker earlier <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/curve-finance-bounty-exploiter/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a>, however, there is still a $1.8 million bounty for information about the yet-to-be-identified hacker.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/metaverse-affyn-grand-prix-season/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/zunami-protocol-manipulation-attack/">Zunami Protocol Loses $2.1M in Fresh Price Manipulation Attack</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/zunami-protocol-manipulation-attack/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Metaverse-gamified Platform Affyn Partners with Grand Prix Season Singapore 2023 to Promote Web3 Adoption</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/metaverse-affyn-grand-prix-season/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/metaverse-affyn-grand-prix-season/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 09:27:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[affyn]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[expedia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fyn]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[kpmg]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[matic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[polygon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[unity]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266760</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/metaverse-affyn-grand-prix-season/">Metaverse-gamified Platform Affyn Partners with Grand Prix Season Singapore 2023 to Promote Web3 Adoption</a></p>
<p>The Affyn metaverse gamify platform has 400 unique items on the Ethereum chain via the Polygon L2 network with about 300 unique owners.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/metaverse-affyn-grand-prix-season/">Metaverse-gamified Platform Affyn Partners with Grand Prix Season Singapore 2023 to Promote Web3 Adoption</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/metaverse-affyn-grand-prix-season/">Metaverse-gamified Platform Affyn Partners with Grand Prix Season Singapore 2023 to Promote Web3 Adoption</a></p>
<p>A well-funded multiverse and play-to-earn Web3 platform Affyn has announced that it has partnered with Grand Prix Season Singapore 2023 (GPSS) to further introduce the Web3 ecosystem during the racing event. Notably, the GPSS event is supported by the Singapore Tourism Board, thus making the collaboration with Affyn strategic to its future growth prospects. Moreover, the Singapore government is keen to help attract digital assets investors and  Web3 project developers in the country to improve its economy.</p>
<p>Interestingly, the one-week Formula One Singapore Grand Prix event is titled Web 3.0 | Art Meets Metaverse. The event is expected to kick off on September 16, 2023, at Suntec City’s Sunthesis with an <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NFT</a> art exhibition and talk show lined up for the attendees. As a result, Affyn protocol anticipates showcasing its digital artworks and other products for potential customers.</p>
<p>“We are proud to partner with GPSS as it underlines Affyn’s intent to bolster Government initiatives and bring Web 3.0 development to the next level. As the only official Web 3.0 company partnering with GPSS, an event supported by STB, it is an incredible opportunity to drive awareness of developments in the industry. We’re looking forward to working with both Web 2.0 and Web 3.0 brands to showcase to a wider audience how the metaverse is changing the world for the better,” Affyn CEO Lucaz Lee noted.</p>
<h2>Affyn Market Outlook</h2>
<p>The Affyn network uses its native token dubbed FYN. Following increased on-chain activity, FYN price has gained approximately 5 percent in the past five days to trade around $0.022 on reporting time. However, the FYN price is still under the water in regard to the listing price of 14 cents earlier last year. The play-to/earn metaverse platform has gained significant momentum with its NFTs on OpenSea dubbed Nexus World &#8211; Gen Zero buddies having a total volume of about 403 Ether.</p>
<p>The Polygon-based Affyn NFTs had a total supply of about 400 items with a floor price of approximately 1.6 ETH. The Affyn NFTs dubbed Buddied include units with unique attributes and properties that can be improved over time. Notably, Affyn’s Buddies can be trained to participate in quests, raids, and user-created activities. The Affyn metaverse land is also viewed as an NFT that is tradeable among other users on the company’s marketplace.</p>
<p>The future developments of Affyn are well secured by notable investors, partners, and experienced leadership including former Unity, Expedia, and KPMG employees. Moreover, the mainstream adoption of digital assets and blockchain technology assures Web3 projects, which are building reputable products, a secure growth outlook.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-global-rice-market/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/metaverse-affyn-grand-prix-season/">Metaverse-gamified Platform Affyn Partners with Grand Prix Season Singapore 2023 to Promote Web3 Adoption</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/metaverse-affyn-grand-prix-season/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>China’s Heavy Rains Pose Threat to Global Rice Market</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-global-rice-market/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-global-rice-market/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 09:18:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fitch ratings]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Flooding]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Grains]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rice Market]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266786</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-global-rice-market/">China’s Heavy Rains Pose Threat to Global Rice Market</a></p>
<p>The global rice market is experiencing a significant upheaval as prices soar to their highest levels in nearly 12 years.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-global-rice-market/">China’s Heavy Rains Pose Threat to Global Rice Market</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-global-rice-market/">China’s Heavy Rains Pose Threat to Global Rice Market</a></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The global rice market is currently on the brink of further strain as China, the world&#8217;s largest rice producer, grapples with heavy rain and flood risks in its grain-producing north-eastern region. </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">The resulting reduction in yields is expected to exert upward pressure on global rice prices, according to a recent </span><a href="https://www.fitchratings.com/research/corporate-finance/heavy-rain-in-north-east-china-may-raise-pressure-on-global-rice-prices-10-08-2023" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">report</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> by Fitch Ratings.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">China’s role in the global rice market cannot be understated. As the leading rice producer, the country not only feeds its own vast population but also contributes significantly to the international rice trade. </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Fitch report highlighted that China’s three key provinces, Heilongjiang, Jilin, and Inner Mongolia, have been grappling with heavy rainfall, prompting flood alerts and raising concerns about the impact on grain production. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">These provinces collectively accounted for a significant portion of China’s grain output in 2021, with Heilongjiang being the largest rice-producing province, contributing 13.7% to the country&#8217;s rice production in the same year. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The heavy rainfall, triggered by the remnants of Typhoon Doksuri and worsened by the approach of Typhoon Khanun, has left many key grain production areas waterlogged. As a result, crop yields for the current year are expected to decrease, although the extent of the damage remains uncertain.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">These adverse conditions are predicted to drive up China&#8217;s domestic grain prices, potentially prompting higher imports during the latter half of 2023 to offset the potential yield loss. While the situation in China raises concerns about potential disruptions to the global rice market, the effects on corn prices are expected to remain contained due to ample global supply.</span></p>
<h2><b>Global Rice Prices Reach 12-Year High</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Meanwhile, the global rice market is experiencing a significant upheaval as prices soar to their highest levels in nearly 12 years, according to the Food and Agriculture Organization’s (FAO) All Rice Price Index. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The recent ban on non-basmati white rice exports by India and the United Arab Emirates has sent shockwaves through the market. With India accounting for over 40% of the world&#8217;s rice trade, this move has had a substantial impact on the availability of rice in international markets. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In addition, Thailand, another significant rice producer, has taken measures to address water scarcity. Low rainfall has prompted the Thai government to urge farmers to plant less rice in order to conserve water resources. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The consequences of these developments have led to a surge in rice prices, with the FAO’s All Rice Price Index reaching levels of 129.7 as of July 2023. Market observers are now anticipating a continuation of higher rice prices as the impacts of these supply disruptions reverberate across the industry.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As China navigates the challenges posed by heavy rains and floods, the global community is reminded of the importance of building resilient </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">agricultural technological systems</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> and collaborative efforts to mitigate the impacts of climate-related events on food production and distribution.</span></p>
<p>Read other <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/markets/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">market news</a> on Coinspeaker.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/trump-ethereum-holding/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-global-rice-market/">China’s Heavy Rains Pose Threat to Global Rice Market</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-global-rice-market/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Trump’s Financial Disclosure Document Reveals Ethereum Holding</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/trump-ethereum-holding/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/trump-ethereum-holding/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Babafemi Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 08:41:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[donald trump]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nft]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=265927</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/trump-ethereum-holding/">Trump’s Financial Disclosure Document Reveals Ethereum Holding</a></p>
<p>Trump’s aversion to crypto is directly opposed to the position of the rest of his party.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/trump-ethereum-holding/">Trump’s Financial Disclosure Document Reveals Ethereum Holding</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/trump-ethereum-holding/">Trump’s Financial Disclosure Document Reveals Ethereum Holding</a></p>

<p>Donald Trump’s 2023 public financial disclosure has revealed that the former president holds Ethereum (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ETH</a>) worth between $250,000 and $500,000. These details were part of a <a href="https://www.documentcloud.org/documents/23876912-donald-trump-oge-public-financial-disclosure-report-2023-part-1" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">revised financial filing submitted</a> by Trump. The filing outlined various income sources for the Trump family and exceeded over $1.2 billion.</p>
<p>While the document only referenced an item described as a “Cryptocurrency Wallet (Ethereum)”, it did not elaborate on the exact source or content. However, the prevailing opinion suggests that the content may be linked to the president&#8217;s sale of non-fungible tokens (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NFTs</a>).</p>
<h2>Possible Source of Ethereum Holding</h2>
<p>In December 2022, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/donald-trump/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Donald Trump</a> launched a limited edition NFT collection after exiting the White House. The collection comprised 44,000 digital trading cards that sold at $99 apiece. Each piece showed the president in different poses and outfits. The NFT collection was generally successful selling out within a day and netting over $8.9 million in sales.</p>
<p>Donald Trump is believed to have earned around $298,000 in licensing fees from this NFT adventure. Interestingly, the crypto wallet that received the earnings is held under CIC Digital, the same Trump entity that collected the licensing fees.</p>
<p>Afterward, Trump launched a <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/trump-nft-trading-cards-4-6m/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">second edition</a> of NFTs which also sold out, although it did not gather as much traction as the first. Also, former first lady Melania Trump launched <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/melania-trump-us-nfts/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">an NFT collection</a>. The collection featured several popular images from NASA’s Apollo moon landings into digital pieces, selling them for $75 each.</p>
<h2>Is Trump’s Position on Cryptocurrencies Changing?</h2>
<p>This development may suggest that Trump’s view of cryptocurrency may be changing. In 2019, the former president tweeted that he was not a fan of Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies. Later, former White House Communications Director, Anthony Scaramucci, noted, that Trump himself may not have authored the tweet.</p>
<p>However, in 2021, Trump removed every doubt about his position, labelling the asset class as ‘fake”. Trump said: </p>
<blockquote>
<p>&#8220;I don’t like it, because it’s another currency competing against the dollar. I want the dollar to be the currency of the world. That’s what I’ve always said.&#8221;</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Such claims are contrary to the latest findings regarding his Ethereum holdings.</p>
<p>Trump’s aversion to crypto is directly opposed to the position of the rest of his party. Many Republicans in the House and Senate have been responsible for sponsoring new bills to improve regulations in the crypto industry.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-javier-milei-argentina/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/trump-ethereum-holding/">Trump’s Financial Disclosure Document Reveals Ethereum Holding</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/trump-ethereum-holding/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pro-Bitcoin Advocate Javier Milei Takes Lead in Argentina’s Primary Election</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-javier-milei-argentina/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-javier-milei-argentina/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 08:38:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266751</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-javier-milei-argentina/">Pro-Bitcoin Advocate Javier Milei Takes Lead in Argentina&#8217;s Primary Election</a></p>
<p>Milei's political platform has been characterized by his passionate advocacy for BTC and his calls for the dissolution of the Argentine central bank.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-javier-milei-argentina/">Pro-Bitcoin Advocate Javier Milei Takes Lead in Argentina&#8217;s Primary Election</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-javier-milei-argentina/">Pro-Bitcoin Advocate Javier Milei Takes Lead in Argentina&#8217;s Primary Election</a></p>
<p>Javier Milei, a prominent Argentinian politician known for his pro-Bitcoin stance and radical views on economic reform, has surged ahead in the country&#8217;s primary presidential election. Milei, who has been a vocal critic of the central bank and a staunch supporter of Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a>), is currently leading the race with over 30% of the votes counted, marking a significant shift in the country&#8217;s political landscape.</p>
<p>With an impressive 84% of the votes counted, Milei&#8217;s party, &#8220;La Libertad Avanza&#8221; (Freedom Advances), has secured 30.73% of the total votes. The figure puts him ahead of his competitors from the &#8220;Juntos por el Cambio&#8221; (Together for Change) party and the &#8220;Unidos por la Patria&#8221; (United for the Homeland) coalition, who have garnered 28.14% and 26.84% of the votes, respectively. The unexpected surge in support for Milei has surprised political analysts and pollsters, as pre-election polls had predicted a much narrower margin for him.</p>
<h2>Milei Says Central Bank Is a Scam</h2>
<p>According to <a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoiner-javier-milei-wins-argentina-presidential-primary" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reports</a>, Milei&#8217;s political platform has been characterized by his passionate advocacy for BTC and his calls for the dissolution of the Argentine central bank. He has repeatedly criticized the central bank, labeling it a &#8220;scam&#8221; that enables politicians to manipulate the economy through inflation.</p>
<p>&#8220;The central bank is a scam, a mechanism by which politicians cheat the good people with inflationary taxes,&#8221; he said.</p>
<p>His unwavering support for the crypto asset as an alternative to traditional financial systems has resonated with a significant portion of the electorate, particularly amid the country&#8217;s staggering annual inflation rate of 116%, the highest it has been in over thirty years.</p>
<p>However, Milei&#8217;s radical views extend beyond monetary policy. He identifies as an anarcho-capitalist and has made controversial statements, including advocating for the legalization of human organ sales and denying the existence of global warming.</p>
<p>Despite these unconventional viewpoints, his popularity has been fueled by his forceful critique of the current government&#8217;s economic policies and his promise to bring about substantial change.</p>
<h2>Half-Baked Support for Bitcoin</h2>
<p>While Milei has shown strong backing for BTC, the Argentinian politician does not endorse the idea of making the digital asset a legal tender within the country, as it was done in El Salvador in 2021 when the government officially adopted the use of the digital asset in the nation.</p>
<p>Instead, he believes in &#8220;dollarization&#8221; for the economy, implying that adopting the US dollar could offer stability and help alleviate the repercussions of inflation.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, according to Bloomberg <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/graphics/2023-argentina-election/">data</a>, the primary election results have set the stage for the general presidential election scheduled for October 22, where the candidates will compete in a three-way contest.</p>
<p>In order to secure the presidency outright, a candidate must receive at least 45% of the vote. However, if no candidate meets this threshold, a runoff vote will be held in November to determine the final winner.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/softbank-vision-fund-stake-arm/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-javier-milei-argentina/">Pro-Bitcoin Advocate Javier Milei Takes Lead in Argentina&#8217;s Primary Election</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-javier-milei-argentina/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>SoftBank Looking to Acquire Vision Fund’s 25% Stake in Arm</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/softbank-vision-fund-stake-arm/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/softbank-vision-fund-stake-arm/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Darya Rudz]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 08:27:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investors News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[IPO News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[arm]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[arm ipo]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[softbank]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[softbank arm]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[softbank group]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[softbank group corp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[softbank vision fund]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vision fund]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266745</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/softbank-vision-fund-stake-arm/">SoftBank Looking to Acquire Vision Fund’s 25% Stake in Arm</a></p>
<p>Arm is scheduled to go public in September, with the listing of its shares on the Nasdaq exchange. Arm's market capitalization by that time is expected to be $60 billion to $70 billion, which would make the deal the world's biggest initial public offering so far this year.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/softbank-vision-fund-stake-arm/">SoftBank Looking to Acquire Vision Fund’s 25% Stake in Arm</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/softbank-vision-fund-stake-arm/">SoftBank Looking to Acquire Vision Fund’s 25% Stake in Arm</a></p>
<p>Tokyo-based conglomerate <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/softbank/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SoftBank Group Corporation</a> (TYO: 9984) is <a href="https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/softbank-talks-buy-vision-funds-25-stake-arm-sources-2023-08-13/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reportedly</a> planning to buy a 25% stake in Arm, a semiconductor and software design company based in Cambridge, from Vision Fund 1 (VF1). Currently, SoftBank which owns 75% of Arm stake, is negotiating with Vision Fund 1 on the terms of the deal. If signed, the deal will benefit VF1 investors who have been struggling to get profit for years.</p>
<p>SoftBank made an agreed offer for Arm company back in 2016, the offer was subject to approval by Arm&#8217;s shareholders. At that time, the CPUs producer was valued at $32 billion. The transaction was completed in September 2016. In 2017, a 25% stake in Arm was transferred to the SoftBank Vision Fund, which received investment from Saudi Arabia&#8217;s Public Investment Fund and Abu Dhabi&#8217;s Mubadala Investment Company.</p>
<p>VF1 investors have been bearing losses until recently, and Vision Fund 2 did not generate revenue as well, which led to SoftBank failing to secure outside investors. Over the last two fiscal years, SoftBank’s Vision Fund lost about $48 billion. Only in the second quarter of this year, Vision Fund posted a revenue following the buzz around artificial intelligence (AI) and living up expectations of those who trusted SoftBank&#8217;s bets on AI startups. As we have <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/softbank-profit-vision-fund/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a>, after five consecutive losing quarters, the Vision Fund gained 159.8 billion yen, about $1.1 billion, in the quarter that ended on June 30.</p>
<div id="div-gpt-ad-1499653692894-0">
<p>Since May 2022, SoftBank has been in &#8216;defense mode&#8217;, which means it has been using an approach to protect against the competition amid economic uncertainty. Now, the company is shifting to &#8216;offense mode&#8217;, capitalizing on the AI revolution. Besides, it is planning to conduct an <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-initial-public-offering-ipo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">initial public offering</a> (IPO) for Arm. Preparation started in March.</p>
<h2>Upcoming Arm IPO</h2>
<p>Arm is scheduled to go public in September, with the listing of its shares on the Nasdaq exchange. Arm&#8217;s market capitalization by that time is expected to be $60 billion to $70 billion, which would make the deal the world&#8217;s biggest initial public offering so far this year.</p>
</div>
<p>Later this month, SoftBank will officially apply to the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">US Securities and Exchange Commission</a> (SEC) for the listing. Next, it will obtain approval from Nasdaq. Among those who will invest in Arm are giants like <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/apple-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Apple Inc</a> (NYSE: AAPL), <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/samsung/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Samsung Electronics</a>, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/nvidia/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Nvidia Corporation</a> (NYSE: NVDA), <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/intel/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Intel Corporation</a> (NASDAQ: INTC), and more.</p>
<p>Initially, Arm was eyeing the UK market for an IPO, which would be a great boost for the UK tech sector and secure London as an appealing destination for high-value IPOs. However, the lack of progress in the UK&#8217;s regulatory and market reform agenda made SoftBank change the target market. The US listing will come as a disappointment to UK ministers who had continually been lobbying the company to list on the London Stock Exchange.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-regulatory-approval-taiwan/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/softbank-vision-fund-stake-arm/">SoftBank Looking to Acquire Vision Fund’s 25% Stake in Arm</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/softbank-vision-fund-stake-arm/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Pursues Regulatory Approval in Taiwan via AML Registration</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-regulatory-approval-taiwan/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 15:08:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Binance News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266698</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-regulatory-approval-taiwan/">Binance Pursues Regulatory Approval in Taiwan via AML Registration</a></p>
<p>Binance is expanding its presence in Asia. The reports about its potential entrance into Taiwan come after the company re-entered the Japanese market last year.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-regulatory-approval-taiwan/">Binance Pursues Regulatory Approval in Taiwan via AML Registration</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-regulatory-approval-taiwan/">Binance Pursues Regulatory Approval in Taiwan via AML Registration</a></p>
<p>Leading global cryptocurrency exchange <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a> is seeking a regulatory license in Taiwan to enable the company to offer crypto services in the country. According to a recent <a href="https://www.theblock.co/post/244320/binance-is-applying-to-get-registered-in-taiwan-for-aml-compliance-sources" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a> by The Block citing people familiar with the matter, the exchange has applied to be registered under the country&#8217;s anti-money laundering (AML) rules.</p>
<p>Taiwan is one of the many nations in the world with stringent AML laws. The country&#8217;s financial watchdog, the Financial Supervisory Commission (FSC), introduced the legislation in 2021, making it mandatory for all digital asset service providers to comply with the law.</p>
<p>Despite its close ties with China, the island nation has underlined its distinct crypto policies from those of mainland China, as the Beijing government has enforced a comprehensive ban on crypto-related activities since 2021.</p>
<h2>Binance Seeks to Enter the Taiwanese Market</h2>
<p>Binance is now seeking national regulatory approval as part of the company&#8217;s commitment to compliance with local regulatory authorities. If approved, the exchange can legally enter the Taiwanese Market and provide its business offerings to customers in the region.</p>
<p>Sources familiar with the matter revealed that Binance is actively engaged in registration, aiming to ensure rigorous compliance with AML regulations as stipulated by Taiwan&#8217;s financial authorities. According to local news <a href="https://abmedia.io/binance-taiwan-application" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">media</a>, the FSC disclosed the information during a confidential meeting with domestic crypto exchanges in Taiwan.</p>
<h2>Binance Partners with Law Enforcement Agency in Taiwan</h2>
<p>While Binance&#8217;s full regulatory status in Taiwan remains pending, the exchange currently operates in the country through a registered entity known as &#8220;Binance International Limited Taiwan Branch (Seychelles).&#8221; The Taiwanese government approved the firm in May 2023, with a registered capital of NT$30 million ($944,000).</p>
<p>In addition to its registration within the nation, Binance has joined forces with the Taiwanese authorities to combat cybercrime. The exchange <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/blog/ecosystem/binance-partners-with-taiwan-law-enforcement-agencies-to-fight-cybercrime-7928081762268486180">announced</a> the partnership in June, noting that it is working with the country&#8217;s Criminal Investigation Bureau (CIB) to share its expertise in tackling digital asset-related crime with more than 200 Taiwanese law enforcement officers.</p>
<h2>Binance Faces Regulatory Hurdles in the US and Europe</h2>
<p>Binance is expanding its presence in Asia. The reports about its potential entrance into Taiwan come after the company re-entered the Japanese market last year. The exchange acquired Sakura Exchange BitCoin in November 2022 to enable it to explore the Asian market.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, while Binance is expanding its reach in Asia, the exchange faces regulatory hurdles in the United States and Europe. The exchange is battling various legal cases in the US, including one with the Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>).</p>
<p>In Europe, the company has chosen to withdraw from several European jurisdictions, including the Netherlands, due to regulatory concerns.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-stablecoin-pyusd-bank-of-america/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-regulatory-approval-taiwan/">Binance Pursues Regulatory Approval in Taiwan via AML Registration</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bank of America: Paypal Stablecoin (PYUSD) Immediate Adoption Might Be Subdued</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-stablecoin-pyusd-bank-of-america/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 14:32:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bank of america]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[paypal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pyusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stablecoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266694</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-stablecoin-pyusd-bank-of-america/">Bank of America: Paypal Stablecoin (PYUSD) Immediate Adoption Might Be Subdued</a></p>
<p>The introduction of PayPal stablecoin (PYUSD) represents a groundbreaking development in the realm of stablecoins and digital currencies.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-stablecoin-pyusd-bank-of-america/">Bank of America: Paypal Stablecoin (PYUSD) Immediate Adoption Might Be Subdued</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-stablecoin-pyusd-bank-of-america/">Bank of America: Paypal Stablecoin (PYUSD) Immediate Adoption Might Be Subdued</a></p>
<p>In a recent move that captured the attention of the financial world <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">PayPal Holdings Inc</a> (NASDAQ: PYPL) announced the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-paypal-usd-stablecoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">launch</a> of its own stablecoin PayPal USD (PYUSD).</p>
<p>While the launch of PYUSD is expected to drive efficiencies in payments, Bank of America analysts Alkesh Shah and Andrew Moss suggested in a recent research <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/08/11/paypals-stablecoin-unlikely-to-see-significant-adoption-in-the-near-term-bank-of-america/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a> that the immediate adoption of this stablecoin might not be as substantial as anticipated.</p>
<p>The report highlights a few key challenges that PYUSD could face on its adoption journey. One significant obstacle noted is the growing competition from <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-central-bank-digital-currency-cbdc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Central Bank Digital Currencies</a> (CBDCs). As governments explore their own digital currencies, the adoption landscape could shift, introducing new variables that could influence the adoption of private stablecoins like PYUSD.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the analysts at Bank of America predicted that yield-bearing stablecoins could sway investor preferences away from PYUSD. This prediction is rooted in the evolving interest rate environment.</p>
<p>When interest rates were nearly zero, non-yield-bearing stablecoins like Tether (USDT) and USD Coin (USDC) seemed acceptable to investors. However, the analysts projected that the emergence of yield-bearing stablecoins offering rates above 5% could alter this calculation, diverting interest and investment from PYUSD.</p>
<p>Remarkably, the Bank of America’s research dives into the regulatory aspects of the PYUSD’s introduction. While the introduction of the stablecoin may not significantly affect systemic risk in traditional markets, the paper notes that regulatory issues may arise if non-banks are barred from issuing stablecoins.</p>
<p>The report also suggests a longer-term perspective, acknowledging that while adoption challenges might persist in the short run, the trajectory could evolve as the financial landscape adapts to new offerings. The potential for PYUSD usage may grow as market dynamics alter, provided PayPal handles upcoming difficulties and successfully leverages its large user base.</p>
<h2>The PayPal Stablecoin (PYUSD) Launch and its Promise</h2>
<p>Stablecoins, a category of cryptocurrencies designed to minimize price volatility by pegging their value to a stable asset such as fiat currencies and commodities have gained prominence as a potential bridge between traditional financial and the world of digital currencies.</p>
<p>PayPal&#8217;s PYUSD is pegged to the US dollar and aims to offer users the advantages of cryptocurrencies without the rollercoaster ride of value fluctuations often associated with assets like <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> (BTC) and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a> (ETH).</p>
<p>The core promise of PYUSD lies in its potential to streamline payment processes and enhance user experiences. Traditional cross-border transactions are often riddled with delays, fees, and complexities arising from intermediaries and currency conversions.</p>
<p>With PYUSD, PayPal envisions a future where these barriers are dismantled, allowing for near-instantaneous cross-border transactions with minimal costs.</p>
<p>Overall, the introduction of PayPal stablecoin (PYUSD) represents a groundbreaking development in the realm of stablecoins and digital currencies. While immediate adoption might be constrained by emerging competition and evolving interest rate dynamics, the stablecoin&#8217;s potential to enhance payments efficiency and customer experience remains significant.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-cto-schwartz-fed-paypal/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-stablecoin-pyusd-bank-of-america/">Bank of America: Paypal Stablecoin (PYUSD) Immediate Adoption Might Be Subdued</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4182 metric#misses=41 metric#hit-ratio=99.0 metric#bytes=1066134 metric#prefetches=202 metric#store-reads=19 metric#store-writes=2 metric#store-hits=208 metric#store-misses=2 metric#sql-queries=34 metric#ms-total=94.65 metric#ms-cache=4.50 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.2252 metric#ms-cache-ratio=4.8 -->