<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 15:48:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Persian Sea Shipping Lines announces token presale</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/persian-sea-shipping-lines-announces-token-presale/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/persian-sea-shipping-lines-announces-token-presale/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Daniela Kirova]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 15:48:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/persian-sea-shipping-lines-announces-token-presale/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The team collaborated with SolidProof to ensure trust among participants The company has vast experience in the maritime industry with high potential for investors&#160; Presale will launch on February 1 on the widely-used Unicrypt platform Persian Sea Shipping Lines, a UAE-based shipping and logistics service provider, announced a token presale, with which it enters the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/persian-sea-shipping-lines-announces-token-presale/">Persian Sea Shipping Lines announces token presale</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>The team collaborated with SolidProof to ensure trust among participants</li>
<li>The company has vast experience in the maritime industry with high potential for investors&nbsp;</li>
<li>Presale will launch on February 1 on the widely-used Unicrypt platform </li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p>Persian Sea Shipping Lines, a UAE-based shipping and logistics service provider, announced a token presale, with which it enters the crypto industry, Coin Journal learned from <a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2022/12/27/2579897/0/en/Persian-Sea-Shipping-Lines-Enters-the-Crypto-Industry.html">a press release</a>. The company has vast experience in the maritime industry with high potential for investors.</p>
<h2>Team collaborated with SolidProof for KYC&nbsp;</h2>
<p>The team collaborated with SolidProof to ensure trust among participants. This helped them complete <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-announces-mandatory-kyc-for-all-users/">a mandatory KYC check</a> and perform an audit on their smart contracts prior to launching. As a result, this project appears to be among the most promising on the market today.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Presale will launch on February 1 on the widely-used Unicrypt platform. The soft and hard cap have been set at 250,000 resp. 600,000 million BUSD. Early access to the PSSL token will be limited.</p>
<h2>Fully customizable user experience&nbsp;</h2>
<p>Unicrypt features a number of benefits, from a fully customizable <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/varanida-is-aiming-to-improve-the-experience-of-web-users-advertisers-and-publishers-with-the-blockchain/">user experience</a> to managing transactions. Users can take part in token sales. Multiple currencies are supported. The ILO round and the internal reserve of the project will each be allocated 25 million tokens. This decision was made to ensure the project&rsquo;s longevity.</p>
<p>Another 13 million tokens will be invested in the project&rsquo;s marketing strategy. The team and the rewards system will each get 5 million. The remaining 2 million tokens will go to the advisory board.</p>
<h2>Excellent token distribution&nbsp;</h2>
<p>One of the most important features of the new PSSL token is excellently balanced token distribution. It has the potential to become the most popular project next year with its total supply capped at 75 million tokens.</p>
<h2>High potential&nbsp;</h2>
<p>The new token links users with services such as bulk maritime transport and ship chartering. In addition, the team mentioned numerous types of sea cargo services, such as storage, booking, and import/export. PSSL is a dynamically growing enterprise with experienced employees in the shipping industry.</p>
<p>All of these factors show that PSSL could have tremendous token potential. The project is well-positioned to provide its users with top-notch services at competitive prices.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/persian-sea-shipping-lines-announces-token-presale/">Persian Sea Shipping Lines announces token presale</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/persian-sea-shipping-lines-announces-token-presale/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Next-gen crypto Unicoin unveils free 10-year asset purchase option</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/next-gen-crypto-unicoin-unveils-free-10-year-asset-purchase-option/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Daniela Kirova]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 15:31:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/next-gen-crypto-unicoin-unveils-free-10-year-asset-purchase-option/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Investors can deposit an amount of up to $2.5 million with Unicoin. Unicoin was created to address early coin volatility Unicoin is the official cryptocurrency of Unicorn Hunters Next-generation asset-backed crypto Unicoin unveiled a new investment opportunity: a free 10-year option to buy its native coin at 20 cents per unit. The platform expects Bitcoin [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/next-gen-crypto-unicoin-unveils-free-10-year-asset-purchase-option/">Next-gen crypto Unicoin unveils free 10-year asset purchase option</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Investors can deposit an amount of up to $2.5 million with Unicoin.</li>
<li>Unicoin was created to address early coin volatility</li>
<li>Unicoin is the official cryptocurrency of Unicorn Hunters</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p>Next-generation asset-backed crypto Unicoin unveiled a new investment opportunity: a free 10-year option to buy its native coin at 20 cents per unit. The platform expects Bitcoin to rally in 2023. A similar offer for BTC would make it available for $13.50 now, with a guaranteed 120,000% ROI, according to <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/unicoin-anticipates-major-crypto-upswing-and-offers-investors-an-industry-first-10-year-option-301709833.html">a press release</a>.</p>
<h2>Plans are for the price to double in 4 years &nbsp;</h2>
<p>Investors can deposit an amount of up to $2.5 million with Unicoin. For a period of a decade, they will be able to convert the deposit into unicoins at 20 cents each. The platform&rsquo;s goal is to double that price by 2027, which will achieve an ROI of 20,000%.&nbsp;</p>
<p>While Unicoin can&rsquo;t guarantee <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/is-lido-a-good-crypto-to-buy-as-it-defies-gravity/">the growth of its price</a>, investors may withdraw their funds in cash after one year. If they hold their deposits for five years, they will generate 50% interest. Unicoin CEO Alex Konanykhin said:</p>
<p><em>Unicoin sold $250 million worth of its native coins via our Buy Now, Pay Later program. We are now offering investors an option that no other cryptocurrency has ever offered &ndash; to move up to 5% of this future funding to the present. The <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ftx-collapse-hearing-kevin-oleary-says-binance-caused-the-ftx-implosion/">collapse of FTX</a> ended the era of non-transparent, assetless cryptocurrencies. They will be replaced by assets-backed, audited, compliant, and publicly-reported solutions like Unicoin. We are working on transforming Unicoin into a major crypto brand, and one of our biggest pros is relying on superior funding options.</em></p>
<h2>Backed by a diverse asset portfolio&nbsp;</h2>
<p>Unicoin was created to address early coin volatility. Among the assets in the diversified portfolio backing it is equity in dynamically growing companies positioned to achieve a valuation of more than $1 billion.</p>
<p>Unicoin&rsquo;s stable and unique offering has garnered the support of industry leaders, business luminaries, and policymakers like Steve Wozniak, Apple&rsquo;s co-founder. Unicoin is the official cryptocurrency of one of the most iconic recent business series, according to Forbes &ndash; Unicorn Hunters. &nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/next-gen-crypto-unicoin-unveils-free-10-year-asset-purchase-option/">Next-gen crypto Unicoin unveils free 10-year asset purchase option</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Filecoin price pumps but product concerns remain</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/filecoin-price-pumps-but-product-concerns-remain/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/filecoin-price-pumps-but-product-concerns-remain/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 11:44:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Filecoin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/filecoin-price-pumps-but-product-concerns-remain/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Filecoin price went parabolic in thin trading volume. There are concerns about the utility of the platform. Filecoin price popped to the highest level since December 16 despite the rising risks of its utility. It rose to a high of $3.31, which was much higher than the year-to-date low of $2.3. Other storage tokens like&#160;Siacoin [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/filecoin-price-pumps-but-product-concerns-remain/">Filecoin price pumps but product concerns remain</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Filecoin price went parabolic in thin trading volume.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">There are concerns about the utility of the platform.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Filecoin price popped to the highest level since December 16 despite the rising risks of its utility. It rose to a high of $3.31, which was much higher than the year-to-date low of $2.3. Other storage tokens like&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/siacoin/"><u>Siacoin</u></a> and Storj also rebounded.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Filecoin utility challenges</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/filecoin/"><u>Filecoin</u></a> is the biggest storage blockchain platform in the world. Like other storage platforms, its use case is relatively simple to grasp. Unlike centralized storage platforms like Google Cloud and Microsoft Azure, it uses decentralize storage platforms.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Anyone with a computer, smartphone, or data center can provide storage in its platform and then earn a reward when people use it. This data is safely stored in their network in a highly encrypted format.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The benefit of using a decentralized platform is that it is highly scalable. For a person in Nairobi, they will access their data from a storage provider in the city. Similarly, for a person in Washington, they will store and access their data from someone in the city.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to its data explorer, there are 3,920 active miners in the network who provide 19.069 EiB in its platform. This is a significant number that is more than 21.9 million terabytes.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Still, Filecoin faces several important challenges. First, the network is competing with well-established brands like Microsoft and Google. These centralized platforms work well and have a long track record of safety.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Second, it is clear that it has a significantly big capacity that is hard to use. One of its biggest use cases is in the storage of Non-Fungible Tokens (NFT) through its partnership with OpenSea. Recently, however, the volume of NFTs traded per month has dropped sharply. Therefore, without a clear use case, it will take a miracle for Filecoin to become a successful platform.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Filecoin price prediction</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2022/11/27/1672141339088-c68ee6bc-5ce2-4572-80dc-3148ecdb0d5c.png" style="width: 587px;height: 291.543px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="587" height="291.543"></p>
<p><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/FILUSD/?exchange=COINBASE">FILUSD chart by TradingView</a></p>
<p dir="ltr">The daily chart shows that the FIL price made a strong bullish breakout on Tuesday as investors bought the token&rsquo;s dip. It moved slightly above the 25-day and 50-day moving averages while the Relative Strength Index (RSI) moved to the overbought level. It has also formed what looks like an inverted head and shoulders pattern.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, despite the H&amp;S pattern, Filecoin will likely resume the bearish trend as fundamentals disappoint. A move above the resistance at $3.50 will invalidate the bearish view.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy Filecoin</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>

    <p>eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=OTg5MDI&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=TX&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy FIL with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    Binance</h3>

    <p>Binance is one of the largest cryptocurrency exchanges in the world. It is better suited to more experienced investors and it offers a large number of cryptocurrencies to choose from, at over 600.

Binance is also known for having low trading fees and a multiple of trading options that its users can benefit from, such as; peer-to-peer trading, margin trading and spot trading.
</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/binance-crypto?guid=OTg5MDI&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=TX&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy FIL with Binance today            </a>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/filecoin-price-pumps-but-product-concerns-remain/">Filecoin price pumps but product concerns remain</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/filecoin-price-pumps-but-product-concerns-remain/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Santa launches its rewarded browser this Christmas to bring in the next 200M users onto Web3.0</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/santa-launches-its-rewarded-browser-this-christmas-to-bring-in-the-next-200m-users-onto-web3-0/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/santa-launches-its-rewarded-browser-this-christmas-to-bring-in-the-next-200m-users-onto-web3-0/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire  ]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 11:11:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=98893</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Road Town, BVI, 27th December, 2022, Chainwire Santa Browser has announced the Version 1 launch of its web3 browser today. Built for an emerging crypto world, the browser claims to bring in the next generation of web3 users by developing tools that allow anyone to leverage the power of blockchain technologies. Due to the extreme [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/santa-launches-its-rewarded-browser-this-christmas-to-bring-in-the-next-200m-users-onto-web3-0/">Santa launches its rewarded browser this Christmas to bring in the next 200M users onto Web3.0</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Road Town, BVI, 27th December, 2022, Chainwire</strong></p>
<p><a href="http://www.santabrowser.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Santa Browser</a> has announced the Version 1 launch of its web3 browser today. Built for an emerging crypto world, the browser claims to bring in the next generation of web3 users by developing tools that allow anyone to leverage the power of blockchain technologies. Due to the extreme volatility of the market, <a href="http://www.santabrowser.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Santa</a> is dedicated to building a &ldquo;Trustable Technology Stack&rdquo; that users can firmly rely upon while browsing the web. With the Christmas release of Santa Browser, users can now earn crypto rewards simply by browsing.</p>
<blockquote><p>&ldquo;We believe that browsers need to evolve a lot more to keep up with the pace at which the internet is evolving.&rdquo; said Alekh B, CEO of <a href="http://www.santabrowser.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Santa Browser</a>. &ldquo;Our approach to Santa Browser is deeply influenced by the principles of web3 &mdash; Anti Monopoly, Transparency, Democracy, Data Privacy, Security &amp; Fair Distribution Of Wealth.&rdquo;</p></blockquote>
<h3><b>Why </b><a href="http://www.santabrowser.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><b>Santa Browser</b></a><b>?</b></h3>
<p><b>Browse-2-Earn<br>
</b>On a mission to reimagine the web, the browser starts with the relationship between users &amp; advertising. With <a href="http://www.santabrowser.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Santa&rsquo;s</a> Browse2Earn, users can earn crypto rewards for their regular activities online (rewards include but are not limited to ad monetization, search monetization, discounted shopping, etc.) while maintaining control over their privacy.</p>
<p><b>Geared For Privacy<br>
</b><a href="http://www.santabrowser.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Santa Browser</a> hosts many features to protect user privacy.</p>
<ul>
<li>Integrated ad blocker &mdash; to stop all invasive ads.</li>
<li>Tracker blocker &mdash; &nbsp;to stop all online trackers &amp; browser fingerprinting practices.</li>
<li>Ungoogling &mdash; while forked from chromium, the browser has been cleansed of all Google trackers, host detectors (tools that identify your IP address) &amp; other privacy-harming features.</li>
<li>Santa also disables other features inherent in the base Chromium build that inhibit control and transparency, while adding/modifying features that promote them. This is an ongoing process.</li>
<li>Santa&rsquo;s partnership with Eyeo ensures that only Acceptable Ads that abide by the criteria specially developed for and by ad-filtering users, and are non-intrusive are allowed to interact with you.</li>
</ul>
<p><b>Military Grade Security<br>
</b><a href="http://www.santabrowser.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Santa Browser&rsquo;s</a> code has been reviewed and tested for vulnerabilities by Veracode, a programme that validates a company&rsquo;s secure software development processes. Veracode Secure code review certification echoes Santa Browser&rsquo;s mature practices for creating secure software.</p>
<p><b>Planned Features<br>
</b>Updates in the next few weeks will see the phased release of interesting features such as free single-tab<b> VPN</b>, an immersive <b>dApp store</b> and the browser&rsquo;s very own decentralized<b> &ldquo;Santa Wallet&rdquo;</b> where users can easily collect their rewards.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" src="https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/dApp_store_image_1671725265HK0u6ArgcD.jpg" alt=""></p>
<p><b>About Santa Browser<br>
</b>A unique Web3 browser exclusively catering to the emerging crypto world &ndash; <a href="http://www.santabrowser.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Santa</a> will give users everything they need to kickstart their crypto journey with safety, ease &amp; convenience. Santa browser does not just resolutely protect the data &amp; privacy of its users, it also generously rewards them. Through Santa&rsquo;s Rewarded Browsing, users have the option to earn rewards through Ad Monetization, Search Monetization, Discounted Shopping, etc.</p>
<p><b>Join Santa Browser communities across the web:</b></p>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://twitter.com/santabrowser" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Twitter</a></li>
<li><a href="https://www.facebook.com/santabrowserofficial" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Facebook</a></li>
<li><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/78394870/admin/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">LinkedIn</a></li>
<li><a href="https://t.me/SantaBrowserCommunity" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Telegram</a></li>
<li><a href="https://discord.gg/PzW5p7kuvU" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Discord</a></li>
</ul>
<h5>Contact</h5>
<p>Mr&nbsp;Simon Hill,&nbsp;Santa Browser,&nbsp;contact@santabrowser.com,&nbsp;+973 3872 4554</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/santa-launches-its-rewarded-browser-this-christmas-to-bring-in-the-next-200m-users-onto-web3-0/">Santa launches its rewarded browser this Christmas to bring in the next 200M users onto Web3.0</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/santa-launches-its-rewarded-browser-this-christmas-to-bring-in-the-next-200m-users-onto-web3-0/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is Lido a good crypto to buy as it defies gravity?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/is-lido-a-good-crypto-to-buy-as-it-defies-gravity/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/is-lido-a-good-crypto-to-buy-as-it-defies-gravity/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 10:33:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/is-lido-a-good-crypto-to-buy-as-it-defies-gravity/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Lido price has made a spectacular recovery recently.&#160; Its total value locked has held steady at $5 billion. Lido price has defied gravity in the past few weeks as activity in its network holds steady. The LDO token was trading at $1.06 on Tuesday, which was the highest it has been since December 16. It [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/is-lido-a-good-crypto-to-buy-as-it-defies-gravity/">Is Lido a good crypto to buy as it defies gravity?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Lido price has made a spectacular recovery recently.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Its total value locked has held steady at $5 billion.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Lido price has defied gravity in the past few weeks as activity in its network holds steady. The LDO token was trading at $1.06 on Tuesday, which was the highest it has been since December 16. It has risen by more than 22% from the lowest level this year.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Lido?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Lido is a leading platform in decentralized finance (DeFi) that makes it possible for users to stake coins and earn rewards. It is the biggest liquid staking protocol, where it lets users stake coins like Solana, Ethereum, Polkadot, Kusama, and Polygon.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Lido has become highly popular among users in the past few months. It has become the biggest holder of&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum"><u>Ethereum</u></a> staking pool where it holds over 4.8 million ETH that provide an APR of 4.6%. It is also the biggest Polkadot pool operator witb over 2.47 million DOT valued at over $11 million with a yield of 14.3%.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Lido faced numerous challenges in 2022. The biggest one was the collapse of Terra and its ecosystem. Before the collapse, Lido was one of the biggest holders of Terra token. As a result, the total value locked (TVL) locked in its ecosystem plunged from over $20 billion to about $5.9 billion.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Lido&rsquo;s performance, while weak, has been relatively stronger than other cryptocurrencies. This is likely because investors believe that its yield solution is better than those provided by centralized protocols. Some of the top centralized platforms that collapsed in 2022 were BlockFi and Celsius.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Another&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/"><u>crypto news</u></a><strong>&nbsp;</strong>was Lido&rsquo;s collaboration with SSV network to create a distributed validator technology. The developers launched the pilot test for the new solution in December.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">As a step towards permissionless participation in Lido&rsquo;s Ethereum validator sets, we&rsquo;re very pleased to present our pilot DVT integration with <a href="https://twitter.com/ObolNetwork?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@ObolNetwork</a>.<a href="https://t.co/bMMLMf4F8l">https://t.co/bMMLMf4F8l</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Lido (@LidoFinance) <a href="https://twitter.com/LidoFinance/status/1606351858490118153?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 23, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Lido price forecast</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2022/11/27/1672137004256-0addd2d7-7d54-40bf-b3a1-3f98a8c36869.png" style="width: 522px;height: 259.26px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="522" height="259.26"></p>
<p style="text-align: center"><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/LDOUSD/?exchange=COINBASE">LDO chart by TradingView</a></p>
<p dir="ltr">The four-hour chart shows that the LDO price has made a spectacular recovery in the past few days. As it rose, it managed to move above the important resistance point at $0.992, the lowest level on December 12. It also crossed the psychological level of $1.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The coin also moved above the 25-day and 50-day moving averages while the Relative Strength Index (RSI) moved to the overbought point at 80. Therefore, the token will likely continue rising as buyers target the next key resistance at $1.2. A drop below the support at $0.992 will invalidate the bullish view.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/is-lido-a-good-crypto-to-buy-as-it-defies-gravity/">Is Lido a good crypto to buy as it defies gravity?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/is-lido-a-good-crypto-to-buy-as-it-defies-gravity/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How will the rising Binance outflows affect BNB price?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/how-will-the-rising-binance-outflows-affect-bnb-price/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/how-will-the-rising-binance-outflows-affect-bnb-price/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 09:04:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance Coin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/how-will-the-rising-binance-outflows-affect-bnb-price/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Binance has had significant outflows in the past few months. Customer assets in its ecosystem have fallen to about $55 billion. Binance is in trouble as crypto investors flee. The company has seen its assets drop from over $70 billion in November to about $55 billion. In the same period,&#160;Binance Coin price has plunged from [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/how-will-the-rising-binance-outflows-affect-bnb-price/">How will the rising Binance outflows affect BNB price?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Binance has had significant outflows in the past few months.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Customer assets in its ecosystem have fallen to about $55 billion.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Binance is in trouble as crypto investors flee. The company has seen its assets drop from over $70 billion in November to about $55 billion. In the same period,&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/binance-coin/"><u>Binance Coin</u></a> price has plunged from an all-time high of $708 to $250.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Binance outflows continue</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Binance is the biggest player in the cryptocurrency industry. At its peak, the company had more than 100 million customers from around the world. It provides numerous services, including a platform to buy and sell cryptocurrencies and one to do margin trading. The firm also has an investment platform where people can buy crypto and earn returns.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Binance has come into the spotlight in the past few weeks following the collapse of FTX and Voyager Digital. Their collapse have had a wake-up call in the crypto industry as regulators work to prevent another meltdown in the sector.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Crypto investors are also afraid about the health of their investments. As a result, many crypto holders have decided to withdraw their digital currencies. Data compiled by DeFi Llama shows that outflows in the crypto industry have been growing.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Investors pulled $116 million from the exchange in the past 24 hours and $957 million in the past 7 days. The exchange have lost over $9.5 billion in the past 30 days. This is a sign that investors are losing confidence in the industry, as I wrote&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-coin-price-prediction-is-all-this-fear-warranted/"><u>here</u></a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The impact of rising outflows is dire for Binance Coin price. BNB has crashed by more than 65% from its highest level this year and is now hovering near its lowest level since June.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The coin has also imploded because of the falling activity in Binance platforms like decentralized finance (DeFi), metaverse, and non-fungible tokens (NFT). The total value locked in Binance&rsquo;s DeFi ecosystem has dropped to about $5.8 billion.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">BNB price prediction</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2022/11/27/1672131839640-a901d289-c031-4eb9-92d1-25b790dedac0.png" style="width: 559px;height: 277.637px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="559" height="277.637"></p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: center"><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BNBUSD/?exchange=BINANCE"><u>BNB/USD chart by TradingView</u></a></p>
<p dir="ltr">The daily chart shows that Binance Coin&rsquo;s price has been in a consolidation phase in the past few days. It has managed to move below the 25-day and 50-day moving averages while the Relative Strength Index (RSI) has moved above the oversold level.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Binance Coin has also moved below the important support level at $254.9, which was the lowest level on November 22. Therefore, there is a likelihood that the coin will have a bearish breakout in the coming days. If this happens, the next key level to watch will be at $200.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy Binance Coin</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>

    <p>eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=OTg4OTk&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=TX&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy BNB with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    Binance</h3>

    <p>Binance is one of the largest cryptocurrency exchanges in the world. It is better suited to more experienced investors and it offers a large number of cryptocurrencies to choose from, at over 600.

Binance is also known for having low trading fees and a multiple of trading options that its users can benefit from, such as; peer-to-peer trading, margin trading and spot trading.
</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/binance-crypto?guid=OTg4OTk&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=TX&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy BNB with Binance today            </a>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/how-will-the-rising-binance-outflows-affect-bnb-price/">How will the rising Binance outflows affect BNB price?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/how-will-the-rising-binance-outflows-affect-bnb-price/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP tops $0.35 after Ripple Lab&#8217;s partnership with Palau</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/xrp-tops-0-35-after-ripple-labs-partnership-with-palau/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/xrp-tops-0-35-after-ripple-labs-partnership-with-palau/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 08:32:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple Labs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/xrp-tops-0-35-after-ripple-labs-partnership-with-palau/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Republic of Palau is working with Ripple Labs to explore the creation of a national stablecoin. XRP is up by more than 5% today and could rally higher soon. The total cryptocurrency market cap stands above $813 billion. Ripple Labs partners with the Republic of Palau Cryptocurrency journalist Wu Blockchain, reported a few hours [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/xrp-tops-0-35-after-ripple-labs-partnership-with-palau/">XRP tops $0.35 after Ripple Lab&#8217;s partnership with Palau</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The Republic of Palau is working with Ripple Labs to explore the creation of a national stablecoin.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">XRP is up by more than 5% today and could rally higher soon.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The total cryptocurrency market cap stands above $813 billion.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Ripple Labs partners with the Republic of Palau</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Cryptocurrency journalist Wu Blockchain, reported a few hours ago that the Republic of Palau is working with Ripple Labs to explore the possibility of creating a national stablecoin.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Palau President Surangel S. Whipps, Jr. said the country&rsquo;s IT team is working with Ripple Labs to explore creating a &ldquo;national stablecoin.&rdquo; As previously reported, Palau will issue ID cards to its digital residents in the form of NFTs on the BNB Chain. <a href="https://t.co/WM1k9DFZvJ">https://t.co/WM1k9DFZvJ</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Wu Blockchain (@WuBlockchain) <a href="https://twitter.com/WuBlockchain/status/1607374336113135622?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 26, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">Palau is set to issue ID cards to its digital residents in the form of NFTs on the BNB Chain. This <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>latest cryptocurrency news</u></a> saw XRP, the native token of the Ripple ecosystem, surge by more than 5% today.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">At press time, the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ripple/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>price of Ripple</u></a> stands at $0.3686. After surpassing the $0.35 resistance level, XRP could surge higher in the near term.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The total cryptocurrency market cap stands above $813 billion, up by less than 1% in the last 24 hours. The Bitcoin price is also up by less than 1% today and is now trading close to the $17k resistance level.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Key levels to watch</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The XRP/USD 4-hour chart has turned bullish as XRP has been performing well over the last 24 hours. The technical indicators show that XRP is the best performer amongst the top 10 cryptocurrencies by market cap.</p>
<div class="fr-img-space-wrap"><span class="fr-img-caption fr-fic fr-dib fr-draggable fr-fil" style="width: 600px"><span class="fr-img-wrap">
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2022/11/27/1672129738429-d44c9669-63c4-4384-a930-b361aebb2ac8.png" style="width: 600px" class="fr-fic fr-dib fr-fil" width="600" height="261"><span class="fr-inner"><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XRPUSD/?exchange=BITSTAMP"><u>XRP/USD Chart By TradingView</u></a></span></p>
<p></p></span></span>
<p class="fr-img-space-wrap2">&nbsp;</p>
</div>
<p dir="ltr">The MACD line crossed into the positive zone a few hours ago, indicating that the bulls have taken control of the XRP market following the Palau partnership with Ripple Labs.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The 14-day RSI of 73 also shows that XRP could enter the overbought region if the rally continues.</p>
<p dir="ltr">With the bulls now in charge, XRP could surge past the first major resistance level at $0.3799 before the end of the day. With the support of the broader cryptocurrency market, XRP could trade above $0.411 for the first time since November.&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Where to buy XRP now</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>

    <p>eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=OTg4OTg&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=TX&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy XRP with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    Bitstamp</h3>

    <p>Bitstamp is a leading cryptocurrency exchange which offers trading in fiat currencies or popular cryptocurrencies.

Bitstamp is a fully regulated company which offers users an intuitive interface, a high degree of security for your digital assets, excellent customer support and multiple withdrawal methods.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/bitstamp-crypto?guid=OTg4OTg&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=TX&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy XRP with Bitstamp today            </a>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/xrp-tops-0-35-after-ripple-labs-partnership-with-palau/">XRP tops $0.35 after Ripple Lab&#8217;s partnership with Palau</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/xrp-tops-0-35-after-ripple-labs-partnership-with-palau/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin is edging closer to $17k as bullish sentiment grows stronger</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-is-edging-closer-to-17k-as-bullish-sentiment-grows-stronger/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-is-edging-closer-to-17k-as-bullish-sentiment-grows-stronger/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 08:29:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-is-edging-closer-to-17k-as-bullish-sentiment-grows-stronger/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The crypto market is trading in the green zone for the second-consecutive day this week. Bitcoin is closing in on the $17k resistance level and could cross it a few hours from now. The total crypto market cap is now close to $815 billion. Bitcoin closes in on the $17k level Bitcoin, the world&#8217;s leading [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-is-edging-closer-to-17k-as-bullish-sentiment-grows-stronger/">Bitcoin is edging closer to $17k as bullish sentiment grows stronger</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The crypto market is trading in the green zone for the second-consecutive day this week.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin is closing in on the $17k resistance level and could cross it a few hours from now.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The total crypto market cap is now close to $815 billion.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Bitcoin closes in on the $17k level</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin, the world&rsquo;s leading cryptocurrency by market cap, has been performing positively for the second-consecutive day. The leading cryptocurrency has been struggling below the $17k resistance level over the past few weeks.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">At press time, the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>price of Bitcoin</u></a> stands at $16,886, up by less than 1% in the last 24 hours. With the bulls gathering momentum, Bitcoin could soon surge past the $17k resistance level in the near term.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin&rsquo;s positive performance aligns with that of the broader cryptocurrency market. The total crypto market cap stands at $813 billion, up by 0.36% in the last 24 hours. The positive performance comes after the market lost less than 1% of its value yesterday.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Ether, the second-largest cryptocurrency by market cap, is also trading in the green zone. So far today, the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>price of Ethereum</u></a> is up by 0.26% and currently stands at $1,223.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Key levels to watch</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The BTC/USD 4-hour chart has turned bullish as Bitcoin has been performing well over the last few days. The technical indicators show that Bitcoin could be preparing for a breakout in the near term.</p>
<div class="fr-img-space-wrap"><span class="fr-img-caption fr-fic fr-dib fr-draggable fr-fil" style="width: 600px"><span class="fr-img-wrap">
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2022/11/27/1672129738410-81133450-3bbb-45a3-a980-e9cb144155c9.png" style="width: 600px" class="fr-fic fr-dib fr-fil" width="600" height="284"><span class="fr-inner"><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/?exchange=COINBASE"><u>BTC/USD Chart By TradingView</u></a></span></p>
<p></p></span></span>
<p class="fr-img-space-wrap2">&nbsp;</p>
</div>
<p dir="ltr">The MACD line crossed into the positive zone a few hours ago, a sign that the bulls are currently in control of the Bitcoin market. The 14-day RSI of 51 also shows that Bitcoin is neutral but could head into the overbought region if it embarks on a rally.</p>
<p dir="ltr">If the bullish trend grows stronger, BTC could move past the first major resistance level at $17,178 before the end of the day.</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, Bitcoin would need the support of the broader crypto market to rally toward the $17,982 resistance level over the coming days.&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Where to buy Bitcoin now</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>

    <p>eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=OTg4OTc&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=TX&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy BTC with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    Bitstamp</h3>

    <p>Bitstamp is a leading cryptocurrency exchange which offers trading in fiat currencies or popular cryptocurrencies.

Bitstamp is a fully regulated company which offers users an intuitive interface, a high degree of security for your digital assets, excellent customer support and multiple withdrawal methods.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/bitstamp-crypto?guid=OTg4OTc&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=TX&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy BTC with Bitstamp today            </a>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-is-edging-closer-to-17k-as-bullish-sentiment-grows-stronger/">Bitcoin is edging closer to $17k as bullish sentiment grows stronger</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-is-edging-closer-to-17k-as-bullish-sentiment-grows-stronger/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin price prediction as the US dollar index plummets</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-the-us-dollar-index-plummets/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-the-us-dollar-index-plummets/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 05:17:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-the-us-dollar-index-plummets/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin price has been in a tight range in the past few weeks. Bitcoin&#8217;s fear and greed index has dropped to the fear level of 25. The US dollar index has plummeted to $103. Bitcoin price has held in a tight range even as the US dollar index (DXY) has plunged to the lowest level [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-the-us-dollar-index-plummets/">Bitcoin price prediction as the US dollar index plummets</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin price has been in a tight range in the past few weeks.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin&rsquo;s fear and greed index has dropped to the fear level of 25.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The US dollar index has plummeted to $103.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin price has held in a tight range even as the US dollar index (DXY) has plunged to the lowest level since June. BTC/USD was trading at $16,858, where it has been in the past few days. This price is more than 70% below its all-time high of near $70,000.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">US dollar index crashes</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin"><u>Bitcoin</u></a> and the US dollar have had a strong inverse relationship in the past few years. In most cases, Bitcoin rises when the greenback retreats.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Recently, this inverse correlation has faded as Bitcoin and the US dollar have continued dropping. The US dollar index has plunged from the year-to-date high of over $115.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">It has crashed in the past few months even after the relatively hawkish Federal Reserve. In its December meeting, the Fed decided to hike interest rates by 0.50% after hiking by 0.75% in the previous four meetings. You can read more about the Fed decision&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-retreats-below-18k-as-fed-raises-interest-rate-to-a-15-year-high/"><u>here</u></a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Fed also hinted that it will continue increasing interest rates in the coming months. Recent numbers are supportive of higher rates. For example, data published last week revealed that the economy expanded by 3% in the third quarter after slumping in the previous two straight quarters.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Additional data revealed that inflation is falling at a relatively slower pace. On Friday, the Fed&rsquo;s favourite inflation gauge showed that it dropped in November as gasoline prices eased.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin price has also dropped as the fear and greed index has remained under pressure. The closely watched Bitcoin fear gauge remains below 30, meaning that investors are fearful about the state of the market.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In my view, the most accurate fear gauge is outflows. Binance has had outflows worth over $9 billion in the past 30 days. Similarly, the leading&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/price/"><u>crypto</u></a> banks like Silvergate have had some of their biggest outflows on record.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitcoin price prediction</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2022/11/27/1672118196695-767d90ae-1461-4a49-9b1a-28bde36602ed.png" style="width: 619px;height: 307.437px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="619" height="307.437"></p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/?exchange=COINBASE"><u>BTC/USD chart by TradingView</u></a></p>
<p dir="ltr">So, is it safe to buy Bitcoin? The 4H chart shows that the BTC price has been in a tight range in the past few weeks. It is hovering at the 16,800 level, where it has been this month. Bitcoin&rsquo;s Relative Strength Index (RSI) has moved close to the neutral point of 50.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, despite the collapse of the US dollar index, there is a likelihood that it will soon have a bearish breakout. If this happens, the next key support level to watch will be at $15,435, the lowest level in 2022. A breakdown below that level will mean that there are still more sellers in the market.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy Bitcoin</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>

    <p>eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=OTg4OTY&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=TX&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy BTC with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    Bitstamp</h3>

    <p>Bitstamp is a leading cryptocurrency exchange which offers trading in fiat currencies or popular cryptocurrencies.

Bitstamp is a fully regulated company which offers users an intuitive interface, a high degree of security for your digital assets, excellent customer support and multiple withdrawal methods.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/bitstamp-crypto?guid=OTg4OTY&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=TX&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy BTC with Bitstamp today            </a>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-the-us-dollar-index-plummets/">Bitcoin price prediction as the US dollar index plummets</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-the-us-dollar-index-plummets/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
