<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 23:32:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>MicroStrategy narrowed its crypto-related impairment charge sharply in Q2</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/microstrategy-narrows-crypto-impairment-charge-in-q2/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wajeeh Khan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 23:29:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MicroStrategy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=148335</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>MicroStrategy bought another 12,333 Bitcoin in its second quarter. The business intelligence company returned to profitability in Q2. MicroStrategy stock has roughly tripled versus the start of 2023. MicroStrategy Inc &#8211; one of the most prominent institutional holder of Bitcoin &#8211; says it returned to profitability in its second financial quarter. Its shares are still [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/microstrategy-narrows-crypto-impairment-charge-in-q2/">MicroStrategy narrowed its crypto-related impairment charge sharply in Q2</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>MicroStrategy bought another 12,333 Bitcoin in its second quarter.</li>
<li>The business intelligence company returned to profitability in Q2.</li>
<li>MicroStrategy stock has roughly tripled versus the start of 2023.</li>
</ul>
<p>MicroStrategy Inc &ndash; one of the most prominent institutional holder of <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> &ndash; says it returned to profitability in its second financial quarter. Its shares are still down 2.0% after-hours.</p>
<h2>MicroStrategy continued to buy Bitcoin in Q2</h2>
<p>The business intelligence company added another 12,333 Bitcoin in Q2 &ndash; the most it has bought in a quarter in about two years. In total, it now has 152,800 BTC on the balance sheet worth about $4.4 billion.</p>
<p>MicroStrategy narrowed the impairment charge related to its crypto holdings in the second quarter to $24.1 million versus close to a billion-dollar last year. Andrew Kang &ndash; its Chief Financial Officer said in the <a href="https://www.microstrategy.com/en/investor-relations/press/microstrategy-announces-second-quarter-2023-financial-results_08-01-2023" target="_blank" rel="noopener">press release</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>We continued to increase bitcoins and did so against the promising backdrop of increasing institutional interest and ongoing regulatory clarity.</p></blockquote>
<p>Bitcoin is currently up about 80% for the year.</p>
<h2>MicroStrategy topped Q2 earnings estimates</h2>
<p>MicroStrategy earned $22.2 million in its recently concluded quarter that translates to $2.35 a share (adjusted) on $120.4 million in revenue &ndash; down 1.0% on a year-over-year basis, as per the <a href="https://www.microstrategy.com/en/investor-relations/press/microstrategy-announces-second-quarter-2023-financial-results_08-01-2023" target="_blank" rel="noopener">press release.</a></p>
<p>In comparison, analysts were at $1.64 a share and $126 million, respectively. According to CEO Phong Le:</p>
<blockquote><p>Growth in our recurring revenue this quarter illustrated the strength of our enterprise cloud platform, despite ongoing macroeconomic headwinds.</p></blockquote>
<p>The news arrives only days after a TD Cowen analyst Lance Vitanza dubbed MicroStrategy the best way for institutional investors to gain exposure to Bitcoin. He sees upside in the software stock to $520 &ndash; about a 21% premium on its current price (<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/microstrategy-stock-has-22-upside-td-cowen-analyst/">find out more</a>).</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/microstrategy-narrows-crypto-impairment-charge-in-q2/">MicroStrategy narrowed its crypto-related impairment charge sharply in Q2</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>ConsenSys releases “Diligence Fuzzing,” tool for testing smart contract vulnerability</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/consensys-releases-diligence-fuzzing-tool-for-testing-smart-contract-vulnerability/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 12:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/consensys-releases-diligence-fuzzing-tool-for-testing-smart-contract-vulnerability/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>More than $471.43 million was lost through Web3 security vulnerabilities in the first half of 2023. The Diligence Fuzzing has been integrated with the smart contract toolkit Foundry. The tool features a free version for developers who wish to test it out before making any payments. The blockchain technology company ConsenSys has announced the public [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/consensys-releases-diligence-fuzzing-tool-for-testing-smart-contract-vulnerability/">ConsenSys releases “Diligence Fuzzing,” tool for testing smart contract vulnerability</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>More than $471.43 million was lost through Web3 security vulnerabilities in the first half of 2023.</li>
<li>The Diligence Fuzzing has been integrated with the smart contract toolkit Foundry.</li>
<li>The tool features a free version for developers who wish to test it out before making any payments.</li>
</ul>
<p>The blockchain technology company ConsenSys has announced the public release of its &ldquo;Diligence Fuzzing&rdquo; smart contract testing tool. The new tool generates &ldquo;random and invalid data points&rdquo; to identify contract flaws prior to the smart contract launch.</p>
<p>The launch is very timely seeing that <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/defi/">decentralized finance</a> hacks cost over $2.8 billion in 2022. ConsenSys claims that as a result of these losses, developers are adopting more sophisticated testing tools to assist in identifying vulnerabilities before attackers do.</p>
<p>Previously, developers had to request access to the closed beta version of the new tool before using it. As of August 1 after the release of the &ldquo;Diligence Fuzzing&rdquo; tool, this approval procedure is no longer required.</p>
<p>Diligence Fuzzing is now integrated with Foundry&rsquo;s smart contract toolkit, and it offers a free version for developers to try out.</p>
<h2>How does the &ldquo;Diligence Fuzzing&rdquo; work?</h2>
<p>According to ConsenSys security services lead Liz Daldalian, developers using the &ldquo;Diligence Fuzzing&rdquo;&nbsp;tool can annotate their contracts using a machine language called &ldquo;Scribble,&rdquo; which is also developed by ConsenSys. After doing this, the fuzzing tool will interpret the annotations and produce &ldquo;unexpected&rdquo; inputs so as to test whether the smart contract can be forced to produce unintended actions.</p>
<p>ConsenSys security researcher Gon&ccedil;alo S&aacute; has, however, stated that the &ldquo;Diligence Fuzzing&rdquo; tool is not a &ldquo;black box fuzzer&rdquo; and that it does not produce completely random data. Instead, Gon&ccedil;alo says that the fuzzing tool acts as a &ldquo;grey-box fuzzer&rdquo; that understands the smart contract&rsquo;s current state to limit the types of data produced, thus increasing the tool&rsquo;s efficiency.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/consensys-releases-diligence-fuzzing-tool-for-testing-smart-contract-vulnerability/">ConsenSys releases “Diligence Fuzzing,” tool for testing smart contract vulnerability</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Cash price prediction as volatility and volume slumps</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-cash-price-prediction-as-volatility-and-volume-slumps/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-cash-price-prediction-as-volatility-and-volume-slumps/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 12:04:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-cash-price-prediction-as-volatility-and-volume-slumps/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin Cash, like other cryptocurrencies, remained in consolidation in July. There are signs of rotation moving from digital currencies to stocks. Bitcoin Cash (BCH) price had a difficult performance in July as the fear and greed index remained neutral at 50. The coin dropped to a low of $230 in July, down from the monthly [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-cash-price-prediction-as-volatility-and-volume-slumps/">Bitcoin Cash price prediction as volatility and volume slumps</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin Cash, like other cryptocurrencies, remained in consolidation in July.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">There are signs of rotation moving from digital currencies to stocks.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin-cash/"><u>Bitcoin Cash</u></a> (BCH) price had a difficult performance in July as the fear and greed index remained neutral at 50. The coin dropped to a low of $230 in July, down from the monthly high of $330.53.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Rotation from crypto to stocks</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin Cash price remained in a tight range as demand and volatility retreated. Data shows that the volume of cryptocurrencies traded in exchanges dropped sharply in July. This happened even after a number of important catalysts happened during the month.</p>
<p dir="ltr">For example, data published by the Bureau of Labor Statistics (BLS) showed that the America&rsquo;s consumer price index (CPI) dropped from 4.1% to 3.0%. The closely watched personal consumption expenditure (PCE) index dropped from 4.0% to 3.1%.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">These numbers mean that the country&rsquo;s inflation is falling at a faster pace than expected. As a result, investors believe that the Federal Reserve has completed hiking interest rates. It hiked them by 0.25% last Wednesday to the highest level in 22 years.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Another important&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/"><u>crypto news</u></a><strong>&nbsp;</strong>in July was the partial victory by Ripple in its long-running case with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). In her judgment, the judge ruled that XRP was not a financial security.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, Bitcoin Cash price likely retreated as investors moved from cryptocurrencies to stocks. The Nasdaq 100 index and S&amp;P 500 indices surged to the highest level in months, with the former soaring by 42% this year. As a result, there is a likelihood that many crypto investors moved their funds to stocks.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitcoin Cash price prediction</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/07/01/1690891329027-b36115b4-481f-4e57-8253-95f25ad1ee48.png" style="width: 639px;height: 311.445px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="639" height="311.445"></p>
<p dir="ltr">The 4H chart shows that the BCH price has moved sideways in the past few weeks. It has moved to the 50-period and 25-period moving averages. Bollinger Bands have narrowed. The coin has moved above the key support level at $230.94, the lowest level in July.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Relative Strength Index (RSI) has moved below 50 while the Average True Range (ATR) has retreated. ATR is one of the most popular measures of volatility.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, there is a likelihood that the indicator will remain in this consolidation phase in the coming days. A drop below the support at $230 in a high environment will push it to the next support at $200. A move at $266 will open the possibility of the Bitcoin Cash price rising to $300.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy Bitcoin Cash</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>

    <p>eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=MTQ4Mjg3&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy BCH with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    Public</h3>

    <p>Public is an investing platform that allows you to invest stocks, ETFs, crypto, and alternative assets like fine art and collectibles&mdash;all in one place.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/public-crypto?guid=MTQ4Mjg3&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy BCH with Public today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptocurrency execution and custody services are provided by Apex Crypto LLC (NMLS ID 1828849) through a software licensing agreement between Apex Crypto LLC and Public Crypto LLC. Crypto trading on Public platforms is served by Public Crypto LLC and offered through APEX Crypto. Please ensure that you fully understand the risks involved before trading." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-cash-price-prediction-as-volatility-and-volume-slumps/">Bitcoin Cash price prediction as volatility and volume slumps</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-cash-price-prediction-as-volatility-and-volume-slumps/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>FTX claimants to hold equity securities and tokens in the rebooted exchange</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/ftx-claimants-to-hold-equity-securities-and-tokens-in-the-rebooted-exchange/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 12:01:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/ftx-com-claimants-to-hold-equity-securities-and-tokens-in-the-rebooted-exchange/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The new FTX CEO is working tirelessly to have the FTX crypto exchange launched. FTT token holders will not receive any distributions from the rebranded FTX exchange. FTX claimants will, however, own interests in the newly established offshore FTX Company. The newly appointed CEO of FTX Trading Ltd., John J. Ray III, has unveiled a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ftx-claimants-to-hold-equity-securities-and-tokens-in-the-rebooted-exchange/">FTX claimants to hold equity securities and tokens in the rebooted exchange</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>The new FTX CEO is working tirelessly to have the FTX crypto exchange launched.</li>
<li>FTT token holders will not receive any distributions from the rebranded FTX exchange.</li>
<li>FTX claimants will, however, own interests in the newly established offshore FTX Company.</li>
</ul>
<p>The newly appointed CEO of FTX Trading Ltd., John J. Ray III, has unveiled a new draft strategy to &ldquo;reboot&rdquo; the defunct FTX cryptocurrency exchange.</p>
<p>In the proposal, which was unveiled on Monday, FTX.com claimants are allowed to own equity securities, tokens, or other types of interests in the newly established offshore company.</p>
<h2>What will happen to FTT holders?</h2>
<p>The new plan describes the debtors&rsquo; approach to grouping claimants into different categories. Users of the offshore FTX.com exchange will be referred to as &ldquo;Dotcom customers,&rdquo; while those using the FTX US will be called &ldquo;U.S. customers.&rdquo;</p>
<p>The Dotcom Customer Pool, the U.S. Customer Pool, and General Pool are the three main recovery pools that are suggested to be created on the new exchange. All fiat, digital, and other specified assets connected to FTX.com and FTX US will be included in these pools.</p>
<p>The newly created company, which was established in collaboration with outside investors, will run a &ldquo;rebooted&rdquo; offshore platform that won&rsquo;t be available to American investors.</p>
<p>Each Dotcom customer will receive a pro-rata share of the proceeds from a pool of assets tied to the FTX.com exchange. However, the new plan indicates that claims from FTT holders, the collapsed exchange&rsquo;s native token, &ldquo;will be cancelled and extinguished as of the Effective Date and holders will not receive any distribution.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Furthermore, claims from non-customers, like the regulatory penalties and taxes claims, will be subordinated.</p>
<p>The development comes a few days after <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ftx-and-genesis-agree-to-resolve-claims-in-the-bankruptcy-case/">FTX and Genesis agreed to an in-principle settlement</a> to resolve claims by the two companies in the bankruptcy proceedings.</p>
<h2>FTX 2.0 impending launch</h2>
<p>The idea of restarting the collapsed FTX exchange was first suggested by the new FTX boss in January. The new management had targeted to <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ftx-considering-relaunching-in-q2-after-asset-recovery/">relaunch in Q2, 2023</a>.</p>
<p>According to a court document filed in May, Ray has been actively investigating the steps needed to restart the business and reviewing and completing the &ldquo;FTX 2.0&rdquo; materials to be distributed to investors.</p>
<p>Following the recent development and the anticipation of the FTX reboot, the FTT token has been climbing. At press time the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ftx-token/">FTT token price</a> was trading at $1.41 up 5% in the last 24 hours.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ftx-claimants-to-hold-equity-securities-and-tokens-in-the-rebooted-exchange/">FTX claimants to hold equity securities and tokens in the rebooted exchange</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto&#8217;s correlation with stocks rising again following temporary deviation</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/cryptos-correlation-with-stocks-rising-again-following-temporary-deviation/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/cryptos-correlation-with-stocks-rising-again-following-temporary-deviation/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dan Ashmore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 11:40:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/cryptos-correlation-with-stocks-rising-again-following-temporary-deviation/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key Takeaways Crypto had moved in line with stocks and other risk assets throughout the interest rate tightening cycle This relationship weakened in June amid the crypto regulatory crackdown The correlation has recently picked up again, however Going forward, relationship may change again as the market anticipates the tightening cycle is coming to a close [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/cryptos-correlation-with-stocks-rising-again-following-temporary-deviation/">Crypto&#8217;s correlation with stocks rising again following temporary deviation</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2 dir="ltr">Key Takeaways</h2>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Crypto had moved in line with stocks and other risk assets throughout the interest rate tightening cycle</li>
<li dir="ltr">This relationship weakened in June amid the crypto regulatory crackdown</li>
<li dir="ltr">The correlation has recently picked up again, however</li>
<li dir="ltr">Going forward, relationship may change again as the market anticipates the tightening cycle is coming to a close</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p dir="ltr">We know that within the digital asset space, the different cryptocurrencies are highly correlated. As a generalisation, it is fair to say that many altcoins tend to trade like levered bets on Bitcoin.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Going beyond the asset class and assessing correlations with other asset types becomes more interesting. One of the most intriguing trends to track is the correlation between Bitcoin and stocks. If we want to assess Bitcoin through a macroeconomic lens, its relationship with other asset classes is of vital importance.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The last eighteen months have thrown this relationship into a new light, as correlations have been extremely high amid one of the fastest interest rate tightening cycles in recent history. With liquidity sucked out of the economy, risk assets were hammered last year, including Bitcoin.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Compared to the tech-heavy Nasdaq, Bitcoin&rsquo;s correlation has been persistently high throughout this period, bar a few noticeable instances. As displayed on the below chart from an analysis we compiled <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-correlation-with-stocks-at-5-year-low-as-regulatory-crackdown-takes-toll/"><u>six weeks ago</u></a>, the collapses of Luna, Celsius and FTX saw deviations in this relationship.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">These explain themselves, as dramatic crypto-specific episodes that had no effect on stocks. However, the more recent deviation was bigger than any: coming in June amid the regulatory crackdown (chart is taken from June 15th, a week after the Binance and Coinbase lawsuits).&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/05/15/1686836790790-e6ad26c9-1132-4a69-b507-7ea8eb63f579.png" style="width: 600px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="600" height="427">In fact, this deviation brought the Nasdaq&rsquo;s correlation with Bitcoin to a five-year low. If we now re-run this chart, we see the correlation has picked back up again, rising to 0.5 and trending upwards.</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14601157">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    &nbsp;
<p dir="ltr">This highlights what we already knew: the deviation is only temporary. It came following a month where the Nasdaq jumped 10% off softer forecasts around the future path of interest rate hikes, while Bitcoin fell 9% over the same time period as lawmakers tightened their squeeze on the industry, suing the two largest exchanges and confirming several tokens constituted securities. &nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The climate has picked up for crypto since. Ripple won an important case (or, <em>partially won,&nbsp;</em>but the result was undoubtedly positive for the space), while a slew of spot ETF applications have also served to increase optimism.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">While the deviation was always going to be temporary, going forward in the medium-term, things could get more interesting. This is because, finally, the market is anticipating that the majority of interest rate hikes are in the rearview window, with perhaps only one more still to be endured, if even.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">This could release the shackles which have been around Bitcoin&rsquo;s ankles, and it remains to be seen how the asset will henceforth move in relation to the stock market. We know that the correlation picked up as soon as the Federal Reserve began hiking interest rates; correlations go to 1 in a crisis, and there is a flight to quality &ndash; risk assets suffer in that scenario, and that is exactly what we saw.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">There is every chance that both stocks and Bitcoin will continue to trade in tandem, but if/when this tightening cycle ends, it will at least give the market a fresh opportunity to trade them whilst global liquidity is not being pulled off the table.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Regardless of the relationship between the duo, the below chart shows just how dependent Bitcoin has been on yields &ndash; the two-year treasury yield, plotted on an inverse scale, has moved exceptionally closely with Bitcoin, ever since the latter&rsquo;s all-time high in November 2021.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14601254">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<h2 dir="ltr">How will Bitcoin&rsquo;s relationship with gold change?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">It is Bitcoin&rsquo;s relationship with gold that provides an equal amount of intrigue, given the former&rsquo;s designs on becoming some sort of digital equivalent of the latter. Should Bitcoin become a store of value, it will need to become a little more boring with regard to price movements &ndash; something gold is well known for.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, correlation between the two assets has dipped, moving in the opposite direction to that of stocks. From rising markedly this year, it has fallen sharply in the last month.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14601183">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">If Bitcoin is to achieve what so many want to do &ndash; become an uncorrelated asset capable of offering a portfolio hedge properties &ndash; it must flip the script here. Its relationship with stocks will need to loosen, while it will need to get closer to the way gold trades.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Having said that, Bitcoin has been around only 14 years, and has traded with reasonable liquidity for far less than that. It is still finding its feet, and it remains early &ndash; certainly compared to gold, which has been around for thousands of years.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/cryptos-correlation-with-stocks-rising-again-following-temporary-deviation/">Crypto&#8217;s correlation with stocks rising again following temporary deviation</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/cryptos-correlation-with-stocks-rising-again-following-temporary-deviation/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Enjinstarter IDO investors win big with AI</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/enjinstarter-ido-investors-win-big-with-ai/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/enjinstarter-ido-investors-win-big-with-ai/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire &#160;]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 10:13:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=148269</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Singapore, Singapore, August 1st, 2023, Chainwire Launchpad delivers 142.4% ROI YTD thanks to carefully curated selection of AI projects Leading IDO launchpad, Enjinstarter, announced today that its stable of AI-powered Web3 projects has earned investors an average ROI of 142.4% YTD in 2023. This puts Enjinstarter firmly in the top 3 of IDO providers worldwide, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/enjinstarter-ido-investors-win-big-with-ai/">Enjinstarter IDO investors win big with AI</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Singapore, Singapore, August 1st, 2023, Chainwire</strong></p>
<p class="ql-align-center">Launchpad delivers 142.4% ROI YTD thanks to carefully curated selection of AI projects</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Leading IDO launchpad, <a href="https://enjinstarter.com/?utm_source=chainwire%20pr&amp;utm_medium=press%20release&amp;utm_campaign=top%20launchpad" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Enjinstarter</a>, announced today that its stable of AI-powered Web3 projects has earned investors <a href="https://cryptorank-images.s3.eu-central-1.amazonaws.com/snapshots/a3e6768815d8e7cf24e8f62e.png?utm_source=chainwire%20pr&amp;utm_medium=press%20release&amp;utm_campaign=cryptorank%20top" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">an average ROI of 142.4% YTD</a> in 2023. This puts Enjinstarter firmly in the top 3 of IDO providers worldwide, according to industry-leading ranking service, <a href="https://cryptorank.io?utm_source=chainwire%20pr&amp;utm_medium=press%20release&amp;utm_campaign=crytorank" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">CryptoRank</a>.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Continued success in Q2 comes on the back of a successful Q1 in which Enjinstarter was <a href="https://twitter.com/_TokenHunter/status/1656841624905760769?utm_source=chainwire%20pr&amp;utm_medium=press%20release&amp;utm_campaign=token%20hunter" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">ranked by TokenHunter</a> as the top-performing IDO launchpad with an average ROI of 538.49%.</p>
<blockquote><p>&ldquo;Our number one goal is to deliver maximum value to our IDO participants. We conduct an exhaustive study of every launchpad applicant to bring our token holders a carefully curated selection of projects set to revolutionize the industry,&rdquo; said <strong>Prakash Somosundram, co-founder and CEO of Enjinstarter. </strong>&ldquo;At the beginning of the year, our team correctly identified the growing trend towards generative AI and was quick to adapt. Our overall success this year can be attributed to our team&rsquo;s ability to find the best among a proliferation of AI-powered Web3 projects.&rdquo;</p></blockquote>
<p class="ql-align-justify">2023 has been the year of AI. The continued evolution of OpenAI&rsquo;s GPT algorithm has led to a proliferation of generative AI-powered apps. Of the 13 IDOs conducted by Enjinstarter so far this year, 8 leverage the power of AI:</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>ChainGPT </strong>&ndash; Infrastructure enabling the future of Web3 innovation with AI</li>
<li><strong>Orbofi AI </strong>&ndash; Advanced platform for creating AI-generated content and fine-tuned AI models.</li>
<li><strong>Eldarune</strong> &ndash; AI-powered RPG with PvE and PvP modes</li>
<li><strong>Cogito Protocol</strong> &ndash; A decentralized and AI-driven tracercoin called GCOIN</li>
<li><strong>KAIF Platform </strong>&ndash; AI-powered decentralized society (DeSoc) platform.</li>
<li><strong>HyperGPT </strong>&ndash; A Web3-based AI marketplace</li>
<li><strong>DexCheck </strong>&ndash; AI-boosted analytics for crypto and NFT trading</li>
<li><strong>SophiaVerse</strong> &ndash; An advanced artificial general intelligence initiative revolutionizing the world of AI and gaming</li>
</ul>
<p class="ql-align-justify">The top performing IDO launched through Enjinstarter in 2023 is ChainGPT with an ROI of 704% at the time of writing. SophiaVerse is a close second at 602%. Data provided by <a href="https://cryptorank.io/fundraising-platforms/enjinstarter?sort=roi&amp;direction=desc&amp;utm_source=chainwire%20pr&amp;utm_medium=press%20release&amp;utm_campaign=cryptorank%20ranking" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">CryptoRank</a>.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Building on the success of its IDO launchpad, Enjinstarter plans to build two additional launchpads. The first is an INO platform to connect utility-driven NFT projects with investors. The second is a <a href="https://enjinstarter.com/impact/index.html?utm_source=chainwire%20pr&amp;utm_medium=press%20release&amp;utm_campaign=impact%20launchpad" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">platform</a> specifically designed for Web3 climate startups to raise funds from impact investors.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Looking ahead, Enjinstarter has <a href="https://launchpad.enjinstarter.com/?utm_source=chainwire%20pr&amp;utm_medium=press%20release&amp;utm_campaign=ejs%20launchpad" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">5 IDO projects</a> in the pipeline: SeaPad, Kvants AI, Boss Fighters, AITECH, and Backstage. It is also planning the release of an expansive storytelling AI NFT game based on an advanced earth concept where factions are embarking on quests and battles throughout the Enjinstarter ecosystem to gather resources and earn rewards.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">To date, the company has helped launch over 80 Web3 projects and platforms since its inception in 2021.</p>
<p>For further media enquiries, please contact:</p>
<p>media@pariahdao.xyz</p>
<h3>About Enjinstarter</h3>
<p>Launched in 2021, Enjinstarter is a next-generation ecosystem and launchpad for promising Web3 gaming, entertainment and metaverse projects. They have supported 70 companies since</p>
<p>inception. They have a collective community of more than 200,000 across various social platforms and manage localised communities in South East Asia, India, Turkey and Spain. They have also launched dedicated market-launchers for North America and Indonesia.</p>
<p>Enjinstarter also has a fast growing Web3 Innovation Consulting practice that works with brands, large corporates and Web2 companies looking to develop a Web3 strategy. Clients that they have supported include Hatten Land and GCEX. Enjinstarter is also a member of the Open Metaverse Alliance.</p>
<p>Enjinstarter raised US$5 million in their Series A round from True Global Ventures 4 Plus, an equity venture capital firm that invests in serial tech entrepreneurs globally. The company has also received initial approval from Dubai&rsquo;s Virtual Assets Regulatory Authority, indicating progress in obtaining full permission to operate within Dubai.</p>
<p>Get connected with Enjinstarter:</p>
<p><a href="https://linktr.ee/enjinstarter" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://linktr.ee/enjinstarter</a></p>
<h3>Contact</h3>
<p>Social Media Lead, Chris Sylvester Basil, Enjinstarter, chris@enjinstarter.com</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/enjinstarter-ido-investors-win-big-with-ai/">Enjinstarter IDO investors win big with AI</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/enjinstarter-ido-investors-win-big-with-ai/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chainlink price prediction: Here’s what top analyst says about LINK</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/chainlink-price-prediction-heres-what-top-analyst-says-about-link/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 19:03:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chainlink News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technical Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/chainlink-price-prediction-heres-what-top-analyst-says-about-link/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Chainlink (LINK) traded to highs of $8.44 before retreating amid broader market uncertainty. A top crypto analyst says LINK seeing a weekly close below the macro downtrend line portends fresh losses.&#160; The &#8220;Macro Breakout is postponed&#8221; the analyst noted on Monday.&#160; Chainlink posted an impressive run in the week of July 13-21, notching a +20% [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chainlink-price-prediction-heres-what-top-analyst-says-about-link/">Chainlink price prediction: Here’s what top analyst says about LINK</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Chainlink (LINK) traded to highs of $8.44 before retreating amid broader market uncertainty.</li>
<li dir="ltr">A top crypto analyst says LINK seeing a weekly close below the macro downtrend line portends fresh losses.<em>&nbsp;</em></li>
<li dir="ltr">The &ldquo;Macro Breakout is postponed&rdquo; the analyst noted on Monday.&nbsp;</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Chainlink posted an impressive run in the week of July 13-21, notching a +20% gain in a single day on July 20 as it hit a three-month high of $8.44. On-chain volume spiked to over $347 million as traders poured into the altcoin amid positive network developments.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Chainlink price analysis</h2>
<p dir="ltr">LINK bulls appeared to be on the way to retesting a key technical level just under $10, with price poised to break a multi-year macro downtrend.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Crypto analyst Rekt Capital highlighted this on Friday, identifying a potential weekly close above the macro downtrend line as a likely indicator of bullish strength.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As can be seen in the chart below, Chainlink price has recoiled from the crucial hurdle with a weekly close below. According to the analyst, the scenario where the would-be macro breakout has fizzled out (at the moment.)</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>$LINK has ultimately performed its new Weekly Close below the Macro Downtrend. As a result, the Macro Breakout is postponed. Unless #LINK is able to reclaim this Macro Downtrend as support, price is positioning itself up for a rejection from here</em>,&rdquo; Rekt Capital <a href="https://twitter.com/rektcapital/status/1686074433058799616" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">shared</a> on X (fka Twitter).</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/31/1690829774163-6ef3c126-c8e6-4674-89b6-a210176ef75b.jpg" style="width: 600px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="600" height="423"><em>Chainlink weekly price chart showing LINK new weekly close. Source: Rekt Capital.</em></p>
<div class="fr-img-space-wrap">LINK currently trades near $7.60, largely flat in the past 24 hours. Investors have seen gains recorded over the past week cut to just 1%. LINK/USD is up 20% in the past 30 days.</div>
<p dir="ltr"></p>
<p dir="ltr">If prices fall below $7.00, the next major support zone could be around $5.00. On the upside, $8.50 and $10 are key supply zones.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Here&rsquo;s something else the analyst points out about Chainlink price performance.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">In the end <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24LINK&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$LINK</a> Weekly Closed below its Range High resistance just like it did many times in the past</p>
<p>And so this <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/LINK?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#LINK</a> bounce may be a relief rally to confirm the Range High as resistance</p>
<p>If that's the case LINK could drop lower in this black-black range<a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Crypto?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Crypto</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Chainlink?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Chainlink</a> <a href="https://t.co/yKlMNiPkqE">pic.twitter.com/yKlMNiPkqE</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Rekt Capital (@rektcapital) <a href="https://twitter.com/rektcapital/status/1686083230837964802?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 31, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chainlink-price-prediction-heres-what-top-analyst-says-about-link/">Chainlink price prediction: Here’s what top analyst says about LINK</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>BALD price nosedives 90% as deployer removes ETH liquidity</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bald-price-nosedives-90-as-deployer-removes-liquidity/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 18:10:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bald-price-nosedives-90-as-deployer-removes-liquidity/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>BALD price down nearly 90% as sell-off pressure mounts Data shows prices plummeted as meme coin&#8217;s deployer removed all ETH liquidity. Bald is a token recently launched on Ethereum layer-2 blockchain Base. Bald (BALD), a recently launched meme coin that went live on the Base blockchain, plunged on Monday as sell-off pressure mounted. As CoinJournal [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bald-price-nosedives-90-as-deployer-removes-liquidity/">BALD price nosedives 90% as deployer removes ETH liquidity</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">BALD price down nearly 90% as sell-off pressure mounts</li>
<li dir="ltr">Data shows prices plummeted as meme coin&rsquo;s deployer removed all ETH liquidity.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Bald is a token recently launched on Ethereum layer-2 blockchain Base.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Bald (BALD), a recently launched meme coin that went live on the Base blockchain, plunged on Monday as sell-off pressure mounted.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As CoinJournal <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bald-token-records-astounding-40000-upside-after-launch-on-base/">reported</a> on July 30, the price of the meme token had skyrocketed as its market cap jumped from near $0 to $70 million in hours. It continued its meteoric rise to hit a market cap of over $85 million and see multiple traders report astounding gains.</p>
<p dir="ltr">But on July 31, with market uncertainty hitting the roof around the actions of the BALD developer, the token&rsquo;s price plummeted.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">BALD price</h2>
<p dir="ltr">According to data from <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/bald" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">CoinGecko</a>, BALD nosedived by nearly 90% as traders reacted to the development that saw Bald&rsquo;s deployer remove millions of dollars&rsquo; worth of token liquidity. The token quickly fell from highs of $0.09 to $0.004, bleeding more than 94% from that peak.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Smart money on-chain account Lookonchain highlighted that the BALD deployer had earned $5.7 million in two days.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">The <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24BALD&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$BALD</a> deployer has removed all liquidity of BALD/ETH.</p>
<p>He bridged 9,385 <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24ETH&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$ETH</a> to <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Base?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Base</a>, and now he holds 12,433 <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24ETH&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$ETH</a>, earning 3,048 <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24ETH&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$ETH</a> ($5.7M) in 2 days.<a href="https://t.co/MghRrP9jw5">https://t.co/MghRrP9jw5</a> <a href="https://t.co/UgFi71mY5D">pic.twitter.com/UgFi71mY5D</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Lookonchain (@lookonchain) <a href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1686056439436161024?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 31, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/coinbase/">Coinbase</a> unveiled Base, an Ethereum layer 2 chain built on the OP stack in January and launched its testnet in February. The L2 blockchain went live for builders in July.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bald-price-nosedives-90-as-deployer-removes-liquidity/">BALD price nosedives 90% as deployer removes ETH liquidity</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tether’s excess reserves rose to $3.3B in Q2: report</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/tethers-excess-reserves-rose-to-3-3b-in-q2-report/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/tethers-excess-reserves-rose-to-3-3b-in-q2-report/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 17:05:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/tethers-excess-reserves-rose-to-3-3b-in-q2-report/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Tether&#8217;s excess reserves for the USDT stablecoin hit $3.3 billion in Q2. An attestation report for the quarter by BDO showed operational profits of over $1 billion. Tether&#8217;s consolidated liabilities was roughly $83.17 billion, while exposure to US Treasuries totaled $72.5 billion. Tether Holdings Limited, the company behind the USDT stablecoin, saw its reserve assets [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tethers-excess-reserves-rose-to-3-3b-in-q2-report/">Tether’s excess reserves rose to $3.3B in Q2: report</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Tether&rsquo;s excess reserves for the USDT stablecoin hit $3.3 billion in Q2.</li>
<li dir="ltr">An attestation report for the quarter by BDO showed operational profits of over $1 billion.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Tether&rsquo;s consolidated liabilities was roughly $83.17 billion, while exposure to US Treasuries totaled $72.5 billion.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Tether Holdings Limited, the company behind the USDT stablecoin, saw its reserve assets held in excess rise to $3.3 billion in Q2, 2023, according to an <a href="https://tether.to/en/tether-excess-reserves-increase-by-850m-to-reach-3-3b-as-leading-stablecoin-reveals-72-5b-overall-exposure-in-us-t-bills-and-unveils-energy-related-investments/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">attestation report</a> for the quarter released on Monday.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The stablecoin issuer&rsquo;s Consolidated Reserves Report (CRR) for the quarterly period ending June 30, 2023 was prepared by the accounting firm BDO. Per the assurance report, <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/tether/">Tether</a> saw its excess reserves increase by $850 million during the quarter to reach $3.3 billion.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As of 30 June 2023, Tether&rsquo;s consolidated total assets were $86,499,251,218, while consolidated total liabilities stood at $83,200,775,340. According to the company, $83,178,020,411 of this was related to the digital tokens it has issued.</p>
<p dir="ltr">With USDT the firm&rsquo;s largest token, total US Treasuries backing USDT by end of Q2 was $72.5 billion, details shared in the report showed.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>I am immensely proud of our most recent reserves attestation, reaffirming our unwavering commitment to transparency</em>,&rdquo; Tether CTO Paolo Ardoino said.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>Transparency is not just a buzzword for us; it is the cornerstone of our philosophy. We believe that open communication and strong financials foster trust and reliability, and this is what the global community deserves especially in a year devastated by many failures across the banking and crypto industry</em>.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Tether also revealed operational profits of over $1 billion for the quarter, signaling a 30% increase in operational profits QoQ. The impressive returns come after the company announced net profits of $1.45 billion in Q1, 2023.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tethers-excess-reserves-rose-to-3-3b-in-q2-report/">Tether’s excess reserves rose to $3.3B in Q2: report</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/tethers-excess-reserves-rose-to-3-3b-in-q2-report/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
