<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 19:30:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>JPMorgan CEO says Bitcoin is ‘a hyped-up fraud’</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/jpmorgan-ceo-says-bitcoin-is-a-hyped-up-fraud/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 19:30:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[JPMorgan]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/jpmorgan-ceo-says-bitcoin-is-a-hyped-up-fraud/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>JPMorgan CEO Jamie Dimon previously slammed Bitcoin as a &#8220;Ponzi scheme&#8221;. On Thursday, he told CNBC&#8217;s Squawk Box that crypto is a decentralised Ponzi scheme and that Bitcoin is just &#8220;hyped-up fraud.&#8221; Dimon says people have lost billions of dollars and believes regulators should have put a stop to crypto &#8220;a long time ago.&#8221; Not [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/jpmorgan-ceo-says-bitcoin-is-a-hyped-up-fraud/">JPMorgan CEO says Bitcoin is ‘a hyped-up fraud’</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>JPMorgan CEO Jamie Dimon previously slammed Bitcoin as a &ldquo;Ponzi scheme&rdquo;.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>On Thursday, he told CNBC&rsquo;s Squawk Box that crypto is a decentralised Ponzi scheme and that Bitcoin is just &ldquo;hyped-up fraud.&rdquo;</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><strong><em>Dimon says people have lost billions of dollars and believes regulators should have put a stop to crypto &ldquo;a long time ago.&rdquo;</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Not for the first time, JPMorgan CEO Jamie Dimon has labelled cryptocurrencies worthless.</p>
<p dir="ltr">On Thursday, during an <a href="https://twitter.com/SquawkCNBC/status/1616039056961323008" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">interview</a> with CNBC&rsquo;s &lsquo;Squawk Box,&rsquo; the noted crypto sceptic again referred to <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> as nothing but a &ldquo;<em>hyped-up fraud</em>.&rdquo; He condemned the benchmark crypto asset as a &ldquo;<em>pet rock</em>&rdquo;, expressing his disapproval by dismissing discussions over BTC and other cryptocurrencies as waste of time.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Dimon says crypto &lsquo;doesn&rsquo;t do anything&rsquo;</h2>
<p dir="ltr">According to the JPMorgan CEO Bitcoin is not a store of value, and he showed his scepticism further by suggesting that there could be more than 21 million bitcoins in the future.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>How do you know it is going to stop at 21 million? Maybe it&rsquo;s going to get to 21 million, and Satoshi&rsquo;s picture is going to come up and laugh at you all. And say ta-da</em>!&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Dimon also went ahead to refer to crypto as a decentralised Ponzi scheme. According to him the hype around digital assets has been extraordinary, stating on the CNBC show:</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>Y</em><em>ou guys, you&rsquo;ve all seen the analysis on Tether, the analysis on all these things &ndash; the lack of disclosures and it&rsquo;s outrageous. Regulators should have stopped all these a long time ago. People have lost billions of dollars. If you look at its low-income people, in some cases retirees</em>.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">On what he had to say about the crypto industry following the collapse of FTX, the JPMorgan exec summed up his outlook by noting that crypto &ldquo;doesn&rsquo;t do anything.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>It&rsquo;s a pet rock</em>,&rdquo; he told the Squawk Box hosts, adding that he doesn&rsquo;t care about Bitcoin.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/jpmorgan-ceo-says-bitcoin-is-a-hyped-up-fraud/">JPMorgan CEO says Bitcoin is ‘a hyped-up fraud’</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is attitude stopping crypto from becoming a common payment option?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/is-attitude-the-thing-stopping-crypto-from-becoming-a-common-payment-option/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 17:54:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto adoption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto payments]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/is-attitude-the-thing-stopping-crypto-from-becoming-a-common-payment-option/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrencies have been around for more than a decade, yet they still haven&#8217;t become a mainstream payment option. Advocates of cryptocurrency tout its advantages, such as its decentralization and rapid transaction speed, while detractors point to its volatility and lack of regulation.&#160; As much as crypto has grown, one factor that may be preventing cryptocurrencies [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/is-attitude-the-thing-stopping-crypto-from-becoming-a-common-payment-option/">Is attitude stopping crypto from becoming a common payment option?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://coinjournal.net/cryptocurrencies/">Cryptocurrencies</a> have been around for more than a decade, yet they still haven&rsquo;t become a mainstream payment option. Advocates of cryptocurrency tout its advantages, such as its decentralization and rapid transaction speed, while detractors point to its volatility and lack of regulation.&nbsp;</p>
<p>As much as crypto has grown, one factor that may be preventing cryptocurrencies from becoming a common payment option is attitude: both businesses and consumers are reluctant to embrace this new payment method. Despite its potential, many people still view cryptocurrencies with skepticism and fear, and this attitude is standing in the way of crypto becoming a mainstream payment option.&nbsp;</p>
<p>To truly make crypto a common payment option, attitudes must shift. People must recognize the potential of crypto and become comfortable with making transactions with it.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Let&rsquo;s take a look at why this is, and how it can be solved.&nbsp;</p>
<h2>Attitude is everything</h2>
<p>To make cryptocurrency a mainstream payment option, people must change the way they think about it.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Cryptocurrency has the potential to transform the world and the economy, but people must recognize this. They must get over the fear of the unknown and embrace the advantages of this new payment method. If people are not willing to give cryptocurrency a chance, then it will not become a common payment option.</p>
<h2>Businesses&rsquo; reluctance to accept cryptocurrency</h2>
<p>One major barrier to cryptocurrency becoming a mainstream payment option is the hesitancy of businesses to accept it. Many companies, such as airlines, hotels and car rental agencies, accept multiple payment methods, but very few accept cryptocurrencies.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Some businesses are unwilling to accept cryptocurrency due to the high volatility of the market. They worry that accepting Bitcoin or another cryptocurrency could lead to losses if the value of the cryptocurrency were to plunge during the transaction.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In some cases, businesses may simply be unaware that they can accept cryptocurrency, or they may be unsure of how to accept and <a href="https://coinjournal.net/compare/best-cryptocurrency-wallets/">safely store it</a>. This problem also discourages some consumers from making cryptocurrency investments.</p>
<h2>Consumers&rsquo; reluctance to use cryptocurrency</h2>
<p>People may also be hesitant to use cryptocurrency because they are unfamiliar with it or are worried about the security of the transaction. Consumers may not know how to use a cryptocurrency wallet or find it difficult and confusing to buy, sell or store cryptocurrency. They may also be worried about the security of cryptocurrency transactions, given the prevalence of cryptocurrency hacking and scams.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Additionally, consumers may be concerned about the legitimacy of cryptocurrencies, given that many are unregulated.&nbsp;</p>
<p>There has not been a lack of demand from investors and advocates over the past several years, as the market has grown exponentially. The problems lie in people&rsquo;s mindset.</p>
<p>Cryptocurrency fuses a tangible real-world asset (cash) with the digital world, and this concerns some users who prefer to see their money in-hand or at least in-bank, backed by standard fiat systems.</p>
<p>We have witnessed the fusion of the digital world and reality, and young people have no issues with using AR in games. The rising popularity of <a href="https://www.skycitycasino.com/games/live-casino-games" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">live casino games</a> compared to their fully-digital alternatives suggests that we inherently have a desire to see the digital and real worlds collide. These games incorporate benefits of digital gameplay &ndash; convenience, ease of access, speed &ndash; with the reality of a real-world roulette wheel or blackjack dealer.</p>
<p>While most online systems are thoroughly vetted, we inherently place more faith in these live-streamed casino games &ndash; we can see the tangible results! It&rsquo;s this portion of the process we&rsquo;re trying to move past &ndash; because digital is not inherently less trustworthy than tangible, whether in gambling, or finance.</p>
<p>In fact, <a href="https://coinjournal.net/casinos/">online casinos</a> and gambling on the internet have become far more popular recently, with people playing daily from all over the world. This is a strong indicator that people enjoy using their money in the digital space, whether that&rsquo;s playing games or even shopping.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The impetus is there, the desire is there, but how do we get things moving toward crypto being accepted widely?&nbsp;</p>
<h2>Steps needed to make crypto a mainstream payment option</h2>
<p>First, businesses must accept cryptocurrencies as payment. This will likely occur gradually as previously hesitant business owners become more familiar with the process of accepting cryptocurrencies and see their customers&rsquo; willingness to use this option. <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ilkerkoksal/2019/08/23/the-rise-of-crypto-as-payment-currency/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">In some areas, this has already begun</a>.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Next, consumers must be willing to use cryptocurrencies as payment. When businesses begin accepting cryptocurrencies, consumers will likely see this as an opportunity to save money by paying with crypto instead of another payment method.</p>
<p>These two things could help to balance out some of the volatility associated with cryptocurrency.&nbsp;</p>
<h2>Education on cryptocurrency</h2>
<p>Lastly, people must be educated on cryptocurrencies. Most are at least slightly familiar with the concept of <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/buy/">investing in Bitcoin</a>, but maybe not a lot other than that. They need to understand the basics of what cryptocurrencies are, how they work and the advantages they offer. This also includes knowing about the various types of cryptocurrencies and how each one works.&nbsp;</p>
<p>People must also be educated on how to safely store their cryptocurrency, including the importance of using a safe and secure wallet.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Finally, people must be educated about how to use cryptocurrency for transactions, as well as the tax implications of using it. With this level of education, people will be more likely to make and accept cryptocurrency payments, and cryptocurrency will transition to become a mainstream payment option.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/is-attitude-the-thing-stopping-crypto-from-becoming-a-common-payment-option/">Is attitude stopping crypto from becoming a common payment option?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Fintech Activities Are Transformed By Effortless Cross-Border Payments?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/how-fintech-activities-are-transformed-by-effortless-cross-border-payments/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 17:19:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto payments]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/how-fintech-activities-are-transformed-by-effortless-cross-border-payments/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>There are changes in technology and cross-border payment systems As adoption grows, cryptocurrency and DeFi transactions are proving triumphant We list the three key trends of cross-border payments in 2023 Soon, international money transfers will work just like any other fintech product, including internet banking or embedded finances. Needs relating to the efficacy of the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/how-fintech-activities-are-transformed-by-effortless-cross-border-payments/">How Fintech Activities Are Transformed By Effortless Cross-Border Payments?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>There are changes in technology and cross-border payment systems</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>As adoption grows, cryptocurrency and DeFi transactions are proving triumphant</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><strong><em>We list the three key trends of cross-border payments in 2023</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Soon, international money transfers will work just like any other fintech product, including internet banking or embedded finances.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Needs relating to the efficacy of the finance sector are evolving in tandem with changes in consumer behavior. Because of this, business-to-business (B2B) financing is under even more pressure as suppliers and retailers shift toward more simplified processes.</p>
<p>However, international legislation controlling and safeguarding financial transactions add complexity to B2B deals, especially those requiring cross-border adaptability. The difficulties are immense, especially in such a dynamic and evolving field as finance, where the need for quick and flexible transactions is of the utmost importance.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Changes in technology and cross-border payment systems</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Although it&rsquo;s no easy task, technology and inventors are making progress to streamline this complex area. According to industry experts, the contemporary market is being driven by a large number of dynamic businesses. For them, the most intriguing innovations occurring in this field now are at the junction of embedded financing and public banking.</p>
<p>According to experts, it may be quite difficult for retailers to handle payments when operating on a global scale. If a business issues an invoice in a denomination other than the client&rsquo;s, the client is typically subject to a foreign transaction fee and uncompetitive interest rates. Long settlement periods can delay delivering products and services to the consumer.</p>
<p>In addition, they state that improved communication and collaboration across fin-serve providers is the result of a deeper appreciation for, and more thorough incorporation of, cross-border transactions within online banking and embedded financing.</p>
<p>The elimination of swipe fees, long settling delays, and the possibility of credit fraud are all advantages of open banking transactions, which allow for the rapid transfer of funds from one bank to the other. SWIFT is being used to enable global open banking exchanges.</p>
<p>However, this is a costly and time-consuming procedure right now, therefore cross-border transaction fintechs require financial institutions and authorities throughout Europe to act swiftly to meet the need for more affordable global financing options.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How open banking paves the door for smooth cross-border payments?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Despite the difficulty of resolving these issues, integrated open banking and prediction model are allowing PSPs and retailers to get accessibility to the complete transactions environment via a specific point of integration. With the use of integrated financing, open banking systems like Yapily allow companies to accept local payments, execute low-cost foreign currency interchange, provide rapid reimbursements and chargebacks, and simplify bookkeeping.</p>
<p>Advantages include &ldquo;enabling firms to spend more efforts on growing abroad while reducing their costs and time as a result of increased transparency into payment details, flexibility over the allocation and movement of cash, and lower expenses associated with receiving and transmitting cross-border payments.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Reasons why cryptocurrency and international DeFi transactions are triumphant</h2>
<p dir="ltr">In the meanwhile, <a href="https://coinjournal.net/cryptocurrencies/">cryptocurrencies</a> have become more popular in international transactions since they are not subject to the same stringent regulatory regulations as fiat currency. And in this approach cryptocurrency marketplaces like <a href="https://the-bitcoin-traders-app.com" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Bitcoin trader</a> have played a vital role as a middleman. Cryptocurrency transactions conducted on the blockchain at present allow buyers and sellers to do business with a heightened degree of anonymity and independence from governmental intervention.</p>
<p>Even while <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/defi/">DeFi</a> is expected to become more ubiquitous in the future decade, many nations still do not permit crypto transactions, which limits its usefulness. With the crypto market mostly unscathed by outside forces, it has become a viable choice for international transactions. Crypto&rsquo;s versatility means it is not as much influenced by nation or region-based financial landscapes. Cryptocurrencies, like Bitcoin, have value swings, but they are more resistant to environmental factors.</p>
<p>As readily movable assets that transcend national currency regulatory limitations, digital currencies have become more popular in the foreign transactions market amid widespread economic uncertainty.</p>
<p>While Europe&rsquo;s economic woes continue, firms in regions seeing rapid development in e-commerce may enjoy the benefits of using worldwide online payments to expand their operations. Those looking to shop online without utilizing funds held in conventional bank accounts may find increasing support for alt-fi businesses as the number of retailers accepting these methods of payment grows.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">China&rsquo;s cross-border payments</h2>
<p dir="ltr">China, the globe&rsquo;s largest provider of products and commodities, has created its metrics to evaluate that assist commerce while also being mindful of anti-money laundering and safety protocols.</p>
<p>Fintech legislation in China may be broken down into two main categories. There are two major regulatory bodies in China: the PBoC and the CAC), respectively, which oversee issues related to information security and information confidentiality. As a general rule, China allows new regions to establish a marketplace and services with little interference from the government. Once the situation is understood, the regulator introduces rules that are consistent with the overarching goals of regulators everywhere.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">The three trends of cross-border payments to watch in 2023</h2>
<p dir="ltr">In 2023, the international payments industry will be shaken up by three major developments. To stay competitive, financial technology banks and businesses will need to provide businesses and suppliers with convenient, low-cost, and safe cross-border transaction solutions. However, to achieve this, they will be required to deal with:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Different payment methodologies: These would comprise quicker, better efficient, and adaptable transactions that appeal to multiple exchange rates including cryptocurrencies. Kiat-Seng Lim says: &ldquo;<em>To compete effectively, organizations must use technology that facilitates quicker transactions, reduced rates, and improved visibility to render them proficient in the arena of cross-border payments</em>.&rdquo;</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Cutting-edge tech: The software and hardware landscape is shifting due to the prevalence of APIs and the rapid development of new technologies. More openness, efficiency, and visibility are needed in international financial transactions.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Risk: As the sector becomes increasingly more digital, the hazards mount with regard to theft, financial fraud, and cyberattacks. To gain consumers&rsquo; confidence, service providers should use the most stringent security measures available.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p>Because it shores up weak spots, the procedure makes the company climate and the user&rsquo;s experience more secure by improving things like macroeconomic stability, data protection, and confidentiality.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">In conclusion</h2>
<p dir="ltr">In 2023, the fintech industry will likely witness an increase in the number of agreements and collaborations formed by the many companies and organizations that provide innovative solutions. As a result, companies may offer their clients novel and interesting open banking usage cases, reduce unnecessary hassles, and open up fresh avenues for expansion.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/how-fintech-activities-are-transformed-by-effortless-cross-border-payments/">How Fintech Activities Are Transformed By Effortless Cross-Border Payments?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Financial expansion driven by cryptocurrency and blockchain adoption in 2023</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/financial-expansion-driven-by-cryptocurrency-and-blockchain-adoption-in-2023/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 16:45:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto adoption]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/financial-expansion-driven-by-cryptocurrency-and-blockchain-adoption-in-2023/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Understand how blockchain technology and cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin work and how they affect financial innovation. Consumer interest in crypto and blockchain, and the digital transactions revolution, are driving financial expansion. What are the benefits of using cryptocurrencies and how will these drive financial expansion in 2023. Recent years have seen widespread media coverage of blockchain-based [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/financial-expansion-driven-by-cryptocurrency-and-blockchain-adoption-in-2023/">Financial expansion driven by cryptocurrency and blockchain adoption in 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>Understand how blockchain technology and cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin work and how they affect financial innovation.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>Consumer interest in crypto and blockchain, and the digital transactions revolution, are driving financial expansion.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><strong><em>What are the benefits of using cryptocurrencies and how will these drive financial expansion in 2023.</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Recent years have seen widespread media coverage of blockchain-based <a href="https://coinjournal.net/cryptocurrencies/">cryptocurrencies</a> like <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a>, Ethereum, and Stellar, making it impossible to ignore their impact on the average person. How does the widespread use of cryptocurrencies and blockchain technology affect online businesses, if at all?</p>
<p dir="ltr">Understanding bitcoin, how it works with the public blockchain, and how these new technologies are expected to affect e-commerce businesses is important as the fight to make cryptos a viable alternative to traditional finance continues.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">In the same manner that online billing channels facilitated e-commerce, and that PayPal as well as other third-party billing distributors ventured in to offer substitute funding choices, the e-commerce sector should now consider the advent of virtual currency and the implications of accepting this mode of payment.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The blockchain is the open, decentralized database it contains that keeps track of all cryptocurrency activities. When e-commerce businesses use blockchains, they get a number of benefits, such as better data security, streamlined operations, and lower costs.</p>
<p dir="ltr">There has been a rise in the number of merchants accepting Bitcoin as payment for products and services as the cryptocurrency craze has spread. As this shift takes place, the significance of Bitcoin and the blockchain to the world of online trade cannot be denied. E-commerce companies may greatly benefit from foresight into the potential outcomes of this technology.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Let&rsquo;s start with some background on blockchain technology and cryptocurrency and how they could affect and be used by an online retailer.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Recognizing blockchain technology and cryptocurrencies</h2>
<p dir="ltr">If you want to buy anything online, you could use cryptocurrency. Unlike government-issued money, the value of this commodity is based on the native blockchain. Due to the decentralized nature of cryptos and the fact that laws are gradually being implemented, the once wildly fluctuating cryptocurrency markets have become somewhat more stable.</p>
<p dir="ltr">A distributed online ledger equipped with robust encryption is used to protect business dealings conducted online.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Most distributed ledger technologies (DLTs) employ blockchain, although there are others. Blockchain is an innovative technological framework, not a language or a program. It&rsquo;s an immutable digital ledger that keeps track of all the money that changes hands in a certain area. Users can safely trade and keep virtual commodities like bitcoins. Payments done using cryptocurrencies are made practical and secure in this way.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Consumers&rsquo; increasing interest in cryptocurrencies&nbsp;</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin may have been the initial cryptocurrency, but today there are more than 4,000 others you can buy. Many people now use the name &ldquo;Bitcoin&rdquo; interchangeably with &ldquo;cryptocurrency&rdquo; or &ldquo;digital currency.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin&rsquo;s limited supply is one of its main selling points. Bitcoin, like gold, is a scarce commodity. Many speculate that Nakamoto deliberately set out to create an inflation-proof digital currency with Bitcoin.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin are not, therefore, the exclusive finite-supply option. The number of Litecoins, Stellar Lumens, and IOTA currencies in circulation is also finite.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Cryptocurrency is used by customers in every region of the globe, while its acceptance varies widely by region. This phenomenon is compatible with economies that rely heavily on mobile shopping yet have limited access to conventional banking infrastructure. It makes sense that e-commerce merchants that embrace cryptocurrencies as a means of payment may find success in expanding their reach into previously untapped markets.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Digital money transactions</h2>
<p dir="ltr">More and more businesses are starting to accept bitcoin as payment as public confidence in cryptocurrencies grows.</p>
<p dir="ltr">When the Xbox online shop started accepting Bitcoin, Microsoft became one of the earliest major firms to do so. Overstock.com, one of the most well-known US e-commerce sites, now accepts cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Some of the earliest businesses ever to accept cryptocurrencies were based in Great Britain, and that includes Shopify, Etsy, and even the cosmetics brand Lush. Despite recently proposing the development of its unique proprietary currency, Amazon has yet to accept cryptos as payments.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Explaining the process of crypto payment processing to retailers&nbsp;</h2>
<p dir="ltr">However, despite its futuristic appearance, Bitcoin is very genuine and easy to adopt as a payment alternative for online merchants. It&rsquo;s possible that Bitcoin would be added to the payment methods that most online stores already use.</p>
<p dir="ltr">It is now easy to anyone to <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/buy/">buy Bitcoin</a>, and for businesses and online stores, the easiest way to start taking cryptocurrency payments is through a bitcoin payment system.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Every item&rsquo;s listed cost in fiat currency is automatically translated to its equivalent in cryptocurrency whenever a customer chooses cryptocurrency as their payment option. The transfer is then processed securely by a payment system in the same way that any other transaction would be, except that it is saved on the blockchain.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This implies that the record of the monetary exchange will exist in the ledger forever and can&rsquo;t be changed. Merchants and customers alike might benefit from this if they wish to maintain track of transactions over the long haul without keeping paper receipts.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Online merchants that want to accept cryptocurrency and blockchain payments will likely need to switch to a payment processor that supports these alternative monies. In addition, there are always options for buying cryptocurrency, such as the <a href="https://bitcoineranew.com" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Bitcoin Era</a>. When choosing a payment gateway, e-commerce retailers should check to see whether it is interoperable with the CMS they employ.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Perks of accepting cryptocurrencies</h2>
<p dir="ltr">There are several benefits to allowing bitcoin payments in online stores. Here are the four most significant advantages:</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">A cryptocurrency transaction cannot be reversed.</h3>
<p dir="ltr">Transactions made using cryptocurrencies are immune to refunds. Since refunds are costly (both financially and in terms of the risk they pose to a merchant&rsquo;s account) and time-consuming (both to resolve and prevent), this is good news for online stores. There is no way to undo a payment after it has been processed since it will be recorded on the blockchain.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Minimal costs are attached to crypto transactions.</h3>
<p dir="ltr">As unbelievable as it may seem, certain cryptocurrencies have very low processing costs. In terms of transaction costs, XLM is the most cost-effective cryptocurrency. There will be more customers willing to use your services once they know you accept cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p dir="ltr">People are looking for methods to spend the cryptocurrency they extracted or the income they made from trading in virtual money as its demand grows. Companies that accept cryptocurrency payments will benefit from this rapidly expanding industry.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Clients might be attracted to your business more easily if you accept cryptocurrency payments. The ability to pay with Bitcoin and other digital currencies has piqued the interest of many customers, who are more likely to patronize a store that accepts this payment method.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Final thoughts</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The blockchain, as was previously said, is an immutable digital ledger that stores financial transactions in an immutable manner. Cryptocurrencies may be transferred and stored safely thanks to blockchain technology. Each successful payment triggers the publication of a new block on the blockchain.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The blockchain links records together to build a chain of transactions. A transaction on the blockchain is created whenever a client makes a cryptocurrency payment. The cryptographic information will be checked against a database to ensure it has never been used before. Since the network keeps track of each activity on the blockchain, the information stored there cannot be erased, changed, or damaged.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/financial-expansion-driven-by-cryptocurrency-and-blockchain-adoption-in-2023/">Financial expansion driven by cryptocurrency and blockchain adoption in 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Koinos announces $500K seed round led by Blockchain Founders Fund</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/koinos-announces-500k-seed-round-led-by-blockchain-founders-fund/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/koinos-announces-500k-seed-round-led-by-blockchain-founders-fund/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 16:09:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/koinos-announces-500k-seed-round-led-by-blockchain-founders-fund/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Koinos is a free-to-use blockchain developed by a group that also helped create the Steem blockchain. The Koinos Group said the Blockchain Founders Fund led the seed round, with blockchain gaming platform Splinterlands participating. Koinos will use the funds to build Koinos Pro, a software product set to help developers build scalable decentralised applications. In [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/koinos-announces-500k-seed-round-led-by-blockchain-founders-fund/">Koinos announces $500K seed round led by Blockchain Founders Fund</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>Koinos is a free-to-use blockchain developed by a group that also helped create the Steem blockchain.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>The Koinos Group said the Blockchain Founders Fund led the seed round, with blockchain gaming platform Splinterlands participating.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><strong><em>Koinos will use the funds to build Koinos Pro, a software product set to help developers build scalable decentralised applications.</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">In the latest <a href="https://coinjournal.net/">cryptocurrency news</a>, Koinos Group, the developer of the free-to-use blockchain Koinos, has announced a $500,000 seed round.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Blockchain Founders Fund leads Koinos seed round</h2>
<p dir="ltr">According to a <a href="https://pr.slicedbrand.com/koinos/investment" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">press release</a> <em>CoinJourna</em>l obtained on Thursday, Singapore-based early stage industry-focused venture fund the Blockchain Founders Fund led the seed round. The round also saw the participation of blockchain gaming firm Splinterlands.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>Blockchain Founders Fund is demonstrating leadership in the space as a whole by committing funds to a company whose entire business model is based on supporting a truly decentralised platform,as opposed to a platform that is decentralised in name alone</em>,&rdquo;said &nbsp;Koinos Group CEO Andrew Levine.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Koinos Group will use the funds to develop Koinos Pro, a subscription product that allows developers to release highly scalable decentralised applications (<a href="https://coinjournal.net/glossary/decentralized-applications-dapps/">dApps</a>). In a <a href="https://twitter.com/TheKoinosGroup/status/1616087547146289153" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">tweet</a> on Thursday, the platform said Koinos Pro is a software that will help completely remove entry barriers to the dApps ecosystem.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">We are excited to announce the close of a $500k seed round which included investments from <a href="https://twitter.com/BlockchainFF?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@BlockchainFF</a> and <a href="https://twitter.com/splinterlands?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@splinterlands</a>. This will allow us to build <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/KoinosPRO?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#KoinosPRO</a>; software for empowering developers to build dApps with NO BARRIERS TO ENTRY! <a href="https://t.co/tWzmL4A93D">https://t.co/tWzmL4A93D</a></p>
<p>&mdash; KoinosGroup &#128302; (@TheKoinosGroup) <a href="https://twitter.com/TheKoinosGroup/status/1616087547146289153?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 19, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">Already, the Koinos blockchain allows developers to build and launch free-to-use dApps in any programming language, which means users can access high-performance apps as easily as is currently within the Web2 ecosystem.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Founded in 2020, the Koinos Group is a project overseen by several blockchain veterans &ndash; including a core developer group of the Steem blockchain.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The funding round comes just over two months after the Koinos mainnet went live, notably without involving an initial coin offering (ICO), pre-mine or airdrop to insiders and such. Koinos&rsquo; &ldquo;Mana&rdquo; system enables people without the native KOIN token to still access the blockchain.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/koinos-announces-500k-seed-round-led-by-blockchain-founders-fund/">Koinos announces $500K seed round led by Blockchain Founders Fund</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/koinos-announces-500k-seed-round-led-by-blockchain-founders-fund/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>=nil; Foundation raises $22M for zero knowledge proofs marketplace</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/nil-foundation-raises-22m-for-zero-knowledge-proofs-marketplace/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/nil-foundation-raises-22m-for-zero-knowledge-proofs-marketplace/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 15:13:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/nil-foundation-raises-22m-for-zero-knowledge-proofs-marketplace/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>=nil; Foundation has raised $22 million in a funding round led by Polychain Capital. The firm will use funds to build a zero-knowledge proofs marketplace for Ethereum and L2s. Apart from improving security and scalability, blockchains using =nil;&#8217;s Proof Market will not need centralised intermediaries &#160;=nil; Foundation, the zero-knowledge proofs research and development platform looking [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/nil-foundation-raises-22m-for-zero-knowledge-proofs-marketplace/">=nil; Foundation raises $22M for zero knowledge proofs marketplace</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>=nil; Foundation has raised $22 million in a funding round led by Polychain Capital.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>The firm will use funds to build a zero-knowledge proofs marketplace for Ethereum and L2s.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><strong><em>Apart from improving security and scalability, blockchains using =nil;&rsquo;s Proof Market will not need centralised intermediaries</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">&nbsp;=nil; Foundation, the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/glossary/zero-knowledge-proof/">zero-knowledge proofs</a> research and development platform looking to build a proofs marketplace for Ethereum and L2s, has secured $22 million in a funding round that valued the firm at $220 million.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Polychain Capital led the funding round, with participation from top blockchain-focused venture firms including Blockchain Capital, Starkware, and Mina Protocol. The investment also attracted several angel investors, including Hasu.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">A Proof Market for Ethereum and other public blockchains</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The nil; Foundation, launched in 2018, will use the funds from the fundraise to boost the development of its zero-knowledge (ZK) Proof Market protocol, according to details shared via a press release on Thursday. Per the company, the funding will go into building solutions aimed at improving the security and scalability of Ethereum, other L1 blockchains and L2s.</p>
<p dir="ltr">A Proof Market will help provide industry players with a trustless and seamless protocol for sharing zk-proofs without having to rely on centralised intermediaries, the nil; Foundation noted in the announcement.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>Proof Market is now ready to ensure secure data transfer between Ethereum and public protocols, but that&rsquo;s not the only thing that our team is aiming at</em>,&rdquo; Konstantin Lomashuk, co-founder of =nil; Foundation, said in a statement obtained by <em>CoinJournal</em>. He added:</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>As the ecosystem grows, computations are getting heavier and more complex, thus posing a roadblock for effective and trustless interaction between Ethereum, L2s and other protocols. Creating a marketplace for computational powers that can prove any information will open new opportunities for the whole market, keeping it aligned with core blockchain principles</em>,&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to the nil; Foundation team, the market already has state proofs for Solana and Mina, while the same should be available on more blockchains soon. Industry players can now use the generated proofs to secure data exchange across Ethereum.</p>
<p dir="ltr">But a fully-fledged Proof Market will work as a zk-proof marketplace, allowing for further accessibility to proofs as blockchains eye more security and scalability.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/nil-foundation-raises-22m-for-zero-knowledge-proofs-marketplace/">=nil; Foundation raises $22M for zero knowledge proofs marketplace</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/nil-foundation-raises-22m-for-zero-knowledge-proofs-marketplace/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum price retreats as the put/call ratio edges upwards</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-price-retreats-as-the-put-call-ratio-edges-upwards/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-price-retreats-as-the-put-call-ratio-edges-upwards/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 12:44:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-price-retreats-as-the-put-call-ratio-edges-upwards/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum put and call ratio on Deribit has risen this week. ETH bullish liquidations have also jumped in the past 2 days. The spectacular crypto comeback has stalled following a series of weak corporate earnings from the United Stats.&#160;Ethereum pulled back to $1,500 on Thursday as data showed that the put/call ratio was heading higher. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-price-retreats-as-the-put-call-ratio-edges-upwards/">Ethereum price retreats as the put/call ratio edges upwards</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Ethereum put and call ratio on Deribit has risen this week.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">ETH bullish liquidations have also jumped in the past 2 days.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">The spectacular crypto comeback has stalled following a series of weak corporate earnings from the United Stats.&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/"><u>Ethereum</u></a> pulled back to $1,500 on Thursday as data showed that the put/call ratio was heading higher. It has fallen by over 5.90% from the highest point this year.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Put and call ratio slips</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The options market is an important one across all asset classes, including cryptocurrencies, stocks, and commodities. It involves placing put-and-call trades on an asset. A call gives the trader the right to buy an asset while a put gives them the right to sell.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The put to call ratio is an essential tool that traders and investors use to predict whether an asset will rise or not. That is why it is an important part of the fear and greed index.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Data compiled by The Block shows that Ethereum&rsquo;s put/call ratio has <a href="https://www.theblock.co/data/crypto-markets/options/open-interest-put-call-ratio"><u>edged</u></a> upward slightly in the past few days. It has risen from 0.24 on January 4 to a high of 0.3. Historically, a lower ratio is usually preferred since it means that there are more buyers in the options market. Still, it should be noted that The Block&rsquo;s data comes only from Deribit and does not include other exchanges.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Meanwhile, another data by CoinGlass shows that the<a href="https://www.coinglass.com/LiquidationData"><u>&nbsp;number</u></a> of short liquidations in key exchanges rose to the highest point in months on January 15. Liquidations have continued but at a slower pace since then. However, at the same time, long liquidations have been rising. On Wednesday, they rose to the highest level since December 16 of last year.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/00/19/1674132244388-4a4fd869-2f4e-44e0-a28d-e251e78ed922.jpg" style="width: 601px;height: 184.177px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="601" height="184.177"></p>
<p dir="ltr">The main reasons for these liquidations is the weak financial results by companies like Goldman Sachs and JP Morgan. Some of these firms have warned about a recession and announced significant job cuts. Microsoft is laying off over 10,000 people.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Ethereum price forecast</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/00/19/1674129133687-fc517a5c-07fa-414d-a636-9298c20249fb.png" style="width: 631px;height: 298.673px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="631" height="298.673"></p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ETHUSD/?exchange=COINBASE">ETH/USD chart by TradingView</a></p>
<p dir="ltr">Ethereum has stumbled as put and call ratio and long liquidations rise. This stumbling happened as the coin reached a high of $1,612, the highest point since November. It has moved slightly below the descending trendline shown in purple.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">At the same time, it has struggled moving above the key point at $1,667, the highest point on November 4. Therefore, I still believe that the outlook for Ethereum is still bullish, with the next key point to watch being at $2,000 as I wrote in this&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-price-targets-2k-as-fear-and-greed-soars/"><u>article</u></a>.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy Ethereum</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>

    <p>eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=OTk3OTM&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=IA&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy ETH with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    Binance</h3>

    <p>Binance is one of the largest cryptocurrency exchanges in the world. It is better suited to more experienced investors and it offers a large number of cryptocurrencies to choose from, at over 600.

Binance is also known for having low trading fees and a multiple of trading options that its users can benefit from, such as; peer-to-peer trading, margin trading and spot trading.
</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/binance-crypto?guid=OTk3OTM&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=IA&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy ETH with Binance today            </a>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-price-retreats-as-the-put-call-ratio-edges-upwards/">Ethereum price retreats as the put/call ratio edges upwards</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-price-retreats-as-the-put-call-ratio-edges-upwards/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Enjin Coin price pumps as ENJ short liqudations soars</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/enjin-coin-price-pumps-as-enj-short-liqudations-soars/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/enjin-coin-price-pumps-as-enj-short-liqudations-soars/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 11:54:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Enjin Coin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/enjin-coin-price-pumps-as-enj-short-liqudations-soars/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Enjin Coin has made a strong comeback in 2023. This rally happened as short liquidations jumped. Metaverse tokens like Decentraland and Sandbox have also surged. Enjin Coin (ENJ) has been in an unstoppable bull run in 2023. It has jumped in all but two days this year, making it one of the top-performing coins. According [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/enjin-coin-price-pumps-as-enj-short-liqudations-soars/">Enjin Coin price pumps as ENJ short liqudations soars</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Enjin Coin has made a strong comeback in 2023.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">This rally happened as short liquidations jumped.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Metaverse tokens like Decentraland and Sandbox have also surged.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/enjin/what-is-enjin/"><u>Enjin Coin</u></a> (ENJ) has been in an unstoppable bull run in 2023. It has jumped in all but two days this year, making it one of the top-performing coins. According to CoinDesk, ENJ was trading at $0.47, which was the highest it has been since November 10 of this year. Here are several reasons why Enjin is soaring.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Short liquidations rise</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The first main reason why Enjin is soaring is that short liquidations have jumped to the highest level in months. Data provided by CoinGlass&nbsp;<a href="https://www.coinglass.com/LiquidationData"><u>shows</u></a> that over $539k worth of short sales were liquidated on Thursday. This was an increase from the $257k short sales that were liquidated on Wednesday.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">As shown below, these liquidations have been moving in an upward trajectory starting from the first week of the year. This trend is mostly because of the ongoing macro issues as inflation started to drop. Data published in the past two weeks has shown that inflation remains under pressure. On Thursday, numbers revealed that the producer price index (PPI) dropped in December.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/00/19/1674129225202-0be4ffc6-c2e3-4b06-9fd2-f4cde9bab2c4.jpg" style="width: 612px;height: 228.48px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="612" height="228.48"></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Metaverse tokens soar</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The other main reason why Enjin coin price has risen is simply because of the performance of NFT and metaverse tokens. As we wrote&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/decentralands-mana-defies-gravity-to-jump-20-but-will-buyers-be-relentless/"><u>here</u></a><strong>,&nbsp;</strong>we have seen most well-known metaverse tokens like Decentraland&rsquo;s MANA and Sandbox&rsquo;s SAND rise to their highest levels in months. Historically, cryptocurrencies in similar industries tend to move in sync with each other.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Meanwhile, data compiled by CryptoSlam shows that the volume of NFT sales has started to creep back up in the past few weeks. This is notable since Enjin exists in the NFT industry. Its Efinity product makes it possible for people to mint and sell NFTs using&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/polkadot"><u>Polkadot&rsquo;s</u></a> technology.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What next for Enjin Coin</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/00/19/1674129133687-fc517a5c-07fa-414d-a636-9298c20249fb.png" style="width: 549px;height: 259.86px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="549" height="259.86"></p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ENJUSD/?exchange=BINANCE"><u>ENJ/USD chart by TradingView</u></a></p>
<p dir="ltr">Enjin Coin was one of the worst-performing crypto coins in 2022 as it transitioned into a fallen angel. It finally woke up in 2023, pushing it to the highest point since November. The coin has surged above all key resistance levels and moved above the 25-day moving average. Further, the closely-watched supertrend indicator is still bullish.</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, as shown in the chart above, some longs have started to liquidate their positions as well. This is a sign that the coin could start pulling back in the next few days. If this happens, the next point to focus on will be at $0.3822.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy Enjin Coin</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>

    <p>eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=OTk3ODk&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=IA&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy ENJ with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    Binance.US</h3>

    <p>Binance.US provides secure and reliable access to the world&rsquo;s most popular cryptocurrencies, with some of the lowest fees in the industry.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/binance-us-crypto?guid=OTk3ODk&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=IA&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy ENJ with Binance.US today            </a>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/enjin-coin-price-pumps-as-enj-short-liqudations-soars/">Enjin Coin price pumps as ENJ short liqudations soars</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/enjin-coin-price-pumps-as-enj-short-liqudations-soars/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Enjin Coin today&#8217;s top gainer: here&#8217;s why it is rising</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/enjin-coin-todays-top-gainer-heres-why-it-is-rising/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/enjin-coin-todays-top-gainer-heres-why-it-is-rising/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 10:32:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Enjin Coin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/enjin-coin-todays-top-gainer-heres-why-it-is-rising/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>At press time, Enjin Coin (ENJ) had gained 15.70% in the past 24 hours. ENJ is currently trading at about $0.4265. Today&#8217;s price surge makes ENJ today&#8217;s top gainer in the crypto market. Enjin Coin (ENJ) has made headlines today after it shot up by about 16% to become the best crypto gainer of the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/enjin-coin-todays-top-gainer-heres-why-it-is-rising/">Enjin Coin today&#8217;s top gainer: here&#8217;s why it is rising</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul class="decimal_type">
<li>At press time, Enjin Coin (ENJ) had gained 15.70% in the past 24 hours.</li>
<li>ENJ is currently trading at about $0.4265.</li>
<li>Today&rsquo;s price surge makes ENJ today&rsquo;s top gainer in the crypto market.</li>
</ul>
<p>Enjin Coin (ENJ) has made headlines today after it shot up by about 16% to become the best crypto gainer of the day according to <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/gainers-losers/">data from CoinMarketCap</a>. The second largest gainer today is KAVA which has gained 10.14% while the third is Hedera (HBAR) which has gained 9.50% adding to its 41% rise in the past two weeks.</p>
<p>While it was trading at $0.4265 at the time of writing, Enjin Coin price high a daily high of $0.4524 earlier today.</p>
<h2>Why is Enjin Coin price rising today?</h2>
<p>Enjin Coin is not known for colossal price movements, making today&rsquo;s price surge a surprise for many crypto traders and investors. Today&rsquo;s hike actually pushed the token for a 51% growth over the past seven days.</p>
<p>But why is the price of ENJ surging? Here is a deep dive into the behind-the-scenes pushing the token&rsquo;s price up.</p>
<p><a href="https://coinjournal.net/enjin/what-is-enjin/"></a><a href="https://coinjournal.net/enjin/what-is-enjin/">Enjin network</a>, the parent blockchain of Enjin Coin cryptocurrency, allows game developers to tokenize in-game items on the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/what-is-ethereum/">Ethereum blockchain</a>. While the protocol&rsquo;s influence among developers has grown since its inception, the recent development update to the platform appears to have energized ENJ buyers as they anticipate the Enjin ecosystem to witness extensive growth in the coming months.</p>
<p>The recent development update saw the protocol launch Enjin wallet, a new non-fungible (NFT) token marketplace called NFT.io, and three core Enjin tooling products. These updates make the platform enticing and easy for game developers thus positioning Enjin as a hub for the growing world of Web3.0 gaming.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/enjin-coin-todays-top-gainer-heres-why-it-is-rising/">Enjin Coin today&#8217;s top gainer: here&#8217;s why it is rising</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/enjin-coin-todays-top-gainer-heres-why-it-is-rising/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
