<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 09:18:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Fidelity Investments on Cusp of Filing Spot Bitcoin ETF with US SEC</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fidelity-spot-bitcoin-etf-us-sec/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fidelity-spot-bitcoin-etf-us-sec/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 09:18:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funds & ETFs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blackrock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fidelity investments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marathon digital]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[riot platforms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=260682</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fidelity-spot-bitcoin-etf-us-sec/">Fidelity Investments on Cusp of Filing Spot Bitcoin ETF with US SEC</a></p>
<p>Once the investment giant Fidelity files for a spot Bitcoin ETF with the US SEC, it will be the second time following the dismissal of the first one two years ago.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fidelity-spot-bitcoin-etf-us-sec/">Fidelity Investments on Cusp of Filing Spot Bitcoin ETF with US SEC</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fidelity-spot-bitcoin-etf-us-sec/">Fidelity Investments on Cusp of Filing Spot Bitcoin ETF with US SEC</a></p>
<p>The heightened Bitcoin demand by institutional investors has pushed asset investment firms to file for an exchange-traded fund (ETF) with the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>). Already <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/blackrock/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BlackRock Inc</a> (NYSE: BLK), Bitwise, Invesco, and WisdomTree have filed a Bitcoin ETF with the US SEC in order to expose their institutional customers to digital asset classes.  While the United States crypto firms wait for the judicial system to offer crypto regulatory clarity, financial firms like Fidelity Investments understand timing is the most important in the digital asset market.</p>
<p>Moreover, Fidelity Investments has a Bitcoin ETF up and running in Toronto, Canada dubbed Fidelity Advantage Bitcoin ETF with a ticker symbol FBTC. According to the latest market data, FBTC closed Tuesday trading at $13.56, up approximately 1.57 percent from the day’s opening price.</p>
<h2>Fidelity Investments Wants a US-Based Spot Bitcoin ETF</h2>
<p>According to a <a href="https://www.theblock.co/post/236588/fidelity-preparing-to-submit-spot-bitcoin-etf-filing-source" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a> by people familiar with the company’s plans, Fidelity is very close to filing a spot Bitcoin ETF with the United States SEC. The company could submit the request to the SEC as early as Tuesday. If the company makes the effort to file for a spot Bitcoin ETF soon, then it will be the second time that the company has made a similar move.</p>
<p>In March 2021, Fidelity Investments submitted a Bitcoin ETF filing with the United States SEC dubbed Wise Origin Bitcoin ETF. The filing was later rejected by the SEC and the current chair, Gary Gensler, argues that Bitcoin price is prone to heavy manipulation and lacks basic investor protection.</p>
<p>With Bitcoin being a globally traded digital asset, the United States SEC has little it can do to control the underlying value. Moreover, the difference between demand and supply significantly determines Bitcoin prices.</p>
<h2>Market Outlook</h2>
<p>The entrance of Fidelity Investments with more than $4.2 trillion in AUM into the crypto market is a clear indication the digital industry is on the cusp of mainstream adoption. According to a recent study conducted by Triple-A, there are at least 420 million crypto asset holders and users in the world right now with Asia accounting for the largest share.</p>
<p>The slow growth of the traditional stock market and the rising inflation has most asset managers seeking alternative risky investments. Moreover, the crypto market has enjoyed global liquidity and a four-year cycle of bullish sentiment.</p>
<p>Currently, Fidelity has a crypto industry digital payments ETF running in North America. Trading around $18.77 on Wednesday, the Fidelity crypto industry ETF tracks top crypto companies like <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase Global Inc</a> (NASDAQ: COIN), Riot Platforms Inc (NASDAQ: RIOT), and Marathon Digital Holdings Inc (NASDAQ: MARA).</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/judge-motions-dismiss-criminal-sbf/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fidelity-spot-bitcoin-etf-us-sec/">Fidelity Investments on Cusp of Filing Spot Bitcoin ETF with US SEC</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fidelity-spot-bitcoin-etf-us-sec/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Federal Judge Denies Pretrial Motions to Dismiss Criminal Charges against SBF Citing Lack of Merits</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/judge-motions-dismiss-criminal-sbf/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/judge-motions-dismiss-criminal-sbf/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 09:12:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alameda research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinex]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sam bankman-fried]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sbf]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=260680</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/judge-motions-dismiss-criminal-sbf/">Federal Judge Denies Pretrial Motions to Dismiss Criminal Charges against SBF Citing Lack of Merits</a></p>
<p>SBF will have to issue arguments beyond doubt to the judge and jury why he is not guilty of the charges levied against him.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/judge-motions-dismiss-criminal-sbf/">Federal Judge Denies Pretrial Motions to Dismiss Criminal Charges against SBF Citing Lack of Merits</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/judge-motions-dismiss-criminal-sbf/">Federal Judge Denies Pretrial Motions to Dismiss Criminal Charges against SBF Citing Lack of Merits</a></p>
<p>Former <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a> boss <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/sam-bankman-fried/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Sam Bankman-Fried</a> alias SBF who squandered over $8.7 billion of customers&#8217; digital assets with risky bets continues to fight for his innocence in a  New York federal court of law. In the latest updates, SBF has been denied all the requests to have the criminal charges filed against him dismissed before the trial session in early October this year. According to the SBF lawyers, the court ought to dismiss most of the charges &#8211; including fraud, bank fraud, operating an unlicensed money transmitter, bribery, and campaign finance charges &#8211; since the indictment does not allege any economic loss to the FTX customers.</p>
<p>However, Judge Lewis Kaplan, of the US District Court for the Southern District of New York, thinks the dismissal of the criminal charges lacks merit as it is only reserved for extreme circumstances. In the memorandum opinion, Judge Kaplan noted that SBF misappropriated the FTX customers&#8217; funds by issuing risky loans to sister firm Alameda Research.</p>
<p>“The Second Circuit has deemed dismissal an &#8216;extreme sanction&#8217; that has been upheld &#8216;only in very limited and extreme circumstances&#8217;, and should be &#8216;reserved for the truly extreme cases&#8217;, &#8216;especially where serious criminal conduct is involved&#8217;,” the judge <a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.nysd.590940/gov.uscourts.nysd.590940.167.0_3.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">indicated</a>.</p>
<p>With SBF accused of obscuring the real state of the company to financial institutions to obtain more funding, the Judge argued that the charges against him stand trial. Moreover, the Judge noted that the Bahamian judicial system knew of the charges even after approving the indictment request.</p>
<h2>SBF Faces Challenging Times Ahead</h2>
<p>The former crypto billionaire faces punitive jail time in the United States if the court finds him guilty of the charges filed against him. Notably, SBF lawyers will have a challenging time-fighting former allies &#8211; including Carolyn Ellison, the former CEO of Alameda Research, and Gary Wang, a co-founder of FTX &#8211; who have all pleaded guilty to the charges and agreed to work together with the United States prosecutors.</p>
<p>Notably, the United States prosecutors promised Ellison and Gary a reduction in their sentences if they agreed to fully cooperate in the FTX and SBF investigations.</p>
<p>Already, the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has shown its commitment to fighting crypto-related crimes. Additionally, New York Attorney General Letitia James has charged several crypto firms including CoinEX, and recovered millions of dollars from unregulated entries. According to AG Letitia, unregistered crypto platforms pose a significant risk to investors, consumers, and the economic fabric system.</p>
<p>As a result, SBF will have to issue arguments beyond doubt to the judge and jury why he is not guilty of the charges levied against him.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripio-license-exchange-spain/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/judge-motions-dismiss-criminal-sbf/">Federal Judge Denies Pretrial Motions to Dismiss Criminal Charges against SBF Citing Lack of Merits</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/judge-motions-dismiss-criminal-sbf/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Latin American Crypto Services Firm Ripio Receives License to Launch Exchange in Spain</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripio-license-exchange-spain/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripio-license-exchange-spain/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 08:55:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mercado libre]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[polygon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ripio]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[visa]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=260674</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripio-license-exchange-spain/">Latin American Crypto Services Firm Ripio Receives License to Launch Exchange in Spain</a></p>
<p>The Argentinian crypto company's license from Spanish authorities allows Ripio to add Spain to a growing list of countries where it operates.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripio-license-exchange-spain/">Latin American Crypto Services Firm Ripio Receives License to Launch Exchange in Spain</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripio-license-exchange-spain/">Latin American Crypto Services Firm Ripio Receives License to Launch Exchange in Spain</a></p>
<p>Ripio has obtained a license to operate as a digital asset exchange in Spain. According to an official announcement, the company now has approval to provide crypto exchange services and digital wallets to interested customers.</p>
<p>Ripio CEO Sebastian Serrano said in a <a href="https://twitter.com/sserrano44/status/1673698527938002947?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener">tweet</a> that the approval is a result of hard work from the team. With the license, Ripio has joined a few crypto companies officially greenlit to provide crypto services by the Bank of Spain. Other licensed firms include Crypto.com, BVNK, Bitpanda, and Bitstamp.</p>
<p>Ripio records transactions worth $200 million each month, across its 8 million users. In addition to Spain, the company operates in the United States, Mexico, Chile, Colombia, Uruguay, and Brazil.</p>
<h2>Ripio Expansion Outside of Spain</h2>
<p>Last August, Ripio <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripio-250k-prepaid-crypto-cards/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">launched</a> prepaid crypto cards for users in Brazil. The firm partnered with international payments giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/visa-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Visa</a> (NYSE: V) to launch the card with support for 28 cryptocurrencies. The card also offers users cashback rewards in crypto. At the time, Ripio said it would launch 250,000 cards before the year ran out.</p>
<p>As part of expansion plans, Ripio hopes to obtain an operating license in several Latin American countries before the end of 2023. The company has its sights on Paraguay, Bolivia, Ecuador, and Peru.</p>
<p>In March, Latin American e-commerce giant Mercado Libre (NASDAQ: MELI) <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/lmercado-libre-crypto-chile/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">launched</a> crypto support in collaboration with Ripio. Following the launch, users in Chile can save or trade Bitcoin (BTC) and Ether (ETH) from their Mercado Pago wallets. The feature also touts a low entry barrier, as users only need 50 Chilean pesos (about 6 cents) to begin trading. According to Mercado Libre president Osvaldo Gimenez, the company hopes to eliminate crypto access barriers by making app operations as simple as possible. This way, all interested persons, regardless of crypto knowledge or experience, can buy, sell, and save crypto.</p>
<p>In November last year, Ripio announced an expansion to the US. The company began operations after receiving a license from the Florida Office of Financial Regulation to offer users exchange and custodial wallet services. Ripio also announced business-to-business B2B integration plans with companies interested in crypto-powered solutions.</p>
<h2>Ripio’s B2B Blockchain</h2>
<p>Ripio <a href="https://polygon.technology/blog/ripio-comes-to-polygon-to-accelerate-blockchain-adoption-in-latin-america" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">partnered with Polygon</a> in February to support blockchain adoption in Latin America. The partnership between both companies allows Ripio to onboard its products on the Polygon network as it develops a B2B blockchain.</p>
<p>Serrano said the aim is to improve crypto, blockchain, and Web3 access. According to the CEO:</p>
<blockquote><p>“We are committed to our users and we seek every day to facilitate access to the crypto world for as many people and institutions as possible. We want to simplify access to Web3, which will undoubtedly be the future.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Headquartered in Argentina, Ripio raised $50 million in a 2021 funding round led by Digital Currency Group (DCG). Ripio said the funds were primarily for expanding into new countries. In addition to DCG, the funding round also received participation from popular Bitcoin investor Tim Draper and Mercado Libre CEO Marcos Galperin. Others were Globant CEO Martin Migoya and Robinhood investor Amplo.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/wise-stock-jumps-deposits/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripio-license-exchange-spain/">Latin American Crypto Services Firm Ripio Receives License to Launch Exchange in Spain</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripio-license-exchange-spain/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Wise Stock Jumps 18% on Customer Deposits and Higher Interest Rates</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wise-stock-jumps-deposits/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wise-stock-jumps-deposits/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 15:16:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FinTech News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bank of england]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[boe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fca]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wise]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[wise stock]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=260632</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/wise-stock-jumps-deposits/">Wise Stock Jumps 18% on Customer Deposits and Higher Interest Rates</a></p>
<p>Despite a few headwinds Wise has recently faced, the company's stock jumped after revealing a spike in profits and revenue.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/wise-stock-jumps-deposits/">Wise Stock Jumps 18% on Customer Deposits and Higher Interest Rates</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/wise-stock-jumps-deposits/">Wise Stock Jumps 18% on Customer Deposits and Higher Interest Rates</a></p>
<p>British fintech online money transfer firm <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/transferwise/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Wise</a>’s (LON: WISE) stock jumped almost 18% on Tuesday in reaction to a rise in company profits. In a recent statement, the London-based fintech noted that its profit before tax tripled to £146.5 million ($186.5 million). The company also reported that its earnings per share tripled to 11.53 pence.</p>
<p>According to data from MarketWatch, Wise stock has gained 6.58% in the last five days and 16.64% in a month. Since January, WISE rose 11.09%, and a whopping 97.6% in the past year. As of 1:49 pm BST, WISE was trading at £624.40 after climbing nearly 19% on the day. The company’s previous close was £525.40.</p>
<p>Wise has recorded a 34% increase in customer growth, with a total of 10 million as of March 31, 2023. Also, the company’s volume hit £104.5 billion after climbing 37%. For revenue, Wise hit £846.1 million, rising 51% from the £559.9 million the year before. Wise’s total income, buoyed by a spike in customer deposits, jumped 73% year-over-year (YoY), cresting at £964.2 million.</p>
<p>Generally, much of Wise’s profits came from rising interest rates initiated by the Bank of England (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/bank-of-england/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BoE</a>). Last week, the BoE <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-raises-interest-13th-time/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">increased interest rates</a> for the 13th consecutive time, adding 50 basis points. The Monetary Policy Committee voted 7-2 in favor of the addition, increasing the BoE’s base rate to 5%.</p>
<p>The apex bank has been consistently increasing interest rates to fight rising inflation. In May, the annual consumer price index (CPI) rose 8.7%, higher than the 8.4% expected by economists.</p>
<h2>Wise Records Stock Spike Despite Headwinds</h2>
<p>The jump in Wise stock is a silver lining amid the company’s issues. Last year, the Abu Dhabi Global Market’s Financial Services Regulatory Authority (FSRA) <a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/fintech-firm-wise-fined-360000-by-abu-dhabi-regulator-2022-08-30/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">fined</a> Wise $360,000 for violating anti-money laundering (AML) laws.</p>
<p>In a statement, the FSRA said Wise Nuqud, a local Wise subsidiary, did not create and operate an AML framework enough to comply with the agency’s requirements. Although the FSRA said it did not find any actual money laundering instances, it identified inadequacy and failures in setting up guideline systems and controls.</p>
<p>UK tax authorities added to Wise’s problems last year after accusing CEO and co-founder Kristo Kaarmann of tax evasion. Her Majesty’s Revenue and Customs fined the CEO £365,651, nearly $495,000 at the time, for filing his personal tax returns late for the 2017/2018 tax year. A company spokesman confirmed that Kaarmann had paid the fine and added required late filing penalties.</p>
<p>In a recent conversation with BBC Radio, Kaarmann seemed to downplay the incident. According to him:</p>
<blockquote><p>“It has really not much to do with the business that we’re running. It was a personal mistake. I was really late with my taxes a long time ago and I paid the fines.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Nonetheless, Kaarmann said the Financial Conduct Authority (FCA) is investigating the incident. The outcome of the FCA’s investigation may affect his position as CEO if found guilty.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/boe-britons-digital-pound-cbdc/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/wise-stock-jumps-deposits/">Wise Stock Jumps 18% on Customer Deposits and Higher Interest Rates</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wise-stock-jumps-deposits/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>BoE Reassures Britons Digital Pound Will Be Privacy-Centric CBDC</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/boe-britons-digital-pound-cbdc/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/boe-britons-digital-pound-cbdc/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 13:38:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bank of england]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[boe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mpc]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=260638</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/boe-britons-digital-pound-cbdc/">BoE Reassures Britons Digital Pound Will Be Privacy-Centric CBDC</a></p>
<p>The Bank of England (BoE) has made extensive research on the best format for developing a digital pound to supplement the fiat system.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/boe-britons-digital-pound-cbdc/">BoE Reassures Britons Digital Pound Will Be Privacy-Centric CBDC</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/boe-britons-digital-pound-cbdc/">BoE Reassures Britons Digital Pound Will Be Privacy-Centric CBDC</a></p>
<p>The Bank of England (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/bank-of-england/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BoE</a>) is working on re-establishing the pound as the preferred global reserve currency through a Central Bank Digital Currency (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-central-bank-digital-currency-cbdc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CBDC</a>). The rise of the digital economy post-Covid-19 global pandemic through the cryptocurrency market has most governments thinking about moving to decentralized ledger technologies (DLTs). Moreover, the use of the digital economy is not only sustainable but also scalable to international markets. Consequently, the forex market will significantly benefit from fast verifiable digital currencies and so will the cryptocurrency market.</p>
<h2>BoE on Digital Pound Key Selling Features</h2>
<p>Over the last few years, the Bank of England has collaborated with different entities in the research of an excellent Central Bank Digital Currency. For instance, in February 2022, the Bank of England and the Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT) agreed to collaborate on a twelve-month research project on CBDC. The Bank of England has also conducted several consultations with the public on how to develop and roll out the CBDC.</p>
<p>As a result, the BoE noted that the digital sterling or more popularly called the Britcoin will primarily focus on user privacy. According to  Tom Mutton, director of fintech at the Bank of England, the bank may look to other technologies beyond blockchain in developing its CBDC. However, Mutton noted that the Bank will give user data security huge attention in order to ensure the government does not become a tracking agent for the users.</p>
<p>“There will be no data shared with the Bank of England, we will know what transactions have happened but we will have no data on the individual who did it. While the wallet provider would have the user data but won’t have access to their transaction data,” Mutton noted.</p>
<p>Reportedly, the Bank of England is comparing the efficiency of using blockchain technology over traditional conventional ledgers in developing the CBDC that is compatible with the private sector.</p>
<p>“We want to be compatible with distributed-ledger business models in the private sector, but we were not convinced that distributed ledgers offered more efficiency over conventional ledgers,” he <a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/digital-pound-will-be-pseudonymous-with-a-focus-on-privacy-boe-cbdc-chief" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">added</a>.</p>
<p>Currently, the Bank of England and the Treasury Department are waiting for feedback from the stakeholders which is open until June 30.</p>
<h2>Market Outlook</h2>
<p>The Bank of England is racing against time to avoid losing its aesthetic attraction to other global currencies like the Chinese Yuan that have already rolled out in the digital format. The launch of the digital pound comes amid a high-interest rate of about 5 percent despite the Bank of England’s Monetary Policy Committee (MPC) trying to bring down inflation to 2 percent.</p>
<p>With the UK operating freely from the shackles of the European Union, its future economic growth prospects are pegged to the relationship the country signs post-Brexit.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/swiss-national-bank-wholesale-cbdc/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/boe-britons-digital-pound-cbdc/">BoE Reassures Britons Digital Pound Will Be Privacy-Centric CBDC</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/boe-britons-digital-pound-cbdc/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Swiss National Bank to Launch Wholesale CBDC (wCBDC) Pilot Soon</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/swiss-national-bank-wholesale-cbdc/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/swiss-national-bank-wholesale-cbdc/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 12:56:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[six]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[snb]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[wcbdc]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=260622</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/swiss-national-bank-wholesale-cbdc/">Swiss National Bank to Launch Wholesale CBDC (wCBDC) Pilot Soon</a></p>
<p>The decision to prioritize wholesale CBDCs, which involve tokenized securities, showcases the SNB's commitment to thoroughly assess and manage any associated risks before considering the introduction of retail CBDCs.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/swiss-national-bank-wholesale-cbdc/">Swiss National Bank to Launch Wholesale CBDC (wCBDC) Pilot Soon</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/swiss-national-bank-wholesale-cbdc/">Swiss National Bank to Launch Wholesale CBDC (wCBDC) Pilot Soon</a></p>
<p>The Swiss National Bank (SNB) is set to create a digital currency known as a wholesale central bank digital currency (wCBDC). According to a Reuters <a href="https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/snb-launch-digital-currency-pilot-chairman-2023-06-26/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a>, the announcement was made by the head of SNB, Thomas Jordan, during a Point Zero conference in Zurich yesterday, 26 June.</p>
<h2>wCBDC by Swiss National Bank</h2>
<p>The wCBDC will be issued on the SIX digital exchange, the largest stock exchange in Switzerland, as part of a pilot program. Jordan said the project would begin soon and is scheduled to run for a limited time. The goal is to understand how the wCBDC performs in practical transactions with market participants.</p>
<p>&#8220;This is not just an experiment. It will be real money equivalent to bank reserves, and the objective is to test real transactions with market participants,&#8221; said the SNB Chairman.</p>
<p>The move by the SNB reflects an increasing trend among central banks to explore and develop digital currencies. These virtual assets are gaining popularity due to their potential to streamline financial processes and improve cross-border payments. Switzerland, known for its financial innovation, aims to leverage this technology to enhance its financial economy.</p>
<p>The Swiss bank began the wCBDC campaign last year. In January, the bank announced the integration of the digital asset into five commercial banks, including Citi, Credit Suisse, and Goldman Sachs, as part of the second phase of its Project Helvetia.</p>
<p>SNB incorporated the wCBDC into the banks&#8217; existing back-office systems and processes.</p>
<p>Aside from Switzerland, other countries such as the United Kingdom, Russia, Japan, India, and even China are <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bank-of-england-boe-cbdc-test/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">exploring</a> the use of central bank-issued virtual assets for cross-border payments.</p>
<p>The International Monetary Fund (IMF) also recently released a blueprint for CBDC creation in compliance with regulatory requirements. The IMF plans to<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/imf-global-cbdc-platform/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"> develop</a> a global platform where users can interact with CBDC.</p>
<h2>SNB Remains Cautious of Public CBDC</h2>
<p>Despite its plans to explore wCBDC, SNB has remained cautious when it comes to the implementation of public or retail <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-central-bank-digital-currency-cbdc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">central bank digital currencies</a> (CBDCs), in contrast to its involvement with wholesale CBDCs.</p>
<p>The SNB Chairman has expressed concerns regarding the potential risks that retail CBDCs might introduce to the financial system, mainly due to the challenges associated with control and oversight.</p>
<p>Jordan acknowledged that the bank does not completely rule out the future introduction of retail CBDCs. However, he emphasized the current prudence exercised by the bank in approaching this area of digital currency.</p>
<p>&#8220;We do not exclude that we will never introduce retail [CBDCs], but nevertheless, we are a little bit prudent at the moment,&#8221; he said.</p>
<p>The decision to prioritize wholesale CBDCs, which involve tokenized securities, showcases the SNB&#8217;s commitment to thoroughly assess and manage any associated risks before considering the introduction of retail CBDCs.  By focusing on this approach, the SNB aims to gain a comprehensive understanding of the potential benefits and challenges of digital currencies while safeguarding the stability of Switzerland&#8217;s financial system.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/whatsapp-business-200m-active-users/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/swiss-national-bank-wholesale-cbdc/">Swiss National Bank to Launch Wholesale CBDC (wCBDC) Pilot Soon</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/swiss-national-bank-wholesale-cbdc/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>WhatsApp Business Announces 200M Active Users and Launches Personalized Customer Messages </title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/whatsapp-business-200m-active-users/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/whatsapp-business-200m-active-users/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 12:39:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Meta]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meta platforms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[whatsapp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[whatsapp business]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=260592</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/whatsapp-business-200m-active-users/">WhatsApp Business Announces 200M Active Users and Launches Personalized Customer Messages </a></p>
<p>WhatsApp Business is introducing new paid features as it announces its monthly active users are now more than 200 million.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/whatsapp-business-200m-active-users/">WhatsApp Business Announces 200M Active Users and Launches Personalized Customer Messages </a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/whatsapp-business-200m-active-users/">WhatsApp Business Announces 200M Active Users and Launches Personalized Customer Messages </a></p>
<p>Meta Platforms-owned WhatsApp Business, a version of the instant messaging app built for small businesses, now has over 200 million users. According to Meta CEO <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/mark-zuckerberg/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Mark Zuckerberg</a>, this is a 4x jump from three years ago. In 2020, 2 years after its launch, WhatsApp Business <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2020/07/09/whatsapp-business-now-with-50m-maus-adds-qr-code-and-catalog-sharing/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announced</a> a monthly active user (MAU) count of 50 million.</p>
<p>Meta is now touting the advantages of business messaging as the company records a decrease in advertising. The social media and tech giant has lost some of its core advertising business to a dwindling economy and a general reduction in spending power.</p>
<p>In 2021, the Facebook company <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/facebook-name-meta/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">rebranded to Meta Platforms</a> to shift its focus to the metaverse. At the time, the company explained that it planned to make the metaverse a reality for users to find other people, grow their communities and advance businesses. However, Meta Platforms is <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-zuckerberg-whatsapp-sales-metaverse/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">shifting its focus</a> from the metaverse to apps. Speaking at a company-wide meeting shortly after announcing it would fire 11,000 workers, Zuckerberg said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“&#8230;The reality is that business messaging is probably going to be the next major pillar of our business as we work to monetize WhatsApp and Messenger more.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>Expected WhatsApp Business Features for Users</h2>
<p>Meta Platforms is still working very hard to develop a metaverse and is investing several billion into the endeavor. To make up for the large investment, the company is focusing on generating revenue from other channels, including WhatsApp. Meta is now introducing more features to ramp up income from WhatsApp Business.</p>
<p>For instance, users on WhatsApp Business can now create “click-to-WhatsApp” ads right from the app instead of via a Facebook account. Zuckerberg mentioned last year during Meta’s earnings call for Q3 that these ads recorded an 80% year-on-year (YoY) growth, exceeding the $1.5 billion annual revenue run rate.</p>
<p>In addition to the in-app ad, WhatsApp Business plans to generate revenue from message automation. The paid feature would allow users to automate the delivery of personalized messages to customers. WhatsApp Business users will be able to create customer lists and automate different personalized messages for each list. Business owners may use this feature to offer a promo or discount code to one or more lists, and not their entire customer base.</p>
<h2>WhatsApp Payments</h2>
<p>WhatsApp is introducing in-app features that allow customers to pay businesses directly. In April, WhatsApp launched end-to-end payments in Brazil, with Zuckerberg <a href="https://web.facebook.com/zuck/posts/pfbid02j4zdLXXJ4yEcqXXkPLH394z4PgdbbBGCpsVp83vzY3aTPnR3dR4KxBXcpQoNH1Tnl?_rdc=1&amp;_rdr" target="_blank" rel="noopener">confirming</a> that anyone can “pay local businesses right in a WhatsApp chat”. In an official announcement, Meta described the feature as a “game-changer” that allows people to complete transactions without opening another app or visiting a website.</p>
<p>Previously, peer-to-peer payments were available to WhatsApp users in Brazil. However, regulatory requirements did not allow Meta to expand the feature for merchant purchases. Merchants had to use a third-party service to generate a payment link and then forward the same via WhatsApp. Now, in-app payments make the process of buying, selling, and paying, a lot more seamless.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/riot-platforms-33280-bitcoin-miners/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/whatsapp-business-200m-active-users/">WhatsApp Business Announces 200M Active Users and Launches Personalized Customer Messages </a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/whatsapp-business-200m-active-users/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Riot Platforms to Onboard 33,280 Bitcoin Miners Ahead of 2024 Halving</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/riot-platforms-33280-bitcoin-miners/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/riot-platforms-33280-bitcoin-miners/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 11:42:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin halving]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc halving]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MicroBT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[riot platforms]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=260606</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/riot-platforms-33280-bitcoin-miners/">Riot Platforms to Onboard 33,280 Bitcoin Miners Ahead of 2024 Halving</a></p>
<p>Riot Platforms’ recent acquisition of Bitcoin miners from MicroBT holds significant importance in the context of the upcoming halving event in 2024.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/riot-platforms-33280-bitcoin-miners/">Riot Platforms to Onboard 33,280 Bitcoin Miners Ahead of 2024 Halving</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/riot-platforms-33280-bitcoin-miners/">Riot Platforms to Onboard 33,280 Bitcoin Miners Ahead of 2024 Halving</a></p>
<p>Riot Platforms Inc (NASDAQ: RIOT), a leading player in the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> (BTC) mining industry has announced a significant development in its quest to expand its mining capabilities.</p>
<p>The company stated in a <a href="https://www.riotplatforms.com/news-media/press-releases/detail/155/riot-purchases-7-6-ehs-of-next-generation-miners-from" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">press release</a> that it has entered into a long-term purchase agreement with MicroBT Electronics Technology Co., LTD, a well-known manufacturer of Bitcoin miners. This strategic partnership aims to enhance Riot&#8217;s mining capacity by securing an initial order of 33,280 next-generation Bitcoin miners from MicroBT.</p>
<p>The total consideration for the initial order amounts to $162.9 million, excluding taxes, fees, and adjustments. This equates to an approximate cost of $21.50 per terahash (TH), a competitive price for the mining equipment.</p>
<p>This strategic move comes in anticipation of the 2024 <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-halving-2024-1-year-away/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">halving event</a>, which is expected to bring significant changes to the Bitcoin mining landscape. With this expansion, Riot Platforms aims to solidify its position as a major player in the crypto mining industry and maximize its mining capabilities for the future.</p>
<p>Riot stated that the miners ordered from MicroBT will be produced in the United States specifically for Riot&#8217;s Corsicana Facility. This move <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/riot-2022-report-growth-plans/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">aligns</a> with Riot&#8217;s strategy of expanding its mining operations within the country. With MicroBT manufacturing the newly acquired miners at a facility in Pittsburgh, PA, this collaboration establishes a robust domestic supply chain for Bitcoin miners, which is a significant milestone for the industry.</p>
<p>Furthermore, Riot noted that the deployment process is expected to take some time due to the significant number of miners involved. According to the agreement, the delivery of the new miners is set to commence in December 2023.</p>
<p>Riot Platforms anticipates completing the full deployment of the 33,280 miners by mid-2024. This time frame allows for careful installation, configuration, and optimization of the mining equipment to ensure optimal performance.</p>
<h2>Significance of Riot Platform&#8217;s Acquisition for the Halving Event</h2>
<p>Riot Platforms’ recent acquisition of Bitcoin miners from MicroBT holds significant importance in the context of the upcoming halving event in 2024. This is because the halving event, which occurs every four years, reduces block rewards for miners, affecting the economics of Bitcoin mining.</p>
<p>However, upon the completion of the deployment, Riot’s self-mining hash rate capacity is projected to increase to 20.1 EH/s (exahashes per second). Increasing the self-mining hash rate capacity is a strategic move by Riot Platforms.</p>
<p>As block rewards decrease, maintaining a competitive hash rate becomes crucial for mining profitability. By expanding its mining fleet and hash rate capacity, Riot Platforms aims to offset the effects of the halving, ensuring continued profitability and operational efficiency.</p>
<p>This significant boost in hash rate capacity positions the company as a major player in the Bitcoin mining industry, solidifying its role in validating transactions and contributing to the overall security and efficiency of the Bitcoin network.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/baidu-ernie-3-5-chatgpt-gpt-4/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/riot-platforms-33280-bitcoin-miners/">Riot Platforms to Onboard 33,280 Bitcoin Miners Ahead of 2024 Halving</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/riot-platforms-33280-bitcoin-miners/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Baidu Says Ernie 3.5 Outdid ChatGPT and GPT-4 in Key Metrics</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/baidu-ernie-3-5-chatgpt-gpt-4/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/baidu-ernie-3-5-chatgpt-gpt-4/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 11:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[baidu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chatgpt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ernie]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gpt-4]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=260605</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/baidu-ernie-3-5-chatgpt-gpt-4/">Baidu Says Ernie 3.5 Outdid ChatGPT and GPT-4 in Key Metrics</a></p>
<p>The result of the AGIEval and C-Eval tests shows that Ernie 3.5 achieved higher scores than other large models, including ChatGPT, and surpassed GPT-4.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/baidu-ernie-3-5-chatgpt-gpt-4/">Baidu Says Ernie 3.5 Outdid ChatGPT and GPT-4 in Key Metrics</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/baidu-ernie-3-5-chatgpt-gpt-4/">Baidu Says Ernie 3.5 Outdid ChatGPT and GPT-4 in Key Metrics</a></p>
<p>Competition in the AI market heats up as China&#8217;s Baidu <a href="http://research.baidu.com/Blog/index-view?id=185" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a> its AI model Ernie 3.5 beats the popular OpenAI&#8217;s ChatGPT AND GPT-4 on key tests. The Chinese internet company <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/baidu-chatgpt-ernie-bot/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">unveiled</a> the Ernie bot at an event in March. At the time of the announcement, CEO Robin Li said that the new product was imperfect and would continue to improve as people use it and give feedback. Within an hour after revealing the Ernie bot, Baidu stated that about 30,000 corporate clients joined the waitlist to access the chatbot.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Baidu has been publicly testing Ernie Bot since it was unveiled in March. The chatbot, built on the Chinese search engine&#8217;s foundational AI model called Ernie, is trained on extensive data. On the other hand, ChatGPT, which Baidu said Ernie 3.5 outperformed, is based on OpenAI&#8217;s GPT 3.5 model. It also added its AI model beats OpenAI&#8217;s latest and more advanced model, GPT-4. It noted that Ernie 3.5 performed better than OpenAI&#8217;s product in Chinese language tests.</p>
<h2>Baidu Claims Ernie 3.5 Is Better than ChatGPT in Multiple Key Area</h2>
<p>The Chinese company made the claim while citing a <a href="https://mp.weixin.qq.com/s/QVdkmofRSTgjQ7UOFX7s1g" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a> by China Science Daily. According to the report, a &#8220;Few-Shot evaluation&#8221; reveals that Ernie 3.5 outperformed ChatGPT in multiple test sets. The three evaluation benchmarks are AGIEval, C-Eval, and MMLU. Microsoft Research the AGIEval evaluation benchmark to examine the model&#8217;s performance level in the &#8220;human-oriented&#8221; standardized test. The focus is on 20 official, public, and distinct qualifying exams, such as SAT exam in the US and college entrance examinations in China. More include Bar exams, American GMAT, GME, and so on. In addition, Berkeley University, Columbia University, the University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign, and the University of Chicago jointly release MMLU. The large-scale multi-task language understanding test measures the models&#8217; English interdisciplinary professional ability. This test covers different educational areas like social sciences, humanities, science, technology, engineering and mathematics (STEM), and more.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the c-Eval evaluation is a Chinese basic model evaluation containing 13,948 multiple-choice questions covering 53 subjects. The evaluation benchmark was created and released by the joint effort of Tsinghua University, the University of Edinburgh, and Shanghai Jiaotong University.</p>
<p>The result of the AGIEval and C-Eval tests shows that Ernie 3.5 achieved higher scores than other large models, including ChatGPT, and surpassed GPT-4. Also, the Baidu AI model also outdid ChatGPT&#8217;s 40.27 points and GPT -4&#8217;s 56.96 points. Ernie 3.5 scored a whopping 64.37 points, making the first position. For the Chinese c-Eval evaluation, Ernie 3.5 outstripped ChatGPT. While the Chinese AI model scored the highest at 71.93 points, ChatGPT measured 51.70 points, and GPT-4 got 68.57 points. In addition, Baidu mentioned more results that showed that Ernie 3.5 has &#8220;outstanding Chinese ability&#8221; and outperformed ChatGPT and GPT-4.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fireblocks-cloud-crypto-custody/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/baidu-ernie-3-5-chatgpt-gpt-4/">Baidu Says Ernie 3.5 Outdid ChatGPT and GPT-4 in Key Metrics</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/baidu-ernie-3-5-chatgpt-gpt-4/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fireblocks Expands Cloud Support for Crypto Custody</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fireblocks-cloud-crypto-custody/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fireblocks-cloud-crypto-custody/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Babafemi Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 11:26:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cloud Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bnp paribas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bny mellon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fireblocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[galaxy digital]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gemini]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[kraken]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[revolut]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[robinhood]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=260518</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fireblocks-cloud-crypto-custody/">Fireblocks Expands Cloud Support for Crypto Custody</a></p>
<p>Fireblocks’ cloud support comes at a time when more and more institutional investors and corporations are joining the crypto space.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fireblocks-cloud-crypto-custody/">Fireblocks Expands Cloud Support for Crypto Custody</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fireblocks-cloud-crypto-custody/">Fireblocks Expands Cloud Support for Crypto Custody</a></p>

<p>Blockchain security service provider, Fireblocks, has expanded its cloud service for crypto custody and settlement. According to the <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/fireblocks-expands-support-for-banking--financial-institutions-with-new-hsm-public--private-cloud-capabilities-301863908.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announcement</a>, the service will now include Amazon Web Services (AWS), Google Cloud Platform, Alibaba Cloud, Thales, and Securosys.</p>
<h2>Cloud Computing Meets Crypto Security</h2>
<p>Fireblocks&#8217; platform uses a combination of security technologies to protect private keys and transactions from cyberattacks, internal fraud and human error. Last year, the company became the first to <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fireblocks-first-ccss-certificate/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">receive</a> the Cryptocurrency Security Standard (CCSS) certification since its inception in 2014. The certificate provided objective proof of the company’s adherence to the highest security standards in the crypto industry.</p>
<p>By expanding its cloud support, Fireblocks’ customers can now enjoy the advantages of cloud computing, such as scalability, flexibility, and saving costs. They can do this without compromising on security and compliance for their digital assets.</p>
<p>According to Fireblocks&#8217; CEO and co-founder Michael Shaulov, cloud support will allow Fireblocks to serve a wider range of customers from different sectors. &#8220;By expanding our cloud support, we are enabling our customers to choose the best option for their business needs, whether it&#8217;s SaaS, private cloud or on-premises,&#8221; Shaulov said.</p>
<p>&#8220;We are also opening up new opportunities for innovation and collaboration in the crypto ecosystem,&#8221; he concluded.</p>
<h2>Crypto Custody and Settlement Market Heats Up</h2>
<p>Meanwhile, Fireblocks’ cloud support comes at a time when more and more institutional investors and corporations are joining the crypto space. This creates a huge demand for crypto custody and settlement solutions that are secure and scalable. A <a href="https://blog.chainalysis.com/reports/2022-global-crypto-adoption-index/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Chainalysis report</a> shows that institutional transactions made up 61% of the crypto market in the first half of 2023, up from 39% in 2020</p>
<p>With more institutional investors and corporations entering the crypto space, there has been a rise in demand for enterprise-grade solutions that can handle large volumes.</p>
<p>Fireblocks already serves some of the biggest names in the crypto and financial industries, such as Binance, Coinbase, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a>, Galaxy Digital, Gemini, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/kraken/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Kraken</a>, Revolut, ANZ Bank, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/bny-mellon/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BNY Mellon</a>, BNP Paribas, and Robinhood. Its platform supports a wide range of tokens, protocols, and exchanges &#8211; about 500, 50, and 300 respectively. With its expanded cloud support, Fireblocks aims to do even more for the crypto community.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/mizuho-45000-employees-test-openai/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fireblocks-cloud-crypto-custody/">Fireblocks Expands Cloud Support for Crypto Custody</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fireblocks-cloud-crypto-custody/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4206 metric#misses=41 metric#hit-ratio=99.0 metric#bytes=1039854 metric#prefetches=207 metric#store-reads=19 metric#store-writes=2 metric#store-hits=213 metric#store-misses=2 metric#sql-queries=34 metric#ms-total=92.54 metric#ms-cache=4.74 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.2368 metric#ms-cache-ratio=5.1 -->