<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 17:20:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Alex The Doge (ALEX) Presale Reports 14 Million Tokens Sold</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/alex-the-doge-alex-presale-reports-14-million-tokens-sold/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/alex-the-doge-alex-presale-reports-14-million-tokens-sold/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire &#160;]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 17:20:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=145163</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Frankfurt, Germany, July 4th, 2023, Chainwire Alex The Doge (ALEX), a memecoin designed to transform the GameFi ecosystem, has reported strong demand for its presale. The presale, which is currently ongoing, gives the crypto community their first opportunity to purchase ALEX tokens. Following completion of the token sale, ALEX will launch on decentralized exchanges. ALEX [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/alex-the-doge-alex-presale-reports-14-million-tokens-sold/">Alex The Doge (ALEX) Presale Reports 14 Million Tokens Sold</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Frankfurt, Germany, July 4th, 2023, Chainwire</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://alexthedoge.live/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Alex The Doge (ALEX)</a>, a memecoin designed to transform the GameFi ecosystem, has reported strong demand for its presale. The presale, which is currently ongoing, gives the crypto community their first opportunity to purchase ALEX tokens. Following completion of the token sale, ALEX will launch on decentralized exchanges.</p>
<p>ALEX aims to combine the fun of memecoins with the utility of decentralized finance (DeFi) and play-to-earn gaming. The project has garnered significant attention from crypto enthusiasts, with more than 13.5 million ALEX tokens sold during the presale so far.</p>
<p>ALEX is built on Polygon, a blockchain network known for its scalability, speed, and security. By leveraging the capabilities of Polygon, ALEX is creating a digital gaming world called the Miracle Verse. This innovative ecosystem will empower users with play-to-earn gaming opportunities, social trading, and DeFi activities. With its gamified approach and extensive suite of products under development, ALEX aims to differentiate itself from other memecoins and gain a foothold in the market.</p>
<p>The project operates at the intersection of GameFi and SocialFi, the latter term describing the creation of strong communities that are united by shared interests and common goals. An extensive roadmap gives interested parties an idea of what to expect from the ALEX ecosystem as it takes shape, with the launch of the Miracle Verse sure to be an eagerly anticipated event.</p>
<p>Through combining the fun factor synonymous with memecoins and the utility built into decentralized finance applications, the team behind Alex The Doge believes it has found a winning formula. The completion of the ALEX presale will set the stage for everything that comes next, starting with the token&rsquo;s DEX debut as Alex The Doge goes live.</p>
<p><strong>Join the Alex The Doge (ALEX) presale using the links below:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Website: <a href="https://alexthedoge.live/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://alexthedoge.live/</a></li>
<li>Telegram: <a href="https://t.me/alexthedoge" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://t.me/alexthedoge</a></li>
<li>Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/AlexTheDoge_p2e" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://twitter.com/AlexTheDoge_p2e</a></li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Contact</strong></p>
<p>Community Lead<br>
Zack Anderson<br>
Alex The Doge<br>
support@alexthedoge.live</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/alex-the-doge-alex-presale-reports-14-million-tokens-sold/">Alex The Doge (ALEX) Presale Reports 14 Million Tokens Sold</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/alex-the-doge-alex-presale-reports-14-million-tokens-sold/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cryptocurrencies are back in fashion as the total crypto market cap keeps rising</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/cryptocurrencies-are-back-in-fashion-as-the-total-crypto-market-cap-keeps-rising/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/cryptocurrencies-are-back-in-fashion-as-the-total-crypto-market-cap-keeps-rising/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mircea Vasiu]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 16:46:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/cryptocurrencies-are-back-in-fashion-as-the-total-crypto-market-cap-keeps-rising/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The total cryptocurrency market capitalization grew by more than 50% in the last six months Investors are optimistic as Bitcoin&#8217;s price holds near the yearly high Ethereum, Litecoin, and Ripple have followed Bitcoin higher The first half of the trading year is behind us, and one of the most notable developments is the increase in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/cryptocurrencies-are-back-in-fashion-as-the-total-crypto-market-cap-keeps-rising/">Cryptocurrencies are back in fashion as the total crypto market cap keeps rising</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>The total cryptocurrency market capitalization grew by more than 50% in the last six months</li>
<li>Investors are optimistic as Bitcoin&rsquo;s price holds near the yearly high</li>
<li>Ethereum, Litecoin, and Ripple have followed Bitcoin higher</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p>The first half of the trading year is behind us, and one of the most notable developments is the increase in the total crypto market capitalization. Following 2022, when many crypto investors got fed up with industry scandals and left, the 2023 rally looks like the start of a new bullish market.</p>
<p>The performance is even more impressive, given that the US dollar is trading with a mixed tone against its fiat rivals.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Investors&rsquo; renewed interest in cryptocurrencies led to the total market capitalization growing by more than 50% in the year&rsquo;s first half. Only in the last week, the market grew by more than 3%, and investors are optimistic because Bitcoin, the leading cryptocurrency, holds near the yearly high.&nbsp;</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/04/1688487752291-bb23ca36-fe26-4844-80e1-624cf1e8b9bc.jpg" style="width: 1800px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="1800" height="387"></p>
<h2>Ethereum, Litecoin, and Ripple have followed Bitcoin higher</h2>
<p>Bitcoin is the main reason why investors are optimistic about the cryptocurrency industry despite the ongoing scandals, frauds, and lawsuits. In the end, all that matters for market watchers is that Bitcoin&rsquo;s price holds close to the yearly high, despite rallying in 2023 by over +85%.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Therefore, the path of least resistance in the year&rsquo;s second half seems to be the upside.&nbsp;</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/04/1688489059236-0fc4fc27-7dad-45c0-983a-c87a2b6ea411.jpg" style="width: 1800px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="1800" height="471"></p>
<p><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/?exchange=CRYPTO" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Bitcoin chart by TradingView</a></p>
<p>Not all currencies performed like Bitcoin, though. For instance, Dogecoin is flat on the year, up by about +0.3% in the first six months of 2023. This is a huge divergence from what Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies did (e.g., Ethereum, Litecoin, Ripple), and it reflects the crypto investors&rsquo; concentration in a few cryptocurrencies.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Moving forward in the year&rsquo;s second half, crypto investors might want to watch the developments in the traditional currency market. More precisely, what will the Fed do with the funds rate?&nbsp;</p>
<p>If the US dollar loses ground against its rival fiat currencies in the next six months, Bitcoin and the other leading cryptocurrencies are well positioned to rally some more. As the Fed paused the rate hikes in June, one should embrace the possibility of the current funds rate being the terminal one for this tightening cycle.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/cryptocurrencies-are-back-in-fashion-as-the-total-crypto-market-cap-keeps-rising/">Cryptocurrencies are back in fashion as the total crypto market cap keeps rising</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/cryptocurrencies-are-back-in-fashion-as-the-total-crypto-market-cap-keeps-rising/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitget debuts in lending with the launch of ‘Crypto Loans’</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitget-launches-crypto-loans/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wajeeh Khan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 16:20:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitget]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=145146</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitget launched its native &#8220;Crypto Loans&#8221; product on Tuesday. Digital lending is expected to advance at a CAGR of 20.5%. Singapore and Thailand have recently banned crypto lending. Bitget &#8211; a Seychelles-based digital assets trading platform launched &#8220;Crypto Loans&#8221; to debut in the lending space on Tuesday. Here&#8217;s what we know so far Its new [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitget-launches-crypto-loans/">Bitget debuts in lending with the launch of ‘Crypto Loans’</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitget launched its native &ldquo;Crypto Loans&rdquo; product on Tuesday.</li>
<li>Digital lending is expected to advance at a CAGR of 20.5%.</li>
<li>Singapore and Thailand have recently banned crypto lending.</li>
</ul>
<p>Bitget &ndash; a Seychelles-based digital assets trading platform launched &ldquo;Crypto Loans&rdquo; to debut in the lending space on Tuesday.</p>
<h2>Here&rsquo;s what we know so far</h2>
<p>Its new product will cater particularly to users that are not fully satisfied with the traditional credit institutions. According to Gracy Chen &ndash; the Managing Director of Bitget:</p>
<blockquote><p>Users now have the opportunity to stake less-demanded coins, enabling them to obtain loans in more liquid assets for investment purposes.</p></blockquote>
<p>Each loan, as per the <a href="https://www.bitget.com/blog/articles/12560603794357" target="_blank" rel="noopener">press release</a>, will be coupled with a specific interest rate. Bitget did not, however, reveal the cryptocurrencies that&rsquo;ll be eligible for Crypto Loans.</p>
<p>The news arrives only days after Bitget formally entered Turkey with a new website as part of its commitment to expand globally (<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitget-formally-enters-turkey-bitget-tr/">find out more</a>).</p>
<h2>Digital lending is seeing strong demand</h2>
<p>Digital lending is expected to grow at a compound annual rate of 20.5% between 2023 and 2032 after hitting the $8.5 billion mark last year which suggests strong demand. Chen also said today in the press release:</p>
<blockquote><p>Bitget&rsquo;s new product highlights flexibility of collateralized currency usage, enhancing capital utilization. Our flexible borrowing and repayment mechanism caters to needs of all users.</p></blockquote>
<p>The top crypto derivatives platform is entering the crypto lending sector at a time when multiple countries, including <a href="https://decrypt.co/147091/singapore-regulator-bans-crypto-exchanges-from-lending-staking-retail-investors/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Singapore</a> and <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/cryptocurrency/thailands-sec-bans-crypto-lending-demands-risk-warning-disclosure/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Thailand</a>, have banned crypto companies from issuing loans.</p>
<p>Bitget did not state in its press release whether the new service will be available in the United States.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitget-launches-crypto-loans/">Bitget debuts in lending with the launch of ‘Crypto Loans’</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano price retests key resistance as DeFi TVL hits record</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/cardano-price-retests-key-resistance-as-defi-tvl-hits-record/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/cardano-price-retests-key-resistance-as-defi-tvl-hits-record/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 15:40:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/cardano-price-retests-key-resistance-as-defi-tvl-hits-record/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Cardano price retested the key resistance level at $0.2972 on Tuesday.&#160; DeFi TVL in Cardano&#8217;s ecosystem jumped to a record high. Cardano price has moved sideways in the past few weeks even as other coins like Bitcoin, AAVE, and Compound surged. ADA token was trading at $0.2972, where it has been for a while. This [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/cardano-price-retests-key-resistance-as-defi-tvl-hits-record/">Cardano price retests key resistance as DeFi TVL hits record</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Cardano price retested the key resistance level at $0.2972 on Tuesday.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">DeFi TVL in Cardano&rsquo;s ecosystem jumped to a record high.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/cardano/"><u>Cardano</u></a> price has moved sideways in the past few weeks even as other coins like Bitcoin, AAVE, and Compound surged. ADA token was trading at $0.2972, where it has been for a while. This price is about 27% above the lowest level in June and 37% below the highest point in May this year.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">DeFi TVL hits record</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Cardano has become one of the most underperforming large-cap cryptocurrencies in the past few weeks. This performance is mostly because of the recent decision by the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) to label it a security.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In the aftermath, Robinhood, one of the biggest companies in the financial services industry, decided to delist the coin. If the SEC&rsquo;s lawsuit against the two exchanges prevails, it means that Americans will not have access to Cardano.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The daily volume of Cardano traded in centralized exchanges has been falling in the past few weeks. It stood at $171 million on Tuesday, down from a peak of over $1 billion in June.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Despite this performance, Cardano&rsquo;s ecosystem is doing well. Data shows that the total value locked (TVL) in its DeFi ecosystem soared to over 702 million ADA tokens, a record high. The figure started the year at around 265 million ADA. In dollar terms, Cardano has a TVL of over $202 million.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The biggest&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/learn/what-is-defi/"><u>DeFi</u></a> dApps in Cardano&rsquo;s ecosystem are Minswap, Indigo, Liquid, and VyFinance among others. TVL is an important metric that measures the value of digital assets locked in a blockchain.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">At the same time, Cardano&rsquo;s NFT ecosystem is not doing all that well. Total Cardano NFT sales&nbsp;<a href="https://www.cryptoslam.io/blockchains/cardano"><u>came</u></a> in at over $8.6 million in June from the previous $8.23 million. While these numbers are good, sales stood at $10 million in March and $23 million in October last year.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Cardano price prediction</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/04/1688485176532-13357269-8c23-4355-b7fe-d00ff23145dd.png" style="width: 602px;height: 292.973px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="602" height="292.973"></p>
<p dir="ltr">The daily chart shows that the ADA price has been in a strong bearish trend for a while. This decline saw it retreat below the important support $0.2972, the lowest level in March this year. It has now retested this level, making a bearish break and retest pattern. Cardano remains below the 25-day and 50-day moving averages.</p>
<p dir="ltr">It has also formed a head and shoulders and a bearish pennant patterns. Therefore, the coin will likely have a bearish breakout in the coming days. If this happens, the next level to watch will be last month&rsquo;s low of $0.23277</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy Cardano</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>


<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=MTQ1MTQ3&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy ADA with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    CEX.IO</h3>


<p>
    <a href="/visit/cex-crypto?guid=MTQ1MTQ3&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy ADA with CEX.IO today            </a>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/cardano-price-retests-key-resistance-as-defi-tvl-hits-record/">Cardano price retests key resistance as DeFi TVL hits record</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/cardano-price-retests-key-resistance-as-defi-tvl-hits-record/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>TON blockchain introduces an on-chain encrypted messaging feature</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/ton-blockchain-introduces-an-on-chain-encrypted-messaging-feature/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/ton-blockchain-introduces-an-on-chain-encrypted-messaging-feature/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 14:15:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/ton-blockchain-introduces-an-on-chain-encrypted-messaging-feature/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways The TON Foundation has introduced an on-chain encrypted messaging feature on the TON blockchain. The messaging feature allows users to send encrypted messages during transactions.&#160; TON releases an on-chain messaging feature The Open Network (TON) announced the release of its on-chain encrypted messaging feature on Monday, July 3rd. In a tweet from the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ton-blockchain-introduces-an-on-chain-encrypted-messaging-feature/">TON blockchain introduces an on-chain encrypted messaging feature</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The TON Foundation has introduced an on-chain encrypted messaging feature on the TON blockchain.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The messaging feature allows users to send encrypted messages during transactions.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr">TON releases an on-chain messaging feature</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The Open Network (TON) announced the release of its on-chain encrypted messaging feature on Monday, July 3rd.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In a tweet from the network&rsquo;s developer, TON Foundation, the new feature makes it possible for private messages to be sent between TON users.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">TON Foundation Introduces Encrypted Transaction Messages&#128071;&#128142;<a href="https://t.co/HXKtk0gxKC">https://t.co/HXKtk0gxKC</a> <a href="https://t.co/0z1z4E5ku1">pic.twitter.com/0z1z4E5ku1</a></p>
<p>&mdash; TON &#128142; (@ton_blockchain) <a href="https://twitter.com/ton_blockchain/status/1675903787729399819?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 3, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">TON is the blockchain network forked from the code created by the social media giant Telegram. Telegram left the project in 2020, and the TON Foundation took over prior to the mainnet launch.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to the TON Foundation, the TON blockchain provides greater scalability and transaction throughput than other options in the Web3 ecosystem. The foundation also added that TON remains a decentralised blockchain.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The blockchain makes it possible for users to send messages in transactions. However, the messages were previously completely public. The new on-chain encrypted feature now makes it possible for users to encrypt their messages end-to-end, enabling only the recipients to read the messages.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">While commenting on this <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>latest cryptocurrency news</u></a>, TON core developer Anatoly Makosov, stated that the new feature allows for the &ldquo;personalization&rdquo; of transactions. Makosov said;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;When sending Toncoin, Jettons, or NFTs on TON you have always been able to include a text for the recipient such as &lsquo;for coffee&rsquo; or &lsquo;happy birthday,&rsquo; thereby personalising the interaction. Now this popular feature [&hellip;] is available with full encryption.&rdquo;</em></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">TON could serve as a reliable method to communicate privately</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Makosov pointed out that if an apocalypse occurs that renders the traditional messenger servers useless, TON could serve as a reliable and safeguarded method to communicate privately.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Web3 users enjoy encrypted messages on various retail wallet apps, including MyTonWallet, OpenMask and TON Wallet. The TON Foundation said the feature would be added mobile wallet Tonkeeper soon.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This latest development comes a few weeks after the TON Foundation&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ton-launches-25-million-accelerator-for-emerging-projects/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>launched a $25 million accelerator</u></a> for emerging projects. The program, called the TON Accelerator Program, will provide funding, mentorship, and other resources to help projects build in the TON ecosystem.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ton-blockchain-introduces-an-on-chain-encrypted-messaging-feature/">TON blockchain introduces an on-chain encrypted messaging feature</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/ton-blockchain-introduces-an-on-chain-encrypted-messaging-feature/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Voyager Digital creditors’ lawyers to pocket $16.48M after the recent invoice</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/voyager-digital-creditors-lawyers-to-pocket-16-48m-after-the-recent-invoice/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/voyager-digital-creditors-lawyers-to-pocket-16-48m-after-the-recent-invoice/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 13:16:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/voyager-digital-creditors-lawyers-to-pocket-16-48m-after-the-recent-invoice/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the third and final bill lawyers representing Voyager Digital creditors have billed $5.1 million. When all the invoices are fully paid, Voyager Digital creditors will have paid a total of $16.48 million to the lawyers. The legal charges will top the firm&#8217;s bankruptcy budget by $5.28 million from the initial $11.2 million. In the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/voyager-digital-creditors-lawyers-to-pocket-16-48m-after-the-recent-invoice/">Voyager Digital creditors’ lawyers to pocket $16.48M after the recent invoice</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul class="decimal_type">
<li>In the third and final bill lawyers representing Voyager Digital creditors have billed $5.1 million.</li>
<li>When all the invoices are fully paid, Voyager Digital creditors will have paid a total of $16.48 million to the lawyers.</li>
<li>The legal charges will top the firm&rsquo;s bankruptcy budget by $5.28 million from the initial $11.2 million.</li>
</ul>
<p>In the recent court filing, the creditors of bankrupt cryptocurrency brokerage company Voyager Digital have been billed $5.1 million by New York-based law firm McDermott Will &amp; Emery. The firm is billing for services offered between March 1 and May 13, 2023.</p>
<p>The law firm submitted a <a href="https://cases.stretto.com/public/x193/11753/PLEADINGS/1175307042380000000001.pdf">court filing</a> on July 3 billing the legal costs to the &ldquo;Official Committee of Unsecured Creditors.&rdquo; According to the filing, the law firm billed for its services at an hourly rate of $1,026.76.</p>
<p>In total, the law firm is charging for 5,332.6 hours of professional, semi-professional, and non-professional services, including advising the unsecured Voyager creditors committee. It also wants to be reimbursed $151,221 for its expenses.</p>
<h2>How much have Voyager Digital creditors paid so far? &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;</h2>
<p>McDermott Will &amp; Emery law firm submitted its third and final bill, bringing its total compensation between July 5, 2022, and May 19, 2023, to $16.48 million, of which $8.97 million has already been paid by the creditors.</p>
<p>McDermott Will &amp; Emery isn&rsquo;t the only law firm that is willing to help Voyager, though. Legal counsel Kirkland &amp; Ellis also sent Voyager a bill for $1.1 million in legal costs for the month of April on June 28.</p>
<h2>Voyager Digital woes</h2>
<p>Voyager Digital <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/cryptocurrency-broker-voyager-digital-files-for-chapter-11-bankruptcy/">filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy</a> in July 2022, after the massive crypto meltdown that resulted from the collapse of Terra Luna. At the time, Voyager <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/voyager-digital-issues-notice-of-default-to-three-arrows-capital/">owed $620 million</a> to the currently bankrupt crypto hedge fund Three Arrows Capital.</p>
<p>The bankruptcy court has since ordered Voyager to pay interim reimbursement to the professionals including its lawyers.</p>
<p>Voyager had agreed to <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ftx-us-wins-bid-to-acquire-voyager-digitals-assets/">FTX&rsquo;s bid for its assets</a> just before FTX went down and also filed for bankruptcy meaning the deal did not go through.</p>
<p>Voyager then agreed to sell its assets to Binance.US but Binance.US pulled out of the deal triggering the liquidation of Voyager. Binance.US has also been locked in a legal battle with the US Securities and Exchanges Commission (SEC) which recently sued it for violating the country&rsquo;s securities laws.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/voyager-digital-creditors-lawyers-to-pocket-16-48m-after-the-recent-invoice/">Voyager Digital creditors’ lawyers to pocket $16.48M after the recent invoice</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/voyager-digital-creditors-lawyers-to-pocket-16-48m-after-the-recent-invoice/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Justin Bieber&#8217;s $1.3M NFT investment depreciates by more than 95%</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/justin-biebers-1-3m-nft-investment-depreciates-by-more-than-95/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/justin-biebers-1-3m-nft-investment-depreciates-by-more-than-95/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 09:33:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/justin-biebers-1-3m-nft-investment-depreciates-by-more-than-95/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Justin Bieber invested about $1.3 million into the Bored Ape Yacht Club (BAYC) NFT. There are speculations that Justin Bieber was gifted the NFT by MoonPay as a promotional tactic. The investment has however depreciated to $59,000. Dexerto revealed in a tweet that global pop superstar Justin Bieber&#8217;s $1.3 million investment in BAYC NFT had [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/justin-biebers-1-3m-nft-investment-depreciates-by-more-than-95/">Justin Bieber&#8217;s $1.3M NFT investment depreciates by more than 95%</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul class="decimal_type">
<li>Justin Bieber invested about $1.3 million into the Bored Ape Yacht Club (BAYC) NFT.</li>
<li>There are speculations that Justin Bieber was gifted the NFT by MoonPay as a promotional tactic.</li>
<li>The investment has however depreciated to $59,000.</li>
</ul>
<p>Dexerto revealed in a <a href="https://twitter.com/Dexerto/status/1675923552250241029?s=20">tweet</a> that global pop superstar Justin Bieber&rsquo;s $1.3 million investment in BAYC NFT had depreciated to $59,000; meaning he has lost about $1.2 million.</p>
<p>Celebrity endorsements and investments have risen sharply since the introduction of non-fungible tokens (NFTs). These blockchain-based, one-of-a-kind digital assets have given celebrities new ways to interact with their fan bases, monetize their brands, and explore the fascinating world of cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>However, the NFT market is infamously unpredictable and volatile, leading to frequent sharp fluctuations in price. Unfortunately for Bieber, this instability led to the loss of his Bored Ape Yacht Club (BAYC) NFT investment. Although a sharp decline in value is unquestionably a serious financial blow, it is crucial to take the bigger picture into account.</p>
<h2>Justin Bieber&rsquo;s forays into NFTs</h2>
<p>The $1.2 million loss from his NFT investment, while significant, is probably manageable for Justin Bieber, whose estimated net worth was $285 million as of September 2021. The &ldquo;Peaches&rdquo; artist has diversified his sources of income, reducing the impact of the NFT&rsquo;s decline through music, merchandising, and endorsements.</p>
<p>There are also speculations that the BAYC NFT was a reward from MoonPay as a promotional tactic.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Justin Bieber was gifted that NFT by the company MoonPay as a promotional tactic so they could use his clout to pump the value of their scam while they dumped their NFTs on retail (you reading this) as you bought.</p>
<p>&mdash; Autism Capital &#129513; (@AutismCapital) <a href="https://twitter.com/AutismCapital/status/1675942028247699457?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 3, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Many famous people have adopted the NFT culture, however, not everyone has been successful. Some people have made these investments as part of a bigger marketing strategy rather than to earn rewards. Celebrities get exposure and audience interaction by affiliating with the forward-thinking digital movement by purchasing NFTs. Some like Snoop Dogg and Wiz Khalifa have gone ahead to <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ape-price-soars-as-snoop-dogg-wiz-khalifa-launch-apecoin-themed-music-nfts/">launch ApeCoin-themed Music NFTs</a>.</p>
<p>However, not all NFT endeavours are unsuccessful. Some celebrities have gotten rich by selling NFTs for astronomical prices. It&rsquo;s a game with a high chance of a high payoff.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/justin-biebers-1-3m-nft-investment-depreciates-by-more-than-95/">Justin Bieber&#8217;s $1.3M NFT investment depreciates by more than 95%</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/justin-biebers-1-3m-nft-investment-depreciates-by-more-than-95/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why is the Verge (XVG) price soaring? It’s up 295%</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/why-is-the-verge-xvg-price-soaring-its-up-295/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/why-is-the-verge-xvg-price-soaring-its-up-295/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 08:39:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/why-is-the-verge-xvg-price-soaring-its-up-295/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>At press time, the price of XVG token had soared 295% over the past seven days. The token was trading at $0.006906. The Verge&#8217;s market cap has also gone up by almost 400% over the past three weeks. What started as a slow steady bull case for the Verge (XVG) token has turned into a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/why-is-the-verge-xvg-price-soaring-its-up-295/">Why is the Verge (XVG) price soaring? It’s up 295%</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul class="decimal_type">
<li>At press time, the price of XVG token had soared 295% over the past seven days.</li>
<li>The token was trading at $0.006906.</li>
<li>The Verge&rsquo;s market cap has also gone up by almost 400% over the past three weeks.</li>
</ul>
<p>What started as a slow steady bull case for the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/verge/what-is-verge/">Verge (XVG</a>) token has turned into a monster Bull Run after the token price went up by about 300% on June 3. And although the price has slightly pulled back from the June 3 high, it is still 295% high compared to where it was seven days ago.</p>
<p>Verge was long considered dead after it drastically dipped at the beginning of 2023 at a time when most of the cryptocurrencies showed some signs of recovery from the 2022 bear market. However, all that started to change in mid-June when the current bull trend started.</p>
<div class="fr-img-space-wrap"><span class="fr-img-caption fr-fic fr-dib fr-draggable" style="width: 615px"><span class="fr-img-wrap">
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/04/1688459245613-69a2f44e-176c-4632-9d8e-5adc2e19b651.jpg" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="615" height="372"><span class="fr-inner" style="background: transparent;position: relative"><em>Verge (XVG) price chart. Source Coinmarketcap</em></span></p>
<p></p></span></span>
<p class="fr-img-space-wrap2">&nbsp;</p>
</div>
<p>While the Verge investors and traders are excited about the current bull case for the token, most crypto investors are still sceptical about the upward movement as questions of why the token is taking a ride ringer. In this article, we shall explain why the Verge (XVG) token price is rising.</p>
<h2>Increased Verge (XVG) activity</h2>
<p>In addition to the price surging, the Verge has also experienced an increased trading volume, which skyrocketed by a staggering 380% on June 4 to a record $507 million. And although the trading volume had dropped to $480 million at press time, the figure still shows there is still a high trading activity.</p>
<p>In addition to the increased market activity, there are speculations of possible manipulation by seasoned cryptocurrency investors otherwise known as crypto whales who could be angling to dispose of their large XVG holdings at a profit. While this is not confirmed, it is important to be careful when <a href="https://coinjournal.net/cryptocurrencies/trade/">trading cryptocurrencies</a> since they are extremely volatile assets.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/why-is-the-verge-xvg-price-soaring-its-up-295/">Why is the Verge (XVG) price soaring? It’s up 295%</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/why-is-the-verge-xvg-price-soaring-its-up-295/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Anthony Pompliano expects SEC to eventually approve a Spot Bitcoin ETF</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/anthony-pompliano-sec-approve-spot-bitcoin-etf/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wajeeh Khan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 01:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Interview]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=145078</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Pompliano says underlying fundamentals of Bitcoin are strengthening. He expects a Spot Bitcoin ETF to be a meaningful catalyst for BTC. Bitcoin is currently up a whopping 85% versus the start of the year. Anthony Pompliano agrees that Bitcoin could see friction in the near term but remains bullish on the digital asset for the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/anthony-pompliano-sec-approve-spot-bitcoin-etf/">Anthony Pompliano expects SEC to eventually approve a Spot Bitcoin ETF</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Pompliano says underlying fundamentals of Bitcoin are strengthening.</li>
<li>He expects a Spot Bitcoin ETF to be a meaningful catalyst for BTC.</li>
<li>Bitcoin is currently up a whopping 85% versus the start of the year.</li>
</ul>
<p>Anthony Pompliano agrees that <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> could see friction in the near term but remains bullish on the digital asset for the long term.</p>
<h2>Pompliano shares his view on Bitcoin</h2>
<p>The Founder of Pomp Investments is constructive because the underlying fundamentals related to the world&rsquo;s largest cryptocurrency by market cap are improving.</p>
<blockquote><p>Bitcoin is anti-fragile. We see hash rate hitting all-time highs. We see adoption hitting all-time highs. People are realizing its value and they&rsquo;re putting all sorts of capital into the network.</p></blockquote>
<p>The total supply of Bitcoin is slated to <a href="https://coinjournal.net/learn/what-is-bitcoin-halving/">halve</a> in April of 2024 which has historically served as a catalyst for its price.</p>
<p>At writing, BTC is already up about 85% versus the start of the year.</p>
<h2>Is a Spot Bitcoin ETF coming soon?</h2>
<p>Pompliano is also convinced that the U.S. SEC will eventually <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/secs-spot-bitcoin-etf-approval-fairly-high-bernstein/">approve</a> a Spot Bitcoin ETF which will likely be another tailwind for the cryptocurrency.</p>
<p>His comments follow a recent wave of applications for such an exchange-traded fund that the regulator has already dubbed <a href="https://www.afr.com/markets/currencies/us-regulator-pushes-back-against-wave-of-spot-bitcoin-etf-filings-20230701-p5dkyt" target="_blank" rel="noopener">inadequate</a>. Still, Pompliano said today on CNBC&rsquo;s &ldquo;<a href="https://www.cnbc.com/video/2023/07/03/bitcoin-is-anti-fragile-says-pomp-investments-anthony-pompliano.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Squawk Box</a>&rdquo;:</p>
<blockquote><p>It&rsquo;s a small detail that is more of a formality. We&rsquo;re watching Wall Street saying we want access to BTC. So, when it [spot bitcoin ETF] happens, a lot of people will pour capital into it.</p></blockquote>
<p>He&rsquo;s confident in particular because among notable names that have recently filed for a Spot Bitcoin ETF is <a href="https://decrypt.co/147177/blackrock-spot-bitcoin-etf-filing-sec-coinbase-surveillance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BlackRock</a> that has a history of going for an exchange-traded fund only when it&rsquo;s convinced it will get approval.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/anthony-pompliano-sec-approve-spot-bitcoin-etf/">Anthony Pompliano expects SEC to eventually approve a Spot Bitcoin ETF</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
