<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 20:54:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Porsche halts NFT mint amid negative feedback from community</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/porsche-halts-nft-mint-amid-negative-feedback-from-community/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/porsche-halts-nft-mint-amid-negative-feedback-from-community/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 20:54:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/porsche-halts-nft-mint-amid-negative-feedback-from-community/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Porsche announces halt to NFT mint of iconic 911 Model, just a day after public mint opened. The German car manufacturer said it had listened to the community&#8217;s feedback and the mint will halt on 25 January at 6 am UTC-5. Porsche had offered 7,500 NFTs for the public mint, with each digital replica priced [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/porsche-halts-nft-mint-amid-negative-feedback-from-community/">Porsche halts NFT mint amid negative feedback from community</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>Porsche announces halt to NFT mint of iconic 911 Model, just a day after public mint opened.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>The German car manufacturer said it had listened to the community&rsquo;s feedback and the mint will halt on 25 January at 6 am UTC-5.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><strong><em>Porsche had offered 7,500 NFTs for the public mint, with each digital replica priced at 0.911 ETH.</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">German sports car maker Porsche has <a href="https://twitter.com/eth_porsche/status/1617942323563991040" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">announced</a> its stopping the minting of its non-fungible token (<a href="https://coinjournal.net/glossary/non-fungible-token-nft/">NFT</a>) collection, less than two days after opening it for the public on 23 January.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Porsche on NFT- &nbsp;the community spoke</h2>
<p dir="ltr">According to an update the car manufacturer posted on Twitter on Tuesday, the decision to halt the inaugural mint follows the response of the community. Per the German-based company, the negative feedback it received from holders was enough for it to cut the supply of the NFTs and halt the mint.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>Our holders have spoken. We&rsquo;re going to cut our supply and stop the mint to move forward with creating the best experience for an exclusive community. More info in the next hours</em>,&rdquo; the Porsche NFT project team noted on Twitter.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The NFT collection offered a digital replica of the car maker&rsquo;s iconic 911 model, with the 7,500 NFTs on offer priced at 0.911 ETH each. At the current <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/">price of Ethereum</a>, that was roughly $1,490 per item &ndash; a price heavily criticized as being too expensive.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Really sad. No community. No comms. No value. Glad our community hasn&rsquo;t fallen for it. Big brands should take note. This is a valuable lesson for them. Extracting value not gonna cut it.</p>
<p>&mdash; Sta&#347; May (@haymaker_studio) <a href="https://twitter.com/haymaker_studio/status/1617703713023614981?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 24, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">The company&rsquo;s Web3 strategy has been criticized as largely underwhelming across the community, and many see this as another example of how much more traditional companies need to learn about Web3 before launching projects.</p>
<p dir="ltr">While Porsche noted the mint was halting, it provided an <a href="https://twitter.com/eth_porsche/status/1617965545982423040">update</a> that noted it would remain open until Wednesday, 25 January at 6 am UTC-5.</p>
<p dir="ltr">At the time of writing, of the total supply provided, 5,639 NFTs are open for minting. The FAQ page <a href="https://nft.porsche.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">shows</a> the mint supports three wallets &ndash; MetaMask, Coinbase and WalletConnect.</p>
<p dir="ltr"></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/porsche-halts-nft-mint-amid-negative-feedback-from-community/">Porsche halts NFT mint amid negative feedback from community</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/porsche-halts-nft-mint-amid-negative-feedback-from-community/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bunzz Raises $4.5M Seed Round to Expand its Smart Contract Hub for DApp Development</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bunzz-raises-4-5m-seed-round-to-expand-its-smart-contract-hub-for-dapp-development/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/bunzz-raises-4-5m-seed-round-to-expand-its-smart-contract-hub-for-dapp-development/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire  ]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 18:37:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=99976</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Singpore, Singapore, 24th January, 2023, Chainwire Bunzz a web3 development platform for decentralized applications, has completed a $4.5M seed round. Investors included gjmp, DG Daiwa Ventures, Coincheck, and Ceres. Funding will be used to help build out Bunzz&#8217;s Smart Contract Hub, which is already used by more than 8,000 dApp developers. (Product page: https://bunzz.dev/ ) [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bunzz-raises-4-5m-seed-round-to-expand-its-smart-contract-hub-for-dapp-development/">Bunzz Raises $4.5M Seed Round to Expand its Smart Contract Hub for DApp Development</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Singpore, Singapore, 24th January, 2023, Chainwire</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://bunzz.dev/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Bunzz</a> a web3 development platform for decentralized applications, has completed a $4.5M seed round. Investors included gjmp, DG Daiwa Ventures, Coincheck, and Ceres. Funding will be used to help build out Bunzz&rsquo;s Smart Contract Hub, which is already used by more than 8,000 dApp developers. (Product page: <a href="https://bunzz.dev/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://bunzz.dev/</a> )</p>
<p>Bunzz has established a strong track record since its launch 11 months ago. Over 8,000 DApp developers have been using the platform, and more than 3,000 DApp projects have been deployed on-chain, making it one of the largest DApp development infrastructures in Asia.</p>
<p>The platform has been recognized by top-tier landmarks as a major infrastructure service in the smart contract development sector. It has been featured on the web3 development infrastructure chaos map published by Coinbase. Additionally, Bunzz was also a finalist in Icetea Lab, Singapore&rsquo;s largest web3 accelerator program.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" src="https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/2023-01-22_171833_1674375526ZGLvl6KpBL.jpg" alt=""></p>
<p>Currently, engineers who can handle DApp development are very rare. The reason is that the barrier to developing smart contracts, which are web3-specific programs, is high. In other words, if web2 software engineers could handle contract development, it would be much easier to enter the web3 space.</p>
<p>Bunzz has succeeded in simplifying the previously complex development process by providing frequently used contracts as modules and wrapping the preparation of nodes and the launch of the development environment.</p>
<p><b>About Bunzz&rsquo;s core feature &ldquo;Smart Contract Hub&rdquo;</b></p>
<p>Bunzz offers a modularized version of <a href="https://lastrust.notion.site/d291eeafc5c145a59cce0744e691d595?v=0056417f7bbf47ea9b4c58155ff39a61" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">frequently used smart contracts</a>. These are freely available to general users and can be reused by other DApp developers.</p>
<p>On the other hand, there is a similar service called Open Zeppelin, an open-source library. The difference between this and Bunzz is convenience. While OZ&rsquo;s code is just a library and cannot be deployed right away as it requires a development environment and nodes, Bunzz&rsquo;s modules can be deployed with just a GUI. It is truly the &ldquo;web3 version of Docker Hub&rdquo;.</p>
<p><b>Partial list of smart contract modules offered by Bunzz</b></p>
<p><u>NFT related modules:</u></p>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://app.bunzz.dev/module-templates/7810bd83-0048-4300-8922-d1462f64744d" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">NFT (IPFS Mintable) </a></li>
<li><a href="https://app.bunzz.dev/module-templates/c22c6394-a79d-440b-a35c-d636795feee0" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">NFT (Breedable) </a></li>
<li><a href="https://app.bunzz.dev/module-templates/73257d1c-065b-11ed-b939-0242ac120002" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">NFT (Custom-URI) </a></li>
<li><a href="https://app.bunzz.dev/module-templates/08ee5804-065d-11ed-b939-0242ac120002" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">NFT (Royalties) </a></li>
<li><a href="https://app.bunzz.dev/module-templates/63680994-14ad-4b83-a35e-52a4df316d43" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Simple Marketplace (For NFT) </a></li>
<li><a href="https://app.bunzz.dev/module-templates/7158ba81-26b1-4c19-99ba-1f0f5a5b4aeb" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Auction Marketplace (NFT) </a></li>
<li><a href="https://app.bunzz.dev/module-templates/6a1a2a56-b1a3-4f53-be87-d18c086596f5" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">NFT (ERC721) </a></li>
<li><a href="https://app.bunzz.dev/module-templates/cd67314e-c753-4fa8-96e5-91e49766da3c" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Non-Tradable Token (ERC4671) </a></li>
<li><a href="https://app.bunzz.dev/module-templates/187ea1d4-97b8-44d3-9a95-2fd5e37e6436" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Simple Marketplace (For MultiToken) </a></li>
<li><a href="https://app.bunzz.dev/module-templates/dce2df51-88ac-4635-9f14-e2c3756aef9c" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Auction Marketplace (For Multi Token) </a></li>
</ul>
<p><u>DeFi related modules:</u></p>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://app.bunzz.dev/module-templates/32c5d245-6b7b-4693-8f6a-7afa68737be7" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Token (ERC20) </a></li>
<li><a href="https://app.bunzz.dev/module-templates/6d56201e-f73b-41e6-81fa-e6904530ce0b" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Token (ERC20 Capped) </a></li>
<li><a href="https://app.bunzz.dev/module-templates/afa05522-5f39-4850-baf3-3390fd139f54" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">TokenERC20DAOToken</a></li>
<li><a href="https://app.bunzz.dev/module-templates/1b198f1a-593b-48f9-9035-a46b1f622313" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">ReflectionToken</a></li>
<li><a href="https://app.bunzz.dev/module-templates/7db815ba-762e-4f45-8db2-bc92f3129179" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">MultiToken (ERC1155) </a></li>
</ul>
<p>Kenta Akutsu, CEO &amp; Co-Founder of Bunzz, explained: <i>&ldquo;Bunzz ultimately aims to become web3&rsquo;s equivalent to Docker Hub. Immutable smart contracts on the blockchain are open programs, also called &lsquo;public goods,&rsquo; because anyone can access and use them without permission. However, the usage flow and the logic of their operation are difficult to understand, making it inconvenient for engineers who want to reuse them. Bunzz aims to solve this problem by incentivizing creators of smart contract modules to create more accurate coding and documentation. Please feel free to contact us via </i><a href="https://twitter.com/BunzzDev" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><i>twitter</i></a><i> or </i><a href="https://discord.gg/ZsqvmdBA4e" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><i>discord</i></a><i>.&rdquo;</i></p>
<p><u>The 13 participating investors:</u></p>
<p><img decoding="async" src="https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/fundraising_PR_main_visual_1674377007ljKn0JO2x7.jpg" alt=""></p>
<p><u>Bunzz pte ltd company profile:</u></p>
<ul>
<li>Company name: Bunzz pte ltd</li>
<li>Representative: Kenta Akutsu</li>
<li>Head Office: 6 Eu Tong Sen Street #12-17 The Central Singapore 059817</li>
<li>Business: Operation of web3 development infrastructure &ldquo;Bunzz&rdquo;</li>
<li>Establishment: May, 2022</li>
<li>Capital: 4,500,000 USD</li>
<li>URL: https://bunzz.dev</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Contact</strong></p>
<p>CEO, Kenta Akutsu, Bunzz pte ltd, kenta@bunzz.dev</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bunzz-raises-4-5m-seed-round-to-expand-its-smart-contract-hub-for-dapp-development/">Bunzz Raises $4.5M Seed Round to Expand its Smart Contract Hub for DApp Development</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/bunzz-raises-4-5m-seed-round-to-expand-its-smart-contract-hub-for-dapp-development/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The global crypto meltdown: Is it the end or just a new start?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/the-global-crypto-meltdown-is-it-the-end-or-just-a-new-start/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/the-global-crypto-meltdown-is-it-the-end-or-just-a-new-start/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 18:07:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDCs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto adoption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/the-global-crypto-meltdown-is-it-the-end-or-just-a-new-start/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrency, volatility and the risks therein. What&#8217;s crypto&#8217;s long-term viability, including the impact of decentralised finance (DeFi). Are Central Bank Digital Currencies (CBDCs) evidence that crypto is here to stay? Since the introduction of the first cryptocurrency transactions and digital tokens in the 1990s following their democratisation in the 2010s, the current crisis in the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-global-crypto-meltdown-is-it-the-end-or-just-a-new-start/">The global crypto meltdown: Is it the end or just a new start?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>Cryptocurrency, volatility and the risks therein.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>What&rsquo;s crypto&rsquo;s long-term viability, including the impact of decentralised finance (DeFi).</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><strong><em>Are Central Bank Digital Currencies (CBDCs) evidence that crypto is here to stay? </em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Since the introduction of the first <a href="https://coinjournal.net/cryptocurrencies/">cryptocurrency</a> transactions and digital tokens in the 1990s following their democratisation in the 2010s, the current crisis in the cryptocurrency market is unprecedented.</p>
<p>In late 2020, <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> took a massive dive from which it has yet to recoup. This precipitous fall is being discussed with the concerning demise of some &ldquo;stablecoins,&rdquo; which were meant to be less unpredictable.</p>
<p>This is exacerbated by the decline of once-prominent cryptocurrencies, especially after being accused of fraud, as in the FTX controversy. Among all the leading trading platforms, FTX has been ranked third as it served a population of one million at the peak of its career.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Its aftermath has had a significant impact on investors, and this, according to experts, would certainly restrict the rate of adoption of crypto assets over the next few seasons.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">The clock of volatility is ticking&nbsp;</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Tokens that may be exchanged for digital currency are one type of crypto asset (i.e. cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin and Ethereum). Security tokens are used to invest in a company through trade assistance bots like <a href="https://the-bitcoin-bank-pro.com" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">bitcoin bank</a>, giving the holder a stake in that company, whereas utility tokens are exchanged for access to a finished good or service once they have been created.</p>
<p>Unlike other cryptocurrencies, <a href="https://coinjournal.net/glossary/stablecoin/">stablecoins</a> are backed by something other than a digital ledger of transactions, such as the U.S. dollar, a commodity like gold, or an investment vehicle like a bank deposit (e.g. a stock or a bond).&nbsp;</p>
<p>The daily news is littered with articles about the decline of Bitcoin. While this isn&rsquo;t the first time its value has dropped, it is the largest loss since late 2020, therefore it deserves special attention.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Investors fled these riskier investments when interest rates rose, which contributed to the crash. Bitcoin may be on the mend, but it has a long way to go before it reaches its former glory.</p>
<p>The media attention that cryptocurrencies have received recently has fanned many people&rsquo;s fears about their long-term viability. The unregulated markets of the latter are notorious for their high levels of volatility and are often linked to speculation.</p>
<p>In fact, the BBC just reported a 30% increase in bitcoin laundering in 2021. Investors lost over $1 billion worth of cryptocurrency to scam schemes in 2021, according to the U.S. Federal Trade Commission, whose job is to protect consumers. Those who lost money due to fraud have, unsurprisingly, seen very little return on their investments.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Crypto serving as the trading lifeline for a billion users&nbsp;</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Still, the business use of cryptocurrencies is rising, albeit slowly. Many publicly traded corporations, including Starbucks and McDonald&rsquo;s, have begun accepting Bitcoin as payment, according to specialists studying the implications of this trend for corporate social responsibility.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This is especially true in their El Salvador locations since Bitcoin has been <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/weekly-report-el-salvador-adopts-bitcoin-as-legal-tender/">recognised as a legal tender</a> there.</p>
<p>Even though Japan is not actively pursuing the adoption of Bitcoin as a currency, certain companies, including the Japanese e-commerce behemoth Rakuten, have decided to accept cryptocurrencies instead.&nbsp;</p>
<p>They claim to be motivated by the need to broaden the range of payment methods available to their clientele.</p>
<p>The number of people using cryptocurrency increases each year. Exchange platform Crypto.com, for instance, predicted that by the end of 2021, over 295 million users would have participated in the cryptocurrency market. As of December 2022, the platform anticipated having one billion users.</p>
<p>In addition, those whose traditional banking options are unreliable or insecure can use cryptocurrencies to gain access to a decentralised financial system. Among the justifications, the Governor of El Salvador offered for recognising Bitcoin as legal cash was to provide an alternative banking system for the country&rsquo;s less well-off citizens.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Crypto to witness a sporty oscillation&nbsp;</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Cryptocurrencies&rsquo; long-term viability is impacted by a number of factors, including rising interest in decentralised finance (DeFi) and the maturation of the metaverse. Stablecoins are frequently used to facilitate the running of decentralised financial systems.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Similarly, the metaverse, a collection of interconnected 3D simulated realities, accepts cryptocurrency payments for goods and services.</p>
<p>Despite the recent meltdown in the crypto asset market, industry experts are certain that decentralised finance, especially in the form of products backed by cryptocurrencies, will survive. This is due to the market existence and competition present.</p>
<p>In addition, they believe that although the recent precipitous drop in cryptocurrency-related markets has eliminated some participants, this is in fact a positive development.</p>
<p>These participants argue that a significant decline in the value of crypto asset marketplaces is not only inevitable but also beneficial because it will help to restore market equilibrium.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">The silver lining: Crypto is the dark horse</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Another piece of evidence that digital currencies are here to stay is the introduction of coins by central banks in the form of blockchain and digital currencies (<a href="https://coinjournal.net/glossary/central-bank-digital-currency-cbdc/">CBDCs</a>). The Bank of Canada is, in fact, developing plans to establish a CBDC.&nbsp;</p>
<p>CBDCs, if released by the Bank of Canada, would be &ldquo;official digital money (that) would keep their dollar amount in Canadian dollars since they are authorized by the Bank of Canada, exactly like bank notes,&rdquo; the institution claims.</p>
<p><a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bahamas-most-advanced-cbdc-but-is-that-a-bad-thing/">The Sand Dollar of the Bahamas</a> and the Naira of Nigeria are only two examples of countries that have produced similar currencies (eNaira). CBDCs are distinct from privately produced digital currencies (like Bitcoin or Ethereum) since they are not designed for speculation or prediction but rather for use in everyday commerce. In terms of utility, they are on par with cash.</p>
<p>Aside from making fiscal and monetary policies easier to implement in the issuing countries, another goal of CBDCs is to increase financial inclusion among those who lack access to the regular banking system.</p>
<p>Cryptocurrency will be here to stay thanks to developments in the realm of digital currencies both in the metaverse and with the advent of the CBDC.</p>
<p>Because of their resilience, crypto asset&rsquo;s physical manifestations will change over time in step with the underlying technology that enables them (principally blockchains) and the cyclical fluctuations in demand from end-users and/or financial backers.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-global-crypto-meltdown-is-it-the-end-or-just-a-new-start/">The global crypto meltdown: Is it the end or just a new start?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/the-global-crypto-meltdown-is-it-the-end-or-just-a-new-start/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum whales are attracted to Bitgert (BRISE): 3 BIG reasons to know!</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/how-the-whales-of-ethereum-attracted-bitgert-brise-3-big-reasons-to-know/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 17:39:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Whales]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/how-the-whales-of-ethereum-attracted-bitgert-brise-3-big-reasons-to-know/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What is Bitgert (BRISE)? Bitgert&#8217;s gasless blockchain and its impact on BRISE price as interest grows. Unlike Ethereum, Bitgert boasts a CEX and an upcoming DEX platform. Ethereum (ETH) has been one of the cryptocurrencies with the best performance on the market so far this month.&#160; According to the figures provided by CMC, the price [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/how-the-whales-of-ethereum-attracted-bitgert-brise-3-big-reasons-to-know/">Ethereum whales are attracted to Bitgert (BRISE): 3 BIG reasons to know!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr"><em>What is Bitgert (BRISE)?</em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><em>Bitgert&rsquo;s gasless blockchain and its impact on BRISE price as interest grows.</em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><em>Unlike Ethereum, Bitgert boasts a CEX and an upcoming DEX platform.</em></li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Ethereum (ETH) has been one of the cryptocurrencies with the best performance on the market so far this month.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to the figures provided by CMC, the price of <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/">Ethereum</a> has climbed by 31% this month, which represents a gain in just 2 weeks. That&rsquo;s quite a remarkable display, indeed.</p>
<p>The price prediction for the Ethereum currency for the month of January appears to be favorable, and it is possible that the coin will keep its optimistic feeling for the upcoming few days. Despite this encouraging trend, though, investors in Ethereum are diversifying their holdings by purchasing other promising cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>During the past few weeks, Ethereum whales have reportedly been purchasing Bitgert (<a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitgert/">BRISE</a>), as stated by experts in cryptocurrencies. In point of fact, during the course of this month, the amount of these whales who have been introducing $BRISE to their holdings have already been significantly expanding. A few individuals have also been stockpiling this coin.</p>
<p>Analysts of cryptocurrencies believe that large holders of Ethereum are drawn to the developments involving Bitgert, which have the chance to cause $BRISE to soar in the coming weeks.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Mentioned below are the leading reasons why Ethereum enthusiasts are interested in Bitgert. But first, let us discuss what ios Bitgerta is and how it operates as a separate digital entity.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Bitgert?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The people who came up with the idea for the company Bitgert (who will be referred to in what follows as the &ldquo;Bitgert team&rdquo;) believe that their primary responsibility is to make a contribution to the formation of a society that is bound together by the shared aspiration to raise their standard of living through application of cutting-edge innovation and the application of technology of the highest possible quality.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In this regard, blockchain is now the technology that is receiving the most attention, and it is generally seen as the technology that will most naturally succeed the internet.</p>
<p>This new method of data and value generation, transmission, storage, and utilization is made possible by blockchain technology, which is a combination of a number of previously developed technologies. These technologies include distributed data space, peer-to-peer data transfer, consensus mechanisms, and encryption algorithms.</p>
<p>Due to the modified codes behind the foundation of Bitgert, it has higher levels of scalability, security, and stability.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Bitgert offers an expanding blockchain network that is user-friendly, low-cost, and configurable by providing cutting-edge architectures of virtual machines, adaptive sandboxes, value exchange protocols, and forking mechanisms.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Bitgert is able to achieve a productivity rate of up to 100,000 transactions per second (TPS) thanks in large part to the optimization of its block interval, block volume, and consensus process.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Bitgert believes that as technology advancement establishes a new power generation relation network, it will address the issue of trust in communication skills and organically incorporate societal consequences, individual behavior, and value swap into an inseparable whole. This will occur as a result of the network&rsquo;s ability to organically implement societal consensus, individual behavior, and value exchange.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">The Bitgert gasless blockchain remains a significant magnet for interest</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The Bitgert BRC20 chain is among the most important products that helped create $BRISE as one of the cryptocurrencies that have the potential to have the greatest impact on the market. The introduction of this blockchain with no initial gas fee caused the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitgert/">price of Bitgert</a> to soar to its all-time high.</p>
<p>The BRC20 blockchain offers significant advantages over Ethereum&rsquo;s chain in terms of cost, speed, and safety.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Despite the fact that Ethereum has <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-finally-migrates-to-a-proof-of-stake-after-completing-the-merge/">transitioned to a PoS model</a>, this remains the case. BRISE&rsquo;s adoption is expected to continue growing at a faster rate than Ethereum&rsquo;s, which should result in improved price and performance for BRISE. One of the grounds ETH whales are purchasing Bitgert right now is because of this.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitgert has its own exchanges</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Despite being one of the most popular cryptocurrencies and the pioneering project in the cryptocurrency space, Ethereum does not yet have its own decentralized exchange.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The <a href="https://coinjournal.net/compare/best-cryptocurrency-exchanges/">cryptocurrency exchange</a> is an essential function that Ethereum is missing, and Bitgert has indeed developed one. However, there are still other trading exchanges that support the trading of Bitgert too.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Due to the recently created CEX and the forthcoming DEX, a significant number of whales are investing in Bitgert coins. These items have the capacity to skyrocket the demand for Bitgert coins, which will draw a significant number of investors.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitgert decentralized sector</h2>
<p dir="ltr">As a result of the anticipated effects of the decentralized market, Ethereum whales are indeed stockpiling Bitgert. The BRISE team considers this to be among the most important things they will be launching this year.&nbsp;</p>
<p>As per the reports given, the decentralized sector of Bitgert is backed up by advanced stages, <a href="https://bigmoneyrushapp.com" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">click here</a> to get further details regarding bots which support the trading of Bitgert tokens. &nbsp;This online marketplace is going to emerge as one of the highly popular.</p>
<h2>The final word</h2>
<p dir="ltr">These are significant new developments surrounding the Bitgert project, which are attracting whales from Ethereum as well as other huge cryptocurrencies. As a result of these recent events, the value of Bitgert&rsquo;s token is expected to skyrocket in the coming weeks. Because of this, a significant number of crypto whales are gravitating toward them.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/how-the-whales-of-ethereum-attracted-bitgert-brise-3-big-reasons-to-know/">Ethereum whales are attracted to Bitgert (BRISE): 3 BIG reasons to know!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Metacade’s (MCADE) Presale Is Selling Out Amid the Crypto Winter – Here’s Why</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/metacades-mcade-presale-is-selling-out-amid-the-crypto-winter-heres-why/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/metacades-mcade-presale-is-selling-out-amid-the-crypto-winter-heres-why/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice Davies]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 17:17:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/metacades-mcade-presale-is-selling-out-amid-the-crypto-winter-heres-why/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>With an ongoing crypto winter leaving many investors dissatisfied with subpar gains (if any) in 2022, 2023 is expected to bring greener pastures. While many tokens are predicted to make a roaring comeback, there&#8217;s one in particular that many have recently placed big bets on. It&#8217;s called Metacade, and the hype surrounding the project has [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/metacades-mcade-presale-is-selling-out-amid-the-crypto-winter-heres-why/">Metacade’s (MCADE) Presale Is Selling Out Amid the Crypto Winter – Here’s Why</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">With an ongoing crypto winter leaving many investors dissatisfied with subpar gains (if any) in 2022, 2023 is expected to bring greener pastures. While many tokens are predicted to make a roaring comeback, there&rsquo;s one in particular that many have recently placed big bets on. It&rsquo;s called Metacade, and the hype surrounding the project has led to continuous sellouts during its token presale. Read on to find out why. </p>
<h2 dir="ltr">The Ongoing Crypto Winter Has Left Many Investors Feeling Frosty</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Following rising inflation, interest rate hikes, and the downfall of some of crypto&rsquo;s most prominent players in 2022, many projects are down significantly from their 2021 highs during the current crypto winter. Bitcoin &ndash; often regarded as the benchmark for crypto performance &ndash; fell 77.5% from its $69,000 high in November 2021 to a low of $15,476 roughly a year later.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Altcoins like DOT plummeted over -92% in the same period, while others have shown a little more resilience. TRX, for example, has roughly matched BTC&rsquo;s performance, falling -74.9% from its 2021 high to its 2022 low. While prices have made a slight resurgence in early 2023, some still consider the crypto winter woes to be far from over. Despite this ongoing bearishness, one token has been attracting millions in investment: Metacade.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Metacade (MCADE)?</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade</u></a> is a play-to-earn (P2E) community hub that&rsquo;s aiming to be an early leader in the GameFi revolution. Its goal is to be the number one place in Web3 to explore, learn, and make the most of P2E gaming. Metacade gives players all the tools they need to get ahead in this fast-growing space, like dedicated forums, reviews, game leaderboards, and leading GameFi alpha shared by P2E veterans.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Moreover, it fosters a loyal community by giving players as much value as possible. Alongside regular tournaments, prize draws, and competitions, Metacade is using the power of decentralization and crypto for good, rewarding players for their contributions and giving them a say in the games they&rsquo;ll be playing. There are even plans for a job board and for the project to transition into a <a href="https://www.investopedia.com/tech/what-dao/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>decentralized autonomous organization (DAO)</u></a>.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">A Deep Dive Into Metacade&rsquo;s (MCADE) Key Features</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Traditionally, gamers are invited to share reviews and tips with others without receiving anything for their efforts. Who benefits from this? Primarily the platform hosting these reviews and tips.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade realizes this, and instead of benefiting and giving nothing back, it&rsquo;s paying users directly with the MCADE token for their role in growing the community. That means even if you&rsquo;re just getting started in P2E, you can earn by simply sharing your opinions on a new game you&rsquo;ve been playing or posting tips that other players can use to get ahead.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">In late 2023, Metacade will also be awarding its first Metagrant. Metagrants enable the community to direct the project&rsquo;s funds toward selected game developers, intending to finance the next generation of community-backed P2E games. Developers enter their game proposals into one of the Metagrant competitions, and the idea that earns the most votes from MCADE holders is awarded funding from the treasury.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The finished title is hosted in Metacade&rsquo;s virtual arcade for anyone to log on and enjoy. All it would take is one groundbreaking game to be produced by the community, and Metacade could be thrust into the mainstream media spotlight, sending the MCADE token soaring.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">As mentioned, Metacade will also be launching a job board. Expected in 2024, this board will feature casual gigs, part-time roles, and full-time positions working with Web3 and GameFi titans. Whether you&rsquo;re interested in testing games using Metacade&rsquo;s testing environment for some extra income or looking to get your foot in the door as a game developer, you&rsquo;re bound to find something that suits your skills.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Finally, Metacade will fully transition to a DAO in late 2024. While the groundwork is expected to be laid as early as Q2 2023, this transition will see the core Metacade team stepping down and handing the reins over to elected Metacade members. From this point forward, MCADE holders will determine the future of the world&rsquo;s first democratically-run virtual arcade.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Metacade (MCADE) Might Just Be One of the Best Performers of 2023</h2>
<p dir="ltr">So just how well has Metacade been performing in presale, despite the ongoing crypto winter? In the first seven weeks of the MCADE presale, approximately $3.4m million has been raised by thousands of investors across the globe.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The price of MCADE tokens has already risen from the starting price of $0.008 to $0.012, with prices expected to reach $0.02 by the end of its presale. However, many analysts believe MCADE has much more room to grow, with some setting targets of at least $0.20 by the end of 2023 if the crypto winter subsides as forecast.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">This is supported by the fact that GameFi is set to take off this year. <a href="https://www.absolutereports.com/global-play-to-earn-nft-games-market-20851980" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Absolute Reports</u></a> puts the industry&rsquo;s annual growth rate at 20.4% between 2022 and 2028, while <a href="https://content-hub-static.crypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/GameFi_Past-Present-and-Future_Overview-with-Comparisons-to-Traditional-Gaming-Industry-2.pdf" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Crypto.com</u></a> predicts that it will grow much faster, at a rate of 100% per year. Given how critical social hubs are to gamers and Metacade&rsquo;s first-mover advantage, it could soon become the premier destination for all things P2E.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">If you think Metacade is on to something, then check out the MCADE presale as soon as possible. Time is quickly running out to grab MCADE tokens at $0.012 before it moves on to the next stage of presale!</p>
<p><strong>You can participate in the Metacade presale&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong><u>here</u></strong></a><strong>.</strong></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/metacades-mcade-presale-is-selling-out-amid-the-crypto-winter-heres-why/">Metacade’s (MCADE) Presale Is Selling Out Amid the Crypto Winter – Here’s Why</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/metacades-mcade-presale-is-selling-out-amid-the-crypto-winter-heres-why/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance admits &#8220;error&#8221; in mixing token reserves and user funds</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-admits-error-in-mixing-token-reserves-and-user-funds/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 17:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance Coin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-admits-error-in-mixing-token-reserves-and-user-funds/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Binance is allegedly working to fix the &#8220;error&#8221;. The crypto exchange released a proof of collateral report for all 94 Binance-pegged tokens, or B-Tokens. Data suggested the Binance wallet holding the exchange&#8217;s own token reserves also held user funds. Binance has reportedly acknowledged storing customers&#8217; funds in a wallet that also holds the cryptocurrency exchange&#8217;s [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-admits-error-in-mixing-token-reserves-and-user-funds/">Binance admits &#8220;error&#8221; in mixing token reserves and user funds</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>Binance is allegedly working to fix the &ldquo;error&rdquo;.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong><em><strong>The crypto exchange released a proof of collateral report for all 94 Binance-pegged tokens, or B-Tokens.</strong></em></strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><strong><em>Data suggested the Binance wallet holding the exchange&rsquo;s own token reserves also held user funds.</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/binance/">Binance</a> has reportedly acknowledged storing customers&rsquo; funds in a wallet that also holds the cryptocurrency exchange&rsquo;s in-house tokens.</p>
<p dir="ltr">A <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-01-24/binance-bnb-acknowledges-storing-users-crypto-with-reserves-in-error" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">report</a> by <em>Bloomberg</em> on Tuesday revealed that Binance had admitted to the fact, but noted this had happened erroneously.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Binance wallet holds B-Tokens and customer funds</h2>
<p dir="ltr">According to details attributed to a Binance official, the report noted the exchange had said the &lsquo;mixing&rsquo; of customer funds and collateral for its B-Tokens was done by mistake.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">B-Tokens are Binance-pegged versions of crypto tokens such as Bitcoin, Ethereum and Polkadot. They are wrapped tokens that allow for usability across BNB Smart Chain and other ecosystems. &nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Binance&rsquo;s proof of collateral report for its in-house tokens released on Monday showed the leading crypto exchange had all 94 B-Tokens fully collateralized. But while the tokens are supposed to be backed 1:1, the <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/collateral-btokens" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">proof of collateral page</a> showed many tokens had way more reserves than that which is needed to match the issued tokens.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This indicates user funds are also stored in the Binance 8 wallet.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The exchange explained the &ldquo;error&rdquo;, noting that the said wallet is a Binance cold wallet that has received collateral assets by mistake. &nbsp;The exchange had started fixing the error, the report added.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/binance-coin/">Binance Coin</a> token traded higher on Tuesday despite the news, with BNB up by 3.5% at the time of writing to change hands around $314.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-admits-error-in-mixing-token-reserves-and-user-funds/">Binance admits &#8220;error&#8221; in mixing token reserves and user funds</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The biggest cryptocurrencies around the world in 2023</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/the-biggest-cryptocurrencies-around-the-world-in-2023/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/the-biggest-cryptocurrencies-around-the-world-in-2023/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 16:58:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto adoption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/the-biggest-cryptocurrencies-around-the-world-in-2023/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Millions have turned to crypto markets to make money. Cryptocurrencies are outlawed in only nine countries in the world. Analysts agree on is that Bitcoin and Ethereum will hold the top two spots for quite some time. Cryptocurrencies, also known as digital currencies, have entirely changed the landscape of modern-day finance. The global financial system [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-biggest-cryptocurrencies-around-the-world-in-2023/">The biggest cryptocurrencies around the world in 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Millions have turned to crypto markets to make money.</li>
<li>Cryptocurrencies are outlawed in only nine countries in the world.</li>
<li>Analysts agree on is that Bitcoin and Ethereum will hold the top two spots for quite some time.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://coinjournal.net/glossary/cryptocurrency/">Cryptocurrencies</a>, also known as digital currencies, have entirely changed the landscape of modern-day finance. The global financial system has changed due to the emergence of these innovative assets.</p>
<p><a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/what-is-bitcoin/">Bitcoin&nbsp;</a>and other digital assets use revolutionary blockchain technology. A blockchain is a secure, public ledger that verifies any transactions.</p>
<p>This secure ledger, which cannot be interfered with or amended, provides validation for users and removes the need for a third party to provide a safe way to facilitate the transaction in the middle, such as a central bank. This is where the term decentralized comes from.</p>
<p><a href="https://coinjournal.net/cryptocurrencies/trade/">Cryptocurrency trading</a> has also become a popular investment option, with millions turning to crypto markets to make money. Of course, traditional markets such as forex and stocks still enjoy a serious market share. However, cryptocurrency trading has become a lucrative way to make money for people.</p>
<p>As more people learn about cryptocurrencies and blockchain technology, they become a common alternative to traditional currency and payment systems.</p>
<p>As a result, countries have begun using Bitcoin as legal tender, and many multibillion-dollar Western institutions are also invested in digital assets.</p>
<h2>Which countries are leading the way in this sector?</h2>
<p>Since the early 2010s, Bitcoin and other digital assets have entered mainstream conversations. As a result, cryptocurrencies are rapidly gaining traction around the world.&nbsp;</p>
<p>With it, the need for governments to create regulations and laws to ensure their safe use has also become a topic of discussion. There are only nine countries in the world where cryptocurrency is completely outlawed:</p>
<ul>
<li>Algeria</li>
<li>Bangladesh</li>
<li>China</li>
<li>Egypt</li>
<li>Iraq</li>
<li>Morocco</li>
<li>Nepal</li>
<li>Qatar</li>
<li>Tunisia</li>
</ul>
<p>On the other hand, countries such as the United Kingdom, Australia, Switzerland and Indonesia have led the way in terms of cryptocurrency adoption, paving the way for other countries to follow suit.&nbsp;</p>
<p>You can even gamble with cryptocurrency anonymously with <a href="https://dappgambl.com/casinos/anonymous-casinos/">anonymous casinos</a> in some locations, according to dappgambl.com. So take a look if you are looking to get a footing in this emerging digital casino market.</p>
<p>Regulations allowing cryptocurrency developers to build their projects have resulted in positive economic outcomes for many of these countries. In some cases, it has permitted specific cryptocurrencies to flourish.&nbsp;</p>
<p>For instance, <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/what-is-ethereum/">Ethereum&nbsp;</a>is the second largest cryptocurrency in the world by market cap, with <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2022-07-31/-wen-flippening-crypto-fans-wager-on-ether-surpassing-bitcoin">some analysts even predicting</a> it will be the number one digital asset in a few years. Their headquarters are in Switzerland.</p>
<h2>Biggest cryptocurrencies in the world</h2>
<p>As we have already touched on, the most prominent cryptocurrency in the world is Bitcoin. Not only is it the most commonly invested in cryptocurrency, but it is also the oldest and most recognizable to people inside and outside the industry.<br>&nbsp;It has the largest market share and often drags the entire market up or down when it rallies or experiences a price retraction.</p>
<p>Ethereum is in second place, and it is the project that has the second-largest market share. Ethereum provides a scalable solution and allows decentralized projects to use their platform to implement their own cryptocurrencies.<br>&nbsp;For the last few years, Bitcoin and Ethereum have been the two big hitters in the industry, and this is unlikely to change anytime soon.</p>
<p>In 2018, <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ripple/what-is-ripple/">Ripple (XRP)&nbsp;</a>was the second biggest cryptocurrency, but it lost much of its share following an SEC lawsuit. However, if this case is resolved in an appropriate timescale within the next six months, it could lead to XRP coming back onto the scene as one of the top five cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>Other cryptocurrencies that make up the chasing pack are the USD stablecoin Tether, which is pegged against the US Dollar, and other emerging projects, such as the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/binance-coin/what-is-binance-coin/">Binance Coin (BNB)</a>.</p>
<h2>Conclusion</h2>
<p>Due to the ever-changing nature of the cryptocurrency market, the only real solid prediction that most analysts agree on is that Bitcoin and Ethereum will hold the top two spots for quite some time. </p>
<p>Both these assets have a lot of institutional investment from hedge funds and investment banks. This means they are more of a safe hedge than other assets that may be newer projects without as much capital being injected into them.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, with tighter regulation around the corner, the industry&rsquo;s landscape could change entirely. Outside of Bitcoin and Ethereum, about a dozen cryptocurrencies could move into the third, fourth and fifth positions at any given time.</p>
<p>However, due to the volatility of the market and the way it operates, don&rsquo;t be surprised to see a few different coins break into the top ten over the next 12 months.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-biggest-cryptocurrencies-around-the-world-in-2023/">The biggest cryptocurrencies around the world in 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/the-biggest-cryptocurrencies-around-the-world-in-2023/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>QuickNode raises $60M in Series B to advance blockchain adoption</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/quicknode-raises-60m-in-series-b-to-advance-blockchain-adoption/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/quicknode-raises-60m-in-series-b-to-advance-blockchain-adoption/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 15:57:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto adoption]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/quicknode-raises-60m-in-series-b-to-advance-blockchain-adoption/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>QuickNode is a Web3 platform developing tools and software solutions designed to accelerate blockchain adoption. The company raised its $60 million series B in a round led by 10T Holdings. QuickNode plans to use the funds to grow its team and scale its activities and tools. QuickNode, a blockchain infrastructure provider helping to power the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/quicknode-raises-60m-in-series-b-to-advance-blockchain-adoption/">QuickNode raises $60M in Series B to advance blockchain adoption</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>QuickNode is a Web3 platform developing tools and software solutions designed to accelerate blockchain adoption.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>The company raised its $60 million series B in a round led by 10T Holdings.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><strong><em>QuickNode plans to use the funds to grow its team and scale its activities and tools.</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">QuickNode, a blockchain infrastructure provider helping to power the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/glossary/web-3-0/">Web3</a> ecosystem, has raised $60 million in a Series B round.</p>
<p dir="ltr">10T Holdings, a digital assets-focused mid to late-stage equity fund, led the round, according to details in a <a href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-raises-60-million-in-series-b-funding/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">blog post</a> published on Tuesday.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The funding round also attracted participated from Seven Seven Six, a venture capital fund co-founded in 2020 by Alex Ohanian. Other investors who have backed QuickNode&rsquo;s latest round include Tiger Global and QED Investors.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">gm!</p>
<p>We're beyond excited to announce that we have raised a $60 million Series B funding round led by <a href="https://twitter.com/10TFund?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@10TFund</a> &mdash; with participation from Tiger Global, <a href="https://twitter.com/sevensevensix?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@sevensevensix</a>, and <a href="https://twitter.com/QEDInvestors?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@QEDInvestors</a>, among others &mdash; to fuel our next phase of growth and development! <a href="https://t.co/aWAu4P3WhX">pic.twitter.com/aWAu4P3WhX</a></p>
<p>&mdash; QuickNode (@QuickNode) <a href="https://twitter.com/QuickNode/status/1617872366759211013?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 24, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">The mission is to power Web3 growth</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Per QuickNode, the funding will help spearhead further adoption of the blockchain technology across the Web3 industry.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>With this funding, we will further solidify ourselves as the most performant blockchain development platform and accelerate our mission to support Web3 developers in building the foundation for a decentralized, globally connected future</em>,&rdquo; the QuickNode team <a href="https://twitter.com/QuickNode/status/1617872370747965440" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">noted</a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">QuickNode, founded in 2017, continued to see growth in 2022 despite the broader crypto market downturn that resulted in the collapse of some leading crypto-focused companies.</p>
<p dir="ltr">After raising $35 million in its series A round in October 2021, the blockchain platform grew its team by 300% while the user base expanded 400% in 2022. The company plans to use the capital injection to grow its team further and make inroads across new markets around the world.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;T<em>he Series B round, led by 10T, provides our tree with sufficient nutrients, allowing us the ideal opportunity to continue building and shipping useful, meaningful &amp; innovative products which will power the Internet for decades to come</em>,&rdquo; Dmitry Shklovsky, co-founder of QuickNode said in a statement.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/quicknode-raises-60m-in-series-b-to-advance-blockchain-adoption/">QuickNode raises $60M in Series B to advance blockchain adoption</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/quicknode-raises-60m-in-series-b-to-advance-blockchain-adoption/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Genesis Coin Inc, Powering 35% of Global Bitcoin ATM Transactions, Acquired by Bitstop Founders</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/genesis-coin-inc-powering-35-of-global-bitcoin-atm-transactions-acquired-by-bitstop-founders/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/genesis-coin-inc-powering-35-of-global-bitcoin-atm-transactions-acquired-by-bitstop-founders/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire  ]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 15:03:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=99956</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Miami, Florida, 24th January, 2023, Chainwire Genesis Coin Inc, the first and largest Bitcoin ATM software platform worldwide announced today that they have been acquired by early Bitcoin ATM pioneers Andrew Barnard and Doug Carrillo. Founded in 2013, Genesis Coin&#8217;s technology powers approximately 35% of global Bitcoin ATM transactions. Barnard and Carrillo, who also founded [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/genesis-coin-inc-powering-35-of-global-bitcoin-atm-transactions-acquired-by-bitstop-founders/">Genesis Coin Inc, Powering 35% of Global Bitcoin ATM Transactions, Acquired by Bitstop Founders</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Miami, Florida, 24th January, 2023, Chainwire</strong></p>
<p>Genesis Coin Inc, the first and largest Bitcoin ATM software platform worldwide announced today that they have been acquired by early Bitcoin ATM pioneers Andrew Barnard and Doug Carrillo.</p>
<p>Founded in 2013, Genesis Coin&rsquo;s technology powers approximately 35% of global Bitcoin ATM transactions. Barnard and Carrillo, who also founded Bitstop, built the first and largest private-label Bitcoin ATM platform based in Miami, FL with over 2,500+ Bitcoin ATMs worldwide. Genesis Coin and Bitstop represent over 75+ operators operating 12,000+ Bitcoin ATMs in the United States and international markets powering billions of dollars in annual sales volume.</p>
<p>As part of the acquisition, Andrew Barnard will become Chief Executive Officer and Doug Carrillo will become Chief Strategy Officer and both will join the Board of Directors of Genesis Coin. Evan Rose, Genesis Coin&rsquo;s founder, will stay on as a technical advisor and remain a member of the company&rsquo;s Board of Directors. The Genesis Coin headquarters will move to Miami, Florida.</p>
<p><i>&ldquo;Genesis Coin gave birth to the Bitcoin ATM industry,&rdquo;</i> said Barnard. &ldquo;It&rsquo;s the first and largest Bitcoin ATM software platform in The World. Evan built a platform trusted by some of the largest Bitcoin ATM operators in our industry, both domestically and internationally, including the Chivo network in partnership with the Government of El Salvador.</p>
<p>Our industry is now rapidly changing and Genesis Coin will lead the way into the future. Accomplishing this requires a solid team of world-class visionaries and developers. At Bitstop, we built an incredible software team and platform which has partnered with some of the largest companies both private and publicly traded from the traditional ATM industry. We plan to bring our background and expertise in building the best technology and team in the Bitcoin ATM industry to Genesis Coin. We believe this is a win-win for all stakeholders,&rdquo; furthered Barnard.</p>
<p><i>&ldquo;Andrew, Doug, and I have been friends for a long time and have also been friendly competitors,&rdquo; co</i>mmented Rose. <i>&ldquo;They have a reputation for their innovative and creative thinking. In addition, they have been successful in establishing key relationships in the Bitcoin space and their technical expertise and knowledge of Bitcoin is very impressive. In turn, this has allowed them to attract and retain top-tier talent and build great products. This transaction represents the coming together of the two leading software platforms in the industry and creates value for both companies&rsquo; stakeholders. It combines the best product, engineering, and leadership teams in the space. I&rsquo;m thrilled to work alongside them and look forward to introducing very exciting new products and services we have planned for this year,&rdquo;</i> commented Rose.</p>
<p>Barnard, Carrillo and Rose stressed the importance of continuing to provide stability to both platforms and continuing to service the needs of operators on both platforms. For the time being, both the Genesis Coin and Bitstop platforms will continue to run independently while exploring technical synergies. Genesis Coin has already made several key hires to its development team with a core focus on product development.</p>
<p><i>&ldquo;This acquisition represents the most significant event in the Bitcoin ATM industry to date,&rdquo;</i> said Carrillo. <i>&ldquo;Our commitment is to provide Genesis Coin with the proper resources it needs to pave the way for continued growth and innovation. We truly believe that this new combination of the best minds in our space will be the catalyst for the Bitcoin ATM industry evolving into its next phase. We are hyper-focused on building the best software for Bitcoin ATMs in the world. Today, the most sophisticated operators in our industry rely on Genesis Coin and Bitstop technology to power their businesses. As a result, we have become &lsquo;The Standard&rsquo; in the Bitcoin ATM space where virtually all industry organic M&amp;A activity today is occurring on the Genesis Coin and Bitstop networks.&rdquo;</i> concluded Carrillo.</p>
<p><i>&ldquo;Leverage dominated the entire cryptocurrency space over the last two years. Many other platforms in our industry couldn&rsquo;t resist the siren song,&rdquo;</i> said Barnard. <i>&ldquo;This is a capital-intensive industry where you do not want to be in a lot of debt. Genesis Coin is financially secure with a strong balance sheet, no debt, and strong cash flow. The company does not have external investors. The result of this is that operators can build their future on the Genesis Coin platform with confidence. In a volatile industry, we are a beacon of stability. We are bullish on the potential of this industry. We see significant market growth from here over the next 10 years. We believe we are in the best position in the industry to unite the very best operators and support their growth. Our goal is to listen to our operators and deliver the very best products and features to them so they can deliver maximum value to their customers at scale,&rdquo;</i> concluded Barnard.</p>
<p><b>About Genesis Coin</b></p>
<p>Genesis Coin is the first and largest white-label Bitcoin ATM network worldwide. We are the premier provider of autonomous vending solutions for bitcoin. Genesis Coin&rsquo;s proprietary managed infrastructure software solution has propelled it to become the largest provider of Bitcoin ATMs and software facilitating self-service buying and selling billions of dollars in cryptocurrencies across the world annually. Genesis Coin&rsquo;s software provides customers with a reliable, tailored operating platform. Genesis Coin delivers its software by selling BTMs to third-party operators who provide opportunities for businesses looking to diversify their revenue and drive foot traffic to their locations. Our machines make bitcoin simple for everyone. <a href="http://www.bitcoinatm.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><u>www.bitcoinatm.com</u></a></p>
<h2>Contact</h2>
<p>CEO, Andrew Barnard, Genesis Coin Inc, media@bitcoinatm.com</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/genesis-coin-inc-powering-35-of-global-bitcoin-atm-transactions-acquired-by-bitstop-founders/">Genesis Coin Inc, Powering 35% of Global Bitcoin ATM Transactions, Acquired by Bitstop Founders</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/genesis-coin-inc-powering-35-of-global-bitcoin-atm-transactions-acquired-by-bitstop-founders/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
