<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
>

<channel>
	<title>CoinCu News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://coincu.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coincu.com</link>
	<description>Coin and Crypto Infomation Update</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 16:13:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/cropped-Screen-Shot-2022-05-31-at-14.56.39-32x32.png</url>
	<title>CoinCu News</title>
	<link>https://coincu.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>SEC And Binance Unite To Thwart Eeon&#8217;s Intervention Bid In Lawsuit</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/206974-sec-and-binance-unite-to-thwart-eeon/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Harold]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 15:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Eeon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=206974</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[SEC and Binance oppose Eeon's bid to intervene in lawsuit on behalf of customers, citing a lack of requirements under the law.<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/206974-sec-and-binance-unite-to-thwart-eeon/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>SEC and Binance oppose Eeon&#8217;s bid to intervene in lawsuit on behalf of customers, citing a lack of requirements under the law.</em></li>



<li><em>Eeon&#8217;s counter-claim deemed vague and unrelated to the lawsuit, further weakening its case for intervention.</em></li>



<li><em>Binance files a motion to dismiss the CFTC lawsuit, intensifying regulatory challenges and impacting the crypto market.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>In a recent development, the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and cryptocurrency exchange Binance have <a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.dcd.256060/gov.uscourts.dcd.256060.91.0.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">joined</a> forces to oppose a petition submitted by third-party entity &#8220;Eeon,&#8221; seeking intervention in an ongoing lawsuit on behalf of customers.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2183-1024x576.png"><img decoding="async" width="1024" height="576" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2183-1024x576.png" alt="SEC And Binance Unite To Thwart Eeon&#039;s Intervention Bid In Lawsuit" class="wp-image-206979" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2183-1024x576.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2183-300x169.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2183-768x432.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2183-1536x864.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2183-750x422.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2183-1140x641.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2183.png 1920w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="SEC And Binance Unite To Thwart Eeon&#039;s Intervention Bid In Lawsuit 1"></a></figure></div>


<p>The dispute has brought to light several critical issues surrounding the legal status and jurisdiction of <a href="https://coincu.com/206699-binance-accuses-cftc-overruling-stop-the-lawsuit/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Binance</a>, one of the world&#8217;s leading crypto exchanges.</p>



<p>The District Court for the District of Columbia received the joint response from both defendant Binance and plaintiff US SEC, firmly opposing Eeon&#8217;s attempts to intervene in the ongoing legal battle. The exchange presented three primary reasons for dismissing Eeon&#8217;s petition.</p>



<p>Firstly, Eeon failed to obtain the necessary consent from the SEC, an essential requirement for intervention under the law. Secondly, the third-party entity did not sufficiently establish itself as a real party with a legitimate interest in the matter. Lastly, Eeon failed to meet the legal criteria for intervention, casting doubts on its eligibility to participate in the proceedings.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2184.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="738" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2184.png" alt="SEC And Binance Unite To Thwart Eeon&#039;s Intervention Bid In Lawsuit" class="wp-image-206981" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2184.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2184-300x216.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2184-768x554.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2184-120x86.png 120w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2184-750x541.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="SEC And Binance Unite To Thwart Eeon&#039;s Intervention Bid In Lawsuit 2"></a></figure></div>


<p>Furthermore, Eeon&#8217;s counter-claim was deemed problematic as it presented vague allegations unrelated to the actual lawsuit. These shortcomings led both the SEC and Binance to contend that Eeon&#8217;s involvement would have no tangible impact on the case and is, therefore, unnecessary.</p>



<p>The SEC, in its opposition to Eeon&#8217;s petition, <a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.dcd.256060/gov.uscourts.dcd.256060.92.0.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">raised</a> concerns about the entity&#8217;s track record as a serial pro se litigant whose previous causes have failed to gain traction in federal courts. Citing the Exchange Act, the <a href="https://coincu.com/206747-sec-warns-accounting-firms/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">SEC</a> argued that private litigants&#8217; intervention is prohibited, emphasizing that Eeon&#8217;s claims closely align with the defendants&#8217; arguments and, as such, would not contribute to the lawsuit in a meaningful way. Furthermore, Eeon&#8217;s counterclaims seeking relief against both the SEC and Binance were found to be contradictory and untenable.</p>



<p>Thus, both the plaintiff (SEC) and defendants (Binance) firmly stand against any intervention by Eeon in the ongoing lawsuit concerning Binance and its CEO, Changpeng &#8220;CZ&#8221; Zhao.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-1025240764-1024x683.webp"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="683" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-1025240764-1024x683.webp" alt="SEC And Binance Unite To Thwart Eeon&#039;s Intervention Bid In Lawsuit" class="wp-image-206980" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-1025240764-1024x683.webp 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-1025240764-300x200.webp 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-1025240764-768x512.webp 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-1025240764-1536x1024.webp 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-1025240764-2048x1365.webp 2048w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-1025240764-750x500.webp 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-1025240764-1140x760.webp 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="SEC And Binance Unite To Thwart Eeon&#039;s Intervention Bid In Lawsuit 3"></a></figure></div>


<p>Meanwhile, Binance has taken another legal step by <a href="https://coincu.com/205581-binance-cz-file-a-petition-dismiss-cftcs-lawsuit/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">filing</a> a motion to dismiss the U.S. Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) lawsuit, contesting the jurisdiction of the global crypto exchange and its ability to sue its CEO, CZ. However, this legal process is expected to extend well into the following year, given the court&#8217;s deadlines for the submission of responses by the CFTC and Binance.</p>



<p>As the legal battle unfolds, the cryptocurrency industry will be closely monitoring the outcome of the SEC lawsuit and the CFTC&#8217;s response to Binance&#8217;s motion to dismiss, as these developments could have far-reaching implications for the sector&#8217;s regulatory landscape.</p>



<p>It is worth noting that Binance&#8217;s regulatory challenges and the increased scrutiny from U.S. regulators have already started to impact trading volumes and liquidity on the exchange, affecting the broader cryptocurrency market as a whole.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER: </em></strong><em>The information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>
<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/206974-sec-and-binance-unite-to-thwart-eeon/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2185-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>ZK Stack: Exploring Potentials And Limitations That Need To Be Overcome</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/206427-zk-stack-potentials-and-limitations/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Harold]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 14:34:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Knowledge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Arbitrum Orbit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hyperchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Layer 3]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OP Stack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[optimism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ZK]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ZK Stack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[zkSync Era]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=206427</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[ZK Stack is based on the open-source code of zkSync Era, utilizing cryptographic zero-knowledge proofs for indisputable transaction verification.<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/206427-zk-stack-potentials-and-limitations/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>ZK Stack, a powerful Hyperchain building toolkit, is based on the open-source code of zkSync Era, utilizing cryptographic zero-knowledge proofs for indisputable transaction verification.</em></li>



<li><em>Advantages include enhanced scalability with 1,000 times cheaper transaction fees, customizable data availability, empowering tokenomics, and tailored development options.</em></li>



<li><em>Challenges involve incomplete customization, dependency on zkSync Era, relatively lower interest compared to competitors, and potential interoperability issues with Layer 3 solutions in crowded networks.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>zkSync has just <a href="https://blog.matter-labs.io/introducing-the-zk-stack-c24240c2532a" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">announced</a> the launch of ZK Stack &#8211; the Hyperchain building toolkit based on the open source code of zkSync Era. So what are the advantages and disadvantages of this toolkit? Let&#8217;s find out more details about Coincu through this article.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2164-1024x576.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="576" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2164-1024x576.png" alt="ZK Stack: Exploring Potentials And Limitations That Need To Be Overcome" class="wp-image-206916" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2164-1024x576.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2164-300x169.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2164-768x432.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2164-750x422.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2164-1140x642.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2164.png 1400w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="ZK Stack: Exploring Potentials And Limitations That Need To Be Overcome 4"></a></figure></div>


<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">What is ZK Stack?</h2>



<p>ZK Stack has emerged and offered a powerful solution for building highly customizable blockchains. Comprising both Layer 2 and Layer 3 components, collectively known as Hyperchains, the toolkit is based on the open-source code of <a href="https://coincu.com/203301-zksync-era-introduced-boojum/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">zkSync Era</a>, showcasing its commitment to transparency and community collaboration.</p>



<p>The standout feature of ZK Stack lies in its implementation of cryptographic zero-knowledge proofs for Layer 2 transactions. Unlike the prevalent &#8220;optimistic&#8221; approach to rollups, which assumes transactions are valid unless proven otherwise, ZK Stack leverages zero-knowledge proofs, providing indisputable verification of transaction validity. This approach sets it apart from two notable counterparts in the field – Optimism&#8217;s <a href="https://coincu.com/205621-optimism-op-stacks-first-fault-proof-system/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">OP Stack</a> and Arbitrum&#8217;s Arbitrum Orbit, both of which are Optimistic Rollup solutions.</p>



<p>Notably, zkSync Era is leading the pack as the pioneer Hyperchain, blazing the trail in the liquidity network. ZK Stack distinguishes itself as a technology-oriented amalgamation of the Modular Blockchain and the Internet Of Blockchain.</p>



<p>Key among ZK Stack&#8217;s offerings are two fundamental features: Sovereignty and Seamless Connectivity. With Sovereignty, creators wield complete ownership rights over the source code, empowering them to customize and shape every aspect of the chain according to their vision and requirements. This level of freedom is an enticing proposition for developers seeking to bring their unique ideas to life on the blockchain.</p>



<p>On the other hand, Seamless Connectivity ensures that <a href="https://coincu.com/206420-hyperchains-amp-hyperbridges/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Hyperchains</a> operate independently, relying solely on Ethereum for survival and security. Additionally, ZK Stack introduces Hyperbridges, facilitating seamless interconnection among all Hyperchains. This innovative solution ensures reliable interoperability between chains, enabling swift and cost-effective transactions within minutes at the price of a single transaction.</p>



<p>The introduction of ZK Stack adds a new dimension to the blockchain ecosystem, catering to the diverse needs of developers, businesses, and end-users alike. By incorporating zero-knowledge proofs and providing customizable solutions, the platform is poised to drive a wave of innovation and adoption in the decentralized space.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2165.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="799" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2165-1024x799.png" alt="ZK Stack: Exploring Potentials And Limitations That Need To Be Overcome" class="wp-image-206918" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2165-1024x799.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2165-300x234.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2165-768x599.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2165-1536x1198.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2165-2048x1598.png 2048w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2165-750x585.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2165-1140x889.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="ZK Stack: Exploring Potentials And Limitations That Need To Be Overcome 5"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">The ZK Stack layers. <em>Image source: Blockchain Capital</em></figcaption></figure></div>


<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Pros and Cons</h2>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Pros</strong></h3>



<p>The innovative design of <a href="https://coincu.com/205141-op-stack-vs-zk-stack/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">ZK Stack</a> comes packed with a host of advantages, setting it apart as a game-changer in the blockchain landscape. Let&#8217;s explore some of the key benefits that make the toolkit a force to be reckoned with:</p>



<ul>
<li>Scalability Boost with ZK Technology: The integration of ZK technology in ZK Stack brings a significant improvement in scalability, particularly concerning transaction speed and fees. Compared to other Rollup platforms currently available, it offers transactions at a fraction of the cost, approximately 1,000 times cheaper. This remarkable cost efficiency makes it an attractive option for developers and users alike.</li>



<li>Optimized Scalability with Customizable Data Availability: ZK Stack takes scalability on Hyperchains to the next level by introducing the concept of customizable Data Availability through zkPorter&#8217;s technology. This enhancement results in near-instant transaction speeds and near-zero transaction fees, a powerful combination that ensures seamless and cost-effective blockchain interactions.</li>



<li>Empowering Tokenomics Customization: ZK Stack&#8217;s flexibility extends to Tokenomics, allowing developers to customize the Native Tokens of their Hyperchains. This adaptability enhances the value of Native Tokens in the eyes of the community, fostering a strong growth engine for active and efficient Hyperchains. Such community engagement holds the potential to drive widespread adoption and long-term sustainability.</li>



<li>Tailored Development with Customization: ZK Stack&#8217;s versatility is evident in its multiple levels of customization, empowering developers to build Layer 2 (L2) or Layer 3 (L3) platforms that align perfectly with their specific needs and visions. This streamlined approach not only fosters creativity and innovation but also accelerates the development process, enabling quicker deployments of novel blockchain solutions.</li>



<li>Proven Success with zkSync Era: ZK Stack draws inspiration from the achievements of zkSync Era, which has been garnering widespread recognition and success in recent times. This successful implementation serves as a testament to the efficacy of the ZK Stack model and instills confidence in developers seeking to build their own Hyperchains using this framework.</li>



<li>A Promising Model: Drawing parallels with other successful projects in the blockchain domain, such as Optimism&#8217;s Superchain and Cosmos&#8217; Internet of Blockchain, positions ZK Stack as a promising contender in the realm of blockchain solutions. The underlying principles of this model and its proven success stories contribute to the optimism surrounding the potential accomplishments of ZK Stack.</li>
</ul>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2166-1024x587.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="587" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2166-1024x587.png" alt="ZK Stack: Exploring Potentials And Limitations That Need To Be Overcome" class="wp-image-206919" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2166-1024x587.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2166-300x172.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2166-768x441.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2166-750x430.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2166-1140x654.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2166.png 1400w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="ZK Stack: Exploring Potentials And Limitations That Need To Be Overcome 6"></a></figure></div>


<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Cons</strong></h3>



<p>While ZK Stack presents a compelling array of advantages, it&#8217;s essential to acknowledge and address the challenges it faces to achieve its full potential. Let&#8217;s explore some of the notable disadvantages of the toolkit and how they can be mitigated:</p>



<ul>
<li>Incomplete Customization: One of the drawbacks of ZK Stack is that its customization capabilities are not yet fully maximized. As the platform continues to evolve, developers may find themselves somewhat constrained in certain aspects, particularly in terms of building exclusively on Ethereum and focusing heavily on Zero-Knowledge Proofs (ZKP). To overcome this limitation, the ZK Stack team must actively seek feedback from the developer community and explore opportunities to expand the range of supported technologies and interoperability with other blockchain ecosystems.</li>



<li>Dependency on zkSync Era: ZK Stack&#8217;s development and upgrades are inherently tied to the progress of zkSync Era. While this shared foundation may facilitate compatibility and cohesion between the two, it also means that any advancements or setbacks in zkSync Era could directly impact ZK Stack and vice versa. To address this issue, the developers should consider making it more modular and agnostic to specific Layer 2 implementations, allowing for greater flexibility and autonomy in upgrades and compatibility with other Layer 2 solutions.</li>



<li>Relatively Lower Interest Compared to Competitors: Despite its promising features, ZK Stack has yet to gain the same level of attention and adoption as its competitor, Optimism&#8217;s OP Stack. The competition in this space is fierce, and the advantages of ZK Stack, such as zkEVM, need to be effectively communicated to the blockchain community. Proactive marketing, engaging developer outreach, and strategic partnerships can help elevate the profile of ZK Stack and attract more interest from the broader blockchain ecosystem.</li>



<li>Potential Interoperability Challenges: As the network grows and becomes more crowded, interoperability between Layer 3 (L3) solutions on different Layer 2 (L2) platforms could pose a challenge for zkSync. Ensuring smooth and efficient communication between disparate L3s will be crucial to maintain the seamless operation of Hyperchains. zkSync should invest in research and development to tackle potential scalability and interoperability hurdles, collaborating with other projects in the space to establish industry-wide standards for cross-chain interactions.</li>
</ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Conclusion</h2>



<p>In conclusion, ZK Stack emerges as a groundbreaking platform that leverages the power of zero-knowledge technology, customization, and successful precedents to revolutionize the blockchain landscape.</p>



<p>With its focus on scalability, cost-effectiveness, and developer empowerment, ZK Stack paves the way for a new era of decentralized applications and Hyperchains, fostering a thriving ecosystem of innovation and growth.</p>



<p>However, ZK Stack exhibits remarkable potential and unique advantages, it also faces certain limitations that require diligent efforts to address.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER: </em></strong><em>The information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>
<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/206427-zk-stack-potentials-and-limitations/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Final-Thumb-8-1-1024x731.jpg" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/jpeg" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Worldcoin&#8217;s Controversy: French Privacy Watchdog Investigates Ambitious Project</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/206960-worldcoins-controversy-french-privacy-watchdog/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Harold]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 14:14:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CNIL]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[French]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Altman]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tools For Humanity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[WLD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Worldcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Worldcoin ID]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=206960</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[French privacy watchdog CNIL investigates Sam Altman's Worldcoin project over the legality of its biometric data collection, raising concerns about storing such data.<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/206960-worldcoins-controversy-french-privacy-watchdog/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>French privacy watchdog CNIL investigates Sam Altman&#8217;s Worldcoin project over the legality of its biometric data collection, raising concerns about storing such data.</em></li>



<li><em>Worldcoin requires users to provide iris scans for a digital ID and offers free cryptocurrency in certain countries, attracting 2.1 million users in a trial period.</em></li>



<li><em>The project&#8217;s unique ID system aims to combat online identity fraud and income inequality, but regulatory scrutiny and investigations in Germany could impact its future.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>On Friday, France&#8217;s privacy watchdog, CNIL, made public its awareness of Sam Altman&#8217;s Worldcoin project and expressed concern over the legality of its biometric data collection.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2181.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="576" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2181-1024x576.png" alt="Worldcoin&#039;s Controversy: French Privacy Watchdog Investigates Ambitious Project" class="wp-image-206969" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2181-1024x576.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2181-300x169.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2181-768x432.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2181-750x422.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2181-1140x641.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2181.png 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Worldcoin&#039;s Controversy: French Privacy Watchdog Investigates Ambitious Project 7"></a></figure></div>


<p>The ambitious venture launched just days ago, has been a topic of controversy in Silicon Valley due to its unorthodox approach to tackling online identity authentication and income inequality.</p>



<p><a href="https://coincu.com/206496-worldcoin-proves-critics-wrong-altman-japan/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Worldcoin</a>&#8216;s concept requires users to provide their iris scans in exchange for a digital ID, and in some countries, they receive free cryptocurrency as well. The platform claims to have already registered 2.1 million participants, primarily through a two-year trial period.</p>



<p>At the core of Worldcoin&#8217;s proposition lies &#8220;Tools for Humanity,&#8221; the company behind the project. According to insiders, Altman has used AI advancements as a compelling incentive to attract investors. As the value of the Worldcoin token, dubbed &#8220;<a href="https://coincu.com/205553-worldcoin-unveils-new-nft-collectible/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">WLD</a>,&#8221; appreciates, it promises to yield substantial returns for Altman and other stakeholders.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/FzX-y4OaAAER3fi.jpeg"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="768" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/FzX-y4OaAAER3fi-1024x768.jpeg" alt="Worldcoin&#039;s Controversy: French Privacy Watchdog Investigates Ambitious Project" class="wp-image-206970" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/FzX-y4OaAAER3fi-1024x768.jpeg 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/FzX-y4OaAAER3fi-300x225.jpeg 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/FzX-y4OaAAER3fi-768x576.jpeg 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/FzX-y4OaAAER3fi-1536x1152.jpeg 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/FzX-y4OaAAER3fi-750x563.jpeg 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/FzX-y4OaAAER3fi-1140x855.jpeg 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/FzX-y4OaAAER3fi.jpeg 2048w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Worldcoin&#039;s Controversy: French Privacy Watchdog Investigates Ambitious Project 8"></a></figure></div>


<p>The process of acquiring a unique <a href="https://coincu.com/204875-worldcoins-world-id-sdk-is-now-available/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Worldcoin ID</a> involves scanning users&#8217; irises using a specialized device called &#8220;The Orb.&#8221; This biometric data collection aims to distinguish real individuals from bots, a critical concern given the rise of large language models like ChatGPT. Additionally, it could play a crucial role in mitigating fraud when governments contemplate implementing &#8220;universal basic income&#8221; programs.</p>



<p>While the project has attracted attention worldwide, it has also raised red flags with regulatory authorities. The British data regulator announced earlier this week that it would be investigating Worldcoin following its recent launch.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2182.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="960" height="503" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2182.png" alt="Worldcoin&#039;s Controversy: French Privacy Watchdog Investigates Ambitious Project" class="wp-image-206971" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2182.png 960w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2182-300x157.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2182-768x402.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2182-750x393.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 960px) 100vw, 960px" title="Worldcoin&#039;s Controversy: French Privacy Watchdog Investigates Ambitious Project 9"></a></figure></div>


<p>In response to inquiries from <em><a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/frances-privacy-watchdog-says-worldcoin-legality-seems-questionable-2023-07-28/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Reuters</a></em>, CNIL expressed reservations about the legitimacy of Worldcoin&#8217;s biometric data collection and storage practices. The French watchdog has initiated its own investigation but has discovered that the Bavarian state authority in Germany holds jurisdiction over the matter. Subsequently, the Bavarian authority has taken the lead in the investigation, with support from CNIL.</p>



<p>As the situation unfolds, Worldcoin&#8217;s future hinges on the resolution of these investigations and compliance with privacy and data protection regulations in various countries. The novel approach to solving complex issues is a double-edged sword, and its success will be closely monitored by both investors and authorities alike.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER: </em></strong><em>The information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>
<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/206960-worldcoins-controversy-french-privacy-watchdog/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2180-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitget And MEXC Create New Breakthrough To Compete With Other Platforms</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/206958-bitget-and-mexc-create-new-breakthrough/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Harold]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 13:52:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BGB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitget]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MEXC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OKX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=206958</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitget and MEXC have entered a strategic partnership, listing each other's platform tokens, BGB and MX, simultaneously.<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/206958-bitget-and-mexc-create-new-breakthrough/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>Bitget and MEXC have entered a strategic partnership, listing each other&#8217;s platform tokens, BGB and MX, simultaneously.</em></li>



<li><em>The move aims to enhance liquidity and accessibility for the tokens, targeting markets in Japan and South Korea.</em></li>



<li><em>BGB token witnessed impressive growth, becoming the best-performing exchange token in H1 2023, backed by the platform&#8217;s successful expansion and innovative features.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>In a bid to strengthen their positions in the ever-competitive cryptocurrency exchange landscape, Bitget and MEXC have taken a bold step forward by <a href="https://www.mexc.com/en-US/support/articles/17827791509716" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">announcing</a> the simultaneous listing of each other&#8217;s native platform tokens.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2177-1024x538.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="538" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2177-1024x538.png" alt="Bitget And MEXC Create New Breakthrough To Compete With Other Platforms" class="wp-image-206963" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2177-1024x538.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2177-300x158.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2177-768x403.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2177-750x394.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2177-1140x599.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2177.png 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Bitget And MEXC Create New Breakthrough To Compete With Other Platforms 10"></a></figure></div>


<p>The renowned crypto derivatives and copy trading platform, <a href="https://coincu.com/205333-bitget-now-listed-wld-token/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Bitget</a>, will be listing its token, BGB, on <a href="https://coincu.com/192190-mexc-global-accused-false-listing/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">MEXC</a>, while MEXC&#8217;s platform token, MX, will find its way onto Bitget&#8217;s exchange. This move is set to bolster liquidity, accessibility, and overall value and utility for both tokens, presenting traders with new opportunities and privileges.</p>



<p>The decision comes at a time when major exchanges like <a href="https://coincu.com/206699-binance-accuses-cftc-overruling-stop-the-lawsuit/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Binance</a> and <a href="https://coincu.com/206128-okx-exchange-breaks-new-records-11-3-billion/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">OKX</a> are increasingly focusing on compliance measures. Bybit, Bitget, and MEXC have recognized the potential to tap into markets like Japan and South Korea, leading them to adopt a more aggressive approach to expand their user base. Their mutual equity relationship ensures a coordinated effort in their advancement strategies, presenting a united front in the competitive crypto arena.</p>



<p>Bitget&#8217;s native token, BGB, plays a crucial role within the platform&#8217;s ecosystem, boasting a circulating supply of 1,400,000,000 and a total supply of 2,000,000,000. Holders of BGB enjoy a range of exclusive privileges and rights on Bitget&#8217;s exchange, including fee discounts, access to high-quality tokens through Launchpad and Launchpool participation, and the highly sought-after Super Airdrop feature.</p>



<p>The decision to list BGB on MEXC is in response to the soaring demand for the token in the market. Impressively, BGB has already attracted over 300,000 holders and achieved a staggering total trading volume of more than two billion USD since the beginning of the year. Its price growth has been remarkable, reaching an all-time high of over 0.51 USDT in February, outperforming even BTC and emerging as the best-performing exchange token in H1 2023.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2176.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="1024" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2176-1024x1024.png" alt="Bitget And MEXC Create New Breakthrough To Compete With Other Platforms" class="wp-image-206962" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2176-1024x1024.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2176-300x300.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2176-150x150.png 150w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2176-768x768.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2176-75x75.png 75w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2176-350x350.png 350w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2176-750x750.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2176.png 1080w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Bitget And MEXC Create New Breakthrough To Compete With Other Platforms 11"></a></figure></div>


<p>Bitget&#8217;s own success and steady growth have undoubtedly contributed to the surge in BGB&#8217;s value. With a rising share in both the spot and derivatives trading markets, the platform has earned a reputation for high financial security, garnering significant traction among traders. Moreover, Bitget&#8217;s impressive track record of listing over 180 coins in 2023 and delivering the best Launchpad performance, with an ATH average ROI of 41.9x, has further enhanced the appeal and use cases for BGB.</p>



<p>The release of the updated BGB whitepaper in April unveiled exciting new features in development, such as the BGB lottery, a trial fund for futures trading, and exclusive earning services. Additionally, Bitget is actively exploring a BGB buyback and burn mechanism to reduce the token&#8217;s circulating supply, thereby increasing its overall value. Another innovative feature, &#8220;Super Airdrop,&#8221; was introduced in May, allowing eligible BGB holders to receive airdrops of new crypto assets listed on the Bitget platform.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2178.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="1024" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2178-1024x1024.png" alt="Bitget And MEXC Create New Breakthrough To Compete With Other Platforms" class="wp-image-206964" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2178-1024x1024.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2178-300x300.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2178-150x150.png 150w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2178-768x768.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2178-75x75.png 75w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2178-350x350.png 350w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2178-750x750.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2178-1140x1140.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2178.png 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Bitget And MEXC Create New Breakthrough To Compete With Other Platforms 12"></a></figure></div>


<p>Besides the developments surrounding BGB, Bitget&#8217;s growing influence and continuous expansion within the cryptocurrency market significantly contribute to the demand and price performance of BGB. According to <a href="https://tokeninsight.com/en/news/bitget-sees-market-share-increase-in-q2-with-bgb-becoming-best-performing-cex-token" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">TokenInsight&#8217;s Crypto Exchange Report Q2 2023</a>, Bitget ranks fourth in trading volume among all CEXs, with its market share surging by 1.81% to 8.7%, the second-highest increase among the Top 5 CEXs. The platform&#8217;s increasing market share in both the spot market and open interest solidifies its position as a leading player in the industry.</p>



<p>As these exchanges unite their efforts, traders and investors can look forward to enhanced opportunities and a more robust trading experience across both platforms. The listings are scheduled to go live on July 31, signifying a significant milestone for both Bitget and MEXC in their pursuit of market dominance.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER: </em></strong><em>The information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>
<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/206958-bitget-and-mexc-create-new-breakthrough/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2179-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>BitDeer Introduces BGB &#8211; Eco-Friendly Bitcoin Mining Investment</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/206945-bitdeer-introduces-bgb-eco-friendly-btc-mining/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Annie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 10:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BGB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitdeer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Eco-Friendly Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=206945</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Key Points: Bitdeer is making waves in the crypto space with the introduction of its groundbreaking eco-friendly Bitcoin mining private equity fund, the Bitdeer Green Bitcoin Fund (BGB). This revolutionary initiative aims to revolutionize the Bitcoin mining industry, paving the way for sustainable and profitable mining operations. Bitdeer&#8217;s BGB Fund will spearhead environmentally conscious mining [&#8230;]<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/206945-bitdeer-introduces-bgb-eco-friendly-btc-mining/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>Bitdeer introduces eco-friendly Bitcoin mining fund to revolutionize the industry and pave the way for sustainable mining operations.</em></li>



<li><em>The Bitdeer Green Bitcoin Fund targets a formidable 600 MW and a total computational capacity estimated to be close to 20EH/s, ensuring long-term planning and stability.</em></li>



<li><em>With a minimum investment requirement of US$5 million, the BGB Fund is a lucrative opportunity for institutional and high-net-worth investors to participate in environmentally responsible Bitcoin mining operations.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong><a href="https://www.bitdeer.com/" data-type="URL" data-id="https://www.bitdeer.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitdeer</a> is making waves in the crypto space with the introduction of its groundbreaking eco-friendly Bitcoin mining private equity fund, the Bitdeer Green Bitcoin Fund (BGB). </strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image is-style-default">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BitDeer-Introduces-BGB-Eco-Friendly-Bitcoin-Mining-Investment-1.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="842" height="596" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BitDeer-Introduces-BGB-Eco-Friendly-Bitcoin-Mining-Investment-1.png" alt="BitDeer Introduces BGB - Eco-Friendly Bitcoin Mining Investment" class="wp-image-206948" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BitDeer-Introduces-BGB-Eco-Friendly-Bitcoin-Mining-Investment-1.png 842w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BitDeer-Introduces-BGB-Eco-Friendly-Bitcoin-Mining-Investment-1-300x212.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BitDeer-Introduces-BGB-Eco-Friendly-Bitcoin-Mining-Investment-1-768x544.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BitDeer-Introduces-BGB-Eco-Friendly-Bitcoin-Mining-Investment-1-120x86.png 120w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BitDeer-Introduces-BGB-Eco-Friendly-Bitcoin-Mining-Investment-1-750x531.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 842px) 100vw, 842px" title="BitDeer Introduces BGB - Eco-Friendly Bitcoin Mining Investment 13"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>This revolutionary initiative aims to revolutionize the Bitcoin mining industry, paving the way for sustainable and profitable mining operations.</p>



<p>Bitdeer&#8217;s BGB Fund will spearhead environmentally conscious mining practices, marking a significant shift in the industry&#8217;s approach to energy consumption and carbon footprint reduction. As the company owns and operates the Bitcoin mining industry, the BGB Fund targets a formidable 600 MW and a total computational capacity estimated to be close to 20EH/s.</p>



<p>The BGB Fund adopts a closed-end structure with a fixed term of 6 years, unless renewed based on the fund&#8217;s documentation. This strategic approach ensures long-term planning and stability, aligning with the company&#8217;s vision of sustainable growth and profitability.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image is-style-default">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BitDeer-Introduces-BGB-Eco-Friendly-Bitcoin-Mining-Investment.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="441" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BitDeer-Introduces-BGB-Eco-Friendly-Bitcoin-Mining-Investment.png" alt="BitDeer Introduces BGB - Eco-Friendly Bitcoin Mining Investment" class="wp-image-206949" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BitDeer-Introduces-BGB-Eco-Friendly-Bitcoin-Mining-Investment.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BitDeer-Introduces-BGB-Eco-Friendly-Bitcoin-Mining-Investment-300x129.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BitDeer-Introduces-BGB-Eco-Friendly-Bitcoin-Mining-Investment-768x331.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BitDeer-Introduces-BGB-Eco-Friendly-Bitcoin-Mining-Investment-750x323.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="BitDeer Introduces BGB - Eco-Friendly Bitcoin Mining Investment 14"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>With a minimum investment requirement of US$5 million, the BGB Fund opens doors for institutional and high-net-worth investors to participate in eco-friendly Bitcoin mining operations, showcasing Bitdeer&#8217;s commitment to promoting environmentally responsible practices.</p>



<p>The first phase of the BGB Fund&#8217;s project is projected to raise an impressive US$80 million, attracting investors seeking both financial returns and a positive impact on the environment. As the demand for green and sustainable investments surges, Bitdeer&#8217;s BGB Fund emerges as a lucrative opportunity for those keen on leveraging the growing interest in eco-conscious initiatives.</p>



<p>Bitdeer&#8217;s foray into eco-friendly Bitcoin mining aligns with the broader industry&#8217;s call for more energy-efficient and environmentally conscious practices. As concerns around energy consumption and environmental impact grow, the BGB Fund signifies a proactive step towards addressing these issues head-on.</p>



<p id="block-643c4ba8-b40b-4525-9a96-f280dbfbeb9d"><strong><em>DISCLAIMER:&nbsp;</em></strong><em>The Information on this&nbsp;website&nbsp;is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>
<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/206945-bitdeer-introduces-bgb-eco-friendly-btc-mining/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BitDeer-Introduces-BGB-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>eToro Secures Bank of Spain&#8217;s Virtual Asset Exchange Approval</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/206925-etoro-secures-bank-of-spains-virtual-asset/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Annie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 10:10:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bank of Spain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eToro]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Virtual Asset Exchange]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=206925</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Bank of Spain's recent approval of eToro as a virtual currency exchange and electronic wallet custody service provider is a testament to the company's commitment to consumer protection and innovation. <p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/206925-etoro-secures-bank-of-spains-virtual-asset/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>The Bank of Spain approves eToro as a virtual currency exchange and electronic wallet custody service provider, a testament to eToro&#8217;s commitment to consumer protection and innovation. </em></li>



<li><em>eToro has been making headlines with a $3.5B valuation, partnering with Twitter, and creating a passive investor portfolio.</em></li>



<li><em>As a multi-asset platform, eToro offers Spanish users access to a diverse range of asset classes, investment tools, and educational resources to help grow knowledge and wealth.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The Bank of Spain&#8217;s recent approval of<a href="https://www.etoro.com/" target="_blank" data-type="URL" data-id="https://www.etoro.com/" rel="noreferrer noopener"> eToro</a> as a virtual currency exchange and electronic wallet custody service provider is a testament to the company&#8217;s commitment to consumer protection and innovation. </strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image is-style-default">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2167.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="968" height="642" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2167.png" alt="eToro Secures Bank of Spain&#039;s Virtual Asset Exchange Approval" class="wp-image-206929" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2167.png 968w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2167-300x199.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2167-768x509.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2167-750x497.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 968px) 100vw, 968px" title="eToro Secures Bank of Spain&#039;s Virtual Asset Exchange Approval 15"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>eToro users in Spain can now enjoy the convenience and security of virtual currency exchange and electronic wallet storage services.</p>



<p>eToro has been making headlines in the financial world, having received a valuation of $3.5 billion earlier this year. The online trading platform has also partnered with Twitter to offer payments and financial features to the social media giant. Recently, eToro announced that it has created a passive investor portfolio consisting of shares from 40 leading fintechs.</p>



<p>Tali Salomon, eToro&#8217;s Regional Manager for Iberia and LatAm, expressed her excitement over the registration. She stated that the approval is a testament to eToro&#8217;s commitment to consumer protection, innovation, and individual investor access. As a multi-asset platform, eToro has been supporting crypto and blockchain technology for a long time. With the Bank of Spain&#8217;s registration, eToro is proud to continue providing Spanish users with access to a diverse range of asset classes, investment tools, and educational resources to help them grow their knowledge and wealth.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image is-style-default">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Tali-Salomon-eToros-Regional-Manager-for-Iberia-and-LatAm.jpeg"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="575" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Tali-Salomon-eToros-Regional-Manager-for-Iberia-and-LatAm-1024x575.jpeg" alt="eToro Secures Bank of Spain&#039;s Virtual Asset Exchange Approval" class="wp-image-206935" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Tali-Salomon-eToros-Regional-Manager-for-Iberia-and-LatAm-1024x575.jpeg 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Tali-Salomon-eToros-Regional-Manager-for-Iberia-and-LatAm-300x168.jpeg 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Tali-Salomon-eToros-Regional-Manager-for-Iberia-and-LatAm-768x431.jpeg 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Tali-Salomon-eToros-Regional-Manager-for-Iberia-and-LatAm-1536x863.jpeg 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Tali-Salomon-eToros-Regional-Manager-for-Iberia-and-LatAm-750x421.jpeg 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Tali-Salomon-eToros-Regional-Manager-for-Iberia-and-LatAm-1140x640.jpeg 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Tali-Salomon-eToros-Regional-Manager-for-Iberia-and-LatAm.jpeg 2048w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="eToro Secures Bank of Spain&#039;s Virtual Asset Exchange Approval 16"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>The registration of eToro by the Bank of Spain is a huge win for the company and its users. It is also a positive development for the crypto and blockchain technology industry, as it further legitimizes the use of virtual currencies and electronic wallets. With eToro&#8217;s commitment to consumer protection and innovation, it is poised to continue making waves in the financial world and empower investors worldwide.</p>



<p id="block-643c4ba8-b40b-4525-9a96-f280dbfbeb9d"><strong><em>DISCLAIMER:&nbsp;</em></strong><em>The Information on this&nbsp;website&nbsp;is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>
<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/206925-etoro-secures-bank-of-spains-virtual-asset/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/eToro-Secures-Bank-of-Spains--1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alchemy Pay Added New Partner To Seamless Payments With Crypto Integration</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/206923-alchemy-pay-added-new-partner/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Harold]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 10:05:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Alchemy Pay]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Checkout.com]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Circle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CNHC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kucoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MasterCard]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Visa]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=206923</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Alchemy Pay partners with Checkout.com to enable seamless fiat-crypto transactions.<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/206923-alchemy-pay-added-new-partner/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>Alchemy Pay partners with Checkout.com to enable seamless fiat-crypto transactions.</em></li>



<li><em>Integration with Visa and Mastercard channels achieves industry-leading payment acceptance rates.</em></li>



<li><em>The collaboration paves the way for the widespread adoption of cryptocurrencies and NFTs.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Alchemy Pay, the leading fiat-crypto payment gateway, has <a href="https://alchemypay.org/news-and-press/alchemy-pay-expands-global-reach-through-checkout-coms-payment-rails" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">struck</a> a notable partnership with Checkout.com, a prominent payment processor catering to global digital businesses.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2168.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="478" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2168-1024x478.png" alt="Alchemy Pay Added New Partner To Seamless Payments With Crypto Integration" class="wp-image-206930" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2168-1024x478.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2168-300x140.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2168-768x359.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2168-750x350.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2168-1140x532.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2168.png 1191w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Alchemy Pay Added New Partner To Seamless Payments With Crypto Integration 17"></a></figure></div>


<p>The collaboration aims to enhance the integration of <a href="https://coincu.com/178066-alchemy-pays-10m-funding-signals-major/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Alchemy Pay</a>&#8216;s on and off-ramp services with Checkout.com&#8217;s Visa and Mastercard channels. The integration will enable users to effortlessly buy and sell cryptocurrencies using these popular card providers. Furthermore, the partnership sets the stage for the future integration of NFT Checkout, opening up new opportunities for the adoption of non-fungible tokens.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2171-1024x682.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="682" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2171-1024x682.png" alt="Alchemy Pay Added New Partner To Seamless Payments With Crypto Integration" class="wp-image-206936" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2171-1024x682.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2171-300x200.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2171-768x512.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2171-750x500.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2171-1140x760.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2171.png 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Alchemy Pay Added New Partner To Seamless Payments With Crypto Integration 18"></a></figure></div>


<p>With Checkout.com&#8217;s payment rails integrated, Alchemy Pay achieves an industry-leading payment acceptance rate, removing barriers to widespread crypto and NFT adoption. The seamless conversion process aligns perfectly with the company&#8217;s mission to bridge the gap between the fiat and crypto economies on a global scale.</p>



<p>Checkout.com has built a strong reputation as a global payments solution provider, catering to large enterprise merchants and processing billions of dollars in payments annually. Its impressive clientele includes renowned names such as Netflix, Farfetch, Sony, and more. By supporting major players in the crypto industry like <a href="https://coincu.com/203389-circles-usdc-suffers-100m-loss-as-usdt-dominates/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Circle</a> and <a href="https://coincu.com/205917-kucoin-faces-profit-woes-surround/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Kucoin</a>, Checkout.com further solidifies its presence and appeal to partners seeking higher acceptance rates, conversion rates, and reduced chargebacks.</p>



<p>In pursuit of expanding its reach, Alchemy Pay actively seeks collaborations with top global acquirers and payment processors to facilitate its on and off-ramp processes. These strategic partnerships not only increase Alchemy Pay&#8217;s global coverage and licensing capabilities but also lead to reduced transaction and operating costs, bolstering its position in the market.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2170.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="576" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2170.png" alt="Alchemy Pay Added New Partner To Seamless Payments With Crypto Integration" class="wp-image-206933" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2170.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2170-300x169.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2170-768x432.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2170-750x422.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Alchemy Pay Added New Partner To Seamless Payments With Crypto Integration 19"></a></figure></div>


<p>In addition to forging alliances with industry players, Alchemy Pay has secured licenses in various countries and regions, including the United States, Canada, Indonesia, and Lithuania. This success has garnered recognition from major payment providers like Visa and Mastercard, further solidifying Alchemy Pay&#8217;s status as a trusted payment service provider.</p>



<p>Highlighting their dedication to innovation, Alchemy Pay in April <a href="https://coincu.com/179755-alchemy-pay-help-buy-and-sell-yuan/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">announced</a> a collaboration with CNHC, the world&#8217;s largest CNH (offshore Chinese Yuan) stablecoin ecosystem. By integrating with Alchemy Pay&#8217;s on and off-ramp solutions, CNHC enables users to seamlessly purchase and trade CNHC using different fiat currencies worldwide.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER: </em></strong><em>The information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>
<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/206923-alchemy-pay-added-new-partner/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2169-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple Lawsuit Unravels: Prominent Attorney To Withdrawal Amidst Settlement Talks</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/206896-ripple-prominent-attorney-to-withdrawal/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Harold]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 09:14:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brad Garlinghouse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gary Gensler]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lisa R. Zornberg]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=206896</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ripple Labs' attorney, Lisa R. Zornberg, requests withdrawal from the SEC lawsuit following Judge's ruling.<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/206896-ripple-prominent-attorney-to-withdrawal/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>Ripple Labs&#8217; attorney, Lisa R. Zornberg, requests withdrawal from the SEC lawsuit following Judge&#8217;s ruling.</em></li>



<li><em>Magistrate Judge urges settlement talks between the company and SEC on key lawsuit issues.</em></li>



<li><em>XRP price surges as legal developments unfold, sparking optimism for its non-security status.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>In a significant development within the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) vs. Ripple lawsuit, the prominent attorney representing Ripple Labs and its CEO, <a href="https://coincu.com/205247-ripple-ceo-brad-garlinghouse-blames-sec/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Brad Garlinghouse</a>, has formally <a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.nysd.551082/gov.uscourts.nysd.551082.880.0.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">requested</a> to withdraw from the case.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2160.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1000" height="667" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2160.png" alt="Ripple Lawsuit Unravels: Prominent Attorney To Withdrawal Amidst Settlement Talks" class="wp-image-206907" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2160.png 1000w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2160-300x200.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2160-768x512.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2160-750x500.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" title="Ripple Lawsuit Unravels: Prominent Attorney To Withdrawal Amidst Settlement Talks 20"></a></figure></div>


<p>This request was made following Judge Analisa Torres&#8217; landmark ruling in the ongoing legal battle. Furthermore, Magistrate Judge Sarah Netburn has urged both <a href="https://coincu.com/203303-ripple-to-initiate-talks-with-us-financial-firms/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Ripple</a> and the SEC to explore a potential settlement on other aspects of the lawsuit.</p>



<p>As per the filing in the District Court For the Southern District of New York on July 27, Ripple submitted a motion for Lisa R. Zornberg of Debevoise &amp; Plimpton LLP to withdraw as attorney for the defendants. The company cited that Lisa R. Zornberg will no longer be associated with the law firm effective from July 31.</p>



<p>Despite this withdrawal, Ripple maintains that the interests of the defendants, including Garlinghouse and co-founder Chris Larsen, will not be adversely affected. The legal representation for Ripple Labs in the lawsuit will continue with other attorneys from Debevoise &amp; Plimpton LLP.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2162-1024x683.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="683" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2162-1024x683.png" alt="Ripple Lawsuit Unravels: Prominent Attorney To Withdrawal Amidst Settlement Talks" class="wp-image-206909" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2162-1024x683.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2162-300x200.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2162-768x512.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2162-750x500.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2162-1140x760.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2162.png 1500w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Ripple Lawsuit Unravels: Prominent Attorney To Withdrawal Amidst Settlement Talks 21"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">Brad Garlinghouse</figcaption></figure></div>


<p>Another attorney, Anna R. Gressel, also filed a motion to withdraw as an attorney for Ripple Labs on July 12. Ripple similarly requested the court to grant Anna R. Gressel of Debevoise &amp; Plimpton LLP the withdrawal, as she is no longer associated with the law firm effective as of July 12.</p>



<p>The case has seen additional changes in legal representation, with the court approving withdrawal motions for attorneys Clayton J. Masterman and Kylie Chiseul Kim, who have also exited from the lawsuit.</p>



<p>In response to the recent ruling and disclosure of Ripple&#8217;s future plans, the price of <a href="https://coincu.com/203962-ripple-jumps-over-10/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">XRP</a> experienced a surge. Notably, XRP holder and lawyer, John E. Deaton, emphasized that even if SEC Chair <a href="https://coincu.com/203493-gary-gensler-feeling-disappointed/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Gary Gensler</a> <a href="https://coincu.com/204894-us-sec-signals-appeal-court-ripple-xrp-case/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">seeks</a> an appeal, XRP will likely retain its classification as a non-security for at least two years. This prediction is based on the complexities the SEC may face in altering its stance on the matter.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2163.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="980" height="653" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2163.png" alt="Ripple Lawsuit Unravels: Prominent Attorney To Withdrawal Amidst Settlement Talks" class="wp-image-206910" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2163.png 980w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2163-300x200.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2163-768x512.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2163-750x500.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 980px) 100vw, 980px" title="Ripple Lawsuit Unravels: Prominent Attorney To Withdrawal Amidst Settlement Talks 22"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">Gary Gensler</figcaption></figure></div>


<p>In light of the ongoing developments and changing legal landscape, Judge Analisa Torres has entrusted Magistrate Judge Sarah Netburn with the responsibility of overseeing the Ripple vs SEC lawsuit. Magistrate Judge Netburn has directed both parties to negotiate and agree on three mutually convenient dates to schedule a settlement conference. This conference aims to address pertinent issues, including the institutional sales of XRP, and explore the possibility of resolving the case outside of court.</p>



<p>Amidst these legal proceedings, it is worth mentioning that Lisa R. Zornberg, the attorney seeking withdrawal from the Ripple case, was appointed as City Hall Chief Counsel by New York City Mayor Eric Adams this week, signifying her transition to a new role within the city&#8217;s administration.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER: </em></strong><em>The information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>
<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/206896-ripple-prominent-attorney-to-withdrawal/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2161-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto.com Gains Official Approval In The Netherlands</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/206893-crypto-com-gains-official-approval-netherlands/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Annie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 08:58:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto.com]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[De Nederlandsche Bank]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DNB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Netherlands]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=206893</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Crypto.com proudly announced today that it has achieved registration approval from De Nederlandsche Bank (DNB) to offer crypto services in the Netherlands. <p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/206893-crypto-com-gains-official-approval-netherlands/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>Crypto.com achieves registration approval from De Nederlandsche Bank (DNB) to offer crypto services in the Netherlands.</em></li>



<li><em>The milestone demonstrates Crypto.com&#8217;s commitment to responsible engagement with regulators and compliance with regulatory standards, strengthening its reputation and bolstering the confidence of users and investors.</em></li>



<li><em>Crypto.com collaborates closely with regulatory bodies to propel the crypto and blockchain industry forward responsibly, and is poised to extend its services and innovative offerings to the Dutch market, providing a secure and regulated environment for users to participate in the burgeoning crypto landscape.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Crypto.com proudly announced today that it has achieved registration approval from De Nederlandsche Bank (DNB) to offer crypto services in the Netherlands. </strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image is-style-default">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2156.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="621" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2156-1024x621.png" alt="image 2156" class="wp-image-206895" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2156-1024x621.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2156-300x182.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2156-768x466.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2156-1536x932.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2156-750x455.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2156-1140x692.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2156.png 1920w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Crypto.com Gains Official Approval In The Netherlands 23"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>This crucial <a href="https://crypto.com/company-news/crypto-com-secures-registration-approval-in-the-netherlands" target="_blank" data-type="URL" data-id="https://crypto.com/company-news/crypto-com-secures-registration-approval-in-the-netherlands" rel="noreferrer noopener">milestone</a> comes as a result of a thorough evaluation of Crypto.com&#8217;s business operations and compliance measures, aligning seamlessly with the stringent guidelines of the Netherlands&#8217; Money Laundering and Terrorist Financing (Prevention) Act (Wwft).</p>



<p>The registration confirmation signifies a significant achievement for Crypto.com, demonstrating its unwavering commitment to responsible engagement with regulators and compliance with regulatory standards. By collaborating closely with regulatory bodies, the platform seeks to propel the crypto and blockchain industry forward responsibly.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image is-style-default">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Crypto.com-Gains-Official-Approval-In-The-Netherlands.webp"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="536" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Crypto.com-Gains-Official-Approval-In-The-Netherlands-1024x536.webp" alt="Crypto.com Gains Official Approval In The Netherlands" class="wp-image-206898" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Crypto.com-Gains-Official-Approval-In-The-Netherlands-1024x536.webp 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Crypto.com-Gains-Official-Approval-In-The-Netherlands-300x157.webp 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Crypto.com-Gains-Official-Approval-In-The-Netherlands-768x402.webp 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Crypto.com-Gains-Official-Approval-In-The-Netherlands-1536x804.webp 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Crypto.com-Gains-Official-Approval-In-The-Netherlands-2048x1072.webp 2048w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Crypto.com-Gains-Official-Approval-In-The-Netherlands-750x393.webp 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Crypto.com-Gains-Official-Approval-In-The-Netherlands-1140x597.webp 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Crypto.com Gains Official Approval In The Netherlands 24"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>Kris Marszalek, the CEO of Crypto.com, expressed the company&#8217;s dedication to upholding compliance and fostering a constructive relationship with regulators. He stated, &#8220;Collaborating with regulators to responsibly advance the crypto and blockchain industry is of paramount importance to Crypto.com. This registration approval from De Nederlandsche Bank is a significant milestone for our business and the latest testament to our commitment to compliance. We look forward to continuing to work with DNB and other regulators around the world.&#8221;</p>


<div class="wp-block-image is-style-default">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2157.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="929" height="523" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2157.png" alt="image 2157" class="wp-image-206899" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2157.png 929w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2157-300x169.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2157-768x432.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2157-750x422.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 929px) 100vw, 929px" title="Crypto.com Gains Official Approval In The Netherlands 25"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>Crypto.com&#8217;s proactive approach in working with regulatory authorities not only strengthens the platform&#8217;s reputation but also bolsters the confidence of users and investors. The company&#8217;s commitment to robust compliance practices and transparent operations aligns with the broader industry&#8217;s push for increased regulation and security.</p>



<p>With the registration approval in hand, Crypto.com is poised to extend its services and innovative offerings to the Dutch market, providing a secure and regulated environment for users to participate in the burgeoning crypto landscape.</p>



<p id="block-643c4ba8-b40b-4525-9a96-f280dbfbeb9d"><strong><em>DISCLAIMER:&nbsp;</em></strong><em>The Information on this&nbsp;website&nbsp;is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>
<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/206893-crypto-com-gains-official-approval-netherlands/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Crypto.com-Gains-Official-Approval-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>ParaSpace Boosts New Support For NFT Lending With zkSync Integration</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/206839-paraspace-boosts-new-support/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Harold]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 08:38:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[NFT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ParaSpace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[WBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web3]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Zksync]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=206839</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[ParaSpace to launch zkSync network, supporting ETH, USDC, and WBTC for NFT lending.<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/206839-paraspace-boosts-new-support/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>ParaSpace to launch zkSync network, supporting ETH, USDC, and WBTC for NFT lending.</em></li>



<li><em>Platform swiftly resolves asset liquidation issues, reimbursing affected users.</em></li>



<li><em>Exciting upgrades in Version 2.0 promise enhanced user experience in DeFi lending.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>ParaSpace, the decentralized NFT lending protocol, has exciting news for its users. The platform has <a href="https://twitter.com/ParaSpace_NFT/status/1684826203499483136" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">announced</a> the upcoming launch of the zkSync network, a move aimed at further enhancing its capabilities and user experience.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2153.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="682" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2153-1024x682.png" alt="ParaSpace Boosts New Support For NFT Lending With zkSync Integration" class="wp-image-206885" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2153-1024x682.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2153-300x200.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2153-768x512.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2153-1536x1024.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2153-2048x1365.png 2048w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2153-750x500.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2153-1140x760.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="ParaSpace Boosts New Support For NFT Lending With zkSync Integration 26"></a></figure></div>


<p>With this integration, ParaSpace will support three major cryptocurrencies: ETH, USDC, and WBTC, expanding its reach and offering even more options to its users.</p>



<p>In addition to the zkSync network launch, ParaSpace has implemented four vital features, namely &#8220;Supply,&#8221; &#8220;Withdraw,&#8221; &#8220;Borrow,&#8221; and &#8220;Repay.&#8221; These features are designed to bolster the overall experience on the platform, providing users with more flexibility and control over their assets.</p>



<p>As a fully decentralized and permissionless protocol built on the Ethereum blockchain, ParaSpace has already gained popularity for its support of a wide range of fungible tokens, including BTC, ETH, DAI, USDC, and APE, along with various blue chip NFT collections. Furthermore, the platform has ambitious plans to promote capital efficiency across the crypto space by enabling cross-chain lending and borrowing for EVM-compatible or equivalent blockchains in the future.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2154-1024x538.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="538" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2154-1024x538.png" alt="ParaSpace Boosts New Support For NFT Lending With zkSync Integration" class="wp-image-206886" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2154-1024x538.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2154-300x158.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2154-768x403.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2154-750x394.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2154-1140x599.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2154.png 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="ParaSpace Boosts New Support For NFT Lending With zkSync Integration 27"></a></figure></div>


<p>Recently, ParaSpace also <a href="https://coincu.com/205075-paraspace-swift-action-on-asset/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">demonstrated</a> its commitment to its users by addressing and rectifying an issue related to asset liquidations that occurred between July 3 and July 4. The platform took prompt action and reimbursed the affected users for the price difference resulting from the liquidations. Moreover, to ensure transparency and provide clarity, ParaSpace plans to host an event for the affected users, demonstrating its dedication to creating a user-friendly ecosystem.</p>



<p>Looking ahead, <a href="https://coincu.com/200128-paraspace-azuki-airdrop-elementals-on-platform/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">ParaSpace</a> is gearing up for the launch of Version 2.0, which is <a href="https://coincu.com/202259-paraspace-upcoming-critical-upgrade-2-0/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">expected</a> to bring significant upgrades to the lending platform. With a strong focus on user-friendliness, this new version aims to empower the web3 community with seamless and powerful borrowing options. As the launch date approaches, excitement is building within the decentralized finance space as ParaSpace marks another milestone in its journey to revolutionize the lending ecosystem for NFTs and cryptocurrencies.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER: </em></strong><em>The information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your research before investing.</em></p>
<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/206839-paraspace-boosts-new-support/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2150-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
