<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 04:04:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Shiba Menu prediction: Is SHMU a good meme coin to buy?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-menu-prediction-is-shmu-a-good-meme-coin-to-buy/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-menu-prediction-is-shmu-a-good-meme-coin-to-buy/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 04:04:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-menu-prediction-is-shmu-a-good-meme-coin-to-buy/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Shiba Menu is a new crypto that is at the intersection of meme coins and AI. The developers have raised over $450k in less than two weeks. Memecoins and artificial intelligence have been some of the most popular themes this year. New meme tokens like Pepe and Keke have grown from nothing into some multi-million [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-menu-prediction-is-shmu-a-good-meme-coin-to-buy/">Shiba Menu prediction: Is SHMU a good meme coin to buy?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Menu is a new crypto that is at the intersection of meme coins and AI.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The developers have raised over $450k in less than two weeks.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Memecoins and artificial intelligence have been some of the most popular themes this year. New meme tokens like Pepe and Keke have grown from nothing into some multi-million dollar cryptocurrencies. On the other hand, AI companies like Nvidia and C3.ai have seen their shares jump by double digits. Shiba Menu, a new meme coin that is at the intersection of meme coins and AI, has also raised over $449k in the past few days.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Shiba Menu?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Meme coins are unique cryptocurrencies that started to boom in 2021. Their performance did well after the success of&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/dogecoin/"><u>Dogecoin</u></a><strong>,&nbsp;</strong>a proof-of-work coin that was promoted heavily by Elon Musk, the richest man on the planet. Since then, many meme tokens have come up, with the most popular ones being Shiba Inu, Floki Inu, and Dogelon Mars.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Several meme coins have come up this year, with the most successful ones being Pepe and Keke. Pepe has gone from nothing to becoming a meme coin valued at over $500 million. It has created many millionaires along the way.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Menu (SHMU) is a new meme coin that is seeking to capitalize on the ongoing success of meme coins and artificial intelligence. According to its&nbsp;<a href="https://shibamemu.com/whitepaper.pdf"><u>white paper</u></a><strong>,&nbsp;</strong>Shiba Menu is an AI-powered, self-marketing cryptocurrency. It will use AI to come up with marketing strategies, including writing its own PR.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Unlike many other meme coins that have no meaningful utility, Shiba Menu will create its utility over time. For example, it will be the only meme coin that can create its own marketing materials like PR and multi-platform marketing materials.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Potential catalysts for Shiba Menu</h2>
<p dir="ltr">There are three main potential catalysts for Shiba Menu. First, there is a likelihood that cryptocurrencies will do well this year. This probability will increase if Bitcoin manages to move above the important resistance at $31,200. If this breakout happens, there is a likelihood that other tokens will rise as well.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">As I wrote in this&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/pro-delivers-a-2-trillion-bch-solana-litecoin-mina-bitcoin-price-prediction/"><u>article</u></a><strong>&nbsp;</strong>on Tuesday, analysts at Standard Chartered expect that Bitcoin could jump to $120k. If this happens, there is a likelihood that other coins and tokens, including Shiba Menu will rise as well.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Second, Shiba Menu could rally because of the meme coin hype. After the success of key tokens like Pepe and Shiba Inu, many traders are constantly in search of the next big thing. After raising over $400k in a few weeks, there is a likelihood that the token will generate hype.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Finally, Shiba Menu is taking advantage of two hyped industries like AI and meme coins. Traders love such assets, as evidenced by the recent performance of key assets like Nvidia. You can buy Shiba Menu using this&nbsp;<a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news"><u>link</u></a><strong>.</strong></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Is Shiba Menu a good buy?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Investing in token presales and Initial Coin Offerings (ICO) is always risky and calls for caution. As such, while I expect Shiba Menu to thrive, I recommend caution. This means that you should only invest a small portion of your funds into the token. Doing this will give you exposure to the upside while limiting your potential risks.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-menu-prediction-is-shmu-a-good-meme-coin-to-buy/">Shiba Menu prediction: Is SHMU a good meme coin to buy?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-menu-prediction-is-shmu-a-good-meme-coin-to-buy/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Singapore&#8217;s Temasek is &#8216;not comfortable&#8217; investing in crypto firms: here&#8217;s why</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/singapore-temasek-not-comfortable-investing-crypto-firms/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wajeeh Khan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 23:29:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Interview]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Singapore]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=145755</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Temasek is reluctant investing in crypto firms due to regulatory uncertainty. Its CIO Rohit Sipahimalani discussed the crypto market with CNBC today. Temasek also recorded its worst returns since 2016 on Tuesday morning. Now is not a suitable time to invest in crypto companies, says Rohit Sipahimalani &#8211; the Chief Investment Officer of Temasek. Why [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/singapore-temasek-not-comfortable-investing-crypto-firms/">Singapore&#8217;s Temasek is &#8216;not comfortable&#8217; investing in crypto firms: here&#8217;s why</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Temasek is reluctant investing in crypto firms due to regulatory uncertainty.</li>
<li>Its CIO Rohit Sipahimalani discussed the crypto market with CNBC today.</li>
<li>Temasek also recorded its worst returns since 2016 on Tuesday morning.</li>
</ul>
<p>Now is not a suitable time to invest in crypto companies, says Rohit Sipahimalani &ndash; the Chief Investment Officer of Temasek.</p>
<h2>Why is Sipahimalani avoiding crypto?</h2>
<p>The enormous rally in <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> since the start of this year has established that cryptocurrencies are here to stay. Recent application for a <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/former-sec-chair-says-bitcoin-etf-approval-hard-to-resist/">Spot Bitcoin ETF</a> from BlackRock is an additional seal of approval as well.</p>
<p>Still, Sipahimalani is reluctant in exposing his Singapore-based investment firm to crypto companies due to the regulatory uncertainty. Speaking with <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/video/2023/07/11/temasek-says-its-very-difficult-to-invest-in-crypto-firms-now.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CNBC</a> this morning, he said:</p>
<blockquote><p>There&rsquo;s a lot of regulatory uncertainty in this environment. We would not be comfortable investing in exchanges given the way things are right now.</p></blockquote>
<p>The Securities and Exchange Commission is currently up against Ripple &ndash; the company behind XRP. It has also sued <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sec-may-fail-against-binance-prof-alexander/">Biance</a> and <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/06/30/sec-vs-coinbase-case-set-for-july-13-after-exchanges-creative-opening-response/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase</a> recently for violating the U.S. securities laws.</p>
<h2>Temasek was once an investor in FTX</h2>
<p>Also on Tuesday, the state-owned conglomerate cited macro and geopolitical challenges and <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-07-11/temasek-posts-worst-performance-in-seven-years-as-markets-slump" target="_blank" rel="noopener">recorded</a> a 5.07% decline in its annual shareholder return &ndash; the worst it has posted since 2016.</p>
<p>According to Sipahimalani, Temasek Holdings Limited is open to investing in crypto firms but only in a more favourable environment.</p>
<blockquote><p>If you have the right regulatory framework, and we&rsquo;re comfortable with, and you have the right investment opportunity, there&rsquo;s no reason for us not to look at it.</p></blockquote>
<p>Note that Temasek <a href="https://www.temasek.com.sg/en/news-and-resources/news-room/statements/2022/statement-FTX" target="_blank" rel="noopener">wrote down</a> its full investment in FTX last November to &ldquo;zero&rdquo;. The net value of its portfolio at writing is about $287 million.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/singapore-temasek-not-comfortable-investing-crypto-firms/">Singapore&#8217;s Temasek is &#8216;not comfortable&#8217; investing in crypto firms: here&#8217;s why</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Axelar and Microsoft partner to advance an intelligent Web3</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/axelar-and-microsoft-partner-to-advance-an-intelligent-web3/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/axelar-and-microsoft-partner-to-advance-an-intelligent-web3/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 15:17:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Microsoft]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/axelar-and-microsoft-partner-to-advance-an-intelligent-web3/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Tech giant Microsoft and cross-chain protocol Axelar have partnered to advance blockchain technologies. Axelar has joined Microsoft&#8217;s Azure marketplace. The partners will leverage the Azure cloud technology to enhance user experience across Web3. Microsoft and cross-chain protocol Axelar have announced an enterprise partnership that will see the two collaborate on interoperability and Web3 integration across [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/axelar-and-microsoft-partner-to-advance-an-intelligent-web3/">Axelar and Microsoft partner to advance an intelligent Web3</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Tech giant Microsoft and cross-chain protocol Axelar have partnered to advance blockchain technologies.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Axelar has joined Microsoft&rsquo;s Azure marketplace.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The partners will leverage the Azure cloud technology to enhance user experience across Web3.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/microsoft/">Microsoft</a> and cross-chain protocol Axelar have announced an enterprise partnership that will see the two collaborate on interoperability and Web3 integration across Web2 systems.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The tech giant and the crypto platform will work towards developing <a href="https://coinjournal.net/learn/what-is-blockchain/">blockchain</a> onramps to support all types of users, from global enterprises to Web3 startups.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Axelar joins Microsoft&rsquo;s Azure markeplace</h2>
<p dir="ltr">In an<a href="https://axelar.network/blog/microsoft-enterprise-partnership-announcement" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">&nbsp;<u>announcement</u></a> on July 11, Axelar said the partnership will also explore how to integrate artificial intelligence (AI) within the public blockchains ecosystem. The collaboration sees the blockchain company join Microsoft&rsquo;s Azure marketplace.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Axelar and Microsoft are pleased to announce a partnership for better integration of Web3 &amp; traditional internet systems. The partnership will explore ways public blockchains can can help secure trust and speed integration of artificial intelligence (AI) in mainstream use cases. <a href="https://t.co/XfKat1PIT0">pic.twitter.com/XfKat1PIT0</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Axelar network (@axelarcore) <a href="https://twitter.com/axelarcore/status/1678753340073603072?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 11, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">As a result of this partnership, Microsoft customers can use the Azure marketplace to access Axelar&rsquo;s blockchain solutions. Thousands of Microsoft&rsquo;s cloud computing partners use the Azure Marketplace for software discovery and integration.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Microsoft and Axelar also eye hybrid blockchain initiatives, including ones targeted at connecting private and public blockchains. The plan is to leverage the Azure OpenAI services to bring new experiences to Web3 users.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Daniel An, the director of business development at Microsoft Web3 &amp; AI, noted that the collaboration will boost further adoption of blockchain technology. He said:</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>We are excited to collaborate with Axelar to accelerate blockchain integration and deliver valuable solutions to our customers. By leveraging our strengths and expertise, we can empower organizations to embrace blockchain technology and transform their operations</em>.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/axelar-and-microsoft-partner-to-advance-an-intelligent-web3/">Axelar and Microsoft partner to advance an intelligent Web3</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/axelar-and-microsoft-partner-to-advance-an-intelligent-web3/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Aave DAO to decide on GHO Stablecoin on Ethereum</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/aave-dao-to-decide-on-gho-stablecoin-on-ethereum/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/aave-dao-to-decide-on-gho-stablecoin-on-ethereum/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 14:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Aave News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/aave-dao-to-decide-on-gho-stablecoin-on-ethereum/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways Aave community members to vote on GHO&#8217;s deployment on Ethereum The stablecoin has been live on the Ethereum blockchain&#8217;s Goerli testnet since February. Aave DAO to vote on GHO&#8217;s deployment on Ethereum The Aave DAO community members are set to start voting on whether to deploy the GHO stablecoin on the Ethereum blockchain. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/aave-dao-to-decide-on-gho-stablecoin-on-ethereum/">Aave DAO to decide on GHO Stablecoin on Ethereum</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Aave community members to vote on GHO&rsquo;s deployment on Ethereum</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The stablecoin has been live on the Ethereum blockchain&rsquo;s Goerli testnet since February.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr">Aave DAO to vote on GHO&rsquo;s deployment on Ethereum</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The Aave DAO community members are set to start voting on whether to deploy the GHO stablecoin on the Ethereum blockchain. The members will commence the vote later today.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Aave is one of the leading cryptocurrency platforms in the world, allowing users to earn yields on their staked tokens. GHO is the stablecoin developed by the Aave team.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Users can mint the GHO stablecoin against a diversified set of crypto assets. According to the development team, GHO holders will continue to earn interest on the supplied collateral, similar to the other lending services on Aave.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The proposal, if approved, would introduce GHO through so-called &ldquo;facilitators.&rdquo; thus, making it possible for &nbsp;Aave version 3 (V3) to mint the stablecoin against token holdings available on the platform.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The proposal stipulates that;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;If approved, the introduction of GHO would make stablecoin borrowing on the Aave Protocol more competitive and generate additional revenue for the Aave DAO by providing to the DAO treasury 100% of the interest payments made on GHO borrows.&rdquo;</em></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">GHO has been available on the Ethereum blockchain since February</h2>
<p dir="ltr">This&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>latest cryptocurrency news</u></a> doesn&rsquo;t come as a surprise, as the GHO stablecoin has been live on the Ethereum blockchain&rsquo;s Goerli testnet since February. So far, there have been no major bugs that affected the stablecoin on the Ethereum blockchain.</p>
<p dir="ltr">AAVE, the native coin of the Aave ecosystem, is up by more than 3% in the last 24 hours. At press time, the&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/aave/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>price of AAVE</u></a> stands at $72.74 per coin.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Aave team pointed out that it would allow users to mint GHO tokens against their supplied collaterals once the stablecoin launches on the Ethereum network.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The GHO stablecoin would be backed by a wide range of cryptocurrencies chosen by users. Furthermore, borrowers would continue to earn interest on their collateral assets.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Similar to other algorithmic stablecoins, GHO would be pegged at $1. However, with GHO, users would be required to supply collateral (at a specific collateral ratio) before they can mint GHO.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">In addition to that, when users repay their loans, the GHO protocol burns that user&rsquo;s GHO stablecoins.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/aave-dao-to-decide-on-gho-stablecoin-on-ethereum/">Aave DAO to decide on GHO Stablecoin on Ethereum</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/aave-dao-to-decide-on-gho-stablecoin-on-ethereum/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rodeo Finance exploited for the second time in a week, $1.53M lost</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/rodeo-finance-exploited-for-the-second-time-in-a-week-1-53m-lost/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/rodeo-finance-exploited-for-the-second-time-in-a-week-1-53m-lost/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 13:35:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hacked]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/rodeo-finance-exploited-for-the-second-time-in-a-week-1-53m-lost/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Rodeo Finance is an Arbitrum-based decentralized finance (DeFi) protocol. The hacker manipulated price oracles and executed trades using the manipulated price. The price of Rodeo Finance&#8217;s native token has plunged 54% after the hack. On July 11, the Arbitrum-powered decentralised finance (DeFi) protocol Rodeo Finance was hacked resulting in the loss of 810 Ether (ETH) [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/rodeo-finance-exploited-for-the-second-time-in-a-week-1-53m-lost/">Rodeo Finance exploited for the second time in a week, $1.53M lost</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul class="decimal_type">
<li>Rodeo Finance is an Arbitrum-based decentralized finance (DeFi) protocol.</li>
<li>The hacker manipulated price oracles and executed trades using the manipulated price.</li>
<li>The price of Rodeo Finance&rsquo;s native token has plunged 54% after the hack.</li>
</ul>
<p>On July 11, the Arbitrum-powered decentralised finance (DeFi) protocol Rodeo Finance was hacked resulting in the loss of 810 Ether (ETH) worth $1.53 million. The DEX was exploited using a code vulnerability in its Oracle.</p>
<p>Peckshield, a blockchain analytics company, revealed data showing that the exploiter eventually transferred the stolen funds from Arbitrum to <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/what-is-ethereum/">Ethereum</a> and exchanged 285 ETH for $unshETH. The ETH was subsequently placed on ETH2 staking by the exploiter. Last but not least, the exploiter used Tornado Cash, a well-known mixer service, to route the stolen ETH.</p>
<h2>Time-Weighted Average Price (TWAP) Orcale manipulation</h2>
<p>The hacker manipulated the Rodeo&rsquo;s Time-Weighted Average Price (TWAP) Orcale and tampered with the pricing of the ETH.</p>
<p>The TWAP Oracle is used by DeFi protocols to calculate the average price of assets for a specific time frame to mitigate price fluctuation due to the volatility in the crypto market. However, it is vulnerable to manipulations through artificial skewing of the calculated average prices of assets.</p>
<p>The exploiter first borrowed a large sum of ETH and then artificially manipulated the price to buy the same asset at a deflated price. Later the hacker returned the loan and made a profit based on the low price after the manipulations.</p>
<h2>Rodeo&rsquo;s TVL drops significantly</h2>
<p>Besides causing the Rodeo Finance (RDO) token to tumble 54%, the hack has also caused the total value locked (TVL) in Rodeo to drastically fall.</p>
<p>Before the hack, the DeFi protocol had $20 million in TVL, but it has since dropped below $500 after the hack.</p>
<p>This is the second time that Rodeo Finance is being hacked in July 2023. It was hacked again on July 5, 2023, and $89,000 worth of crypto assets were lost due to a vulnerability in its &lsquo;mintProtocolReserves&rsquo; function.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/rodeo-finance-exploited-for-the-second-time-in-a-week-1-53m-lost/">Rodeo Finance exploited for the second time in a week, $1.53M lost</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/rodeo-finance-exploited-for-the-second-time-in-a-week-1-53m-lost/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Memu presale: Meet the robot meme dog with a touch of AI genius</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memu-presale-meet-the-robot-meme-dog-with-a-touch-of-ai-genius/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memu-presale-meet-the-robot-meme-dog-with-a-touch-of-ai-genius/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 13:29:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOGE]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memu-presale-meet-the-robot-meme-dog-with-a-touch-of-ai-genius/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Shiba Memu is looking to dominate the meme coin sector with a pioneering AI-powered utility token. The concept behind this robot meme with a touch of AI genius is what could astound the legacy meme coins space. SHMU presale has raised more than $356k in less than a week. Talk of meme coins today and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memu-presale-meet-the-robot-meme-dog-with-a-touch-of-ai-genius/">Shiba Memu presale: Meet the robot meme dog with a touch of AI genius</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Shiba Memu is looking to dominate the meme coin sector with a pioneering AI-powered utility token.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The concept behind this robot meme with a touch of AI genius is what could astound the legacy meme coins space.</li>
<li dir="ltr">SHMU presale has raised more than $356k in less than a week.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Talk of meme coins today and what&rsquo;s likely to pop up in front of you would be the latest Shiba Inu dog meme dubbed Shiba Memu (SHMU).</p>
<p dir="ltr">Granted, <a href="https://coinjournal.net/dogecoin/">Dogecoin (DOGE)</a> and Shiba Inu (SHIB) sit pretty in the upper deck of the market cap ranking, their status as top meme dogs not under immediate threat. But is there a hint of investor focus shifting to a new project that promises to bring the best of two technology worlds together in an explosive marketing powerhouse?</p>
<p dir="ltr">The SHMU presale, which can be accessed <a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>here</u></a>, suggests this scenario could indeed surface.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Shiba Memu?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Today&rsquo;s biggest trends are crypto and artificial intelligence (AI) &ndash; and raring to go amid the exuberance is Shiba Memu. So the question one might want to ask is &lsquo;what is Shiba Memu?&rsquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">As briefly noted earlier, Shiba Memu is a new, revolutionary meme token that combines the power of blockchain and <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/ai/">AI</a>. While the meme token possesses all the attributes of memenomics, it comes loaded with &ldquo;new tricks&rdquo; that could see it become an unstoppable marketing powerhouse.</p>
<p dir="ltr">It will run on both ERC20 and Binance Smart Chain networks.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How does Shiba Memu work?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">AI tools can do wonders when it comes to tapping into machine learning and natural language processing (NLP), the reason it&rsquo;s such a hot topic even in the mainstream tech industry.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu taps into this to replace the human effort that traditional meme tokens employ to gain traction. Instead, the <a href="https://shibamemu.com/whitepaper.pdf" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">whitepaper</a> outlines a self-sufficient marketing platform powered by the native SHMU token.</p>
<p dir="ltr">At the heart of all the marketing will be an AI dashboard accessible and visible to all token holders. It will use NLP and ML as well as sentiment analysis, predictive analytics, image and video recognition and personalization (think of how effective ads marketing has become and tinker with that using an AI-powered dog that&rsquo;s capable of so much).</p>
<p dir="ltr">Some of the things the meme can achieve include creating marketing strategies, writing own PRs, and promoting itself over and over again. Leveraging AI means the project can outperform tabloid newspapers when it comes to getting content across for the purpose of attracting even more attention.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Other than churning &ldquo;gazillions&rdquo; of data and marketing details about the project, the robot meme dog will also monitor its own performance and adjust for optimized output. Engaging with users directly is another strategy of this project, the result of which could be increased visibility and trust in the token and potential uptick in specific demand for SHMU.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Shiba Memu presale</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The roadmap for Shiba Memu includes the launch of the above-mentioned AI dashboard in Q1, 2024. The platform will also implement user engagement features such as feedback and integrate social media platforms to boost marketing.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Development of the project will continue throughout the first half of the year, with listing on major exchanges expected in Q3, 2024. These future developments are however preceded by a <a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news"><u>token presale</u></a> that will see 85% of total supply of 1 billion SHMU available to early investors.</p>
<p dir="ltr">It&rsquo;s barely a week into that presale and investors have allocated over $356k into the project, with more than 25.7 million SHMU grabbed. Investors know that participating in the presale is one of the ways to get hold of Shiba Memu at greatly discounted prices.</p>
<p dir="ltr">One major difference between the Shiba Memu presale and similar token sales is that this one is open-ended and is scheduled to last 8 weeks. During this time, SHMU&rsquo;s price will increase every day at 6pm GMT.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The current presale price is $0.012475 and the next uptick will see it rise to $0.0127. It will double from here every time it increases until it reaches $0.0244.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How do you buy Shiba Memu tokens?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">There&rsquo;s only one way to buy SHMU during the presale &ndash; visit the project&rsquo;s <a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news"><u>website</u></a>. The project will go live on both the ERC20 and BSC networks. This means buying is available via ETH, USDT, BNB, and BUSD and one will need to have a supported wallet.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Currently, that&rsquo;s MetaMask for desktop users and Trust Wallet when buying on a smartphone.</p>
<p dir="ltr">After the presale and when tokens go live, earning SHMU will be possible via providing liquidity on a DEX and get rewarded in transaction fees. Another way to get hands on more of these meme tokens would be through buying on exchanges or staking to earn rewards.</p>
<p>Do you want to know more about Shiba Memu? <a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news"><u>Click here</u></a>.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memu-presale-meet-the-robot-meme-dog-with-a-touch-of-ai-genius/">Shiba Memu presale: Meet the robot meme dog with a touch of AI genius</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memu-presale-meet-the-robot-meme-dog-with-a-touch-of-ai-genius/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pro delivers a $2 trillion BCH, Solana, Litecoin, Mina, Bitcoin price prediction</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/pro-delivers-a-2-trillion-bch-solana-litecoin-mina-bitcoin-price-prediction/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/pro-delivers-a-2-trillion-bch-solana-litecoin-mina-bitcoin-price-prediction/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 12:43:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/pro-delivers-a-2-trillion-bch-solana-litecoin-mina-bitcoin-price-prediction/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An analyst at Standard Chartered delivered a strong Bitcoin prediction. He expects BTC price to jump to $120,000 in 2024. Bitcoin price has continued wavering in the past few weeks as investors wait for the next important crypto news and US inflation data. The coin was trading at $30,400, where it has been at in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/pro-delivers-a-2-trillion-bch-solana-litecoin-mina-bitcoin-price-prediction/">Pro delivers a $2 trillion BCH, Solana, Litecoin, Mina, Bitcoin price prediction</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">An analyst at Standard Chartered delivered a strong Bitcoin prediction.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">He expects BTC price to jump to $120,000 in 2024.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/"><u>Bitcoin</u></a> price has continued wavering in the past few weeks as investors wait for the next important crypto news and US inflation data. The coin was trading at $30,400, where it has been at in the past two weeks. As a result, the fear and greed index has moved to the neutral point of 56.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Standard Chartered is bullish on Bitcoin</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin price has jumped by more than 90% in 2023, meaning it has outperformed popular financial assets like the Dow Jones and the Nasdaq 100 indices. It has also done better than gold and other metals.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Now, despite the recent consolidation, some analysts believe that Bitcoin price has more upside in the next few months. The two biggest potential catalysts are the potential for a Bitcoin ETF. Analysts believe that the SEC will accept one or all of the recent proposals by companies like Blackrock and Invesco.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The other potential catalyst for Bitcoin will be the upcoming halving, which will happen in April next year. Historically, Bitcoin tends to rally ahead of the halving event. We can also look at the spectacular performance of Litecoin price since July last year. Litecoin&rsquo;s halving will happen in August.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Some analysts are bullish about Bitcoin. The most bullish analyst is from Standard Chartered. Two months ago, the analyst said that Bitcoin could surge to $100,000 by the end of 2024. In a note this week, the analyst said that he believes that BTC price could jump to $120,000. The analyst cited the ongoing miner activity,&nbsp;<a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/standard-chartered-bumps-up-bitcoin-forecast-120000-2023-07-10/"><u>saying</u></a>:</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;It is the equivalent of miners reducing the amount of bitcoins they sell per day to just 180-270 from 900 currently. Over a year, that would reduce miner selling from 328,500 to a range of 65,700-98,550 &ndash; a reduction in net BTC supply of roughly 250,000 bitcoins a year.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">&lsquo;If Standard Chartered&rsquo;s Bitcoin prediction is accurate, it means that its market cap could hit over $2.3 trillion by the end of 2024. That&rsquo;s because BTC has a market cap of over $591 billion.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Altcoins could jump as well</h2>
<p dir="ltr">If this Bitcoin&rsquo;s prediction is accurate, it means that other altcoins will do the same. For example, popular proof-of-work coins like Litecoin and&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin-cash/"><u>Bitcoin Cash</u></a> could resume their bullish rally. Litecoin has already jumped by over 134% from its 2022 lows. Bitcoin Cash, which is a Bitcoin&rsquo;s hard fork, has risen by over 100% in the past few weeks.</p>
<p dir="ltr">These coins are doing well because of their upcoming halving events. Litecoin will go through halving in August while Bitcoin Cash&rsquo;s will take place in December. These coins will also benefit if the SEC accepts the ETF since more companies will be motivated to launch their ETFs.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Other cryptocurrencies like Compound, Solana, Mina. and Internet Computer (ICP) could benefit because of the close correlation that exists in the crypto industry.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy Bitcoin</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>


<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=MTQ1NjM1&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy BTC with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    CEX.IO</h3>


<p>
    <a href="/visit/cex-crypto?guid=MTQ1NjM1&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy BTC with CEX.IO today            </a>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/pro-delivers-a-2-trillion-bch-solana-litecoin-mina-bitcoin-price-prediction/">Pro delivers a $2 trillion BCH, Solana, Litecoin, Mina, Bitcoin price prediction</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/pro-delivers-a-2-trillion-bch-solana-litecoin-mina-bitcoin-price-prediction/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin consolidation continues ahead of the US inflation report</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-consolidation-continues-ahead-of-the-us-inflation-report/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-consolidation-continues-ahead-of-the-us-inflation-report/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mircea Vasiu]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 11:35:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-consolidation-continues-ahead-of-the-us-inflation-report/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin forms a possible pennant formation ahead of the US inflation report The disinflationary process in the US is set to continue If the dollar takes a hit, Bitcoin may rise above horizontal resistance Summer trading is usually slow and tricky. Even the cryptocurrency market often consolidates levels longer than the norm. It is the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-consolidation-continues-ahead-of-the-us-inflation-report/">Bitcoin consolidation continues ahead of the US inflation report</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitcoin forms a possible pennant formation ahead of the US inflation report</li>
<li>The disinflationary process in the US is set to continue</li>
<li>If the dollar takes a hit, Bitcoin may rise above horizontal resistance</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p>Summer trading is usually slow and tricky. Even the cryptocurrency market often consolidates levels longer than the norm.</p>
<p>It is the case with Bitcoin lately. The good news for cryptocurrency fans is that Bitcoin price holds close to the year&rsquo;s high.</p>
<p>Therefore, one could only ask if this consolidation is a continuation pattern before another leg higher or if sellers put pressure here ahead of the key US inflation report to be released tomorrow.</p>
<p>Like it or not, Bitcoin&rsquo;s performance is linked to the way the US dollar moves. As such, US economic data is critical for the digital asset&rsquo;s performance, especially data directly impacting the Federal Reserve&rsquo;s monetary policy decisions.</p>
<h2>June US CPI is expected to show further declines</h2>
<p>It should be obvious by now that inflation is cooling in the Western Hemisphere. Not all countries have seen similar trends, but the disinflationary process is in full force.</p>
<p>That is why traders expect the June US CPI report, due for release tomorrow, to show that the annual inflation in the United States dropped to 3.1% from 4% previously. If matched by the actual data, the US dollar will take a hit as the bets of further increases from the Fed will decline dramatically.</p>
<p>Hence, Bitcoin should pop above the horizontal resistance seen at $32k.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/11/1689074986789-0e022f43-0f8d-4a18-9196-5f9008361253.jpg" style="width: 1800px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="1800" height="488"></p>
<p><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/?exchange=CRYPTO" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Bitcoin chart by TradingView</a></p>
<h2>A possible pennant keeps Bitcoin hodlers optimistic</h2>
<p>A pennant is a bullish technical analysis pattern. The market typically rallies after a bullish breakout and travels a distance equal to the distance prior to the pennant&rsquo;s formation.</p>
<p>In Bitcoin&rsquo;s case, this is about $6k on top of $31k, so $37k is the logical target.</p>
<p>But that won&rsquo;t happen unless the US inflation report delivers a positive surprise. More precisely, if the inflation cools down more than expected, the Fed is less likely to raise rates, and so the US dollar should weaken.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-consolidation-continues-ahead-of-the-us-inflation-report/">Bitcoin consolidation continues ahead of the US inflation report</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-consolidation-continues-ahead-of-the-us-inflation-report/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Zuckerberg’s Threads hits 100 million users- What&#8217;s in it for Chancer?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/zuckerbergs-threads-hits-100-million-users-whats-in-it-for-chancer/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/zuckerbergs-threads-hits-100-million-users-whats-in-it-for-chancer/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 11:07:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Twitter]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/zuckerbergs-threads-hits-100-million-users-whats-in-it-for-chancer/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Twitter rival Threads has raced to more than 100 million users days after its launch. Chancer is a predictive markets app built on the blockchain and which seeks to disrupt the betting market. The $CHANCER presale is gaining upside momentum amid investor exuberance on project&#8217;s potential. Chancer&#8217;s presale is gathering fresh momentum, with over 67 [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/zuckerbergs-threads-hits-100-million-users-whats-in-it-for-chancer/">Zuckerberg’s Threads hits 100 million users- What&#8217;s in it for Chancer?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Twitter rival Threads has raced to more than 100 million users days after its launch.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Chancer is a predictive markets app built on the blockchain and which seeks to disrupt the betting market.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The $CHANCER presale is gaining upside momentum amid investor exuberance on project&rsquo;s potential.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Chancer&rsquo;s presale</a> is gathering fresh momentum, with over 67 million tokens sold and nearly $680k raised so far. This comes as the investor community gets to learn about the potential impact of this blockchain-based predictive markets platform in the global betting industry.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The project is also attracting interest at a time when what would end up as an epic battle in the social media space takes shape.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What&rsquo;s Threads?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Mark Zuckerberg, the CEO &amp; founder of Meta Platforms (formerly Facebook), recently announced the launch of Threads, a new social media platform touted as the biggest threat to Twitter. Days after the launch, which saw over 30 million sign ups in hours, Threads has hit more than 100 million users.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The rivalry between this Instagram sister app and the Elon Musk-owned platform might just be at the beginning of what could turn into a titanic battle. Already, Musk has labelled Threads a copycat and his lawyers have threatened legal action over allegations that Meta snapped former Twitter employees to gain insider information that it used to create Threads.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Threads has Twitter-like features such as liking posts, commenting, retweeting (reposting), and sharing. There are no direct messages or hashtags. The app however supports 500 characters per thread (more than Twitter), and videos of up to 5 minutes.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Twitter vs. Threads: &nbsp;Who&rsquo;s your money on?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Statistics <a href="https://www.statista.com/statistics/303681/twitter-users-worldwide/">show</a> Twitter&rsquo;s users number less than 370 million, which means Threads could possibly overtake it. It is notable that Twitter had to wait five years to reach 100 million users &ndash; something Threads did in four days.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Predictions on the possibility of Threads overtaking Twitter or not are part of the social conversation now. Also not surprising is the fact that some people might have placed wagers on one or the other outcome.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">While the Musk vs. Zuckerberg &ldquo;caged match&rdquo; type of battle has zero chance of happening, if it ever does, blockchain-based Chancer app could be where most wagers happen due to its completely different approach to betting.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Chancer?</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Chancer</a> is a new predictive markets platform that looks to tap into the power of blockchain technology to revolutionise the betting industry. While a few crypto projects offer prediction markets products, Chancer is taking a new approach to the industry &ndash; one that is tailored towards removing control from traditional bookmakers.</p>
<p dir="ltr">It seeks to replace the centralised approach of legacy betting companies with a decentralised peer-to-peer (P2P) model. The goal, according to the Chancer whitepaper, is to put users in control of the markets (odds, rules, payouts).</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bettors placing wager on any market can play by their own rules and leverage the utility of the native $CHANCER token to benefit from passive income opportunities. Token holders also have a chance to earn passively by staking tokens to bolster network security.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Chancer presale gains fresh momentum</h2>
<p dir="ltr">$CHANCER is a Binance Smart Chain token currently in presale. There&rsquo;s fresh momentum for the token sale as investors poured over $200k in two days to push overall fundraising proceeds to over $676k.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">As CoinJournal <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-introduces-a-unique-betting-platform-for-cryptocurrency-enthusiasts/">highlighted</a> in June, Chancer&rsquo;s unique approach could be very attractive to investors.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Investors who participate in the presale are helping Chancer raise funds to achieve its mission of democratising the betting industry. And it&rsquo;s likely that investing now while prices of the native token are still low could come with significant future returns.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The platform targets $15 million across 12 presale stages. </p>
<h2 dir="ltr">A look at the Chancer roadmap</h2>
<p dir="ltr">As well as the <a href="https://chancer.com/whitepaper.pdf" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">whitepaper</a> that outlines the technology behind the project and how it works, many people eyeing investments in its token also look at the roadmap. In most cases, a clear roadmap with strategic milestones is critical to a project&rsquo;s overall success.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer&rsquo;s roadmap includes the token launch on exchanges in the third quarter of 2023 before further development of the P2P platform in the next quarter. Testnets for the product will then pave the way for the mainnet launch expected in Q1, 2024.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The platform will also integrate Filecoin for file storage and launch its quadratic governance system as it works on achieving true decentralisation.</p>
<p dir="ltr">If you are looking for more details about Chancer before you invest, a good place to start would be <a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">here</a>.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/zuckerbergs-threads-hits-100-million-users-whats-in-it-for-chancer/">Zuckerberg’s Threads hits 100 million users- What&#8217;s in it for Chancer?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/zuckerbergs-threads-hits-100-million-users-whats-in-it-for-chancer/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
