<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 22:17:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin miner Marathon Digital reports a disappointing second quarter</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-miner-marathon-digital-q2-earnings-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wajeeh Khan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 22:17:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=149032</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Marathon Digital reports weaker-than-expected results for its fiscal Q2. CEO Fred Thiel was still positive in the press release on Tuesday. Marathon Digital stock is currently up more than 350% year-to-date. Shares of Marathon Digital Holdings Inc showed resilience in extended hours even though the Bitcoin miner reported disappointed financial results for the second quarter. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-miner-marathon-digital-q2-earnings-report/">Bitcoin miner Marathon Digital reports a disappointing second quarter</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Marathon Digital reports weaker-than-expected results for its fiscal Q2.</li>
<li>CEO Fred Thiel was still positive in the press release on Tuesday.</li>
<li>Marathon Digital stock is currently up more than 350% year-to-date.</li>
</ul>
<p>Shares of Marathon Digital Holdings Inc showed resilience in extended hours even though the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> miner reported disappointed financial results for the second quarter.</p>
<h2>CEO Fred Thiel was still positive in the press release</h2>
<p>The digital asset technology company lost 13 cents a share on an adjusted basis in its recently concluded quarter on $81.8 million in revenue.</p>
<p>In comparison, analysts had called for a loss of 6 cents per share only and $83.4 million in revenue. Still, CEO Fred Thiel said in the <a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2023/08/08/2721192/0/en/Marathon-Digital-Holdings-Reports-Second-Quarter-2023-Results.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">press release</a> today:</p>
<blockquote><p>After a strong start to the year, we accelerated our progress in the second quarter by significantly growing our hash rate and improving our efficiency.</p></blockquote>
<p>Shares of <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/mara-stock-price-tests-key-resistance-is-marathon-digital-a-buy/">Marathon Digital Holdings</a> are up more than 350% year-to-date at writing.</p>
<h2>Marathon Digital sold 63% of produced Bitcoin in Q2</h2>
<p>Marathon Digital produced 2,926 Bitcoin in total in its second quarter and gained $23.4 million as it sold 63% of them to fund operating costs. According to the Chief Executive:</p>
<blockquote><p>We exited the quarter with $113.7 million in unrestricted cash and equivalents and 12,538 Bitcoin, the market value of which was approx. $380 million on June 30<sup>th</sup>.</p></blockquote>
<p>The miner also saw impairment charges narrow sharply to $8.4 million in its Q2.</p>
<p>On Tuesday, Marathon Digital also confirmed in an <a href="https://ir.mara.com/sec-filings/all-sec-filings/content/0001493152-23-027172/0001493152-23-027172.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener">8-K filing</a> that it had to restate cash flow for Q1. Wall Street currently has a consensus &ldquo;overweight&rdquo; rating on the world&rsquo;s largest listed Bitcoin miner.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-miner-marathon-digital-q2-earnings-report/">Bitcoin miner Marathon Digital reports a disappointing second quarter</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chancer token sale thriving as crypto fear and greed index sleeps</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-token-sale-thriving-as-crypto-fear-and-greed-index-sleeps/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-token-sale-thriving-as-crypto-fear-and-greed-index-sleeps/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 20:58:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-token-sale-thriving-as-crypto-fear-and-greed-index-sleeps/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The fear and greed index in the crypto industry has remained in a neutral phase. Chancer, a new blockchain for the betting market, has raised over $1.2 million. Cryptocurrencies have been in a tight range since the first week of July as their demand has fizzled. Most coins, including popular names like Bitcoin,&#160;Ethereum, and Ripple [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-token-sale-thriving-as-crypto-fear-and-greed-index-sleeps/">Chancer token sale thriving as crypto fear and greed index sleeps</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The fear and greed index in the crypto industry has remained in a neutral phase.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Chancer, a new blockchain for the betting market, has raised over $1.2 million.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Cryptocurrencies have been in a tight range since the first week of July as their demand has fizzled. Most coins, including popular names like Bitcoin,&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum"><u>Ethereum</u></a>, and Ripple have consolidated as the fear and greed index has been stuck at the neutral point of 50.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Despite this consolidation, crypto investors are still taking advantage of emerging trends like buying pre-sale tokens.&nbsp;<a href="https://chancer.com/"><u>Chancer</u></a>, a new blockchain aiming to disrupt the sports betting industry, has emerged as one of the top tokens. It has raised over $1.2 million in the past 30 days.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Chancer?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The sports betting industry is a major one. For example, DraftKings has a market cap of more than $14 billion while Flutter Entertainment and Entain are valued at 26 billion and 8.93 billion pounds, respectively. Other multi-bilion dollar betting companies are Penn Entertainment, Churchill Downs, and Boyd Gaming among others.</p>
<p dir="ltr">These companies have grown rapidly, thanks to the internet and friendly regulations in most countries. For example, a Supreme Court ruling striked down a federal law that prohibated sports betting. As a result, it is now legal to bet in many states in the United States.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer is aiming to disrupt the industry by using the blockchain technology. Its platform will be loaded with additional features that will make betting easier and more social. For example, any $CHANCER holder will be able to create a market and make money as people place their bets in it. &nbsp;Chancer&rsquo;s&nbsp;<a href="https://chancer.com/whitepaper.pdf"><u>white paper</u></a><strong>&nbsp;</strong>adds:</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;These tokens not only grant you the ability to create markets but also provide an opportunity to invest in markets created by other individuals. By holding $CHANCER tokens, you have a direct stake in our platform&rsquo;s triumph.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">You can buy the Chancer token&nbsp;<a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news"><u>here</u></a>.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Chancer will be highly decentralized</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Most importantly, Chancer will be highly decentralized. While it will be centralized in the beginning, the developers will later on create a&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/learn/what-is-a-dao/"><u>decentralized autonomous organization</u></a><strong>&nbsp;</strong>(DAO) that will govern the network. This DAO will set rules, add integrations, and make key decisions.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Further, Chancer users will be able to share the profits made by the network. This is contrary to what centralized betting companies like DraftKings and Flutter Entertainment, where the managers make all the decisions.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, there is a likelihood that the Chancer token will do well when the token is listed in exchanges like Binance, Huobi, and OKX. It has already demonstrated that there is demand for the token during the pre-sale period.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Most importantly, this token sale is happening when there is limited demand for cryptocurrencies as evidenced by the fear and greed index, which has remained at the neutral phase of 50.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-token-sale-thriving-as-crypto-fear-and-greed-index-sleeps/">Chancer token sale thriving as crypto fear and greed index sleeps</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-token-sale-thriving-as-crypto-fear-and-greed-index-sleeps/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Exploring the bullish case for AltSignals in 2023 as presale accelerates</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/exploring-the-bullish-case-for-altsignals-in-2023-as-presale-accelerates/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/exploring-the-bullish-case-for-altsignals-in-2023-as-presale-accelerates/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Motiur Rahman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 18:01:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technical Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/exploring-the-bullish-case-for-altsignals-in-2023-as-presale-accelerates/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>AltSignals has built a successful trading signal service since 2017&#160; The platform will tilt towards an AI-led service that is expected to increase investors&#8217; earnings $ASI has huge potential for up to 10x returns on continued use of its platform While investors maintain a lukewarm sentiment on crypto, newly launched projects are gaining success. AltSignals [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/exploring-the-bullish-case-for-altsignals-in-2023-as-presale-accelerates/">Exploring the bullish case for AltSignals in 2023 as presale accelerates</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals has built a successful trading signal service since 2017&nbsp;</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The platform will tilt towards an AI-led service that is expected to increase investors&rsquo; earnings</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">$ASI has huge potential for up to 10x returns on continued use of its platform</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">While investors maintain a lukewarm sentiment on crypto, newly launched projects are gaining success. AltSignals ($ASI), a successful trading signal service in the UK, has attracted investors at the presale. The presale raises funds for a new artificial intelligence trading platform. AltSignals expects the AI platform to improve the quality of trading signals and supercharge earnings. Investors can&nbsp;<a href="https://token.altsignals.io/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>join</u></a> the AI trading signal platform by purchasing $ASI, the native token.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Leveraging AI in trading &ndash; The power of AltSignals</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals is a platform created in 2017 by a team of experienced UK traders. Since then, the platform has grown popular, with its quality trading signals averaging 64% accuracy rates. Over 52,000 traders use the signal service.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">In the past, AltSignals has been using the AltAlgo&trade; indicator to generate trading signals. Following exponential growth, AltSignals is tapping into the power of AI to generate trading signals. AI is expected to improve the quality of signals and help the team cover more financial instruments.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">In line with the new growth focus, AltSignals will create a new platform dubbed ActualizeAI. Members will own $ASI, the token to power transactions and transfer value on the platform.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>What are the benefits of owning $ASI?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Investing in $ASI means becoming a member of ActualizeAI, with full benefits of AltSignals trading signals. With a successful trading service, investors will benefit from quality signals increasing their incomes.</p>
<p dir="ltr">$ASI also holds a huge potential to increase value and return to early investors. The value of the cryptocurrency will be determined by the continued use of ActualizeAI.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Investing in AltSignals also means accessing and belonging to a trading community. Investors learn from the AltSignals team and other traders on the platform. Regular trading contests and tournaments are ideal for traders to showcase their skills. They also learn from peers to improve their trading competencies. Investors get rewarded with $ASI for winning the contests.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals also gives members a chance to get involved in the project. Investors can join the AI Members Club and be rewarded for giving ideas and feedback on the project. Members will also use their tokens to vote on governance issues. Other benefits of $ASI include exclusive access to presale opportunities and AI-powered products.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>&nbsp;Will $ASI become bullish in 2023?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">$ASI will be listed on Uniswap in Q3 2023. This could be when the token will have a genuine chance of skyrocketing in value. The prediction is based on historical price trends, where tokens rise strongly after listing.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">2023 is also a year that AI is gaining prominence. As a result, $ASI could ride on the optimism to increase in value.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, $ASI presents an opportunity beyond 2023. Most developmental activity for the ActualizeAI platform will happen in 2024. It means sustainable gains in $ASI could be realised beyond 2023 from the use of the AI platform.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Given how fast the presale is happening, $ASI could rise by up to three-digit percentages in 2023. In 2024, $ASI could be 10x investment or higher in the future.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Should you invest in $ASI while on presale?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">One of the benefits of purchasing $ASI in presale is gaining early access to the AI trading platform. For traders, this is an opportunity of a lifetime to benefit from quality trading signals. These signals cover forex markets, crypto, stocks, and CFDs.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Investing in $ASI on presale is also advantageous since the token&rsquo;s value is still low. The value will be higher when the $ASI lists and investors will spend more to buy it.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">With the current price at $0.01875, $ASI is a bargain for value-seeking investors. Investors will also ride a bullish momentum when it occurs after listing.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/exploring-the-bullish-case-for-altsignals-in-2023-as-presale-accelerates/">Exploring the bullish case for AltSignals in 2023 as presale accelerates</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/exploring-the-bullish-case-for-altsignals-in-2023-as-presale-accelerates/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kraken listing sends Reddit community tokens to the moon</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/kraken-listing-sends-reddit-community-tokens-to-the-moon/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 17:48:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kraken]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/kraken-listing-sends-reddit-community-tokens-to-the-moon/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The r/FortNiteBR Bricks (BRICK) token hit a high of $0.1792 after a 443% surge today. The r/CryptoCurrency Moons (MOON) token hit a high of $0.498 after a 48% surge today. The two Reddit community tokens are rising after Kraken announced it will list the two coins. Kraken on August 7, announced the listing of the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/kraken-listing-sends-reddit-community-tokens-to-the-moon/">Kraken listing sends Reddit community tokens to the moon</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul class="decimal_type">
<li>The r/FortNiteBR Bricks (BRICK) token hit a high of $0.1792 after a 443% surge today.</li>
<li>The r/CryptoCurrency Moons (MOON) token hit a high of $0.498 after a 48% surge today.</li>
<li>The two Reddit community tokens are rising after Kraken announced it will list the two coins.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/kraken/">Kraken</a> on August 7, announced the listing of the two Reddit community tokens, Moon and Brick, for spot trading and long-term futures. At press time, Kraken users could only deposit the two tokens through the Arbitrum Nova network.</p>
<p>The two tokens r/FortNiteBR Bricks (BRICK) and r/CryptoCurrency Moons (MOON) have been at the centre of the top cryptocurrency gainers in the recent past; which is the likely reason as why Kraken decided to list them.</p>
<h2>Reddit community cryptocurrencies&rsquo; hype</h2>
<p>Reddit launched its cryptocurrencies in 2021 after a <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/reddit-full-steam-ahead-with-cryptocurrency-to-reward-good-posting/">beta test in 2020</a> as part of the Reddit Community Points (RCP) initiative to incentivize content production on the platform. Interestingly, when Reddit users exchange their community tokens for rewards, Reddit pays the gas fee needed for the transaction. In addition, community token holders can participate in governance proposals that seek to introduce new functionality to the tokens.</p>
<p>Currently, the two main Reddit Community tokens are r/FortNiteBR Bricks (BRICK) and r/CryptoCurrency Moons (MOON).</p>
<p>MOON is a community token developed for the Reddit subreddit r/CryptoCurrency. It is used to award Reddit users for comments and posts. In addition, users can trade Moon for emojis and badges to use inside the subReddit. The token also entitles holders to the right to vote in polls held by the r/CryptoCurrency community.</p>
<p>BRICK, on the other hand, is a community token developed for the Battle Royale Game subReddit r/FortNiteBR. Every four weeks, bricks are distributed to users based on their Karma, or reputation points, and stored in Reddit&rsquo;s native cryptocurrency wallet, Reddit Vault. The bricks can then be traded in for exclusive memberships and unlocked features on r/FortNiteBR.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/kraken-listing-sends-reddit-community-tokens-to-the-moon/">Kraken listing sends Reddit community tokens to the moon</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin stays below $30k: Will inflation data push it higher?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-stays-below-30k-will-inflation-data-push-it-higher/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-stays-below-30k-will-inflation-data-push-it-higher/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 15:43:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-stays-below-30k-will-inflation-data-push-it-higher/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways Bitcoin has been trading below the $30k level in recent days, but favourable inflation data could push it higher. Chancer&#8217;s stage two presale is now close to the $1.2 million mark.&#160; The cryptocurrency market has been choppy over the past few weeks, with prices of most coins stuck within certain regions. BTC has [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-stays-below-30k-will-inflation-data-push-it-higher/">Bitcoin stays below $30k: Will inflation data push it higher?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin has been trading below the $30k level in recent days, but favourable inflation data could push it higher.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Chancer&rsquo;s stage two presale is now close to the $1.2 million mark.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">The cryptocurrency market has been choppy over the past few weeks, with prices of most coins stuck within certain regions.</p>
<p dir="ltr">BTC has been trading below the $30k level for the past few days, with market experts still believing it could drop lower in the near term.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitcoin stays below $30k</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin, the world&rsquo;s number one cryptocurrency by market cap, began the week in a positive manner. BTC has added more than 1.5% to its value so far today but continues to trade below the $30k psychological level.</p>
<p dir="ltr">At press time, the&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>price of Bitcoin</u></a> stands at $29,424. Bitcoin could be heading towards the $30k level over the new few hours or days if the inflation data in the United States comes out favourably.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The inflation data could determine if the US Federal Reserve continues its rate hikes or will stop them. Halting rate hikes could be a bullish sign for Bitcoin and the broader cryptocurrency market.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Chancer?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The recent bearish trend in the market has not affected Chancer&rsquo;s ongoing presale event.&nbsp;<a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Chancer</u></a> is a web3 project that seeks to decentralise the betting ecosystem.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">It is a Web3 peer-to-peer (P2P) custom betting platform allowing users to live stream betting events. Chancer will operate as a completely decentralised online gaming platform.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer is building a platform that will offer improved services compared to what they are getting from the traditional sports and casino betting platforms. With Chancer, users can bet on any event, even ones they make up themselves.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The funds raised from the funding rounds will be used to build the decentralised P2P betting platform. According to their whitepaper, Chancer users will have access to a wide range of features, including betting markets in real-time and based on user interests, social media connections, and expertise.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Users will also be able to set up their custom P2P betting markets, allowing others to bet on selected events and games.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Chancer&rsquo;s second presale generates nearly $1.2 million</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer&rsquo;s presale event will occur in stages, and the second stage is currently underway. The team has raised nearly $1.2 million of the $2 million required in the second stage.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Chancer</u></a> will use the funds from the presale to develop its products. The team will conduct 12 presale events, with a target of $15 million.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Currently, CHANCER, the native token of the ecosystem, is going for $0.011 per token, with the price set to increase to $0.012 in the next presale round.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The native token has numerous utilities within the ecosystem. Token holders can create markets and also invest in markets launched by other users.</p>
<p dir="ltr">By holding the token, users can create, participate in, and profit from their very own predictive markets.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">You can purchase the CHANCER tokens by connecting your Web3 wallet to the Chancer website. Trust Wallet, MetaMask, Coinbase Wallet, and Rainbow are some supported wallets.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://console.igms.io/news-articles/manage/67227" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Visit the Chancer website</u></a> to get more information about the presale.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Should you buy CHANCER tokens now?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Investing in a project during its presale or private sale is usually one of the best decisions investors make. This is because the tokens are not available to the general public yet.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">With&nbsp;<a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Chancer</u></a>, it could be an excellent idea to invest in the project now. Chancer is a promising project and could gain massive adoption over the coming months and years.</p>
<p dir="ltr">If the adoption level rises, CHANCER&rsquo;s price could skyrocket, and early investors could benefit. Early investors in projects such as Ethereum, Solana, Dogecoin, and Shiba Inu, recorded thousands of percentages in ROI.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">If CHANCER gains the necessary adoption combined with a Bull Run, its price could soar higher in the medium to long term.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-stays-below-30k-will-inflation-data-push-it-higher/">Bitcoin stays below $30k: Will inflation data push it higher?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-stays-below-30k-will-inflation-data-push-it-higher/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance becomes first fully-licensed crypto exchange in El Salvador</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-becomes-first-fully-licensed-crypto-exchange-in-el-salvador/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 15:06:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[El Salvador]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-becomes-first-fully-licensed-crypto-exchange-in-el-salvador/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Binance has secured approval as both a Bitcoin Services Provider and the first non-provisional Digital Assets Services Provider. The licenses allow the exchange to offer tailor-made crypto products and services in El Salvador, according to a press release. Binance has been granted two key licenses in El Salvador, becoming the first fully-licensed crypto exchange in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-becomes-first-fully-licensed-crypto-exchange-in-el-salvador/">Binance becomes first fully-licensed crypto exchange in El Salvador</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Binance has secured approval as both a Bitcoin Services Provider and the first non-provisional Digital Assets Services Provider.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The licenses allow the exchange to offer tailor-made crypto products and services in El Salvador, according to a press release.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/binance/">Binance</a> has been granted two key licenses in <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/el-salvador/">El Salvador</a>, becoming the first fully-licensed crypto exchange in the country. El Salvador recognised Bitcoin as legal tender in 2021, the first country in the world to take the step.</p>
<p dir="ltr">CEO Changpeng Zhao tweeted (Xd) the news.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Binance?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Binance</a> is pleased to announce that it has become the first fully licensed crypto exchange in El Salvador.&#127480;&#127483;</p>
<p>Let&rsquo;s keep making crypto more accessible.<a href="https://t.co/kz91z2LAcL">https://t.co/kz91z2LAcL</a></p>
<p>&mdash; CZ &#128310; Binance (@cz_binance) <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1688919529399992320?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 8, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Binance acquires two licenses in El Salvador</h2>
<p dir="ltr">According to an <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/blog/ecosystem/binance-becomes-first-fully-licensed-crypto-exchange-in-el-salvador-348306456147004721" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">announcement</a> the Binance team published on Tuesday, the exchange has received the Bitcoin Services Provider license (BSP) and the Digital Assets Services Provider license (DASP) &ndash; issued by El Salvador&rsquo;s Central Reserve Bank (Banco Central de Reserva) and the National Commission of Digital Assets (Comisi&oacute;n Nacional de Activos Digitales) respectively.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The DASP license sees Binance become the first non-provisional crypto services provider in the Central American country.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>We are honored to be granted this license, as Binance continues to work collaboratively with regulatory agencies around the world to support global standards for the crypto and blockchain industry</em>,&rdquo; Min Lin, Binance Head of Latin America, said in a statement.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The approvals and the official announcement come after regulators completed all the due diligence and is a pointer to Binance&rsquo;s continued pursuit of <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/regulation/">regulatory compliance</a> across the world, the exchange noted in a press release.</p>
<p dir="ltr">El Salvador is thus among several countries to license Binance or grant it registration status, including Italy, France, Spain, Sweden and Dubai.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Commenting on the latest approval, Daniel Acosta, the Binance General Manager for Colombia, Central America and Caribbean, noted:</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>These licenses allow Binance to expand the products and services offered including options tailored to the needs of our customers in El Salvador. It is also a great opportunity to collaborate closely with government authorities to support the adoption of crypto assets in the country, foster financial inclusion, innovation and ensure customer protection</em>.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Binance was sued by the SEC in June and has exited a number of countries due to regulatory issues. However, it&rsquo;s also been aggressive in its expansion efforts, including into Japan.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-becomes-first-fully-licensed-crypto-exchange-in-el-salvador/">Binance becomes first fully-licensed crypto exchange in El Salvador</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Akash Network price outlook: can bulls push for $1?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/akash-network-price-outlook-can-bulls-push-for-1/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/akash-network-price-outlook-can-bulls-push-for-1/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 14:16:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/akash-network-price-outlook-can-bulls-push-for-1/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Akash Network price was up 12% in the past 24 hours. The AKT/USD pair reached highs near $0.70, and needs to flip the hurdle into support to strengthen upside momentum. Hype around AI and cloud computing could add to the bullish outlook. Akash Network, a decentralized marketplace for cloud computing, has seen the price of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/akash-network-price-outlook-can-bulls-push-for-1/">Akash Network price outlook: can bulls push for $1?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Akash Network price was up 12% in the past 24 hours.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The AKT/USD pair reached highs near $0.70, and needs to flip the hurdle into support to strengthen upside momentum.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Hype around AI and cloud computing could add to the bullish outlook.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Akash Network, a decentralized marketplace for cloud computing, has seen the price of its native token AKT jump by more than 12% in the past 24 hours.</p>
<p dir="ltr">While the resistance level at $0.70 remains key for bears, bulls&rsquo; sharp bounce over the past day has AKT trading in a positive trend. With <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/altcoins/">altcoins</a> also mirroring Bitcoin&rsquo;s trajectory, the latest upsurge could be the base for a fresh attempt at recapturing the coveted $1.00 level.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Akash Network price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Selling pressure saw AKT lose the important $1.00 level in May 2022, with lows of $0.22 reached in May this year. Since then, bulls have hit the $0.75 zone twice in the past two months. However, rejection at the level meant a retest of support at $0.50 in mid-July.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Prices have however remained above an ascending trendline support, suggesting bulls are still determined to reclaim the upper hand. If price breaks above $0.75, it could go on to retest the supply wall expected at $1.00.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Part of the Akash Network&rsquo;s bullish momentum is likely to come from the launch of its Akash GPU mainnet. After successfully navigating the <a href="https://twitter.com/akashnet_/status/1662134249988960258" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">testnet</a> in May, with multiple AI models tested on the NVIDIA A100, Akash moved a step closer to offering the first open-source marketplace for HD GPUs.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">NVIDIA H100s remain in record-high demand, but distribution is still limited and inefficient.</p>
<p>The launch of the Akash GPU Mainnet is almost here, which will create the first open-source marketplace for high-density GPUs.</p>
<p>The world is ready for the <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/AISupercloud?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#AISupercloud</a>. <a href="https://t.co/y6OTupy9iZ">https://t.co/y6OTupy9iZ</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Akash Network (@akashnet_) <a href="https://twitter.com/akashnet_/status/1687139561174966279?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 3, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">Excitement for what could be AI Supercloud, fueled by massive predictions for the artificial intelligence industry, will likely cascade into the AKASH market.</p>
<div class="fr-img-space-wrap"><span class="fr-img-caption fr-fic fr-dib fr-draggable" style="width: 700px"><span class="fr-img-wrap">
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/07/08/1691503576404-f7118642-114b-4000-bc00-15b0ae54997c.png" style="width: 700px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="700" height="267"><span class="fr-inner">Akash Network price chart. Source:&nbsp;<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/xZIlONgz/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">TradingView</a></span></p>
<p></p></span></span>
<p class="fr-img-space-wrap2">The daily RSI indicates that momentum remains with the bulls, a scenario likely to be helped by a strengthening of the MACD indicator.&nbsp;</p>
<p class="fr-img-space-wrap2">Also key is the continued support of the 50-day exponential moving average, currently providing a base at $0.57.</p>
</div>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/akash-network-price-outlook-can-bulls-push-for-1/">Akash Network price outlook: can bulls push for $1?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/akash-network-price-outlook-can-bulls-push-for-1/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Justin Sun addresses Huobi&#8217;s insolvency concerns, calls it a FUD</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/justin-sun-addresses-huobis-insolvency-concerns-calls-it-a-fud/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 13:34:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Huobi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Huobi-token News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/justin-sun-addresses-huobis-insolvency-concerns-calls-it-a-fud/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Huobi saw a record $64 million in outflows over the weekend. The Outflows followed reports that the exchange&#8217;s executives had been arrested in China. An Angel investor has also pointed to inconsistencies in Huobi&#8217;s reserves. Huobi customers withdrew $64 million over the weekend due to worries about the cryptocurrency exchange company going bankrupt and rumours [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/justin-sun-addresses-huobis-insolvency-concerns-calls-it-a-fud/">Justin Sun addresses Huobi&#8217;s insolvency concerns, calls it a FUD</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Huobi saw a record $64 million in outflows over the weekend.</li>
<li>The Outflows followed reports that the exchange&rsquo;s executives had been arrested in China.</li>
<li>An Angel investor has also pointed to inconsistencies in Huobi&rsquo;s reserves.</li>
</ul>
<p>Huobi customers withdrew $64 million over the weekend due to worries about the cryptocurrency exchange company going bankrupt and rumours that Chinese authorities were looking into their management.</p>
<p>All these started on August 4 after Chinese authorities allegedly detained Huobi&rsquo;s top executives. It was reported that the arrests were the result of an investigation into the exchange&rsquo;s ties to betting websites.</p>
<h2>Huobi woes</h2>
<p>The rules governing cryptocurrency trading platforms appear to be getting stricter in China. Also, uncertainty exists regarding whether the recent resignation of one of the exchange&rsquo;s senior executives was related to the ongoing investigations in China.</p>
<p>However, Huobi&rsquo;s social media manager refuted the allegations and stated that the exchange is &ldquo;currently doing well.&rdquo;</p>
<p>But according to angel investor and fintech executive Adam Cochran, Huobi is allegedly having financial issues. Adam Cochran has specifically pointed to some inconsistencies in the exchange&rsquo;s <a href="https://coinjournal.net/tether/what-is-tether/">Tether (USDT)</a> balances.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">11/16</p>
<p>So users *think* they have balances of $631M in Huobi, but there is only $90M there.</p>
<p>The rest Justin Sun is using to prop up his other defi apps, and paying a yield on it to get users to deposit more into Huobi.</p>
<p>&mdash; Adam Cochran (adamscochran.eth) (@adamscochran) <a href="https://twitter.com/adamscochran/status/1687959127048298496?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 5, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>According to Cochran, Huobi&rsquo;s most recent &ldquo;Merkle Tree Audit&rdquo; claims that they hold $630 million in USDT, but on-chain data revealed that as of August 5, they had less than $90 million in assets, which according to the investor suggests that Huobi might not be able to pay its debts.</p>
<h2>Justin Sun&rsquo;s response</h2>
<p>Justin Sun, the CEO of the Huobi Exchange, responded to the circulating allegations of the crypto exchange being about to fail and called it a FUD.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">The past two days have seen people getting concerned due to the spreading FUD. </p>
<p>We want to take a second to respond in the open, with absolute sincerity and clarity:<a href="https://t.co/t4tf1uiE9q">https://t.co/t4tf1uiE9q</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Huobi (@HuobiGlobal) <a href="https://twitter.com/HuobiGlobal/status/1688459973141966848?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 7, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script> </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/justin-sun-addresses-huobis-insolvency-concerns-calls-it-a-fud/">Justin Sun addresses Huobi&#8217;s insolvency concerns, calls it a FUD</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase to buy back up to $150M of its $1B bonds</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-to-buy-back-up-to-150m-of-its-1b-bonds/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-to-buy-back-up-to-150m-of-its-1b-bonds/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 12:49:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-to-buy-back-up-to-150m-of-its-1b-bonds/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Coinbase&#8217;s partial bonds buyback targets up to $150 million of the $1 billion bonds. City Global Managers will be the offer&#8217;s dealer manager. Coinbase said on Monday that it is commencing a partial repurchase of its $1 billion bonds. Per the company, whose Q2, 2023 financial report came in stronger than forecast, the plan is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-to-buy-back-up-to-150m-of-its-1b-bonds/">Coinbase to buy back up to $150M of its $1B bonds</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Coinbase&rsquo;s partial bonds buyback targets up to $150 million of the $1 billion bonds.</li>
<li dir="ltr">City Global Managers will be the offer&rsquo;s dealer manager.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/coinbase/">Coinbase</a> said on Monday that it is commencing a partial repurchase of its $1 billion bonds.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Per the company, whose Q2, 2023 financial report came in stronger than forecast, the plan is to buy back up to $150 million of the 3.265% bonds. The bonds are set to mature in 2031.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Offer expires on September 1</h2>
<p dir="ltr">A <a href="https://investor.coinbase.com/news/news-details/2023/Coinbase-Commences-Cash-Tender-Offer-for-Up-to-150.0-Million-Aggregate-Purchase-Price-of-its-Outstanding-3.625-Senior-Notes-Due-2031/default.aspx" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">press release</a> from Coinbase indicated that investors who tender their Notes for the purchase program before August 18 will be eligible for an early buy offer that includes a $30 premium. This group of holders will receive $645 per $1,000 of the bond&rsquo;s principal amount, translating to 64.5 cents on each dollar.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Meanwhile, participants who validly offer to sell their bonds after August 18 but before the offer&rsquo;s expiry date of September 1 will get $615 per $1000 of the bond&rsquo;s principal value. In any case, both sets of participants will see a premium return on unaffected, preannouncement bond price of 60 cents per dollars&rsquo; worth.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Coinbase reported $708 million in revenue for the second quarter, beating analyst estimates of $628 million by more than 13%. Adjusted earnings per share loss came in at $0.42, compared to forecasts of $0.76.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Citigroup Global Markets will be the buyback program&rsquo;s Dealer Manager.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-to-buy-back-up-to-150m-of-its-1b-bonds/">Coinbase to buy back up to $150M of its $1B bonds</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-to-buy-back-up-to-150m-of-its-1b-bonds/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
