<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 17:15:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitstamp registered as a cryptoasset business by UK’s FCA</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitstamp-registered-as-a-cryptoasset-business-by-uks-fca/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 17:15:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Policy and Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitstamp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FCA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitstamp-registered-as-a-cryptoasset-business-by-uks-fca/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitstamp is now among 42 firms listed by the Financial Conduct Authority (FCA) as registered cryptoasset businesses. The exchange&#8217;s UK arm was added to the list on June 13, 2023. It joins other platforms like eToro, Revolut and Moonpay on the FCA list of firms complying with Money Laundering, Terrorist Financing and Transfer of Regulations [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitstamp-registered-as-a-cryptoasset-business-by-uks-fca/">Bitstamp registered as a cryptoasset business by UK’s FCA</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Bitstamp is now among 42 firms listed by the Financial Conduct Authority (FCA) as registered cryptoasset businesses.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The exchange&rsquo;s UK arm was added to the list on June 13, 2023.</li>
<li dir="ltr">It joins other platforms like eToro, Revolut and Moonpay on the FCA list of firms complying with Money Laundering, Terrorist Financing and Transfer of Regulations (MLRs). </li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Crypto exchange <a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/bitstamp/"><u>Bitstamp</u></a> has been registered as a cryptoasset business by the UK&rsquo;s Financial Conduct Authority (FCA), joining a small list of crypto firms to be duly registered in the United Kingdom.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitstamp UK Limited is FCA&rsquo;s only crypto exchange<a href="https://register.fca.org.uk/s/firm?id=0014G00002wQe9NQAS">&nbsp;<u>registration</u></a> so far in 2023, with its licensing as compliant with the Money Laundering, Terrorist Financing and Transfer of Regulations 2017 (MLRs) effective on June 13.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>The achievement acknowledges Bitstamp for our constant and unwavering commitment to operating at the highest standard. It additionally confirms that our platform offers compliant and secure access to cryptocurrencies in the UK, in accordance with the strict requirements set forth by the FCA</em>,&rdquo; Bitstamp wrote in a <a href="https://blog.bitstamp.net/post/bitstamp-registered-as-a-cryptoasset-business-by-the-financial-conduct-authority-in-the-uk/"><u>blog announcement</u></a> on Tuesday.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The other platform to receive FCA&rsquo;s nod was online trading platform Interactive Brokers Limited.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitstamp joins eToro and Revolut on FCA list</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The FCA now lists 42 crypto and crypto related firms registered under compliance with the MLRs, including Ziglu Limited, Gemini Payments UK LTD, Zumo Financial Services Limited, Coinpass Limited, Baanx.com Ltd, ICONOMI LTD, Fidelity Digital Assets, Bitpanda Custody Ltd, Wintermute Trading LTD, Galaxy Digital UK Limited, MoonPay (UK) Limited, eToro (UK) Ltd and Revolut.</p>
<p dir="ltr">For Bitstamp, the UK regulator&rsquo;s move now sees the exchange have approval across 52 jurisdictions globally. The exchange serves both institutional and retail customers, including providing crypto custody services, fiat-to-crypto purchases and sales and crypto-to-crypto trading.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Registration comes amid the crackdown on crypto exchanges in the US, with both Binance and Coinbase sued by the SEC. The not-so-friendly <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/crypto-regulation/">crypto regulation</a> environment in the US has seen Asia, particularly Hong Kong and UAE look to take advantage in quest to become crypto hubs.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitstamp-registered-as-a-cryptoasset-business-by-uks-fca/">Bitstamp registered as a cryptoasset business by UK’s FCA</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Horizen partners with Auros to increase ZEN liquidity ahead of EON launch</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/horizen-partners-with-auros-to-increase-zen-liquidity-ahead-of-eon-launch/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/horizen-partners-with-auros-to-increase-zen-liquidity-ahead-of-eon-launch/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 15:53:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[smart contracts]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/horizen-partners-with-auros-to-increase-zen-liquidity-ahead-of-eon-launch/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Horizen partners with Auros for $ZEN liquidity ahead of its launch of EVM-compatible platform EON Auros is a leading algorithmic trading and market making platform. The partnership aims at enhancing liquidity for the $ZEN token across CEX and DEX platforms. Horizen, a leading layer-0 public blockchain, has announced a partnership with Auros, a global algorithmic [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/horizen-partners-with-auros-to-increase-zen-liquidity-ahead-of-eon-launch/">Horizen partners with Auros to increase ZEN liquidity ahead of EON launch</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Horizen partners with Auros for $ZEN liquidity ahead of its launch of EVM-compatible platform EON</li>
<li dir="ltr">Auros is a leading algorithmic trading and market making platform.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The partnership aims at enhancing liquidity for the $ZEN token across CEX and DEX platforms.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://www.horizen.io/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Horizen</a>, a leading layer-0 public blockchain, has announced a partnership with Auros, a global algorithmic trading and market making firm.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Horizen&rsquo;s eyes increased liquidity for $ZEN</h2>
<p dir="ltr">According to a <a href="https://blog.horizen.io/horizen-partners-with-auros-to-enhance-liquidity-for-its-evm-compatible-smart-contracting-platform-eon/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">press release</a> shared with CoinJournal on Tuesday, the strategic partnership aims to increase access to $ZEN, Horizen&rsquo;s native token.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">This comes ahead of the launch of EON, a new EVM-compatible <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/smart-contracts/">smart contracts</a> network developed by the Horizen team, the platform noted in the announcement.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Auros is one of the leading market participants, with trades of over a billion dollars daily. It is integrated with several venues and its algorithmic and high-frequency heritage will underpin this partnership.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>We are thrilled to join forces with Auros, a market leader in algorithmic trading and market-making services. Their expertise in bespoke liquidity solutions will undoubtedly enhance the EON ecosystem</em>,&rdquo; said Rob Viglione, Co-founder of Horizen.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Per Horizen, the partnership with Auros will provide enhanced liquidity for the $ZEN token across centralised and decentralised exchanges. People can easily <a href="https://coinjournal.net/horizen/buy/">buy $ZEN</a>, which will increase opportunities for traders, <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/defi/">DeFi users</a>, and builders to participate in the EON ecosystem.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This should help unlock not just liquidity but also the utility and innovation within the smart contract platform&rsquo;s ecosystem. It will also boost overall growth within the digital assets space, Ben Roth, the Chief Information Officer and co-founder of Auros said in a statement.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>Bringing our proprietary trading technology and strategies to Horizen&rsquo;s EON, we are proud to expand the availability of liquidity in both the platform and the $ZEN token, delivering more value for all of its users</em>,&rdquo; Roth said.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>Beyond liquidity provision, this partnership also represents a significant step and a new hope for the decentralised ecosystem as we jointly work towards a more resilient future for digital assets</em>.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Horizen EON is live on the Gobi testnet.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/horizen-partners-with-auros-to-increase-zen-liquidity-ahead-of-eon-launch/">Horizen partners with Auros to increase ZEN liquidity ahead of EON launch</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/horizen-partners-with-auros-to-increase-zen-liquidity-ahead-of-eon-launch/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto is losing touch with institutional cash</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-is-losing-touch-with-institutional-cash/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-is-losing-touch-with-institutional-cash/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dan Ashmore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 15:40:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Volatility]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-is-losing-touch-with-institutional-cash/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key Takeaways Crypto.com this week shut down its institutional exchange in the US, citing a lack of demand The regulatory climate has worsened significantly in the US, meaning crypto is becoming less practical for institutions&#160; The macro picture and scandals across the space last year have also contributed, writes our Head of Research, Dan Ashmore [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-is-losing-touch-with-institutional-cash/">Crypto is losing touch with institutional cash</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2 dir="ltr">Key Takeaways</h2>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Crypto.com this week shut down its institutional exchange in the US, citing a lack of demand</li>
<li>The regulatory climate has worsened significantly in the US, meaning crypto is becoming less practical for institutions&nbsp;</li>
<li>The macro picture and scandals across the space last year have also contributed, writes our Head of Research, Dan Ashmore</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p dir="ltr">Two months ago, I put together a <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/has-institutional-money-left-crypto/"><u>piece</u></a> analysing institutional money and crypto. Specifically, it asked whether institutional cash had fled the industry.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">This weekend, we got the latest demonstration of quite how stark the exodus of institutional money has been. Crypto.com announced they were shutting down their institutional exchange in the US, blaming a lack of demand. While the retail platform will stay open, the institutional platform will no longer be operational.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">This is no surprise. Neither is the timing, as the announcement comes amid the increasingly hostile regulatory crackdown that is occurring in the US. Both Binance and Coinbase were sued by the SEC last week, with fears increasing that crypto will be pushed offshore.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">But while it is a key factor, the reasons for institutional cash jumping ship are not just limited to regulation.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Macro environment</h2>
<p dir="ltr">During the pandemic boom, we saw Tesla announce they were purchasing Bitcoin to hold on their balance sheet (before later selling most of that Bitcoin). We saw fund managers on TV seemingly daily, discussing the heightened demand from their clients to offer Bitcoin investment vehicles. A Bitcoin spot ETF was rumoured as imminent.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Fast forward eighteen months, and things are slightly different. Despite a run-up of 55% this year, Bitcoin remains 60% off its peak as markets across the financial system have struggled.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14104624">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">This follows a transition to tight monetary policy &ndash; the first regime of its kind during Bitcoin&rsquo;s lifespan, which was launched in 2009 into what would become a decade of basement-level interest rates.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The increasing interest rates have pushed institutions back on the risk curve. T-bills today offer 5%, a viable alternative, unlike the near-zero rate offered for most of the last fifteen years. This alternative and the syphoning of liquidity out of the system, with the hope of curtailing rampant inflation, has suppressed the price of all risk assets. The tech-heavy Nasdaq demonstrates this well, losing a third of its value last year. Bitcoin is even more risk-on than tech, and it has struggled to attract funds as a result.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/13627363">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<h2 dir="ltr">Reputation</h2>
<p dir="ltr">While the macro picture is outside of the crypto industry&rsquo;s control, perhaps the most concerning development is the damage to its long-term reputation. Last year saw the spectacular collapse of the UST stablecoin, part of a once-thriving $60 billion Terra ecosystem. Then followed Celsius, Voyager Digital and a host of crypto lending institutions who were caught up in the contagion.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">But perhaps it was FTX&rsquo;s shocking demise in November, led by disgrace Sam Bankman-Fried, which was the cherry on top. The exchange&rsquo;s kingpin had lobbied on behalf of the industry for congress, appeared on the front page of magazines, and had Wall Streeters swooning over his charisma and drive to take crypto the top.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">It was all a lie. For some, it may have been the straw that broke the camel&rsquo;s back. You know when Bitcoin bull Cathie Wood is concerned over the fallout for institutions that there is a problem (she is sticking by her $1 million price prediction for Bitcoin). &nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;The one thing that will be delayed is perhaps institutions stepping back and just saying, &lsquo;OK, do we really understand this?&rsquo;&rdquo;, Wood said in an interview with Bloomberg last year.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Regulation</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Regardless of whether institutions see crypto&rsquo;s reputation as sullied, or whether the macro picture dents its attractiveness for managers, the issue of regulation is a pressing one. Even if institutions want to buy, the crackdown in the US could make it significantly harder to do so. And the greater the friction, the less likely mass pickup is.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">There is very real concern that the American crypto industry is being curtailed to such a degree that companies will be forced to migrate elsewhere. As I wrote <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/opinion-binance-sued-by-sec-an-inevitable-but-ominous-day-for-crypto/"><u>last week</u></a>, I don&rsquo;t think certain counterparties in the crypto industry have helped themselves (and that ties into my point earlier on reputation), but whether it is deserved or not is kind of beside the point. It&rsquo;s happening, and that is all that matters.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">For institutions, that means it&rsquo;s only getting harder and harder to buy. What funds are going to be willing to load up on Ethereum while nobody is sure whether it is a security, and while the exchanges through which they want to buy it are fighting lawsuits from the SEC?</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Final thoughts</h2>
<p dir="ltr">There is nothing particularly groundbreaking in this piece. All these developments are plain to see. There are no charts, minimal data, and not much beyond some obvious surmising. But in a way, that is kind of the point. The change in the space over the last year, especially regarding institutional attitude (and that means beyond the crypto bubble!), is striking.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The crypto landscape has had many ups and downs over the years, but the conwern this time is that, while the percentage decline may be similar, the previous bear markets did not happen on such a big stage. The dollar amounts of bigger, but the reputational blow is too. This was crypto&rsquo;s big time in the lights. Institutions were genuinely looking towards this as a reputable asset class elbowing into the mainstream.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">While this could help Bitcoin separate itself from the crowd and carve out its own niche (even more so than it has already done), it has still been a setback. But the true concern is more with the rest of crypto, which faces a much tougher battle to regain any semblance of legitimacy.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-is-losing-touch-with-institutional-cash/">Crypto is losing touch with institutional cash</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-is-losing-touch-with-institutional-cash/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Blur to unlock 196M BLUR, increasing circulating supply by 40%</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/blur-to-unlock-196-million-tokens-increasing-circulating-supply-by-40/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 14:52:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/blur-to-unlock-196-million-tokens-increasing-circulating-supply-by-40/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Roughly 196 million BLUR tokens will be unlocked on June 14, 2023. The token unlock is set to increase Blur&#8217;s circulating supply by 40%, which currently stands at just over 495.2 million BLUR. Blur launched in October 2022 and has quickly grown to become one of the leading NFT marketplaces. Blur, the NFT marketplace for [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/blur-to-unlock-196-million-tokens-increasing-circulating-supply-by-40/">Blur to unlock 196M BLUR, increasing circulating supply by 40%</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Roughly 196 million BLUR tokens will be unlocked on June 14, 2023.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The token unlock is set to increase Blur&rsquo;s circulating supply by 40%, which currently stands at just over 495.2 million BLUR.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Blur launched in October 2022 and has quickly grown to become one of the leading NFT marketplaces.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Blur, the NFT marketplace for pro traders, will have about 196 million BLUR tokens unlocked on Wednesday, June 14, 2023.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The scheduled release of the tokens into circulating supply comes amid a wave of negativity across crypto, with regulatory and macroeconomic headwinds contributing to BLUR price dipping 27% in the past week.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">BLUR unlock to add 40% to circulating supply</h2>
<p dir="ltr">According to data from<a href="https://token.unlocks.app/blur" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">&nbsp;<u>Token Unlocks</u></a>, the 196 million BLUR tokens being unlocked is equivalent to about 6.5% of the platform&rsquo;s total supply. However, it will translate to about 40% increase in circulating supply, with 115.6 million tokens going to core contributors, 75.4 million to investors and 4.9 million to advisors.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The circulating supply for Blur is currently just over 495.2 million tokens, giving the cryptocurrency a market cap of $154 million.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Blur&rsquo;s maximum supply is 3 billion BLUR. About 83% of the total supply is currently locked, which is 2.49 billion BLUR worth approximately $769 million. Unlocked tokens are 511.3 million BLUR worth approximately $158 million at BLUR&rsquo;s current price of $0.309.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">NFT marketplace growth</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Blur launched in October 2022 and grew rapidly to see its NFT volumes in the first quarter of 2023 surpass those of leading marketplace OpenSea.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As CoinJournal <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/nft-trading-volume-rose-230-in-q1-nansen-finds/">highlighted</a> in early May, accounted for $2.93 billion in NFT sales. In comparison, OpenSea registered $1.02 billion in sales volume during the quarter.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The NFT marketplace<a href="https://twitter.com/blur_io/status/1582777825483841546" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"> <u>announced</u></a> in October that the NFT platform&rsquo;s team includes experienced developers from MIT, Citadel, Square, and YC. The project raised over $14 million from investors and traders. It also closed a $15M-$30M funding round in February, which was at a $1 billion valuation.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/blur-to-unlock-196-million-tokens-increasing-circulating-supply-by-40/">Blur to unlock 196M BLUR, increasing circulating supply by 40%</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Uniswap V4 code draft features custom liquidity pools plugins</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/uniswap-v4-code-draft-features-custom-liquidity-pools-plugins/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/uniswap-v4-code-draft-features-custom-liquidity-pools-plugins/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 14:18:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[UNI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uniswap News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/uniswap-v4-code-draft-features-custom-liquidity-pools-plugins/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>By volume, Uniswap is the biggest decentralized cryptocurrency exchange in the entire world. The release of the Uniswap V4 is the first step to launching the new Uniswap version. The final stage before launch is a vote by UniswapDAO. Uniswap Labs has released a draft of the code for its Uniswap V4. The updated code [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/uniswap-v4-code-draft-features-custom-liquidity-pools-plugins/">Uniswap V4 code draft features custom liquidity pools plugins</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>By volume, Uniswap is the biggest decentralized cryptocurrency exchange in the entire world.</li>
<li>The release of the Uniswap V4 is the first step to launching the new Uniswap version.</li>
<li>The final stage before launch is a vote by UniswapDAO.</li>
</ul>
<p>Uniswap Labs has released a draft of the code for its Uniswap V4. The updated code features &ldquo;hooks&rdquo; or &ldquo;plugins&rdquo; that let programmers design customized liquidity pools.</p>
<p>The most recent <a href="https://coinjournal.net/uniswap/what-is-uniswap/">Uniswap&nbsp;</a>version, the Uniswap V3, was released on May 2021 and it recently <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/uniswap-v3-to-deploy-on-boba-network-after-approval-by-its-dao/">deployed on Boba Network</a>.</p>
<h2>Uniswap V4 draft code</h2>
<p>According to a post published today by Uniswap&rsquo;s Founder, Hayden Adams, when the V4 is implemented, the &ldquo;hooks&rdquo; feature will enable developers to add many new innovations to the exchange, including on-chain limit orders, automatic deposits to lending protocols, automatically compounded liquidity provider (LP) fees, and many more.</p>
<p>According to Adams in the post, the purpose of Uniswap V4 is to:</p>
<p><em>&ldquo;Create a way for pool deployers to introduce code that performs a designated action at key points throughout the pool&rsquo;s lifecycle &ndash; like before or after a swap, or before or after an LP position is changed.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p>Deployers will be able to make time-weighted average market makers (TWAMMs), for instance, which let users sell large amounts of cryptocurrency gradually in smaller batches. This could help traders in avoiding negative price changes or being front-run by EVM bots. Additionally, on-chain limit orders will be feasible because pools will be able to implement logic that will allow them to fill an order only when a token reaches a specific price.</p>
<p>Another example of the featured &ldquo;hooks&rdquo; is code that allows for the repositioning of fees back into an LPs pool or lending out inventory when a particular pool isn&rsquo;t being used.</p>
<h2>Steps to launching the new Uniswap V4</h2>
<p>Releasing the source code is the first step in launching a new version of Uniswap.</p>
<p>The group now intends to consult with Uniswap users and iterate on this foundational code over time. Afterwards, V4 will become a formal proposal to be presented to Uniswap&rsquo;s governing body, UniswapDAO, once enough agreement has been reached on a final version of it.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/uniswap-v4-code-draft-features-custom-liquidity-pools-plugins/">Uniswap V4 code draft features custom liquidity pools plugins</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/uniswap-v4-code-draft-features-custom-liquidity-pools-plugins/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hinman speech contained “made-up analysis”, Ripple’s Chief legal officer says</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/hinman-speech-contained-made-up-analysis-ripples-chief-legal-officer-says/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 13:58:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Policy and Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple Labs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/hinman-speech-contained-made-up-analysis-ripples-chief-legal-officer-says/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Former SEC official William Hinman delivered his speech in June 2018, commenting that Bitcoin and Ether were not securities. SEC sued Ripple Labs in December 2020, alleging that the company illegally sold unregistered securities in the form of its XRP token. Ripple attorney Stuart Alderoty says the documents contained &#8220;made-up analysis.&#8221; Ripple news today is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/hinman-speech-contained-made-up-analysis-ripples-chief-legal-officer-says/">Hinman speech contained “made-up analysis”, Ripple’s Chief legal officer says</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Former SEC official William Hinman delivered his speech in June 2018, commenting that Bitcoin and Ether were not securities.</li>
<li dir="ltr">SEC sued Ripple Labs in December 2020, alleging that the company illegally sold unregistered securities in the form of its XRP token.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Ripple attorney Stuart Alderoty says the documents contained &ldquo;made-up analysis.&rdquo;</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/ripple/">Ripple news</a> today is that the US-based company continues to edge closer to a verdict in its battle against the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">This follows Tuesday&rsquo;s release of documents related to a speech by former SEC official William Hinman, which was delivered in June 2018.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ripple/">price of XRP</a>, the native Ripple cryptocurrency that the SEC alleges is a security in a lawsuit filed in 2020, rose more than 8% to above $0.55.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Ripple lawyer comments on release of Hinman emails</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The document&rsquo;s release to the public means Hinman&rsquo;s views about cryptocurrencies deemed as securities.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Specifically, the former SEC Division of Corporation Finance official highlighted in his 2018 speech that Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH) were not securities.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Commenting on the release of the files, Ripple&rsquo;s Chief Legal Officer Stuart Alderoty<a href="https://twitter.com/s_alderoty/status/1668601225418543109" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">&nbsp;<u>tweeted</u></a>:</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>It&rsquo;s been 5 years since Bill Hinman gave his infamous speech &ndash; and through the SEC&rsquo;s lawsuit against @Ripple (and 7 court orders), we can finally share what happened behind the scenes through the now public emails / drafts of the speech</em>.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">On Hinman&rsquo;s comments, Ripple&rsquo;s legal chief stated the ex-SEC official ignored warnings about his remarks and that he included &ldquo;<em>made up analysis with no basis in law</em>.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>We now can all see Hinman ignored multiple warnings that his speech contained made-up analysis with no basis in law, was divorced from the Howey factors, exposed regulatory gaps, and would create not just confusion, but &ldquo;greater confusion&rdquo; in the market</em>,&rdquo; he added.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>A refresher: Hinman, as Head of the SEC&rsquo;s Corp Fin, gave a speech in June 2018 declaring that a token is not a security once it becomes &ldquo;sufficiently decentralized&rdquo; and he invented factors to consider when making a &ldquo;sufficiently decentralized&rdquo; determination.</em>&ldquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">It is these statements that are now at the center of Ripple&rsquo;s defense, with the company having maintained since December 2020 that XRP is not a security.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The belief that the SEC is losing this case is the reason the community&rsquo;s sentiment has become so upbeat in recent weeks.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/hinman-speech-contained-made-up-analysis-ripples-chief-legal-officer-says/">Hinman speech contained “made-up analysis”, Ripple’s Chief legal officer says</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hedera, Fantom, XRP, Filecoin prices rise as US inflation dips</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/hedera-fantom-xrp-filecoin-prices-rise-as-us-inflation-dips/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/hedera-fantom-xrp-filecoin-prices-rise-as-us-inflation-dips/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 12:59:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FIL]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Filecoin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/hedera-fantom-xrp-filecoin-prices-rise-as-us-inflation-dips/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The headline consumer price index dropped to 4.0% in May. The data came as the FOMC prepares to conduct its June meeting. Economists expect that the bank will leave interest rates unchanged. Altcoin prices jumped on Tuesday after the US published encouraging consumer inflation data. Hedera Hashgraph price has jumped by about 4% in the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/hedera-fantom-xrp-filecoin-prices-rise-as-us-inflation-dips/">Hedera, Fantom, XRP, Filecoin prices rise as US inflation dips</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The headline consumer price index dropped to 4.0% in May.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The data came as the FOMC prepares to conduct its June meeting.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Economists expect that the bank will leave interest rates unchanged.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Altcoin prices jumped on Tuesday after the US published encouraging consumer inflation data. Hedera Hashgraph price has jumped by about 4% in the past 24 hours. Similarly, other altcoins like Fantom, XRP,&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/filecoin/"><u>Filecoin</u></a>, and Uniswap have jumped by over 4% in the past 24 hours.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">US inflation retreats</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies have jumped in the past few hours after the encouraging US consumer price index data. According to the Bureau of Labor Statistics (BLS), the headline consumer price inflation dropped from 4.9% in April to 4.0% in May. This was a bigger decline than what analysts were expecting. It was also the biggest decline in several months.</p>
<p dir="ltr">These numbers are important because they came on the same day that the Federal Open Market Committee (FOMC) is set to start its two-day meeting. As a result, the committee will be comfortable to leave interest rates unchanged at 5.25%. It has delivered interest rate hikes in the past ten meetings straight.</p>
<p dir="ltr">A Fed pause and an eventual pivot will be good news for risky assets like cryptocurrencies and stocks. This explains why the stock-focused fear and greed index has jumped while key indices like the Dow Jones and Nasdaq 100 have gained by double-digits this year.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Regulatory concerns remain</h2>
<p dir="ltr">For cryptocurrencies like&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/hedera/"><u>Hedera Hashgraph</u></a>, Filecoin, Fantom, and XRP, these inflation numbers are welcome. However, the biggest risk in the crypto industry is that regulators in the US and the UK have gone to war with these assets.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Last week, the SEC filed a major lawsuit against Binance and Changpeng Zhao. On the following day, the agency filed another one against Coinbase, the biggest exchange in the United States. A common allegation in the lawsuit is that they offer unregulated products.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Some of these unregulated products are proof-of-stake tokens that have a yield element. The SEC has already sued Ripple alleging that it is an unregulated cryptocurrency. It has also identified several tokens it believes are securities.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As a result, we could see exchanges that serve American customers start delisting these tokens, which could hurt many of them.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/hedera-fantom-xrp-filecoin-prices-rise-as-us-inflation-dips/">Hedera, Fantom, XRP, Filecoin prices rise as US inflation dips</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/hedera-fantom-xrp-filecoin-prices-rise-as-us-inflation-dips/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>6.5M tokens bought within hours of the highly anticipated Chancer Presale launch</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/6-5m-tokens-bought-within-hours-of-the-highly-anticipated-chancer-presale-launch/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/6-5m-tokens-bought-within-hours-of-the-highly-anticipated-chancer-presale-launch/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 12:18:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNB]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/6-5m-tokens-bought-within-hours-of-the-highly-anticipated-chancer-presale-launch/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Chancer is a revolutionary betting platform that seeks to leverage the power of blockchain technology. The CHANCER token is going for 0.01 BUSD in the current stage. CHANCER token holders will have the opportunity of creating customized betting markets on the Chancer platform. Chancer, one of the most intriguing new Web3 projects of 2023, officially [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/6-5m-tokens-bought-within-hours-of-the-highly-anticipated-chancer-presale-launch/">6.5M tokens bought within hours of the highly anticipated Chancer Presale launch</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul class="decimal_type">
<li>Chancer is a revolutionary betting platform that seeks to leverage the power of blockchain technology.</li>
<li>The CHANCER token is going for 0.01 BUSD in the current stage.</li>
<li>CHANCER token holders will have the opportunity of creating customized betting markets on the Chancer platform.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://chancer.com/">Chancer</a>, one of the most intriguing new Web3 projects of 2023, officially launched its crypto presale today.</p>
<p>By removing the &ldquo;house&rdquo; from the equation and firmly placing the markets in the hands of the bettors, Chancer seeks to disrupt the betting industry by enabling users to create their own betting markets, set their own odds, and establish their own rules.</p>
<p>Chancer is the first decentralized predictive markets app in the world, and its creators, brothers Adam and Paul Kelbie, believe it will fundamentally alter the way people bet and ultimately restore the fun to gambling.</p>
<h2>How Chancer seeks to alter the betting industry</h2>
<p>Chancer wants to capitalize on the sizeable online betting and gambling market, which is estimated to be worth $64 billion by 2022 and establish a dominant position there.</p>
<p>Chancer users can create peer-to-peer (P2P) bets, positioning the platform as a betting facilitator rather than a betting house. The bets can range from small, casual wagers among close friends to massive, viral wagers involving thousands of people, such as picking the winner of the Oscar for Best Director or guessing the Champions League final score.</p>
<p>Contrary to most bookmakers, Chancer allows bets to be placed on any prediction or event, not just sports. Users have complete control over their bets and won&rsquo;t lose to a traditional bookmaker who sets the odds against them, which is part of its inherent appeal.</p>
<p>Commenting about Chancer and the coming months for the project, the CEO of Chancer, Adam Kelbie, said:</p>
<p><em>&ldquo;We&rsquo;re confident that we can change the way betting and gambling works. The next few months are going to be very exciting, and we&rsquo;re thrilled that we can offer a new cryptocurrency in such a competitive market. We&rsquo;re doing something no one else has done, disrupting an industry that has had the odds stacked against consumers since it began. It won&rsquo;t be easy, but we&rsquo;re ready for the fight.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p>All bet payouts will be made in Chancer&rsquo;s native token, &ldquo;CHANCER,&rdquo; which will be tradable on several <a href="https://coinjournal.net/compare/best-cryptocurrency-exchanges/">cryptocurrency exchanges</a> once the presale is completed.</p>
<h2>Chancer token presale</h2>
<p>The Chancer token presale officially launched today and at press time, 6,541,850 tokens had been sold out raising $65,418.49 barely a few hours after the presale went live.</p>
<p>According to the project&rsquo;s <a href="https://chancer.com/whitepaper.pdf">whitepaper</a>, the presale will be conducted over twelve stages with the first stage seeking to sell 100 million tokens to raise $1 million. The CHANCER token, which is BUILT ON THE Binance Smart Chain (BSC), is currently going for 0.01 BUSD stablecoin.</p>
<h2>What&rsquo;s unique about Chancer betting platform?</h2>
<p>The project has a well-planned roadmap outlining a variety of product use cases to pique the interest of various types of investors, as stated in the whitepaper. Additionally, Chancer seeks to achieve and uphold true decentralization.</p>
<p>So that no one party can take control of the network, Chancer will have a proof of stake consensus mechanism. The platform&rsquo;s users will take control of decision-making under quadratic governance.</p>
<p>In addition, the source code for Chancer will always be available for inspection. This implies that anyone is free to examine, contribute, and suggest modifications to the platform&rsquo;s operation with the confidence that their ideas will be taken into consideration.</p>
<p>In a novel way, Chancer will also use Google&rsquo;s WebRTC&rsquo;s real-time communication capabilities to broadcast events live to its community.</p>
<p>Additionally, it will offer a Share2Earn program, staking, and discounted fees for those who create and participate in the market, making the platform affordable for those who use it frequently. Users can also generate passive income by becoming node validators.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/6-5m-tokens-bought-within-hours-of-the-highly-anticipated-chancer-presale-launch/">6.5M tokens bought within hours of the highly anticipated Chancer Presale launch</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/6-5m-tokens-bought-within-hours-of-the-highly-anticipated-chancer-presale-launch/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Etoro to limit US customers&#8217; access to four major cryptocurrencies</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/etoro-to-limit-us-customers-access-to-four-major-cryptocurrencies/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/etoro-to-limit-us-customers-access-to-four-major-cryptocurrencies/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 11:07:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dash News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Etoro]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/etoro-to-limit-us-customers-access-to-four-major-cryptocurrencies/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>eToro is an Israeli multi-asset investment platform widely known for social trading. eToro will delist ALGO, MATIC, MANA, and DASH for US customers. US customers can, however, still hold and sell already open positions in these tokens. https://twitter.com/eToroUS/status/1668323758199955456 According to a tweet by eToro, four tokens &#8212; ALGO, MATIC, MANA, and DASH &#8212; will be [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/etoro-to-limit-us-customers-access-to-four-major-cryptocurrencies/">Etoro to limit US customers&#8217; access to four major cryptocurrencies</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>eToro is an Israeli multi-asset investment platform widely known for social trading.</li>
<li>eToro will delist ALGO, MATIC, MANA, and DASH for US customers.</li>
<li>US customers can, however, still hold and sell already open positions in these tokens.</li>
</ul>
<p>https://twitter.com/eToroUS/status/1668323758199955456</p>
<p>According to a tweet by <a href="https://coinjournal.net/brokers/etoro/">eToro</a>, four tokens &mdash; ALGO, MATIC, MANA, and DASH &mdash; will be delisted starting July 12, 2023, as the company adjusts its cryptocurrency offering for customers in the US.</p>
<p>The platform claims that the new change won&rsquo;t have an impact on non-US customers and that US customers can continue to hold and sell any open positions in these tokens.</p>
<p>eToro makes no mention of the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sec-sues-binance-and-cz-for-breaking-us-securities-rules/">SEC lawsuit against the two largest cryptocurrency exchanges</a>, Coinbase and Binance. It, however, claimed it was taking the action &ldquo;in light of recent developments.&rdquo;</p>
<p>In the SEC&rsquo;s most recent legal actions, the four tokens mentioned in the eToro announcement were classified as securities.</p>
<h2>Similar actions by trading platforms in the US</h2>
<p>The move by eToro comes shortly after one similar one by Robinhood in June. Robinhood declared that, in light of its &ldquo;latest review,&rdquo; it would be removing SOL, MATIC, and ADA from its platform.</p>
<p>With the SEC&rsquo;s recent enforcement strategy toward cryptocurrencies, more businesses may follow in the footsteps of eToro and Robinhood in order to avoid regulatory issues that could further negatively impact users based in the US.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/etoro-to-limit-us-customers-access-to-four-major-cryptocurrencies/">Etoro to limit US customers&#8217; access to four major cryptocurrencies</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/etoro-to-limit-us-customers-access-to-four-major-cryptocurrencies/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
