<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 13:44:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>JPMorgan Chief Jamie Dimon Expects Interest Rates to Surge Past 5% amid Underlying Inflation</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-dimon-inflation/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-dimon-inflation/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 13:44:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jamie dimon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jpmorgan]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=233227</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-dimon-inflation/">JPMorgan Chief Jamie Dimon Expects Interest Rates to Surge Past 5% amid Underlying Inflation</a></p>
<p>Jamie Dimon believes that if the United States ends up in a recession, the Fed might end up raising rate hikes as high as 6%. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-dimon-inflation/">JPMorgan Chief Jamie Dimon Expects Interest Rates to Surge Past 5% amid Underlying Inflation</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-dimon-inflation/">JPMorgan Chief Jamie Dimon Expects Interest Rates to Surge Past 5% amid Underlying Inflation</a></p>
<p>During his latest interview with CNBC, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/jpmorgan-chase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">JPMorgan</a> chief <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/jamie-dimon/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Jamie Dimon</a> shared his views on the current economic outlook while adding that he expects the interest rates to go much higher than Fed&#8217;s current projection.</p>
<p>Dimon believes that as inflation remains stubbornly high, the Fed could be forced to raise rates beyond 5%. Speaking from the World Economic Forum from Davos, Switzerland, on Thursday, Dimon told CNBC:</p>
<blockquote><p>“I actually think rates are probably going to go higher than 5% &#8230; because I think there’s a lot of underlying inflation, which won’t go away so quick&#8221;.</p></blockquote>
<p>In order to battle persistent inflation, the Federal Reserve has already raised the benchmark interest rates to 4.25-4.5%. These are the highest rates over the last 15 years. During the December meeting, the &#8220;terminal rate&#8221; where the Fed is likely to end any further hikes was supposed to be 5.1%.</p>
<p>During the month of December 2022, the consumer price index (CPI) jumped by 6.5% from a year ago. However, this was the smallest annual increase in over a year since October 2021. But Dimon believes that the recent easing of inflation is due to temporary factors such as the pandemic-driven slowdown in China and the pullback in oil prices. Commenting further, he <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/01/19/jamie-dimon-says-rates-will-rise-above-5percent-because-there-is-still-a-lot-of-underlying-inflation.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">added</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“We’ve had the benefit of China’s slowing down, the benefit of oil prices dropping a little bit. I think oil gas prices probably go up the next 10 years &#8230; China isn’t going to be deflationary anymore.”</p></blockquote>
<p>However, the aggressive rate hikes have already fueled concerns regarding an impending US recession. But as the labor market and the consumer market remains strong, the Fed still feels the need to raise interest rates.</p>
<h2>What If the US Enters a Recession?</h2>
<p>Speaking on the matter, JPMorgan&#8217;s chief stated that if the US were to enter a recession, the interest rates could rise to 6%. However, he notes that it would be hard for anyone to predict economic downturns.</p>
<p>“I know there are going to be recessions, ups and downs. I really don’t spend that much time worrying about it. I do worry that poor public policy that damages American growth,” added he.</p>
<p>While Jamie Dimon shared his views over the Fed action going ahead, he didn&#8217;t shy to lash out at Bitcoin once again. Dimon, who has been an ardent critic of Bitcoin and crypto in the past, <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/01/19/jamie-dimon-says-bitcoin-itself-is-a-hyped-up-fraud.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">noted</a> that Bitcoin itself is a ‘hyped-up fraud’.</p>
<p>JPMorgan itself has been doing good and last week, the bank reported its fourth-quarter earnings and revenue while beating the Street expectations. “Our lines of business performed well in the quarter, and we continued to see momentum in our areas of strategic focus,” Dimon said.</p>
<p>On Wednesday, January 18, the JPMorgan (NYSE: JPM) stock came under selling pressure dropping by 3% and ending the trading at $136.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/martin-sorrell-tech-stocks-rebound/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-dimon-inflation/">JPMorgan Chief Jamie Dimon Expects Interest Rates to Surge Past 5% amid Underlying Inflation</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-dimon-inflation/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>UK Ad Mogul Martin Sorrell Believes US Tech Stocks to Rebound This Year</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/martin-sorrell-tech-stocks-rebound/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/martin-sorrell-tech-stocks-rebound/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 13:28:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alphabet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Amazon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Martin Sorrell]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Meta]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meta platforms]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=233207</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/martin-sorrell-tech-stocks-rebound/">UK Ad Mogul Martin Sorrell Believes US Tech Stocks to Rebound This Year</a></p>
<p>Advertising spending has reduced over the past year, contributing to the woes of Meta Platforms. However, Sorrell says the ease in the crackdown from Beijing is a positive growth factor for the US tech stocks.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/martin-sorrell-tech-stocks-rebound/">UK Ad Mogul Martin Sorrell Believes US Tech Stocks to Rebound This Year</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/martin-sorrell-tech-stocks-rebound/">UK Ad Mogul Martin Sorrell Believes US Tech Stocks to Rebound This Year</a></p>
<p>Martin Sorrell, the UK ad mogul and founder of the advertising agency, S4 Capital has weighed in on the potential of American tech stocks in the face of global economic distress. As <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/01/19/ad-mogul-sees-meta-rebounding-extremely-strongly-amazon-ad-revenue-hitting-100bn.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reported</a> by CNBC, Sorrell sees a good year for Facebook parent company <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/meta/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Meta Platforms Inc</a> (NASDAQ: META), as well as retail giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/amazon/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Amazon.com Inc</a> (NASDAQ: AMZN) and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/alphabet-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Alphabet Inc</a> (NASDAQ: GOOGL).</p>
<p>According to Sorrell, Meta Platforms will rebound “extremely strongly this year” despite the fact that there are still some underlying economic headwinds to overcome. Sorrell believes the company’s efforts to thrive in the midst of top competition will be its most resourceful survival tactics in the near term.</p>
<p>“I think you’ll see Meta come back extremely strongly this year, on the back of reels and business messenger, to deal with the competition from TikTok and other short-form video competitors,” Sorrell told CNBC on the sidelines of the World Economic Forum in Davos, Switzerland.</p>
<p>Meta Platforms has been hit in a very different way over the past year with its shares plunging to its lowest since 2016 when it provided weak guidance when it released its 4th Quarter Earnings report. Meta has struggled with not just a dwindling valuation, but also of its operating profits and it made the tough decision to <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-mass-staff-layoff-costs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">retrench</a> as many as 11,000 of its employees or 13% of its entire workforce last November.</p>
<p>Thus far, tech giants have notably retrenched more than 60,000 workers, a sign of the broad-based strain that most of them have faced at a time when the interest rate has continued to grow significantly.</p>
<h2>Martin Sorrell Sees Tech Stock Recovery</h2>
<p>Besides Meta Platforms, Martin Sorrell is optimistic that other tech giant’s stocks also have what it takes to record a significant upshoot. On Google and Amazon’s potential, the ad mogul noted:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Google had a solid year last year, and I think they’ll have a strong year this year. Amazon increased its advertising revenues from $31bn to $41bn, and I think [it] will hit $100bn in time, despite what you’re seeing in terms of jobs and hiring.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Advertising spending has reduced over the past year, contributing to the woes of Meta Platforms. However, Sorrell says the ease in the crackdown from Beijing is a positive growth factor for the US tech stocks. He believes companies expanding into the United States will need the kind of platform and reach that is only offered by these mainstream companies.</p>
<p>Sorrell had a successful career with WPP Plc (NYSE: WPP) and he started S4 Capital when he left in 2018. He said his company’s clients have a more targeted focus for their ad spending this year and this borders on “topline growth in activation and performance” as well as in “reducing [the] cost of digital transformation.”</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/2m-lawsuit-compass-mining/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/martin-sorrell-tech-stocks-rebound/">UK Ad Mogul Martin Sorrell Believes US Tech Stocks to Rebound This Year</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/martin-sorrell-tech-stocks-rebound/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Aggrieved Customers Serve $2M Lawsuit to Compass Mining for Failing to Return Their Bitcoin Mining Machines</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/2m-lawsuit-compass-mining/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/2m-lawsuit-compass-mining/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 13:24:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[compass mining]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=233209</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/2m-lawsuit-compass-mining/">Aggrieved Customers Serve $2M Lawsuit to Compass Mining for Failing to Return Their Bitcoin Mining Machines</a></p>
<p>Compass Mining recently sustained a lawsuit by customers who claim the company lost their crypto mining machines in a deal with Bit River.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/2m-lawsuit-compass-mining/">Aggrieved Customers Serve $2M Lawsuit to Compass Mining for Failing to Return Their Bitcoin Mining Machines</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/2m-lawsuit-compass-mining/">Aggrieved Customers Serve $2M Lawsuit to Compass Mining for Failing to Return Their Bitcoin Mining Machines</a></p>
<p>Compass Mining is currently facing a <a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.flsd.626919/gov.uscourts.flsd.626919.1.0.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">lawsuit</a> for losing Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a>) mining machines procured by customers. According to <a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/compass-mining-sued-for-losing-bitcoin-mining-machines-bought-by-customers" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reports</a>, the aggrieved Bitcoin mining machine owners are suing Compass Mining for more than $2 million because the company failed to return the machines after severing ties with Russian hosting firm Bit River. Furthermore, the lawsuit alleges Compass Mining fraud and claims that the mining firm did not disclose its &#8216;middleman&#8217; status to Bit River. As it stands, plaintiffs believe that Bit River may have assumed that Compass owned the mining machines.</p>
<p>The plaintiffs filed the lawsuit against Compass on January 17th with the United States District Court for The Southern District of Florida. Furthermore, the court document states that Compass issued a notice last April of its business termination with Bit River. The mining company also cited the sanctions imposed by <a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/us-treasury-dept-lists-digital-currencies-as-part-of-effort-to-sanction-russia-s-government" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Executive Order 14024</a> as the reason for the &#8220;relationships and dealings&#8221; termination.</p>
<h2>Lawsuit Alleges Compass Mining Exhibited Apathy towards Return of Customers&#8217; Assets</h2>
<p>However, Compass allegedly did not offer to return or retrieve the assets its customers placed in its care. These BTC mining assets were reportedly deployed at Bit River&#8217;s facilities in Russia. Despite misplaced concern that returning the machines would violate Executive Order 14024, which frowns upon dealings with sanctioned entities, the court document thinks otherwise. According to this document, Compass has &#8220;both the right and obligation to effect the return of its customers&#8217; miners.&#8221;</p>
<p>The court document also said that Compass&#8217; claims of its machines&#8217; &#8220;uptime of 95%&#8221; were inaccurate. According to the plaintiff, this figure was closer to 50% or 60%. In addition, the document pointed out that mines were offline for weeks or months in many instances.</p>
<p>However, Compass representatives responded to the concerns of customers with hostility. The firm, primarily involved in Bitcoin mining machine brokerage and hosting services, maintains it cannot conduct business with Bit River. When out of exasperation, customers reached out to Bit River instead, the Russian company allegedly directed them back to Compass. Explaining the need for the aggrieved party to return to Compass to chart a way forward, Bit River representatives said:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;From a legal point of view, Bit River&#8217;s contract is with Compass, and all equipment is owned by Compass. Thus, you must address all questions directly with Compass.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The Compass partnership with Bit River initially sought to make the former&#8217;s customers host their machines at Bit River&#8217;s facilities. Furthermore, this arrangement was to leverage &#8220;enterprise-grade, low-cost and low-carbon cryptocurrency mining facilities in Russia.&#8221;</p>
<h2>Compass Announced Job Cuts in July 2022 to Remain Profitable amid Crypto Winter</h2>
<p>Last July, Compass became the first mining firm to announce a notable headcount reduction amid the sustained crypto bearish period. The company cut around 15% of its headcount, with top executives and other remaining staff taking sizable pay cuts. July&#8217;s Compass downsizing also came on the heels of the resignation of CEO Whit Gibbs and CFO Jodie Fisher.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coindesk-full-partial-sale/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/2m-lawsuit-compass-mining/">Aggrieved Customers Serve $2M Lawsuit to Compass Mining for Failing to Return Their Bitcoin Mining Machines</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/2m-lawsuit-compass-mining/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>CoinDesk Contemplates Full or Partial Sale as Parent Company Scampers for Funds</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coindesk-full-partial-sale/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coindesk-full-partial-sale/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 12:46:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investors News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Alameda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coindesk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dcg]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital currency group (dcg)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[genesis global]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[liquidity]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=233183</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coindesk-full-partial-sale/">CoinDesk Contemplates Full or Partial Sale as Parent Company Scampers for Funds</a></p>
<p>DCG is currently looking for ways to save its business and grow its capital.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coindesk-full-partial-sale/">CoinDesk Contemplates Full or Partial Sale as Parent Company Scampers for Funds</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coindesk-full-partial-sale/">CoinDesk Contemplates Full or Partial Sale as Parent Company Scampers for Funds</a></p>
<p>Crypto-based firm CoinDesk has begun weighing its options regarding a potential sale as it looks to attract growth capital. According to the <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/crypto-media-outlet-coindesk-taps-bankers-for-potential-sale-11674076000?mod=latest_headlines&amp;enowparentmodules=opsconsole-csm%2Cusage-tracking-csm%2Cdata-api-proxy-csm&amp;enowpopup=" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">WSJ</a>, the firm has recently received offers above $200 million. And if the deal goes through, that would amount to an almost 40,000% return on its initial investment. Recall that Digital Currency Group &#8211; CoinDesk&#8217;s parent company, acquired the firm for an amount between $500,000 to $600,000 in 2016.</p>
<p>Despite the offer, however, CoinDesk is now seeking advice from Lazard, a specialist firm focused on mergers and restructuring.</p>
<h2>CoinDesk Potential Sale: a Confirmation of DCG&#8217;s Financial Troubles</h2>
<p>Recently, several reports have surfaced about DCG having liquidity issues. So much so, that on January 17, the group itself announced to its shareholders that it would halt dividends immediately. In its explanation, DCG claimed that the decision was to help it improve its balance sheet and ultimately “preserve liquidity.”</p>
<p>In another related headline, Bloomberg <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-01-18/crypto-firm-genesis-said-to-prepare-bankruptcy-filing-as-soon-as-this-week" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reported</a> less than 24 hours ago that another DCG subsidiary, crypto lender Genesis Global, may be planning to file for bankruptcy as well. Genesis reportedly owes its creditors over $3 billion. Considering such a huge amount of debt, it is not exactly surprising that DCG is now actively looking for ways to save its business.</p>
<p>About the potential sale, CoinDesk CEO Kevin Worth says it must be done right and that&#8217;s why the firm is employing the services of investment professionals such as Lazard. Worth said in part:</p>
<blockquote><p>“My goal in hiring Lazard is to explore various options to attract growth capital to the CoinDesk business, which may include a partial or full sale.”</p></blockquote>
<p>According to DCG&#8217;s website, the group has about 200 crypto-based businesses under its venture capital scheme. Some other popular firms owned by DCG include crypto exchange Luno and asset management firm Grayscale Investments.</p>
<p>For what it&#8217;s worth,  there&#8217;s a popular opinion that CoinDesk’s expose on Alameda Research’s balance sheet in November may have been the beginning of the end for the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a> exchange. But there&#8217;s a more interesting twist to that story. The same <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-exchange-files-for-bankruptcy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX collapse</a> is also now responsible for the liquidity issues currently being faced by Genesis and DCG, and the broader crypto market.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tech-companies-job-cuts-2023/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coindesk-full-partial-sale/">CoinDesk Contemplates Full or Partial Sale as Parent Company Scampers for Funds</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coindesk-full-partial-sale/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tech Companies Announce Fresh Job Cuts in 2023</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tech-companies-job-cuts-2023/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tech-companies-job-cuts-2023/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 12:41:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Amazon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[microsoft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[netflix]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[salesforce]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[satya nadella]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[shopify]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stripe]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=233188</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tech-companies-job-cuts-2023/">Tech Companies Announce Fresh Job Cuts in 2023</a></p>
<p>Tech jobs cut include Amazon dismissing 11,000 employees, Twitter lowering headcounts by 3,700, and others.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tech-companies-job-cuts-2023/">Tech Companies Announce Fresh Job Cuts in 2023</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tech-companies-job-cuts-2023/">Tech Companies Announce Fresh Job Cuts in 2023</a></p>
<p>After a series of job cuts across the tech industry last year, more companies are planning to further reduce their headcounts in 2023. This is coming after the tech space saw a surge in consumer demand at the coronavirus pandemic&#8217;s peak. Now that people are no longer forced to stay home, companies are beginning to see slower growth due to fewer sales. At the same time, the interest rates hike as ordered by the Feds to tackle inflation and the possibility of a recession, all contribute to the tech industry being hit.</p>
<p>One of the top tech giants, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/microsoft/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Microsoft Corporation</a> (NASDAQ: MSFT), recently <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-lay-off-employees/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">announced</a> plans to dismiss 10,000 employees. The company said the victims would exit the company through the 31st of march in preparation for slower revenue growth. While all departments will be impacted, the sales and marketing teams will lose more staff.</p>
<p>CEO <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/satya-nadella/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Satya Nadella</a> commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;As we saw customers accelerate their digital spend during the pandemic, we&#8217;re now seeing them optimize their digital spend to do more with less. We&#8217;re also seeing organizations in every industry and geography exercise caution as some parts of the world are in a recession and other parts are anticipating one.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The tech company&#8217;s job cuts began in July 2022 when it said it was letting go of 1% of its staff. This follows a massive recruitment of 181,000 people in 2021. Microsoft notified the 1% affected in July that their roles were eliminated. In October, the multinational tech company confirmed more job cuts that included about 1,000 workers. Before its latest dismissal spree, which started in 2022, the last time Microsoft announced a layoff round was in 2017, after the beginning of its new fiscal year.</p>
<h2>Tech Firms Plan More Job Cuts</h2>
<p>Another tech company on a fresh round of job cuts is <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/amazon/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Amazon.com Inc</a> (NASDAQ: AMZN). The company announced Wednesday that it would fire over 18,000 employees, which is positioned to be its largest workforce cuts in 28 years. According to CEO Andy Jassy, workers in the human resources and store sections will be most impacted. Amazon initially planned to reduce its headcount by 10,000 workers.</p>
<p>American cloud-based software company Salesforce (NYSE: CRM) <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/salesforce-workforce-pandemic/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">announced</a> earlier this year that it is laying off more than 7,000 workers. The company plans to cut 10% of its personnel and shut down some officer spaces. Shedding more light on the decision, co-CEO Marc Benioff <a href="https://www.sec.gov/Archives/edgar/data/1108524/000110852423000003/ex991-lettertoemployees.htm" target="_blank" rel="noopener">wrote</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;I&#8217;ve been thinking a lot about how we came to this moment. As our revenue accelerated through the pandemic, we hired too many people leading into this economic downturn we&#8217;re now facing, and I take responsibility for that.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>More tech jobs cut include Amazon dismissing 11,000 employees, Twitter lowering headcounts by 3,700, and more. Stripe, Shopify (NYSE: SHOP), and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/netflix/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Netflix</a> (NASDAQ: NFLX) workers also felt the layoff hit.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/dogecoin-shiba-bonk-25b-trading-volume/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tech-companies-job-cuts-2023/">Tech Companies Announce Fresh Job Cuts in 2023</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tech-companies-job-cuts-2023/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dogecoin, Shiba Inu &amp; Bonk Inu Recently Combine for $25B in Monthly Trading Volume</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/dogecoin-shiba-bonk-25b-trading-volume/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/dogecoin-shiba-bonk-25b-trading-volume/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 11:48:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bonk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[doge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[shib]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[shiba inu]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=233177</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/dogecoin-shiba-bonk-25b-trading-volume/">Dogecoin, Shiba Inu &#038; Bonk Inu Recently Combine for $25B in Monthly Trading Volume</a></p>
<p>Canine-inspired tokens, including Dogecoin and Shiba Inu, saw around $25 billion in trading volume in the past month. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/dogecoin-shiba-bonk-25b-trading-volume/">Dogecoin, Shiba Inu &#038; Bonk Inu Recently Combine for $25B in Monthly Trading Volume</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/dogecoin-shiba-bonk-25b-trading-volume/">Dogecoin, Shiba Inu &#038; Bonk Inu Recently Combine for $25B in Monthly Trading Volume</a></p>
<p>Dogecoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/dogecoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">DOGE</a>), Shiba Inu (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/shiba-inu/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SHIB</a>), and Bonk Inu (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bonk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BONK</a>) have collectively <a href="https://decrypt.co/119529/dogecoin-bonk-shiba-inu-25-billion-monthly-trading-volume" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">accounted</a> for $25.6 billion in trading volume within the past month. By comparison, leading crypto Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a>) has accounted for $618.7 billion worth of trading volume in the same period.</p>
<p>Nonetheless, the canine-themed digital currencies&#8217; recent trading volume underscores how popular they are still. DOGE and SHIB remain the leaders in this category, with the former being the top dog. As it stands, Dogecoin saw $17.5 billion in trading volume over the past month compared to SHIB&#8217;s $7.2 billion. Meanwhile, the Solana-based BONK, arguably the least-known of the trio, has done $885 million in trading volume since its December 25th launch. In addition, Bonk Inu&#8217;s roller-coaster price trajectory has also inspired a non-fungible token (NFT) collection and induced a Solana price surge.</p>
<p>The three digital assets still managed considerable trading volume despite a massive downturn from their all-time highs. DOGE and Shiba Inu are currently at an 86% drawdown from their record highs. In addition, BONK is trading 76% lower than its highest price of $0.00000487, set just two weeks ago.</p>
<p>Unlike Shiba Inu and Bonk Inu, which operate on existing proof-of-stake (PoS) networks, Dogecoin is a proof-of-work (PoW) token. This makes DOGE similar to Bitcoin because both digital assets are mined and operate on their own networks.</p>
<h2>The Musk Effect</h2>
<p>Dogecoin has famously benefitted from <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/elon-musk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Elon Musk&#8217;s</a> endorsement since 2019 and became a meme coin in 2021. On several occasions, the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/tesla/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tesla</a> CEO touted DOGE&#8217;s applicability for several dynamic transactions – over Bitcoin (BTC) and Ether (ETH). In addition, Musk also frequently described the digital currency as his favorite crypto and considered accepting it as payment for Tesla cars.</p>
<p>Alongside DOGE, Musk also embarked on a high-profile promotional sequence for Shiba Inu crypto. At the time, the brash Tesla boss even acquired a real-life Shiba Inu breed to further his cause. In late 2021, the billionaire businessman frequently posted well-documented pictures of his Shiba Inu puppy named &#8216;Floki.&#8217; At the time, Musk&#8217;s antics helped to drive up the price of the namesake crypto and brought invaluable visibility to SHIB.</p>
<h2>Dogecoin, Shiba Inu Trading Volume Inspires Other DOGE-centric Crypto Monikers</h2>
<p>Several tokens out there seek to leverage Dogecoin&#8217;s name by including some variation of &#8216;Doge&#8217; in their own names. According to CoinGecko, at least 169 digital currencies are guilty of this perceived promotional gimmick. However, the strategy is paying off as these Doge-influenced digital assets saw more than $323 million in monthly trading volume.</p>
<p>Amid the recent Dogecoin and Shiba Inu trading volume development, it remains unknown if any meme coin would match DOGE&#8217;s meteoric rise. The most popular canine-themed crypto once reached 73 cents in May 2021 before Musk made a televised appearance. However, following the outspoken businessman&#8217;s comments on &#8216;Saturday Night Live&#8217; at the time, Dogecoin sank 20% in a single hour.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fincen-binance-counterparty-bitzlato/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/dogecoin-shiba-bonk-25b-trading-volume/">Dogecoin, Shiba Inu &#038; Bonk Inu Recently Combine for $25B in Monthly Trading Volume</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/dogecoin-shiba-bonk-25b-trading-volume/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>FinCEN Names Binance as Counterparty in Order against Bitzlato</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fincen-binance-counterparty-bitzlato/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fincen-binance-counterparty-bitzlato/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 10:25:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Binance News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitzlato]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FinCEN]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ofac]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=233153</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fincen-binance-counterparty-bitzlato/">FinCEN Names Binance as Counterparty in Order against Bitzlato</a></p>
<p>According to the FinCEN order, Bitzlato has been used to launder as much as $700 million since its inception, and according to the terms of the order, the regulator wants the named counterparties to stop doing business with Bitzlato.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fincen-binance-counterparty-bitzlato/">FinCEN Names Binance as Counterparty in Order against Bitzlato</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fincen-binance-counterparty-bitzlato/">FinCEN Names Binance as Counterparty in Order against Bitzlato</a></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The United States Treasury Department’s Financial Crimes Enforcement Network (FinCEN) has named the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a> exchange, the largest crypto trading platform in the world, as one of the counterparties in the order, it just issued against Bitzlato exchange. According to the </span><a href="https://www.fincen.gov/sites/default/files/shared/Order_Bitzlato_FINAL%20508.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">release</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> from FinCEN, Bitzlato is incorporated in Hong Kong and it represents a primary source of money laundering for Russian illicit finance.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The FinCEN said Bitzlato has an extensive operation in facilitating “deposits and funds transfers by Russian ransomware groups or affiliates, such as Conti” as well as its core roles in pushing illicit financial transactions for the “Russian darknet markets on behalf of both darknet customers and darknet vendors.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Bitzlato is not the only platform in the world that may be involved in related illicit transactional activities, but it comes off as the one the government has beamed its radar on in recent times. According to the regulator, Bitzlato has different counterparties it sends money and receives funds from.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The top three listed include Binance, darknet market Hydra and The Finiko, a Russian Ponzi Scheme network.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&#8220;Approximately two-thirds of Bitzlato’s top receiving and sending counterparties are associated with darknet markets or scams. For example, Bitzlato’s top three receiving counterparties, by total amount of BTC received between May 2018 and September 2022 were: (1) Binance, a VASP; (2) the Russia-connected darknet market Hydra; and (3) the alleged Russia-based Ponzi scheme “TheFiniko,” the order said.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to the FinCEN order, Bitzlato has been used to launder as much as $700 million since its inception, and according to the terms of the order, the regulator wants the named counterparties to stop doing business with Bitzlato in order to stop enabling the flow of funds from bad Russian actors.</span></p>
<h2><b>Binance Helped FinCEN in Bitzlato Investigation</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Following the break of the news that Binance is one of the counterparties linked to Bitzlato, the trading platform has come out to say it helped FinCEN in its investigation into the Hong Kong-based entity.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&#8220;Binance is pleased to have provided substantial assistance to international law enforcement partners in support of this investigation. This exemplifies Binance’s commitment to working collaboratively with law enforcement partners worldwide,&#8221; a Binance spokesperson </span><a href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/01/19/binance-named-as-counterparty-in-fincen-order-against-bitzlato/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">said</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Over the course of the past 12 months, the United States authorities have been up and doing with respect to the sanctioning of blockchain-based platforms that have ties to illicit activities. Back in May last year, the regulator sanctioned wallets connected to Blender.io, a crypto mixer for its alleged ties to the Lazarus Group, a hacking syndicate from North Korea.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Later in the year, the Treasury’s OFAC office also </span><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-treasury-sanctions-tornado-cash/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">sanctioned</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> another crypto mixer, Tornado Cash, a move that stirred up protests from the broader crypto ecosystem. Leaders and organizations rebelled against the regulator noting that sanctioning a piece of technology for how it is being used is an affront to innovation. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">OFAC refused to rescind its sanctions, </span><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tornado-cash-users-ofac-sanctions/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">stirring a significant plunge</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> in the usage of Tornado Cash in general.</span></p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/aussie-bank-stablecoin-audn/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fincen-binance-counterparty-bitzlato/">FinCEN Names Binance as Counterparty in Order against Bitzlato</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fincen-binance-counterparty-bitzlato/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Aussie Bank Mints Stablecoin AUDN on Ethereum and Algorand Blockchains</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/aussie-bank-stablecoin-audn/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/aussie-bank-stablecoin-audn/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sanaa Sharma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 10:22:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[algo]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[algorand]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[aubn]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nab]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=233118</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/aussie-bank-stablecoin-audn/">Aussie Bank Mints Stablecoin AUDN on Ethereum and Algorand Blockchains</a></p>
<p>NAB chief innovation officer Howard Silby said the decision to mint the AUDN stablecoin, which is backed 1:1 by the Australian dollar (AUD), was based on the bank’s belief that blockchain infrastructure will play a key role in the new evolution of finance.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/aussie-bank-stablecoin-audn/">Aussie Bank Mints Stablecoin AUDN on Ethereum and Algorand Blockchains</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/aussie-bank-stablecoin-audn/">Aussie Bank Mints Stablecoin AUDN on Ethereum and Algorand Blockchains</a></p>
<p>The National Australia Bank (NAB), one of the central banks in Australia, has <a href="https://www.afr.com/companies/financial-services/nab-creates-a-stablecoin-in-boost-for-digital-economy-20230117-p5cd8f" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">launched</a> a stablecoin named AUDN. The stablecoin is all set to be launched in the middle of this year, according to the Australian Financial Review (AFR) report.</p>
<p>NAB will go on to become the second &#8220;Big 4&#8221; Australian Bank to introduce an Australian dollar-puffed stablecoin on the Ethereum Network. NAB chief innovation officer Howard Silby previously stated that the decision to mint the AUDC stablecoin, which is supported by the Australian dollar (AUD) was made on the bank&#8217;s conviction that blockchain establishment will play an important role in the next evolution of Finance.</p>
<p>NAB chief innovation officer Howard Silby said the decision to mint the AUDN stablecoin &#8211; which is backed 1:1 by the Australian dollar (AUD) &#8211; was based on the bank’s belief that blockchain infrastructure will play a key role in the new evolution of finance.</p>
<p>According to Silby, the idea of AUDN is to enable customers to resolve money transfers on Blockchain Technology in real-time using Australian Dollars. AUDN also has the prospect of being used for other activities like carbon credit trading, overseas money transfers, etc. The stablecoin will be launched on the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a> and Algorand blockchains, which is a small contract platform.</p>
<p>The application of AUDN for real-time cross-border remittances could become a convenient way for customers to avoid the tedious and expensive SWIFT payment network. Carbon credit trading and other forms of tokenized real-world assets will be a significant use case for the AUDN, according to Silby. He also stated that the company was planning to deliver stablecoins in several different currencies for which the bank possesses authorization.</p>
<p>NAB&#8217;s disclosure of the AUDN comes nine months after rival Australia and New Zealand Banking Group (ANZ) introduced thirty million tokens of its stablecoin, which can also be used for international remittances and carbon trading.</p>
<p>A stablecoin is a kind of cryptocurrency whose value is attached to another asset class, such as a fiat currency or gold, to stabilize the rate. It is assumed to be more effective and less expensive than the interbank cross-border payments solutions SWIFT.</p>
<p>Before the launch of ANZ and NAB&#8217;s stablecoin ventures, the two banks also decided on collaborating with the other two &#8220;Big Four&#8221; in Australian banks- Commonwealth Bank of Australia and Westpac, to co-launch a pan-Australia stablecoin supported by the AUD. However, it wasn&#8217;t very successful because of competition issues and the banks being at different levels in their adoption and strategy.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/21shares-etp-crypto-staking/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/aussie-bank-stablecoin-audn/">Aussie Bank Mints Stablecoin AUDN on Ethereum and Algorand Blockchains</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/aussie-bank-stablecoin-audn/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>21Shares Launches Crypto Staking ETP as ‘Safer &amp; More Secure’ Crypto Exposure Alternative</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/21shares-etp-crypto-staking/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/21shares-etp-crypto-staking/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 10:20:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[21shares]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ada]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bnb]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bx swiss]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[polkadot]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sol]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[solana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tezos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xtz]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=233119</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/21shares-etp-crypto-staking/">21Shares Launches Crypto Staking ETP as &#8216;Safer &#038; More Secure&#8217; Crypto Exposure Alternative</a></p>
<p>Crypto firm 21Shares recently launched the world's first crypto staking ETP on the local stock exchange BX Swiss.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/21shares-etp-crypto-staking/">21Shares Launches Crypto Staking ETP as &#8216;Safer &#038; More Secure&#8217; Crypto Exposure Alternative</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/21shares-etp-crypto-staking/">21Shares Launches Crypto Staking ETP as &#8216;Safer &#038; More Secure&#8217; Crypto Exposure Alternative</a></p>
<p>Digital currency firm 21Shares has <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/21shares-unveils-worlds-first-crypto-staking-index-etp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">debuted</a> its new crypto staking exchange-traded product (ETP) on the BX Swiss exchange. This initiative, dubbed the 21Shares Staking Basket Index ETP, is a crypto staking index tailored to track proof-of-stake (PoS) coins. According to reports, the firm&#8217;s crypto staking ETP can track as many as 10 PoS digital currencies. It is also the world&#8217;s first crypto staking index ETP that offers diversified staking income.</p>
<p>However, Arthur Krause, director of ETP product at the firm&#8217;s parent company 21.co, also provided a caveat. According to Krause, the Staking Basket ETP does not engage in lending. Instead, the staking initiative is a crypto-native strategy that allows investors to commit assets that support validating blockchain transactions. Meanwhile, lending is a traditional financial strategy that sees lenders compensated for the risk involving the potential default of lent assets.</p>
<p>On 21Shares&#8217; impetus for launching the Staking Basket Index ETP, Krause <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/21shares-unveils-worlds-first-crypto-staking-index-etp-301723801.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">explained</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Our research has shown that investors are interested in diversified, crypto-native return streams – especially amid crypto winter.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Furthermore, Krause also added that the crypto staking ETP would be an attractive addition to several portfolios.</p>
<h2>More on New 21Shares ETP</h2>
<p>The exchange-traded product immediately starts trading on the local bourse BX Swiss under the ticker STAKE. In addition, at launch, the 21Shares STAKE ETP tracks six digital currencies. These include Binance Coin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/binance-coin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BNB</a>), Cardano (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/cardano/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ADA</a>), Cosmos (ATOM), Polkadot (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/polkadot-new/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">DOT</a>), Solana (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/solana/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SOL</a>), and Tezos (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-tezos-xtz-protocol/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">XTZ</a>). Furthermore, this index will rebalance on a semi-annual basis in March and September following market shifts.</p>
<p>Krause played up the immediate benefits that stake offers to investors, explaining:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;STAKE provides value for investors by using the ETP&#8217;s assets to generate a passive yield that may offer additional returns by contributing to the network&#8217;s security.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>In addition, Krause emphasized that assets widely linked to defunct crypt exchange<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"> FTX</a> do not have any impact on 21Shares&#8217; products. Citing Solana as an example, the director noted that &#8220;Solana &#8211; like virtually all other crypto assets &#8211; experienced significant price declines in 2022 but suffered no fundamental impairment that would preclude its inclusion in the index. &#8221;</p>
<p>With STAKE&#8217;s addition, 21Shares and parent company, 21.co, now offer 47 crypto ETP products across 12 exchanges in nine countries. In addition, these ETPs offer a safer and more secure way for crypto exposure by providing a direct crypto investment alternative.</p>
<p>The STAKE ETP launch comes a few years after 21Shares started dabbling into staking exchange-traded products. In 2019, the digital currency firm launched its 21Shares Tezos Staking ETP (AXTZ). Furthermore, 21Shares also debuted its Solana Staking ETP (ASOL) in June 2021.</p>
<p>However, both products experienced a marked decline last year due to the sustained bear market. ETPs have settled into an encouraging rally since the beginning of 2023. This trend is underscored by the year-to-date (YTD) upswings of AXTZ (38%) and ASOL (78%).</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-boss-sec-battle-wef/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/21shares-etp-crypto-staking/">21Shares Launches Crypto Staking ETP as &#8216;Safer &#038; More Secure&#8217; Crypto Exposure Alternative</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/21shares-etp-crypto-staking/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple Boss Speaks about Prolonged SEC Battle at WEF</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-boss-sec-battle-wef/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-boss-sec-battle-wef/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 10:17:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brad garlinghouse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[wef]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=233152</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-boss-sec-battle-wef/">Ripple Boss Speaks about Prolonged SEC Battle at WEF</a></p>
<p>The Ripple boss hinted some optimism, stating that there may finally be a resolution to its legal battle with the SEC.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-boss-sec-battle-wef/">Ripple Boss Speaks about Prolonged SEC Battle at WEF</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-boss-sec-battle-wef/">Ripple Boss Speaks about Prolonged SEC Battle at WEF</a></p>
<p>While <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ripple-labs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ripple</a> remains entangled in its legal battle, the company&#8217;s CEO <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/brad-garlinghouse/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Brad Garlinghouse</a> recently mentioned some emails from the Security and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) while <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LNTS1u7Jvag" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">speaking</a> at the World Economic Forum (WEF). The event in Davos recorded many industry leaders and government officials in attendance, discussing different topics across multiple sectors.</p>
<h2>Ripple Boss on SEC Case at 2023 WEF</h2>
<p>The emails came specifically from SEC Director Bill Hinman. Speaking at the WEF, the Ripple CEO revealed that the SEC director&#8217;s emails had been ordered to be submitted to the judge. He believes that the messages may contain some damning information. Garlinghouse noted that the exposition of the documents to the public would likely trigger questions on why the Commission brought the lawsuit against Ripple. He explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;When those come to light, I think that we will see more kind of like &#8216;How is it possible the SEC decided to bring a case against Ripple given what they were saying within their walls.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>In addition, the Ripple boss hinted some optimism at the WEF, stating that there may finally be a resolution to its legal battle with the SEC. According to Garlinghouse, the prolonged lawsuit may eventually end within the first half of this year. The case began in 2020 when the SEC alleged that Ripple and its executives illegally sold unregistered XRP to clients. The dispute raised the question of whether XRP should be considered a security. After much back and forth with the case, the SEC and Ripple submitted the final rounds of briefs in December. The parties asked for a summary judgment of the case.</p>
<h2>Is the SEC&#8217;s Case against Ripple about to End?</h2>
<p>In an <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/01/18/ripple-ceo-optimistic-crypto-firm-will-get-sec-xrp-lawsuit-ruling-soon.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">interview</a> with CNBC&#8217;s &#8220;Squawk Box Europe&#8221; at the WEF, the Ripple CEO noted his expectation from the SEC lawsuit. He emphasized his optimism in a resolution within the first six months of 2023. Garlinghouse said he feels &#8220;very good&#8221; about the lawsuit&#8217;s current state, adding that &#8220;judges take however long judges will take. He mentioned that Ripple is open to a settlement if it comes to that.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We have always said that we would love to settle, but it requires one very important thing, and that is that, on a go-forward basis, it&#8217;s clear that XRP is not a security. The SEC and Gary Gensler has very outwardly said he views almost all crypto as a security. And so that leaves very little space in the Venn diagram for settlement.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/xrp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">XRP</a> may have to deal with stricter restrictions if it is pronounced security. This means the crypto asset will be more transparent, provide higher investor protections, and more.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitzlato-arrest-700m-illicit-funds/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-boss-sec-battle-wef/">Ripple Boss Speaks about Prolonged SEC Battle at WEF</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-boss-sec-battle-wef/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>