<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 17:49:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Authorities dismantle a cross-border crypto fraud network in Europe</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/authorities-dismantle-a-cross-border-crypto-fraud-network-in-europe/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/authorities-dismantle-a-cross-border-crypto-fraud-network-in-europe/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 15:53:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/authorities-dismantle-a-cross-border-crypto-fraud-network-in-europe/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The cross-border fraud network used call centres to defraud victims. The network operated in Germany, Serbia, Cyprus, and Bulgaria. 15 people connected to the network have been arrested so far. After the raid on Nexo&#8217;s offices in Bulgaria, the European Union Agency for Criminal Justice Cooperation and Europol has arrested 15 people allegedly connected to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/authorities-dismantle-a-cross-border-crypto-fraud-network-in-europe/">Authorities dismantle a cross-border crypto fraud network in Europe</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul class="decimal_type">
<li>The cross-border fraud network used call centres to defraud victims.</li>
<li>The network operated in Germany, Serbia, Cyprus, and Bulgaria.</li>
<li>15 people connected to the network have been arrested so far.</li>
</ul>
<p>After the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/nexo-offices-in-bulgaria-raided-by-authorities-money-laundering-claims/">raid on Nexo&rsquo;s offices in Bulgaria</a>, the European Union Agency for Criminal Justice Cooperation and Europol has arrested 15 people allegedly connected to a crypto cross-border fraud network. 14 people were arrested in Serbia while the fifteenth person was nabbed in Germany.</p>
<p>The Bulgarian authorities have however said that the raid of Nexo&rsquo;s offices is not connected to the crypto fraud network arrests.</p>
<p>The fraudsters reportedly used call centres from Serbia to defraud international victims and had until their arrest defrauded victims tens of millions of euros. The search leading to the arrest of the fraudsters was started back in 2021 and involved Europol and the European Union Agency for Criminal Justice Cooperation.</p>
<h2>Assets seized in the arrests</h2>
<p>According to <a href="https://www.eurojust.europa.eu/news/takedown-fraudulent-cryptocurrency-network-bulgaria-cyprus-and-serbia">reports</a>, during the arrests, the law enforcement agencies seized 150 computers, two luxury apartments, three cars, $1 million worth of cryptocurrencies, and 50,000 in euros. The victims of the fraudsters are mainly in Austria, Australia, Switzerland, Germany, and Canada.</p>
<p>The authorities have however said that the arrests are &ldquo;almost the tip of the iceberg&rdquo; since they found &ldquo;high volumes of financial transactions.&rdquo;</p>
<p>The authority&rsquo;s announcement said that the group:</p>
<p><em>&ldquo;Operated the call centres from Serbia and used a technological infrastructure in Bulgaria to run the scheme and allegedly, Cyprus was the base for laundering the illegal proceedings.&rdquo;</em></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/authorities-dismantle-a-cross-border-crypto-fraud-network-in-europe/">Authorities dismantle a cross-border crypto fraud network in Europe</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/authorities-dismantle-a-cross-border-crypto-fraud-network-in-europe/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why have Some Exchanges not Released Proof of Reserves?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/why-have-some-exchanges-not-released-proof-of-reserves/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/why-have-some-exchanges-not-released-proof-of-reserves/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 14:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Research]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/why-have-some-exchanges-not-released-proof-of-reserves/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The fall of FTX has led to calls for increased transparency among crypto exchanges. Several centralised exchanges have released proof of reserves to regain public trust. However, it may take more than publishing proof of reserves before customers can fully trust exchanges. Here, we discuss the problems with proof of reserves. What is Proof of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/why-have-some-exchanges-not-released-proof-of-reserves/">Why have Some Exchanges not Released Proof of Reserves?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">The fall of FTX has led to calls for increased transparency among crypto exchanges. Several centralised exchanges have released proof of reserves to regain public trust. However, it may take more than publishing proof of reserves before customers can fully trust exchanges. Here, we discuss the problems with proof of reserves.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Proof of Reserves?</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://www.okx.com/proof-of-reserves" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Proof of Reserves</u></a> is an attestation by the exchange that all customers&rsquo; deposits are safe and fully backed by on-chain assets. It proves that the exchange will become independent in case of a bank run. Exchanges are essentially custodians and are not supposed to use their customers&rsquo; assets for any other purpose beyond safekeeping. Proof of reserves is an excellent way to show this. Due to these reasons, several exchanges, such as Binance, Bitfinex, <a href="https://www.okx.com/proof-of-reserves/detail"><u>OKX</u></a>, Kraken, Gate.io, etc., have all published their reserves.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Which Exchanges have not Released Proof of Reserves?&nbsp;</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Coinbase is one of the major exchanges that still need to publish proof of reserves. Coinbase&rsquo;s decision is premised on the fact that it is a public company which means it is held to a higher degree of transparency than other exchanges. It has a quarterly external auditor review of its financials and must provide the Securities and Exchange Commission with annual audited financial statements. The exchange must also include customers&rsquo; funds as liabilities and assets on its balance sheet.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Problems with Proof of Reserves</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Other exchanges that are not publicly traded are not bound to the same standards as Coinbase. Therefore, a Merkle tree-based proof of reserves is the best way to demonstrate solvency. Despite this, there are still valid concerns about the auditing process to provide reliable proof of reserves. The problems include the following:</p>
<h3 dir="ltr"><strong>Lack of Expertise</strong></h3>
<p dir="ltr">Blockchain technology is relatively new and still evolving. While it might borrow some concepts from traditional finance, the accounting process differs. Therefore, there needs to be additional expertise among auditors to review these exchanges&rsquo; financial records. Most auditors operate with traditional financial rules and standards, and they must be fully aware of the unique risks associated with cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The need for more expertise among auditors has lowered the confidence in reports from these auditors. This was an issue for Mazars, the accounting firm that audited the proof of reserves of several crypto exchanges, including Binance. It has ceased working with all crypto entities, claiming a lack of confidence in its reports and media scrutiny.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">There has been a history of collapsing crypto exchanges even after auditors vouched for their financial health. In 2019, New Zealand-based exchange Cryptopia collapsed a few months after Grant Thornton&rsquo;s audit and positive rating. Moreover, the FTX collapse also occurred despite Armanino LLP&rsquo;s audit processes.&nbsp;</p>
<h3 dir="ltr"><strong>Lack of Interest from leading Audit Companies</strong></h3>
<p dir="ltr">Traditional auditors have faced issues due to a lack of understanding of digital assets. However, &nbsp;there is a high degree of unwillingness from leading accounting firms to collaborate with crypto exchanges. This is due to the reputational risk if the exchange fails. The big four accounting firms &ndash; KPMG, Deloitte, Ernst &amp; Young, and PWC &ndash; are usually reluctant to work with most crypto firms. Therefore, crypto exchanges use less dependable auditors or rely on in-house auditing as a last recourse.&nbsp;</p>
<h3 dir="ltr"><strong>Possibilities of Human Error</strong></h3>
<p dir="ltr">Another major issue with proof of reserves is the dependency on humans. While auditors are independent, they must rely on the exchange&rsquo;s information. If the exchange supplies inaccurate data and the auditor fails to exercise due diligence, the audited proof of reserves would be purposeless as it will fail to disclose the actual financial situation.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>Need for Crypto Auditing Standards</strong></p>
<p dir="ltr">Despite the flaws of proof of reserves, it is still the best way for crypto exchanges to demonstrate that they are in good condition. Therefore, the problems with the current crypto auditing standards must be addressed. Ideally, crypto companies and traditional auditors must invest in education and training to improve their expertise.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/why-have-some-exchanges-not-released-proof-of-reserves/">Why have Some Exchanges not Released Proof of Reserves?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/why-have-some-exchanges-not-released-proof-of-reserves/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>FTX has the green light to sell its other businesses including LedgerX</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/ftx-has-the-green-light-to-sell-its-other-businesses-including-ledgerx/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/ftx-has-the-green-light-to-sell-its-other-businesses-including-ledgerx/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 14:26:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/ftx-has-the-green-light-to-sell-its-other-businesses-including-ledgerx/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The judge in charge of overseeing the FTX bankruptcy proceedings has given FTX approval to sell some assets. The assets under consideration include LedgerX among other assets. The move will allow FTX to get money to repay its creditors. After filing for permission to be allowed to sell some of its functioning businesses in December [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ftx-has-the-green-light-to-sell-its-other-businesses-including-ledgerx/">FTX has the green light to sell its other businesses including LedgerX</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>The judge in charge of overseeing the FTX bankruptcy proceedings has given FTX approval to sell some assets.</li>
<li>The assets under consideration include LedgerX among other assets.</li>
<li>The move will allow FTX to get money to repay its creditors.</li>
</ul>
<p>After <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ftx-seeking-to-auction-its-functioning-businesses-including-ledgerx/">filing for permission to be allowed to sell some of its functioning businesses</a> in December 2022, FTX can now breathe a sigh of relief after the judge in charge of overseeing the FTX bankruptcy proceedings <a href="https://restructuring.ra.kroll.com/FTX/Home-DocketInfo?DocAttribute=4562&amp;DocAttrName=SALEDOCUMENTS_Q&amp;MenuID=9892&amp;AttributeName=Sale%20Document">approved</a> the sale of its assets to aid its efforts in repaying its creditors.</p>
<p>The businesses that FTX has been allowed to sell include the derivatives platform LedgerX, it regional arms FTX Europe and FTX Japan, and the stock clearing platform Embed.</p>
<h2>All systems go for auction</h2>
<p>After the Delaware Bankruptcy Court Judge, John Dorsey gave the go-ahead for the sale of the four key FTX units, interested bidders can now Perella Bank which is tasked with overseeing the sale process. The investment bank will be representing FTX and its assets in the process.</p>
<p>Earlier this week, about 117 parties had expressed interest in buying the said FTX assets. These parties will now be allowed to access information regarding the assets so as to perform their due diligence before making up their minds on whether to go ahead with the purchase.</p>
<p>FTX Europe has its license suspended while FTX Japan is subject to business suspension orders.</p>
<p>The sale approval is a reprieve for the embattled crypto exchange which has so far <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ftx-has-recovered-over-5b-in-assets-report/">recovered about $5 billion in assets</a> since its collapse. The funds obtained from the sale will go a long way in raising funds for repaying the exchange&rsquo;s creditors.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ftx-has-the-green-light-to-sell-its-other-businesses-including-ledgerx/">FTX has the green light to sell its other businesses including LedgerX</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/ftx-has-the-green-light-to-sell-its-other-businesses-including-ledgerx/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What do layoffs at Crypto.com mean? Crypto winter rages on</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/what-do-layoffs-at-crypto-com-mean-crypto-winter-rages-on/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/what-do-layoffs-at-crypto-com-mean-crypto-winter-rages-on/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dan Ashmore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 12:58:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto.com]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/what-do-layoffs-at-crypto-com-mean-crypto-winter-rages-on/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key Takeaways Crypto.com is laying off 20% of its workforce, having cut 5% last summer Fellow exchanges Coinbase, Kraken, Huobi and Swyftx have all downsized over last month Tech sector as a whole is laying off thousands, with Amazon, Salesforce, Meta and Twitter just a few of the big names Crypto sector misjudged its vulnerability [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/what-do-layoffs-at-crypto-com-mean-crypto-winter-rages-on/">What do layoffs at Crypto.com mean? Crypto winter rages on</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>Key Takeaways</h2>
<ul>
<li>Crypto.com is laying off 20% of its workforce, having cut 5% last summer</li>
<li>Fellow exchanges Coinbase, Kraken, Huobi and Swyftx have all downsized over last month</li>
<li>Tech sector as a whole is laying off thousands, with Amazon, Salesforce, Meta and Twitter just a few of the big names</li>
<li>Crypto sector misjudged its vulnerability to price levels in the market</li>
<li>Volatility of Bitcoin was overlooked as companies expanded aggressively during COVID</li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Crypto.com has become the latest crypto company to lay employees off, <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-com-announces-layoffs-cites-negative-economic-developments/">announcing</a> Friday that it is cutting 20% of its workforce. CEO Chris Marszalek cited &ldquo;market conditions and recent industry events&rdquo; for the downsizing, in line with what other crypto CEOs have blamed, as the bear market continues to take victims.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">As I shared with the team today, while we continue to perform well, market conditions and recent industry events have made this the right decision for the company at this time.</p>
<p>&mdash; Kris | Crypto.com (@kris) <a href="https://twitter.com/kris/status/1613757936492507137?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 13, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2><strong>Layoffs flood the industry</strong></h2>
<p>Crypto.com is far from the only <a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/">exchange</a> that has been forced to make workers redundant. Kraken, Swyftx and Huobi have all laid off workers in the last month. Kraken cut 30% of its staff, Australian exchange Swyftx chopped 40% and Huobi chopped 20%. Coinbase also <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/what-is-happening-at-coinbase-another-20-of-employees-laid-off/">announced</a> earlier this week that it was chopping 20% of its workforce, having already laid off 18% in June.</p>
<p>It is not only crypto companies that have been affected, however. The tech industry at large has wobbled. Amazon, Twitter, Meta and Salesforce are just a few names that have reduced their workforce by thousands.</p>
<p>The tech sector is notoriously volatile and has been hurt by increasing interest rates over the past year. Given so many tech companies fail to turn a profit, valuations are often derived from the discounting of future cash flows back to the present. When interest rates were zero, this led to high valuations across the board.</p>
<p>However, with inflation spiralling, central banks have been forced to raise rates aggressively. This has lowered the value of these discounted cashflows and reduced company valuations.</p>
        <div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/12432907">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<h2><strong>Contagion in the cryptocurrency industry</strong></h2>
<p>But crypto has faced its own battles separate from the macro climate, too. There is no shortage of scandals to point to when Marszalek says &ldquo;recent industry events&rdquo;, but the most recent is the staggering <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ftx-insolvent-what-next-for-crypto/">collapse of FTX</a>.</p>
<p>The exchange was one of the top three, alongside Coinbase and Binance, and its demise has triggered a fresh <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/expect-crypto-contagion-as-ftx-crisis-is-far-from-over/">wave of contagion</a> across the industry.</p>
<p>While $8 billion is the amount of customer assets that are missing in the FTX scandal, the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/luna-why-i-sold-my-ust-for-95-cents-on-the-dollar-today/">LUNA crash</a> of May was perhaps even more devastating, as the one-time $60 billion ecosystem collapsed following the death spiral of its not-so-stable stablecoin, UST.</p>
<p>This triggered a series of bankruptcies and collapses across the industry, including crypto lender Celsius and hedge fund Three Arrows Capital.</p>
<p>These scandals have decimated prices. With dropping prices, volumes and interest, alongside the macro headwinds mentioned earlier, &nbsp;crypto companies have been forced to pare back operations in order to survive.</p>
        <div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/12388412">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<h2><strong>Crypto.com&rsquo;s expansion was too rapid</strong></h2>
<p>In a criticism that is far from limited to Crypto.com, the exchange expanded too rapidly amid the hysteria of the pandemic bull market.</p>
<p><em>&ldquo;We grew ambitiously at the start of 2022, building on our incredible momentum and aligning with the trajectory of the broader industry. That trajectory changed rapidly with a confluence of negative economic developments&rdquo;,</em> said CEO Marszalek.</p>
<p>Crypto.com has seen meteoric growth to 70 million users. But it has had its share of missteps along the way. In February, it received widespread criticism for a rather cringe-worthy Matt Damon Superbowl advert. The commercial cost $10 million, and Crypto.com laid off 5% of its workforce only four months later, in what was the biggest signal of all that it had misjudged the sustainability of the bull run.</p>
<p><em>&ldquo;The reductions we made last July positioned us to weather the macro economic downturn&rdquo;&nbsp;</em>said Marszalek.<em>&nbsp;</em></p>
<p>However, he added that<em> &ldquo;it did not account for the recent collapse of FTX, which significantly damaged trust in the industry. It&rsquo;s for this reason, as we continue to focus on prudent financial management, we made the difficult but necessary decision to make additional reductions in order to position the company for long-term success&rdquo;.&nbsp;</em></p>
<h2><strong>Crypto companies misjudged correlated nature</strong></h2>
<p>While these events were described as &ldquo;unforeseeable&rdquo;, some analysts point towards a mismanagement of risk, given how correlated the industry is to the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> price. Bitcoin has been notoriously volatile historically, with the below chart showing how many pullbacks the industry has suffered.</p>
        <div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/12433128">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p>There was a bullishness during COVID that crypto had finally beaten this tendency for violent bear markets. Ultimately, this was misguided, with much of the expansion predicted on cheap money and a warm printer.</p>
<p>The federal reserve hiking rates pulled liquidity out of the system and risk assets dropped harshly. There are few assets further out on the risk spectrum than crypto, which got crushed.</p>
<p>A glance at the Coinbase share price during 2022 is all that needs to be done in order to see how rapidly things have turned south for crypto exchanges. Since going public in April 2021, Coinbase has shed close to 90% of its value.</p>
        <div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/12090035">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p>A chart which illustrates quite how beholden to the crypto gods these exchanges are is the plotting of Coinbase&rsquo;s share price against the Bitcoin price.</p>
<p>The correlation is extreme, with a falling Bitcoin price linked with a drop in volume and interest in the industry, and ultimately less revenue for crypto exchanges.</p>
        <div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/12399513">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<h2><strong>Final thoughts</strong></h2>
<p>Of course, this is all well and good in hindsight. Not many predicted a pullback of this magnitude, and as said above, the tech industry outside of crypto is also getting punished.</p>
<p>While Crypto.com have certainly made some errors and misjudged how vulnerable they are to the overall price level and volatility in the crypto market, they are far from the only one.</p>
<p>The macro climate has shifted immeasurably over the last year, with the speed of interest rate hikes catching all corners by surprise. It was never going to be pretty for crypto, even aside from all the scandals that have rocked the space.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/what-do-layoffs-at-crypto-com-mean-crypto-winter-rages-on/">What do layoffs at Crypto.com mean? Crypto winter rages on</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/what-do-layoffs-at-crypto-com-mean-crypto-winter-rages-on/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hodlnaut stares at liquidation after creditors reject restructuring plan</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/hodlnaut-stares-at-liquidation-after-creditors-reject-restructuring-plan/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/hodlnaut-stares-at-liquidation-after-creditors-reject-restructuring-plan/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 12:58:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/hodlnaut-stares-at-liquidation-after-creditors-reject-restructuring-plan/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Investigations show that Hodlnaut lost about $190 million in the Terra LUNA crash. The lender had proposed a restructuring plan to allow creditors to have a view of the company&#8217;s operations. The creditors however want liquidation of the company&#8217;s assets. Troubled Singapore-based crypto lender Hodlnaut seems to be heading for a possible liquidation after its [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/hodlnaut-stares-at-liquidation-after-creditors-reject-restructuring-plan/">Hodlnaut stares at liquidation after creditors reject restructuring plan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Investigations show that Hodlnaut lost about $190 million in the Terra LUNA crash.</li>
<li>The lender had proposed a restructuring plan to allow creditors to have a view of the company&rsquo;s operations.</li>
<li>The creditors however want liquidation of the company&rsquo;s assets.</li>
</ul>
<p>Troubled Singapore-based crypto lender Hodlnaut seems to be heading for a possible liquidation after its creditors rejected a proposed restructuring plan and instead sought liquidation of the lender&rsquo;s assets.</p>
<p>Hodlnaut started by downplaying its exposure to the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ust-debacle-pulls-terra-luna-from-80-to-0-024-in-a-week-heres-where-to-buy-luna/">Terra LUNA collapse </a>but after the platform suspended withdrawals citing lack of liquidity and market volatility, investigations were carried out and it immerged that <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/hodlnaut-reports-nearly-200-million-financial-shortfall-as-it-seeks-court-protection/">it lost about $190 million</a> in the Terra debacle and the executive later deleted numerous documents related to their investments in order to avoid exposure.</p>
<p>Hodlnaut later sought judicial management to avoid liquidation and it was eventually placed under a creditor protection program with hopes that it would restore its asset-to-debt ratio to 1:1 and allow users to withdraw funds.</p>
<p>The government-aided judicial program seems not to have helped. In November investors lodged complaints resulting in the investigation of the founders for &ldquo;underplaying their exposure to certain crypto tokens and misrepresentations of facts.&rdquo;</p>
<h2>Hodlnaut restructuring plan</h2>
<p>The proposed restructuring plan allowed the current directors to oversee the operations of the lending company during the restructuring process meaning the interim judicial managers were to be sidelined. However, in a hearing on January 12, the application to remove the interim judicial managers was rejected.</p>
<p>The firm&rsquo;s creditors rejected the restructuring plan rather and asked for liquidation of the platform&rsquo;s assets. They believe that the restructuring would not help remove the crypto lender from its current woes and that it was in their best interest that the firm wind down and liquidates its assets.</p>
<p><a href="https://coinjournal.net/algorand/what-is-algorand/">Algorand</a>, for example, which is one of Hodalnut&rsquo;s creditors, called for immediate liquidation and distribution of the remaining assets among the creditors.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/hodlnaut-stares-at-liquidation-after-creditors-reject-restructuring-plan/">Hodlnaut stares at liquidation after creditors reject restructuring plan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/hodlnaut-stares-at-liquidation-after-creditors-reject-restructuring-plan/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Metacade Price Prediction as Investors Fear Binance Exchange Is Next to Collapse</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-price-prediction-as-investors-fear-binance-exchange-is-next-to-collapse/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-price-prediction-as-investors-fear-binance-exchange-is-next-to-collapse/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice Davies]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 12:45:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-price-prediction-as-investors-fear-binance-exchange-is-next-to-collapse/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>BNB investors fear that Binance exchange may not last through the bear market. However, investors are still optimistic about the long-term future of Web3, and Metacade has been a key project bringing positive sentiment back to the crypto markets. The MCADE presale attracted seven figures worth of funding and sold out the beta phase in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-price-prediction-as-investors-fear-binance-exchange-is-next-to-collapse/">Metacade Price Prediction as Investors Fear Binance Exchange Is Next to Collapse</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">BNB investors fear that Binance exchange may not last through the bear market. However, investors are still optimistic about the long-term future of Web3, and Metacade has been a key project bringing positive sentiment back to the crypto markets.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The MCADE presale attracted seven figures worth of funding and sold out the beta phase in just three weeks. Now, investors have started to look forward once again.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Binance exchange is under fire, and investors are starting to worry</h2>
<p dir="ltr">After FTX collapsed in November, Binance exchange conducted a <a href="https://uk.news.yahoo.com/binance-worlds-biggest-crypto-exchange-025729346.html" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>proof-of-reserves audit</u></a> to show that digital assets fully backed user funds; however, some have highlighted a key inconsistency in the report.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>Binance&rsquo;s BTC liabilities were $245 million bigger than their BTC reserves</strong>, meaning an FTX-style bank run could cause major problems. In such an event, Binance may be forced to pause withdrawals and sell other assets, which could have a negative impact on price action for the entire crypto market.</p>
<p dir="ltr">After Changpeng Zhao appeared on CNBC to discuss the financial situation of Binance exchange, it appeared that the CEO of Binance exchange was reluctant to hire a top four auditing firm to reveal liabilities. This hesitancy has invited more fear, uncertainty, and doubt (FUD) during the 2022 crypto bear market.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is BNB?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Binance (BNB) is a digital asset exchange platform for trading various cryptocurrencies. BNB tokens are the native tokens on Binance exchange and Binance Smart Chain &ndash; a Layer 1 blockchain that was forked from Ethereum while being developed by Binance exchange.</p>
<p dir="ltr">BNB is used to facilitate transactions on Binance and pay fees for trading activities such as listing or withdrawal fees. The BNB token also serves as an essential component of the Binance exchange ecosystem, allowing users to receive rewards through a cash-back program and participate in community voting events.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Metacade (MCADE)?</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>Metacade is building the biggest arcade that can be found anywhere on the blockchain</strong>.It is the first community-driven project of its kind and aims to become a central hub for Web3 users to play, earn, socialize, and learn about all things <a href="https://coinjournal.net/glossary/gamefi/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>GameFi</u></a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Metacade will offer various arcade games and merge its classic titles with play-to-earn mechanics. In addition, gamers can participate in tournaments and access several different methods of earning a crypto income through <a href="https://metacade.co/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade</u></a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">After announcing the launch of the MCADE token presale, Metacade attracted a significant level of investment in a short space of time. The beta phase of the presale sold out in just three weeks, as Metacade rapidly sold 140,000,000 MCADE tokens at the price of $0.008.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How does Metacade work?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Built on the Ethereum blockchain, Metacade is a comprehensive gaming platform that offers crypto rewards to gamers in various major arcade games. As well as this, users can discover the latest GameFi trends, share game reviews, and earn MCADE tokens for contributing helpful information to the community.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Through Metacade, users can also kickstart a career in Web3. The platform will connect gamers to paid job opportunities and offer beta testing roles to its community, allowing gamers to earn crypto while playing brand-new blockchain-based games.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade</u></a> can drive growth in the GameFi sector through the Metagrants program. This scheme will allow users to vote for the best up-and-coming blockchain games and provide early-stage funding to support game development. Metacade is an all-in-one GameFi project that offers significant value to the crypto gaming community.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Metacade is, without a doubt, the best investment opportunity</h2>
<p dir="ltr">BNB investors are worried about Changpeng Zhao&rsquo;s recent comments and what they might mean for the future of Binance exchange. In contrast, early adopters of MCADE have been getting increasingly excited about the future.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>MCADE is a brand-new token that has huge long-term potential</strong>. Early participants in the presale have a rare opportunity to make gains above 10x over the next few years, as the current price of $0.01 looks undervalued.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As Metacade completes its presale and launches its all-in-one gaming platform, it could become one of the biggest gaming platforms in Web3. Over time, the MCADE token could be worth over $1 &ndash; a major 50x price rise from the end of the presale.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Is MCADE worth buying?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">While BNB investors are fearful, the future certainly looks bright for Metacade. Metacade could be the best investment opportunity during the bear market, forecasted to become one of the biggest gaming platforms available.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The MCADE token is currently just $0.01, and the price will rise to $0.02 by the end of the presale. Investors have a limited time only to access MCADE at this price level before Metacade sells out. As you can see, Metacade certainly looks like a strong investment, as early investors could enjoy gains up to 50x during 2023.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>You can buy Binance tokens at eToro&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://coinjournal.net/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=OTk1MTA" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong><u>here</u></strong></a><strong>.</strong></p>
<p><strong>You can participate in the MCADE presale&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong><u>here</u></strong></a><strong>.</strong></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-price-prediction-as-investors-fear-binance-exchange-is-next-to-collapse/">Metacade Price Prediction as Investors Fear Binance Exchange Is Next to Collapse</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-price-prediction-as-investors-fear-binance-exchange-is-next-to-collapse/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cryptocurrency price prediction: AGIX, MULTI, Aptos</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/cryptocurrency-price-prediction-agix-multi-aptos/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/cryptocurrency-price-prediction-agix-multi-aptos/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 12:41:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/cryptocurrency-price-prediction-agix-multi-aptos/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrencies had a strong week as investors reacted to the FTX bankruptcy proceedings and the latest American inflation data. In the biggest crypto news&#160;of the week, FTX said that it had found more than $5 billion in liquid assets that it could sell. Another key news was data that showed that America&#8217;s inflation was cooling. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/cryptocurrency-price-prediction-agix-multi-aptos/">Cryptocurrency price prediction: AGIX, MULTI, Aptos</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Cryptocurrencies had a strong week as investors reacted to the FTX bankruptcy proceedings and the latest American inflation data. In the biggest <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/"><u>crypto news</u></a><strong>&nbsp;</strong>of the week, FTX said that it had found more than $5 billion in liquid assets that it could sell. Another key news was data that showed that America&rsquo;s inflation was cooling. This crypto price prediction will look at what to expect with AGIX, Aptos, and MULTI.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">AGIX price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr">AGIX is the native token for SingularityNet, a relatively small but fast-growing AI platform built on Cardano. The AGIX crypto price surged to a high of $0.130 this week, the highest point since October 14. It has jumped by more than 253% from the lowest point in 2022. It is unclear why the token rose but a likely reason is that it was in sync with other AI-focused coins.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Turning to the daily chart, we see that the token went parabolic this week. As it rose, it moved above the important resistance point at $0.072, the highest point on December 13. The coin managed to move above all moving averages and is now approaching the important resistance point at $0.136 In the same period, oscillators like the Relative Strength Index (RSI) and the MACD have all surged.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, I suspect that SingularityNet&rsquo;s token is about to have a major pullback. If this happens, the next key support level to watch will be at $0.10, which is about 25% below the current level.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/1673613569907-210dd8ff-0410-4b95-9366-3a34eed9955a.png" style="width: 612px;height: 289.68px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="612" height="289.68"></p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/AGIXUSD/?exchange=BINANCE"><u>AGIX chart by TradingView</u></a></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy SingularityNET token</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Aptos price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Aptos price also surged this week as several apps in its ecosystem saw significant outflows. APT surged to a high of $7, which was the highest point since November. Precisely, Aptos soared by more than 120% from the lowest point this year. It also moved above the important resistance point at $5.42. The token surged above the 25-day and 50-day moving averages.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Like AGIX, I feel that Aptos price has now gotten so overbought, meaning that it will likely retreat. If this happens, the next key level to watch will be at $5.42, which is about 20% below the current level.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/1673613569847-7d15b516-b27f-4015-93b2-388b97b7e74b.png" style="width: 694px;height: 328.493px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="694" height="328.493"></p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/APTUSD/?exchange=COINBASE"><u>AGIX chart by TradingView</u></a></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy Aptos</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    Binance.US</h3>

    <p>Binance.US provides secure and reliable access to the world&rsquo;s most popular cryptocurrencies, with some of the lowest fees in the industry.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/binance-us-crypto?guid=OTk1MTE&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=CA&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=1" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy APT with Binance.US today            </a>
    </p>
<h2 dir="ltr">MULTI price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr">MULTI is the native token for Multichain, which was previously known as AnySwap. It is a leading platform in the Arbitrum ecosystem. Like Aptos and AGIX, the token surged to a high of $6.50 this week. It was up by more than 110% from the lowest level this year. It has also moved above all moving averages while oscillators are highly overbought. Therefore, I also suspect that the token will pullback in the coming days on profit taking.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/1673613569974-8aea8c7e-ff5e-485c-8d97-6ba81cfc0d43.png" style="width: 618px;height: 292.52px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="618" height="292.52"></p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/MULTIUSD/?exchange=KRAKEN"><u>MULTI chart by TradingView</u></a></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy MULTI</h2>
<p dir="ltr">
                </p><p>As MULTI is such a new asset, it's yet to be listed on major exchanges. You can still purchase MULTI using a DEX (decentralised exchange) though, which just means there are a few extra steps. To buy MULTI right now, follow these steps:</p>

                                    <h3>1. Buy ETH on a regulated exchange or broker, like <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=OTk1MTE&amp;component=news-table-1inch" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">eToro &rsaquo;</a></h3>
                    <p>We suggest <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=OTk1MTE&amp;component=news-table-1inch" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">eToro</a> because it's one of the world's leading multi-asset trading platforms, an exchange and wallet all-in-one with some of the lowest fees in the industry. It's also beginner-friendly, and has more payment methods available to users than any other available service.</p>
                                    <h3>2. Send your ETH to a compatible wallet like Trust Wallet or MetaMask</h3>
                    <p>You'll need to create your wallet, grab your address, and send your coins there.</p>
                                    <h3>3. Connect your wallet to the 1Inch DEX</h3>
                    <p>Head to 1Inch, and 'connect' your wallet to it.</p>
                                    <h3>4. You can now swap your ETH for MULTI</h3>
                    <p>Now that you're connected, you'll be able to swap for 100s of coins including MULTI.</p>
                

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/cryptocurrency-price-prediction-agix-multi-aptos/">Cryptocurrency price prediction: AGIX, MULTI, Aptos</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/cryptocurrency-price-prediction-agix-multi-aptos/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>US SEC has filed charges against Gemini and Genesis</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/us-sec-has-filed-charges-against-gemini-and-genesis/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/us-sec-has-filed-charges-against-gemini-and-genesis/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 09:21:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gemini]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/us-sec-has-filed-charges-against-gemini-and-genesis/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The US SEC is accusing Gemini and Genesis of selling unregistered securities. Genesis and Gemini did not register their partnership as a lending partnership. Genesis has been having liquidity issues after FTX&#8217;s collapse and has paused withdrawals to date. The US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has filed charges against Genesis and Gemini accusing the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/us-sec-has-filed-charges-against-gemini-and-genesis/">US SEC has filed charges against Gemini and Genesis</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>The US SEC is accusing Gemini and Genesis of selling unregistered securities.</li>
<li>Genesis and Gemini did not register their partnership as a lending partnership.</li>
<li>Genesis has been having liquidity issues after FTX&rsquo;s collapse and has paused withdrawals to date.</li>
</ul>
<p>The US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has filed charges against Genesis and Gemini accusing the two of selling unregistered securities through the Gemini Earn product.</p>
<p>According to the SEC, the Gemini Earn allowed Gemini and Genesis to earn billions of dollars from investors despite the product being unregistered.</p>
<h2>Unregistered lending partnership</h2>
<p>Gemini introduced the Gemini Earn product in February 2021 and the product ran until January 8 2022. &nbsp;At the same time, Gemini had a partnership with Genesis, which is a subsidiary of Digital Currency Group (DCG). The partnership allowed Gemini customers to earn yield by lending their crypto assets to Genesis.</p>
<p>The SEC however claims that the two firms (Genesis and Gemini) misrepresented their business model by advertising returns of up to 8% to clients without first registering the partnership as a lending partnership with the relevant authorities.</p>
<h2>Genesis withdrawals</h2>
<p>To make matters worse, Genesis found itself in turmoil after the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/expect-crypto-contagion-as-ftx-crisis-is-far-from-over/">FTX&rsquo;s collapse</a> and even <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/genesis-2-8b-crypto-lending-unit-halts-withdrawals/">paused withdrawals due to liquidity issues</a>. According to open letters written by Cameron Winklevoss, the co-founder of Gemini Earn, Genesis currently owes $900 million to 340,000 users of the Earn product.</p>
<p>The SEC also claims that the &ldquo;US retail investors who participated in the Gemini Earn program have suffered significant harm.&rdquo; The SEC Chair Gary Gensler said:</p>
<p><em>&ldquo;Today&rsquo;s charges build on previous actions to make clear to the marketplace and the investing public that crypto lending platforms and other intermediaries need to comply with our time-tested securities laws.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p>Gemini co-founder has however said that Gemini will defend itself saying that SEC claims are &ldquo;parking ticket.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/us-sec-has-filed-charges-against-gemini-and-genesis/">US SEC has filed charges against Gemini and Genesis</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/us-sec-has-filed-charges-against-gemini-and-genesis/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto.com announces layoffs, cites negative economic developments</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-com-announces-layoffs-cites-negative-economic-developments/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-com-announces-layoffs-cites-negative-economic-developments/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 08:04:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto.com]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-com-announces-layoffs-cites-negative-economic-developments/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Crypro.com CEO cited poor market conditions and recent events in the industry as reasons for layoffs. The layoffs come just days after Coinbase announced similar layoffs. The Cronos (CRO) token price has responded positively to the news. The co-founder and CEO of Crypto.com exchange, Kris Marszalek, has today announced that the company is laying off [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-com-announces-layoffs-cites-negative-economic-developments/">Crypto.com announces layoffs, cites negative economic developments</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Crypro.com CEO cited poor market conditions and recent events in the industry as reasons for layoffs.</li>
<li>The layoffs come just days after Coinbase announced similar layoffs.</li>
<li>The Cronos (CRO) token price has responded positively to the news.</li>
</ul>
<p>The co-founder and CEO of Crypto.com exchange, Kris Marszalek, has today announced that the company is laying off some of its staff to reduce its global workforce. The CEO said that they are reducing the workforce by 20%.</p>
<p>In the <a href="https://crypto.com/company-news/company-update">announcement</a>, the CEO said:</p>
<p><em>&ldquo;Today we made the difficult decision to reduce our global workforce by approximately 20%.&rdquo; &nbsp;</em></p>
<p>In a follow-up tweet post addressing the matter, Marszalek wrote:</p>
<p><em>&ldquo;We grew ambitiously at the start of 2022, building on our incredible momentum and aligning with the trajectory of the broader industry. That trajectory changed rapidly with a confluence of negative economic developments.&rdquo;</em></p>
<h2>Crypto firms laying off workers in mass</h2>
<p>According to sources, Crypto.com has about 3500 to 4500 employees, meaning the 20% layoffs would affect about 700 to 900 employees.</p>
<p>Crypto.com is not the only crypto firm to announce layoffs this year. Huobi announced layoffs at the start of the year while <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-lays-off-950-employees-ceo-says-the-exchange-is-well-capitalized/">Coinbase also announced layoffs</a> a few days ago.</p>
<p>The laying off of workers sends mixed signals since the crypto market is currently on a recovery trajectory and investors are expecting some good performance this year compared to last year. Crypto.com has also grown to over 70 million users worldwide, something that is seen as a positive development for the company.</p>
<h2>Cronos (CRO) token price surge</h2>
<p>The <a href="https://coinjournal.net/cronos/">Cronons (CRO) token price</a> has responded positively to the news and risen by about 3.08% in the last 24 hours.</p>
<p>The CRO coin has been on a positive trajectory since the start of the year having gained about 15.3% over the past 14 days.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-com-announces-layoffs-cites-negative-economic-developments/">Crypto.com announces layoffs, cites negative economic developments</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-com-announces-layoffs-cites-negative-economic-developments/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
