<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 15:33:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bank of America Releases Better than Expected Q4 Earnings Report</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bank-of-america-q4-earnings/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bank-of-america-q4-earnings/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 15:33:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wall Street]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bank of america]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[boa]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=232546</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bank-of-america-q4-earnings/">Bank of America Releases Better than Expected Q4 Earnings Report</a></p>
<p>In the released earnings report, Bank of America recorded a net income of $3.6 billion for the fourth quarter while client balances stayed flat at $1.6 trillion. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bank-of-america-q4-earnings/">Bank of America Releases Better than Expected Q4 Earnings Report</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bank-of-america-q4-earnings/">Bank of America Releases Better than Expected Q4 Earnings Report</a></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">American multinational investment bank and financial services holding company </span><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/bank-of-america/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Bank of America Corp</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> (NYSE: BAC) has </span><a href="https://d1io3yog0oux5.cloudfront.net/_be62467122df7498b6555528a17a1296/bankofamerica/db/806/9782/earnings_release/The+Press+Release.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">released</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> its performance report for the fourth quarter of 2022 with figures showing the company benefited from the Federal Reserve’s interest rate hikes.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to the company, its revenue came in at $24.66 billion as against $24.33 billion which was expected by analysts polled by Refinitiv. Earnings came in at 85 cents, an amount that was more than the 77 cents that were projected by Refinitiv. However, the company’s Net Interest Income of $14.7 billion fell slightly short of the $14.8 billion estimate given by StreetAccount.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">With the fourth quarter earnings season now underway, the report from the Bank of America will lend good succor to the broader financial market ecosystem. The impressive net interest income was fueled by the higher interest rate hikes, and this helps to offset the slump in the firm’s investment banking fees.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">These fees dropped by over 50% to $1.1 billion and remained at par with StreetAccount’s estimate. While many are considering giving Bank of America some accolades for its Performance, Chief Executive Officer, Brian Moynihan described the financial ecosystem as “increasingly slowing.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“The themes in the quarter have been consistent all year as organic growth and rates helped deliver the value of our deposit franchise. That coupled with expense management helped drive operating leverage for the sixth consecutive quarter,” Moynihan said in a statement.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The signs of struggle in the financial terrain were felt across the board with several Wall Street giants laying off their staff over the course of the past quarter in a bid to cut down on operations costs. Amongst the biggest names that </span><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-mass-staff-layoff-costs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">laid off</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> staff, we can name </span><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/amazon/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Amazon.com Inc</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> (NASDAQ: AMZN), and </span><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/meta/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Meta Platforms Inc</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> (NASDAQ: META).</span></p>
<h2><b>Bank of America Business Segment Highlights</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In the released earnings report, Bank of America recorded a net income of $3.6 billion for the fourth quarter while client balances stayed flat at $1.6 trillion. The bank Average deposits of more than $1 trillion, up $20 billion, or 2% combined credit/debit card spend of $223 billion, up 5%.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The financial services giant also reported that its Consumer Banking unit recorded an approximate growth of 195,000 net new Consumer checking accounts. This growth accounts for the 16th consecutive quarterly growth despite the general turmoil the industry has seen over the past months.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The global took a more visible kick as total Assets Under Management (AUM) balances came in at $1.4 trillion atop a decline of $237 billion. With credit and debit card spending rising year over year, the outstanding balances on credit cards also soared by 14%.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Bank of America shares dropped by over 2% in the pre-market and are up by about 4% since the start of the year despite the general fear rocking the financial sector of an impending recession.</span></p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tencent-tiktok-wechat-channels/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bank-of-america-q4-earnings/">Bank of America Releases Better than Expected Q4 Earnings Report</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bank-of-america-q4-earnings/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tencent Pushes to Challenge TikTok via WeChat Channels</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tencent-tiktok-wechat-channels/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tencent-tiktok-wechat-channels/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 12:32:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bytedance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tiktok]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[wechat]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=232540</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tencent-tiktok-wechat-channels/">Tencent Pushes to Challenge TikTok via WeChat Channels</a></p>
<p>In addition to challenging TikTok, Tencent also connects its products with Channels to help creators to stream content.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tencent-tiktok-wechat-channels/">Tencent Pushes to Challenge TikTok via WeChat Channels</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tencent-tiktok-wechat-channels/">Tencent Pushes to Challenge TikTok via WeChat Channels</a></p>
<p>Chinese multinational and entertainment company <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/tencent/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tencent Holdings</a> is set to challenge ByteDance&#8217;s dominance with its own TikTok. A source revealed that Tencent had created a team of content creators to launch its own short video platform TikTok, which launched in the Chinese market in 2016 and has exploded to reach more global audiences over the years.</p>
<h2>Tencent Relies on WeChat to Develop Own TikTok</h2>
<p>China&#8217;s WeChat Channels hosted an online concert during last year&#8217;s summer that featured the Backstreet Boys. The boy band performed on a stage in Pennsylvania and about 44 million views across different locations tuned in to be entertained. This show is another event conducted by WeChat owner Tencent to promote its app&#8217;s short-video platform. In addition to the BackStreet Boys, Tencent has also featured the likes of Westlife and Taiwan&#8217;s Jay Chou for live-streamed concerts as it makes efforts to challenge TikTok. Meanwhile, the tech giant&#8217;s founder Pony Ma has referred to the platform as &#8220;the hope of the company&#8221;.</p>
<p>A senior analyst at research firm Analysys, Liao Xuhua, said:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Tencent hopes it can turn Channels into the next WeChat Pay. It has a shot at it. But it is also going to be difficult.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Some reliable sources who are familiar with Tencent mentioned how they have continually discussed Channels&#8217; importance within the multinational company. Channels have been of significant advantage to Tencent, which experienced some hits last year due to stricter gaming legislation and the persistent coronavirus pandemic. The video and photo public feed recorded explosive growth in 2022 as its total number of views increased more than 3X. At the same time, the number of daily active creators and video uploads went up X2.</p>
<h2>WeChat Channels Growth</h2>
<p>Tencent added that gross merchandise value (GMV) from live-streaming e-commerce popped by over 800% on WeChat Channels. However, the company did not state the specific figures recorded on GMV. Per a LatePost report on Channels&#8217; daily transactions, the platform&#8217;s sales reached over 100 million yuan (15 million) in September 2022 for the first time. This signifies an annual rate of around 36 billion yuan.</p>
<p>In addition to challenging TikTok, Tencent also connects its products with Channels to help creators to stream content. The company integrated its Tencent Meetings with the platform, which will help hosts to conduct interviews and live streams on Channels. In addition, the multinational conglomerate lowered the monetization threshold on Channels. While Tencent allows users with as low as 10 followers to earn through advertisement. You have to have over 10,000 followers to start monetizing on TikTok.</p>
<p>Tencent resident Martin Lau revealed in November that Channels advertising was on its way to reaching 1 billion yuan in 2022 Q4.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/judge-ftx-sell-ledgerx-units/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tencent-tiktok-wechat-channels/">Tencent Pushes to Challenge TikTok via WeChat Channels</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tencent-tiktok-wechat-channels/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Judge Rules for FTX to Sell LedgerX, Other Units as Hundreds of Buyers Express Their Interest</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/judge-ftx-sell-ledgerx-units/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/judge-ftx-sell-ledgerx-units/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 11:40:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx collapse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx europe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx japan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ledgerx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sam bankman-fried]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sbf]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=232467</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/judge-ftx-sell-ledgerx-units/">Judge Rules for FTX to Sell LedgerX, Other Units as Hundreds of Buyers Express Their Interest</a></p>
<p>Interested buyers may officially begin to indicate their interests between January 18 and February 1.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/judge-ftx-sell-ledgerx-units/">Judge Rules for FTX to Sell LedgerX, Other Units as Hundreds of Buyers Express Their Interest</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/judge-ftx-sell-ledgerx-units/">Judge Rules for FTX to Sell LedgerX, Other Units as Hundreds of Buyers Express Their Interest</a></p>
<p>Bankruptcy judge John Dorsey has cleared <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a> to sell four of its key units in its bid to raise funds to repay creditors. This means that the collapsed exchange may now sell off its FTX Europe, FTX Japan, its derivatives arm LedgerX and Embed &#8211; its stock-clearing platform. The sell-offs will be overseen by investment bank Perella Weinberg.</p>
<p>Judge Dorsey issued the <a href="https://restructuring.ra.kroll.com/FTX/Home-DownloadPDF?id1=MTQzNzk0NA==&amp;id2=-1" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">order</a> on Thursday following a Wednesday hearing. Per the order, sales notices will be made available to the public within three working days. However, interested buyers may officially begin to indicate their interests between January 18 and February 1.</p>
<p>Interestingly, court documents show more than 117 buyers already have an interest in the sell-offs. But many more are also expected to join in within the given timeframe.</p>
<h2>FTX Plans a Quick Sell-off of Its Units</h2>
<p>FTX exchange used to be a major force in the crypto industry up until it <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-exchange-files-for-bankruptcy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">filed for bankruptcy</a> on November 11, 2022. The crypto empire crumbled shortly after reports surfaced about inconsistencies in the balance sheet of FTX trading arm Alameda Research.</p>
<p>Since filing for bankruptcy, FTX has been seeking for opportunities to at least repay creditors. So, now, it wants to sell off the more solvent parts of its business, hoping to do so very quickly.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the Department of Justice DoJ has some reservations about the upcoming sales. The DoJ is considering the allegations of wrongdoings that have been presented against some top executives of the firm. Therefore, it insists that every claim linked to former senior executives and their families will not be included in the sale. At least, for now, that facts have not yet been established. FTX also agrees to the DoJ&#8217;s request and assures that such claims will not be included.</p>
<p>So far, however, former FTX CEO <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/sam-bankman-fried/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Sam Bankman-Fried</a> has pleaded not guilty to charges leveled against him. And his former partners &#8211; Caroline Ellison and Gary Wang, are also said to be fully cooperating with investigators.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/wyre-removes-withdrawal-cap/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/judge-ftx-sell-ledgerx-units/">Judge Rules for FTX to Sell LedgerX, Other Units as Hundreds of Buyers Express Their Interest</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/judge-ftx-sell-ledgerx-units/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Wyre Removes Withdrawal Cap after Funding from Partner</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wyre-removes-withdrawal-cap/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wyre-removes-withdrawal-cap/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Babafemi Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 11:34:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[metamask]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[wyre]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=232426</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/wyre-removes-withdrawal-cap/">Wyre Removes Withdrawal Cap after Funding from Partner</a></p>
<p>Wyre has assured the crypto community that it is ready to resume regular operations.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/wyre-removes-withdrawal-cap/">Wyre Removes Withdrawal Cap after Funding from Partner</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/wyre-removes-withdrawal-cap/">Wyre Removes Withdrawal Cap after Funding from Partner</a></p>

<p>Crypto payment platform Wyre has removed its withdrawal cap after securing additional funding from a strategic partner. Recall that a few days ago, Wyre <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/wyre-imposes-withdrawal-limit/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">imposed a 90% withdrawal limit</a> on its users. The company also laid off 75 employees and announced changes to its managerial structure.</p>
<p>Emerging reports suggested that the crypto winter was giving the company a tough time and its collapse was imminent. The company also cited market conditions as its reason when it announced the withdrawal cap.</p>
<p>However, the firm noted that it was in “the best interest of our community,” to set the withdrawal cap at the time. CEO Ioannis Gianna said noted the firm was scaling back operations to plan its next steps. In the wake of the rumors, MetaMask severed ties with the company, removing the platform from its mobile aggregator and browser extension. It also advised its users to stay away from the platform.</p>
<h2>Withdrawal Cap Gone: Business Back to Usual</h2>
<p>However, Wyre has assured the crypto community that it is ready to resume regular operations. The company noted it received funds from an unnamed strategic partner. “This additional capital will help us continue to deliver on our mission to simplify and revolutionize the global financial ecosystem,” it added.</p>
<p>Following the funding, Wyre removed the withdrawal cap and noted it would begin receiving deposits and withdrawal requests. “As a regulated financial institution, we’re proud that we were able to continue delivering our services in a safe and sound manner without pausing withdrawals,” it added.</p>
<p>Today’s announcement suggests that the company’s financial situation may have improved despite the insolvency reports. However, user confidence is at an all-time low.</p>
<h2>VeVe Users Decry Return to Wyre</h2>
<p>After Wyre announced a limitation on withdrawals, digital collectibles firm VeVe suspended payouts and crypto pay-in requests. Following Wyre’s latest announcement, it <a href="https://twitter.com/veve_official/status/1613714679486124032" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a> that they “will be assessing Wyre&#8217;s capability to resume all services and support before re-enabling Payout.”</p>
<p>However, VeVe users have decried this move, suggesting that VeVe should seek out other payment providers. One user, @BitcornioGoat said, “That is a red flag&#8230; we would rather wait a bit longer for payout, so you can hire a better, more reliable payout partner that will be reliable for the long run.”</p>
<p>Read more <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/crypto/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">crypto news</a> on our website.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-cash-bch-price-hard-fork/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/wyre-removes-withdrawal-cap/">Wyre Removes Withdrawal Cap after Funding from Partner</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wyre-removes-withdrawal-cap/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Cash (BCH) Kickstarts Rally with 10% Price Gains, Ahead of May 2023 Hard Fork</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-cash-bch-price-hard-fork/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-cash-bch-price-hard-fork/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 11:18:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bch]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bch price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin cash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin cash price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=232478</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-cash-bch-price-hard-fork/">Bitcoin Cash (BCH) Kickstarts Rally with 10% Price Gains, Ahead of May 2023 Hard Fork</a></p>
<p>The Bitcoin Cash hard fork ahead this year will bring added security and privacy to the network with CashTokens enabling decentralized applications (Dapps) to run. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-cash-bch-price-hard-fork/">Bitcoin Cash (BCH) Kickstarts Rally with 10% Price Gains, Ahead of May 2023 Hard Fork</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-cash-bch-price-hard-fork/">Bitcoin Cash (BCH) Kickstarts Rally with 10% Price Gains, Ahead of May 2023 Hard Fork</a></p>
<p>The price of Bitcoin Cash (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin-cash/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BCH</a>), the native crypto of the first offshoot of the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> blockchain, has shot up by more than 10% in the last 24 hours. As of press time, BCH is <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/bitcoin-cash/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">trading</a> at a price of $120 with a market cap of $2.37 billion.</p>
<p>The latest rally in the BCH also coincides with the broader pump in the altcoin space this week. As a result, the Bitcoin Cash (BCH) price is up by more than 20% on the weekly charts. With today&#8217;s price action, Bitcoin Cash has broken above its resistance levels of $108. This sets up the altcoin to rally further up to its next resistance level of $150.</p>
<h2>Euphoria around Bitcoin Cash Hard Fork</h2>
<p>Some market traders believe that today&#8217;s gain in Bitcoin Cash (BCH) comes as euphoria kicks in as potential network changes are likely with the Bitcoin Cash hard fork upgrade ahead this year in May 2023.</p>
<p>Back in November 2022, Jason Dreyzehner, a developer for Bitcoin Cash had updated that the hard fork will potentially introduce key privacy and security changes to the fledging network.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the developers plan to introduce CashTokens, which would enable to run decentralized applications (Daaps) on the Bitcoin Cash blockchain. Currently, contracts on Bitcoin Cash lack primitives for issuing messages that can be verified by other contracts.</p>
<p>Some of the other proposed improvements that come along with Bitcoin Cash hard fork would include small transaction sizes. This would help to considerably speed up the transactional times as well as the smart contracts functionality. This, in turn, would allow the building of Bitcoin Cash-based applications for recurring payments, crowdfunding opportunities, and derivatives trading, in addition to other uses for Bitcoin Cash users.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Cash (BCH) Price Rally</h2>
<p>Similar to other altcoins, Bitcoin Cash suffered a major price correction last year in 2022 with its price dropping to nearly one-third on the yearly chart. Andrew Kang, founder of Mechanism Capital wrote that the fundamental improvements coupled with the bottom of BCH prices sets the runway for a greater BCH price surge in the coming weeks. “Charts look insanely bottomed and ready for impulse,” Kang tweeted.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="474" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24BCH&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$BCH</a></p>
<p>&#8211; Charts look insanely bottomed and ready for impulse<br />&#8211; Most BCH whales (Ver, Jihan) either capitulated or inactive<br />&#8211; Biggest network upgrade/hardfork in years in May 2023 (more efficient smart contracts, L2 capabilities)<a href="https://t.co/sqb2gtE1tS">https://t.co/sqb2gtE1tS</a> <a href="https://t.co/ESaslrDfHv">pic.twitter.com/ESaslrDfHv</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Andrew Kang (@Rewkang) <a href="https://twitter.com/Rewkang/status/1613569987704410112?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 12, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Along with Bitcoin Cash, another altcoin Litecoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/litecoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">LTC</a>) is scheduled for a hard fork ahead this year.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-house-republicans-crypto-subcommittee/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-cash-bch-price-hard-fork/">Bitcoin Cash (BCH) Kickstarts Rally with 10% Price Gains, Ahead of May 2023 Hard Fork</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-cash-bch-price-hard-fork/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>US House Republicans to Create Crypto Subcommittee for Oversight and Legislation</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-house-republicans-crypto-subcommittee/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-house-republicans-crypto-subcommittee/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 11:14:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sam bankman-fried]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sbf]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=232489</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-house-republicans-crypto-subcommittee/">US House Republicans to Create Crypto Subcommittee for Oversight and Legislation</a></p>
<p>Representative French Hill (R-Ark), who led Republicans in the effort to test the successful ability of a CBDC, will head the new subcommittee of crypto assets, financial technology, and inclusion.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-house-republicans-crypto-subcommittee/">US House Republicans to Create Crypto Subcommittee for Oversight and Legislation</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-house-republicans-crypto-subcommittee/">US House Republicans to Create Crypto Subcommittee for Oversight and Legislation</a></p>
<p>The US House Republicans plan to <a href="https://www.politico.com/news/2023/01/12/mchenry-reveals-house-crypto-panel-names-subcommittee-chairs-00077667" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">establish</a> a subcommittee to oversee the crypto space amid the ongoing industry-wide downturns. This move signifies that the GOP is putting crypto legislation and management on its agenda. A January 12th report by Politico cites the incoming chair of the financial services committee, North Carolina Representative Patrick McHenry, who revealed his plans on the House Republicans crypto subcommittee. In an interview, McHenry emphasized the need to set up the panel as there is “a big hole” in the committee’s current structure.</p>
<h2>House Republicans Focus on Subcommittee to Oversee Crypto</h2>
<p>Representative French Hill (R-Ark), who led Republicans in the effort to test the successful ability of a <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-central-bank-digital-currency-cbdc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CBDC</a>, will head the new subcommittee of crypto assets, financial technology, and inclusion. To assist him as the vice chair would be Representative Warren Davidson (R-Ohio). Notably, Davidson has always been vocal about cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>Indeed, crypto has become a non-dismissable subject that has led the US House Republicans to set up a subcommittee on its oversight and legislation. Digital assets have also dominated the financial regulation agenda in Congress compared to the past. Before now, the Financial Services Committee was majorly focused on overseeing the affairs of the traditional financial system like banks, Wall Street, and their regulators.</p>
<p>After a massive boom in the crypto industry, the market is now at its lows following the dramatic crash of the ex-crypto exchange giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a>. The House Financial Services Committee is expected to hold another hearing on the company’s failure. This is coming after a previous hearing in December where many members questioned if SBF’s actions were intentional or due to gross incompetence. They also slammed the former billionaire&#8217;s “apology tour.” However, Texas Representative Al Green noted:</p>
<blockquote><p>“R. Bankman-Friend has pretty much indicated that he just made a big mistake, that he was doing the best that he could to be a servant of great service to humankind. I find it difficult to believe we’re dealing with conscientious stupidity.”</p></blockquote>
<p>At the time, the committee concluded to hold a second hearing this new year.</p>
<p>Since the company’s demise, crypto companies have been in a defensive position as authorities file fraud charges against many crypto executives. Moving forward, the new crypto subcommittee by the House Republicans will conduct hearings and participate significantly in developing bills. According to McHenry, one of the council&#8217;s responsibilities will be to create explicit rules among federal regulators. The group will also develop policies to help underserved communities enjoy financial technology. The chair added they&#8217;ve “got to respond to oversight and policymaking on a new asset class.”<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-car-prices-us-europe/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-house-republicans-crypto-subcommittee/">US House Republicans to Create Crypto Subcommittee for Oversight and Legislation</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-house-republicans-crypto-subcommittee/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tesla Slashes Its Car Prices in US and Europe</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-car-prices-us-europe/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-car-prices-us-europe/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 11:09:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Transportation News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ev]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[model 3]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tesla]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tesla model 3]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tesla model y]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tesla shares]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tesla stock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tsla stock]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=232496</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-car-prices-us-europe/">Tesla Slashes Its Car Prices in US and Europe</a></p>
<p>This latest price cut by Tesla is becoming a trend and it represents almost the third time the firm will be slashing its car prices around the world.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-car-prices-us-europe/">Tesla Slashes Its Car Prices in US and Europe</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-car-prices-us-europe/">Tesla Slashes Its Car Prices in US and Europe</a></p>
<p>American multinational electric vehicle maker <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/tesla/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tesla Inc</a> (NASDAQ: TSLA) has slashed the prices of its vehicles in the United States, and other key markets in Europe. As <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/01/13/tesla-cuts-prices-in-us-and-europe-to-stoke-sales.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reported</a> by CNBC, the price slash extends to its pricing in the United Kingdom, Austria, France, Germany, the Netherlands, Norway, and Switzerland.</p>
<p>The price slash ranges from 1% to 17% depending on the specification of the car, as highlighted by Reuters, giving reference to the Model 3 and Y vehicles in Germany. Tesla’s Model 3 remains one of the top-demanded vehicles in Germany and the current price slash may position the company right to further beat existing competitors like the Volkswagen ID.4.</p>
<p>The motive for slashing the prices is notably uniform across the board and it all boils down to attracting new buyers at a time when more competing electric vehicle makers are introducing cheaper cars into the market. Tesla is notably facing a significant headwind as to reducing demand across the board</p>
<p>The company delivered a total of 405,278 vehicles in the fourth quarter even though it produced a total of 439,701 vehicles. The price slash may change the narrative for Tesla as independent EV market researcher Troy Teslike shared that the price of the Model Y is now $13,000 cheaper before the tax credit and $20,500 cheaper including the tax credit.</p>
<p>There are speculations that the price slashes will help Tesla secure some form of the tax credit, one major incentive it has relied on to maintain market dominance. With retail pricing one of the crucial factors that is considered to offer this EV tax credit, The Tesla move now appears to be a smart one for both the company and its customers alike.</p>
<h2>Tesla and Price Slashes: a Growing Trend</h2>
<p>This latest price cut by Tesla is becoming a trend and it represents almost the third time the firm will be slashing its car prices around the world. As Coinspeaker <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-cut-price-model-3-y-china/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a> earlier this month, Tesla effectively slashed prices in China on its Model 3 and Model Y.</p>
<p>While this move is designed to help attract customers, the price slashes have resulted in what looks like the opposite of its desired goals. Some customers in China are reportedly protesting after taking deliveries of their vehicles at a relatively higher rate compared to when the price slashes were implemented.</p>
<p>Unless Tesla is able to correctly find a way to appease customers and increase its demand across the board, its shares may continue to suffer in the aftermath of all these unsettled changes. According to a note to investors from Bernstein Analysts on Thursday, Tesla is facing more competition with higher interest rates and slower consumer spending than in recent years.</p>
<p>“We believe that many investors underestimate the magnitude of the demand challenges Tesla is facing,” they said, giving Tesla an “Underperform” rating and a price target of $150. At the time of writing, Tesla shares are changing hands at $117.81, down 4.65% in the Pre-Market.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sbf-users-funds-substack-letter/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-car-prices-us-europe/">Tesla Slashes Its Car Prices in US and Europe</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-car-prices-us-europe/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>SBF Maintains Claim He Did Not Steal Users’ Funds in New Substack Letter</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sbf-users-funds-substack-letter/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sbf-users-funds-substack-letter/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 11:06:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Alameda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[changpeng zhao]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cz]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sam bankman-fried]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sbf]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=232441</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sbf-users-funds-substack-letter/">SBF Maintains Claim He Did Not Steal Users&#8217; Funds in New Substack Letter</a></p>
<p>While SBF covered many areas in his substack letter, one thing was echoed over and again, and that is the fact that he did not steal users' funds.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sbf-users-funds-substack-letter/">SBF Maintains Claim He Did Not Steal Users&#8217; Funds in New Substack Letter</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sbf-users-funds-substack-letter/">SBF Maintains Claim He Did Not Steal Users&#8217; Funds in New Substack Letter</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/sam-bankman-fried/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Sam Bankman-Fried</a> (SBF), the founder and former Chief Executive Officer of bankrupt FTX Derivatives Exchange has maintained his innocence with respect to stealing the trading platform users’ funds as alleged by Federal Prosecutors. In a Thursday morning <a href="https://sambf.substack.com/p/ftx-pre-mortem-overview" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Substack letter</a>, Bankman-Fried fried explained that the collapse of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a> and its sister trading firm Alameda Research is a function of the broader turmoil that the financial industry has recorded over the past year.</p>
<p>In the letter, SBF noted that over the course of 2021, the Net Asset Value of Alameda Research grew to $100 billion with $8 billion of net borrowing (leverage), and $7 billion of liquidity on hand. Amid this growth, SBF acknowledged that Alameda Research failed to hedge its market exposure and by implication, the firm lost approximately 80% of its value over that time span.</p>
<p>The disgraced CEO argued that his comment bordered on the insolvency of FTX International as FTX US, against the claims by prosecutors, is fully solvent and is in a position to repay all of its customers.</p>
<p>“FTX US remains fully solvent and should be able to return all customers’ funds.  FTX International has many billions of dollars of assets, and I am dedicating nearly all of my personal assets to customers,” he wrote.</p>
<p>SBF claimed the run toward the filing of bankruptcy by FTX was precipitated by the CEO of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a> Changpeng “<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/changpeng-zhao/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CZ</a>” Zhao who tweeted back on November 6 that he will be selling off the exchange’s stash of FTT tokens. To Sam Bankman-Fried, this is a months-long PR effort to get FTX down.</p>
<p>SBF is awaiting trial on <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-bankman-fried-charges/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">8 count charges</a> including those bordering on money laundering and fraud, a case that was solidified when his two top comrades, Caroline Ellison and Gary Wang both <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ellison-wang-guilty-ftx/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">pleaded guilty</a> to similar charges. While both of them could still change their pleas later on, SBF pleaded not guilty right away and per his recent revelations, he may have just the right defense to substantiate his stance.</p>
<h2>SBF Maintains He Did Not Steal User’s Funds</h2>
<p>While SBF covered many areas in his substack letter, one thing was echoed over and again, and that is the fact that he did not steal users&#8217; funds.</p>
<p>“I didn’t steal funds, and I certainly didn’t stash billions away.  Nearly all of my assets were and still are utilizable to backstop FTX customers.  I have, for instance, offered to contribute nearly all of my personal shares in Robinhood to customers–or 100%, if the Chapter 11 team would honor my D&amp;O legal expense indemnification,” he said.</p>
<p>While the industry <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-sbf-alameda-robinhood-shares/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">believes SBF misappropriated funds</a>, the 30-year-old bemoaned the confusion between liquidators and regulators with respect to separating customers of solvent FTX US and those of insolvent FTX International. According to him, FTX International, even in its insolvency, is supposed to be able to muster assets if properly managed to repay all of its creditors.</p>
<p>SBF’s trial is set for October 2 this year in New York.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/polygon-pos-chain-hard-fork/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sbf-users-funds-substack-letter/">SBF Maintains Claim He Did Not Steal Users&#8217; Funds in New Substack Letter</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sbf-users-funds-substack-letter/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Polygon Prepares for PoS Chain Hard Fork to Boost Performance, MATIC Price Up 3%</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/polygon-pos-chain-hard-fork/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/polygon-pos-chain-hard-fork/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 11:02:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[matic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[matic network]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[polygon]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=232459</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/polygon-pos-chain-hard-fork/">Polygon Prepares for PoS Chain Hard Fork to Boost Performance, MATIC Price Up 3%</a></p>
<p>The Polygon ecosystem has grown exponentially in the past year with over 207 million unique addresses, and more than 2.3 billion processed transactions.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/polygon-pos-chain-hard-fork/">Polygon Prepares for PoS Chain Hard Fork to Boost Performance, MATIC Price Up 3%</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/polygon-pos-chain-hard-fork/">Polygon Prepares for PoS Chain Hard Fork to Boost Performance, MATIC Price Up 3%</a></p>
<p>Polygon (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/matic-network/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">MATIC</a>) network, an <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a> scaling solution, has announced a hard fork scheduled for January 17 to reduce the severity of gas spikes and address chain reorganizations (reorgs) in an effort to reduce time to finality.</p>
<h2>Polygon Hard Fork</h2>
<p>The Polygon community gave the hard fork proposal in a forum discussion following updates provided by the governance team. At the top of the discussion forum, the Polygon community was asked to vote on changes in BaseFeeChangeDenominator and SprintLength. Out of the 15 votes, 87 per cent agreed that decreasing SprintLength to 16 blocks from 64 and increasing BaseFeeChangeDenominator from 8 to 16 will address the current Polygon impasse.</p>
<p>The Polygon governance team noted that changing BaseFeeChangeDenominator from 8 to 16 will help smooth out the increase and decrease rate in baseFee when the gas exceeds or falls below the target gas limits in a block.</p>
<p>The Polygon ecosystem has grown exponentially in the past year with over 207 million unique addresses, and more than 2.3 billion processed transactions. With over 37k decentralized applications already built on the Polygon network &#8211; including Uniswap and Aave as well as major companies like Robinhood, Adobe, and Stripe &#8211; system changes to improve overall performance are paramount.</p>
<p>Moreover, there are competing smart contract chains with scalable infrastructure and Polygon is not immune to them.</p>
<p>“Longer-term technical upgrades to Polygon PoS are being worked on, like parallelization, even while another promising tech for scaling, like Polygon zkEVM, is being built. But there are also more immediate steps to improve Polygon PoS performance and predictability–proposals that require the network’s approval to become reality,” Polygon network <a href="https://polygon.technology/blog/hardfork-incoming-upgrading-polygon-pos-chain-to-boost-performance" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">noted</a>.</p>
<h2>Polygon Network Market Outlook</h2>
<p>The Polygon network has a market capitalization of approximately $7,964,643,386 and a 24-hour trading volume of $538,218,050. With 8,734,317,475 MATIC in circulating supply, approximately 4 billion units have been staked on the PoS program. Moreover, the Polygon network takes pride in 13k delegators on PoS and 100 active validators.</p>
<p>Trading at $0.912286, Polygon MATIC has gained approximately 17 percent in the last seven days. However, MATIC is down over 61 percent in the past year, according to our latest crypto price oracles. Nonetheless, the digital asset has gained over 28882.6 percent from its all-time low achieved three years ago.</p>
<p>The upcoming hard fork is expected to stir up more <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-decentralized-finance-defi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">DeFi</a> activities on the Polygon network as gas fees and transaction finality issues will be addressed. Ultimately, the Ethereum network is expected to remain at the top of the smart contract race despite the emergence of ETH killers.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-genesis-gemini-securities/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/polygon-pos-chain-hard-fork/">Polygon Prepares for PoS Chain Hard Fork to Boost Performance, MATIC Price Up 3%</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/polygon-pos-chain-hard-fork/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>SEC Charges Genesis and Gemini for Offering and Selling Unregistered Securities</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-genesis-gemini-securities/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-genesis-gemini-securities/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 10:07:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[barry silbert]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cameron winklevoss]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dcg]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gemini]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[genesis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tyler winklevoss]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=232423</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-genesis-gemini-securities/">SEC Charges Genesis and Gemini for Offering and Selling Unregistered Securities</a></p>
<p>The SEC also revealed that Genesis and Gemini generated assets worth hundreds of dollars from hundreds of thousands of investors.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-genesis-gemini-securities/">SEC Charges Genesis and Gemini for Offering and Selling Unregistered Securities</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-genesis-gemini-securities/">SEC Charges Genesis and Gemini for Offering and Selling Unregistered Securities</a></p>
<p>On the 12th of January, the US Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) charged crypto exchange Gemini and crypto lending firm Genesis Global Capital with offering and selling unregistered securities. Both companies entered a deal in December 2020 to provide customers of the exchange company with a yield-bearing crypto product. After they reached an agreement, the product tagged Gemini Earn, which touted up to 8% yields for customers, was launched in February 2021. Per the agreement, Gemini customers would loan their crypto assets to Genesis while the crypto lending firm repays with interest.</p>
<h2>Sec Files Complaint against Genesis and Gemini</h2>
<p>As the SEC charges both Genesis and Gemini, the Commission <a href="https://www.sec.gov/news/press-release/2023-7" target="_blank" rel="noopener">claims</a> that the Earn program constitutes the offering and sales of securities that should have been registered. The agency explained that after Genesis sent a portion of the profits of the loan back to Gemini, the latter deducted an agent fee. According to the SEC, the agent fee sometimes could be more than 4%, after which the crypto exchange gives the balance to its users. SEC officials stated that Genesis should have registered the product as a securities offering.</p>
<p>Additionally, the SEC revealed that Genesis and Gemini generated assets worth hundreds of dollars from hundreds of thousands of investors. The agency has started an investigation to determine if the joint venture violated other securities laws. It also investigates if there are other entities and persons involved in the “alleged misconduct.” SEC boss Gary Gensler commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Today’s charges build on previous actions to make clear to the marketplace and the investing public that crypto lending platforms and other intermediaries need to comply with our time-tested securities laws. Doing so best protects investors. It promotes trust in markets. It’s not optional. It’s the law.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Meanwhile, Genesis announced on the 10th of November that it had about $172 million worth of funds in FTX, which recently crumbled. Its parent company Digital Currency Group (DCG), sent $140 million on the same day to help “strengthen its balance sheet.” However, it was not enough, as Genesis halted withdrawal a few days later, citing “unprecedented market turmoil.”</p>
<h2>Cameron Winklevoss Calls out DCG CEO</h2>
<p>This led to Gemini co-founder <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/cameron-winklevoss/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Cameron Winklevoss</a>&#8216;s claims that Genesis and DCG owe the exchange’s clients $900 million. The businessman wrote an <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cameron-winklevoss-accuses-barry-silbert/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">open letter</a> to DCG CEO Barry Silbert, stating that 349,000 Gemini Earn users are impacted by the withdrawal&#8217;s suspension. He added that Silbert has been engaging in bad faith despite Gemini&#8217;s effort to have a conversation about the situation.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/tyler-winklevoss/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tyler Winklevoss</a> of Gemini responded to the SEC complaint on Twitter, saying that:</p>
<blockquote><p>“It’s disappointing that the SEC chose to file an action today as Gemini and other creditors are working hard together to recover funds. This action does nothing to further our efforts and help Earn users get their assets back. Their behavior is counterproductive.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Read other <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/crypto/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">crypto market news</a> on Coinspeaker.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-com-mass-layoffs/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-genesis-gemini-securities/">SEC Charges Genesis and Gemini for Offering and Selling Unregistered Securities</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-genesis-gemini-securities/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>