<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 16:54:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>OVER GATE Console: Creating, Hosting, and Managing Metaverse Events</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/over-gate-console-creating-hosting-managing-metaverse-events/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/over-gate-console-creating-hosting-managing-metaverse-events/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 16:52:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[metaverse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[over]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OVER GATE Console]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=232563</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/over-gate-console-creating-hosting-managing-metaverse-events/">OVER GATE Console: Creating, Hosting, and Managing Metaverse Events</a></p>
<p>Metaverse decentralized infrastructure service provider OVER has launched its much-awaited OVER GATE Console as it seeks to play a more dominant role in the evolution of Web3.0 through the powers of Augmented Reality.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/over-gate-console-creating-hosting-managing-metaverse-events/">OVER GATE Console: Creating, Hosting, and Managing Metaverse Events</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/over-gate-console-creating-hosting-managing-metaverse-events/">OVER GATE Console: Creating, Hosting, and Managing Metaverse Events</a></p>
<p>The OVER GATE Console is designed to bring help users to create geo-localized experiences that will help in bridging the gap between the physical and digital worlds.</p>
<p>The <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-metaverse/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">metaverse</a> is currently growing beyond just a concept as more startups are now exploring new products and solutions to help the wider populace gain exposure to the new world. The OVER GATE Console will come off as one of the most advanced channels to enter the metaverse and will offer every user the opportunity to create customized meetings and events without limitations.</p>
<p>With its advanced interactive features, the OVER GATE Console supports every type of event ranging from DJ concerts to conferences and meetings. The metaverse accessibility tool is designed such that its desktop app permits users to conduct these meetings through their OVRLands, a piece of real estate in the OVER metaverse.</p>
<p>While owning land in OVER is an avenue to gain a unique appreciation of the OVER GATE Console, users can also download the desktop app for free and participate in meetings without having land of their own.</p>
<p>&#8220;OVER GATE console connects augmented reality experiences to real geographic locations and thus enables creators to augment the physical world,&#8221; said Davide Cuttini, co-founder and CEO of OVER. &#8220;This geo-realism is an exciting feature that breathes new life into AR. With OVER GATE, users can create unique experiences, play games, and participate in live metaverse events such as music festivals and virtual meetings.&#8221;</p>
<h2>OVER GATE Console Offers Enhanced Functionalities</h2>
<p>The OVER GATE Console offers an easy way to retain a dominant presence for meeting hosts in a way that has not really been seen before, however, attendees also benefit immensely from the thrilling features of the platform. Attendees of events hosted on OVER can join through their own Avatars.</p>
<p>These Avatars can be controlled through the user’s keypad and mouse, and the user’s personalities can be showcased through their Avatars. As a high-tech startup, users who want a more engaging and thrilling experience in the metaverse can also wear a motion-sensing tracksuit to teleport their entire body in the metaverse and stream its movements in real time.</p>
<p>One major mission that OVER has is to make the metaverse an accessible venue for everyone. While there are huge barriers to entry based on the current metaverse solutions around today, for users to experience the offerings from OVER, their mobile phones alone are enough to gain the right access to the OVRLands.</p>
<p>With the OVER GATE Console, users can be a part of thrilling fashion shows, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Non-Fungible Token</a> (NFT) art exhibitions, and other unique experiences to mention a few.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/eu-postpones-final-vote-mica/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/over-gate-console-creating-hosting-managing-metaverse-events/">OVER GATE Console: Creating, Hosting, and Managing Metaverse Events</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/over-gate-console-creating-hosting-managing-metaverse-events/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>EU Postpones Final Vote on MiCA Legislation Again Following Issues in Legal Document Translation</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/eu-postpones-final-vote-mica/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/eu-postpones-final-vote-mica/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 15:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mica]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=233032</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/eu-postpones-final-vote-mica/">EU Postpones Final Vote on MiCA Legislation Again Following Issues in Legal Document Translation</a></p>
<p>The EU deferred its final MiCA legislation vote for the second time in two months.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/eu-postpones-final-vote-mica/">EU Postpones Final Vote on MiCA Legislation Again Following Issues in Legal Document Translation</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/eu-postpones-final-vote-mica/">EU Postpones Final Vote on MiCA Legislation Again Following Issues in Legal Document Translation</a></p>
<p>The European Union (EU) has postponed the final vote on its Markets in Crypto Assets regulation (MiCA) until April this year. Due to a technical issue, the 27-member state intergovernmental union decided to defer the decisive vote on its highly anticipated crypto ruleset. Reports state that the guiding 400-page legal document could not be translated into the Union’s official 24 languages. It is mandatory that legal documents, such as the MiCA, comply with EU regulations that require publishing in all its 24 official languages.</p>
<p>By default, the Markets in Crypto Assets regulation rule book comes in an English Language draft.</p>
<p>The latest delay in the EU MiCA final vote marks the second occurrence in roughly two months. The supranational political and economic union previously postponed the ultimate vote from November last year to February 2023. The initial delay in November 2022 that resulted in a deferment to early 2023 was also due to translation issues. The recent delay implies that financial regulators in Europe must wait longer to draft legislative implementation rules. Notwithstanding, once the MiCA receives official approval, European financial regulators have up to 18 months to produce the technical standards.</p>
<p>Using MiCA as a framework, European policymakers also look to create a standard regulation to harmonize rules for crypto assets at the EU level. These projected harmonized guidelines could offer legal certainty to crypto assets not covered by existing EU legislation. The crypto regulation will lay guidelines for the operation, structure, and governance of digital asset token issuers. In addition, the said digital currency legislation also provides rules regarding transparency and disclosure requirements for crypto asset trading and issuance.</p>
<h2>EU Greenlit MiCA Legislation for Vote Two Years After Initial Proposal</h2>
<p>The European parliamentary committee <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-union-mica-crypto-regulation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">passed</a> the MiCA legislation last October, roughly two years after its initial introduction in September 2020. At the time, the approved MiCA <a href="https://data.consilium.europa.eu/doc/document/ST-13198-2022-INIT/en/pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">text</a> read in part:</p>
<blockquote><p>“It is important to ensure that the Union’s financial services legislation is fit for the digital age and contributes to a future-ready economy that works for the people, including by enabling the use of innovative technologies. The Union has a stated and confirmed policy interest in developing and promoting the uptake of transformative technologies in the financial sector, including distributed ledger technology (DLT).”</p></blockquote>
<p>In October, the EU parliament also approved an anti-money laundering bill focusing on the Transfer of Funds Regulation. This proposal seeks to ensure compliance standards regarding crypto assets.</p>
<h2>Bank of France Wants Stricter Crypto Regulations Ahead of MiCA Legislation</h2>
<p>In other recent news, the central bank of France has <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/central-bank-france-crypto-regulations-mica/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">agitated</a> for crypto regulations before the MiCA standards. Speaking on the need for the immediate imposition of stricter regulations for crypto firms, Bank of France governor Francois Villeroy de Galhau explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>“All the disorder in 2022 feeds a simple belief: it is desirable for France to move to an obligatory licensing of [Digital Asset Service Providers] DASP as soon as possible, rather than just registration”.</p></blockquote>
<p>Although obtaining a DASP in France is currently optional, Villeroy seeks to make it mandatory for crypto firms looking to operate there.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-halts-apple-glasses/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/eu-postpones-final-vote-mica/">EU Postpones Final Vote on MiCA Legislation Again Following Issues in Legal Document Translation</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/eu-postpones-final-vote-mica/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Apple Halts Development of Its Apple Glasses</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-halts-apple-glasses/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-halts-apple-glasses/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 14:48:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Virtual Reality & Augmented Reality News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Apple Glass]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AR/VR Headsets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[google]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=233035</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-halts-apple-glasses/">Apple Halts Development of Its Apple Glasses</a></p>
<p>While Apple has made it a more productive venture to focus its developmental efforts on AR/VR headsets and to find ways to make them more affordable, its focus is also on what the future of communication will evolve into eventually.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-halts-apple-glasses/">Apple Halts Development of Its Apple Glasses</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-halts-apple-glasses/">Apple Halts Development of Its Apple Glasses</a></p>
<p>American multinational technology giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/apple-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Apple Inc</a> (NASDAQ: AAPL) has indefinitely delayed the launch of its most revered Apple Glasses headsets. As first <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-01-18/apple-postpones-ar-glasses-plans-cheaper-mixed-reality-headset" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reported</a> by Bloomberg, the postponement was based on the fact that Apple is facing significant technical difficulties to develop the product at this time.</p>
<p>The news comes after about a year when Bloomberg shared an update that Apple is actually considering postponing the launch date of the AR headsets until this year. Much work has already been committed to the development of the AR Glasses, however, the company will slow down on its efforts in this regard.</p>
<p>The AR Headsets are designed to work like the Google Glass smart glasses that are lightweight and offer digital representation that is overlaid with the real world as compared to the virtual world as presented by its Augmented Reality/Virtual Reality (AR/VR) headsets. The argument for starting work on the Apple Glass focuses on the fact that the AR headsets are too bogus and are not convenient for use outdoors.</p>
<p>With the indefinite push of its possible debut day, Apple has reportedly stopped its active work on the product and has tasked its AR team to intensify work on the AR headsets.</p>
<p>Amongst the major challenges experienced by Apple in its plans to float an AR headset involves securing the right hardware to produce a lightweight headset as well as getting the right battery that can power the device just like the iPhone. Despite the notable halt in active development, the sources who spoke to Bloomberg affirmed that the company still sees the Apple Glasses as a product that has what it takes to truly replace the iPhone in the near future.</p>
<h2>Apple Glasses and the Metaverse Push</h2>
<p>For the majority of the tech giants around the world, projecting into the future comes off as one of the most important research and development works they can ever get focus on today.</p>
<p>While Apple has made it a more productive venture to focus its developmental efforts on AR/VR headsets and to find ways to make them more affordable, its focus is also on what the future of communication will evolve into eventually.</p>
<p>Based on the current trend, many believe the metaverse is the next frontier in social communications. While <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/meta/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Meta Platforms Inc</a> (NASDAQ: META) has changed its name and corporate ideology to focus on metaverse-related products, other tech giants are also exploring avenues to plug into this new niche with the next iteration of their products.</p>
<p>Apple is known not to share many details about its products until when it launched, and while the production of the Apple Glasses that it considers are more sustainable is being halted, there is confidence that it will heighten its research into the metaverse and make its pivot whenever it considers as the right time.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-415-million-hack/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-halts-apple-glasses/">Apple Halts Development of Its Apple Glasses</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-halts-apple-glasses/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>FTX Identifies $415 Million Hack amongst Recoverable $5.5 Billion Digital Assets</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-415-million-hack/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-415-million-hack/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 14:41:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cybersecurity News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance zh]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[changpeng zhao]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sam bankman-fried]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sbf]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=233030</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-415-million-hack/">FTX Identifies $415 Million Hack amongst Recoverable $5.5 Billion Digital Assets</a></p>
<p>Embattled crypto exchange FTX fingered a $415 million hack from November as part of assets recovered to pay off creditors.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-415-million-hack/">FTX Identifies $415 Million Hack amongst Recoverable $5.5 Billion Digital Assets</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-415-million-hack/">FTX Identifies $415 Million Hack amongst Recoverable $5.5 Billion Digital Assets</a></p>
<p>Fallen crypto exchange <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a> has <a href="https://www.bbc.com/news/business-64313624" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">identified</a> a $415 million crypto hack as part of the $5.5 billion worth of digital assets for recovery. In a statement, the exchange&#8217;s new CEO, John Ray III, said it took extensive investigative efforts from the team to achieve this revelation.</p>
<p>On Tuesday, FTX also provided further details revealing that it had recovered $1.7 billion in cash and $3.5 billion in liquid crypto. In addition, the former second-largest crypto exchange in the world also recovered $300 million in liquid securities.</p>
<p>In a statement on Tuesday, Ray noted:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We are making important progress in our efforts to maximize recoveries, and it has taken a Herculean investigative effort from our team to uncover this preliminary information.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>FTX Looks to Claw Back $2.1 Billion Binance Repurchase Payment in Addition to $415 Million &#8216;Hack&#8217; Sum</h2>
<p>In addition to the $415 million hack that FTX tries to recover, the bankrupt company is also examining another possible asset recovery. According to reports, FTX&#8217;s advisors are reviewing a $2.1 billion share repurchase payment from the exchange to rival <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a> in Q3 2021. Although Binance was FTX&#8217;s first outside investor, the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/changpeng-zhao/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Changpeng Zhao</a>-led firm eventually sold its stake back to FTX in 2021.</p>
<p>Zhao trusted his lawyers when asked whether the potential $2.1 billion clawback is part of FTX&#8217;s bankruptcy proceedings. He said, &#8220;I think we&#8217;ll leave that to the lawyers. I think our legal team is perfectly capable of handling it.&#8221;</p>
<p>Lawyers and advisors representing FTX debtors updated recovery-bound identifiable total liquid assets in a presentation titled &#8220;Maximizing FTX Recoveries.&#8221; The total value of said recoverable assets is $5.5 billion, including &#8220;unauthorized third-party transfers&#8221; of $323 million of the international business &#8211; FTX.com. In addition, the $5 billion ballpark figure identified by the FTX debtor legal team also includes $90 million from FTX US. Furthermore, the embattled crypto exchange alleges that it lost another $2 million in crypto belonging to sister firm Alameda Research. According to FTX, this missing crypto ties to the November hack of its systems following its dramatic collapse.</p>
<p>At the time of the hack, the stolen FTX crypto was $477 million in value, according to blockchain analytics firm Elliptic. Also, despite the recent spate of asset recoveries, FTX did not estimate total liabilities. Since early November, the bankrupt exchange&#8217;s FTT token has been at a 90% drawdown.</p>
<h2>SBF Alleged Financial Misappropriation</h2>
<p>Disgraced former FTX chief executive <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/sam-bankman-fried/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Sam Bankman-Fried</a> has also been accused of diverting billions of dollars of users&#8217; funds to Alameda Research. These accusations allege that SBF channeled the vast sums to the liquidity-based crypto trading platform to offset debts. However, the once-celebrated crypto wunderkind has since <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sbf-pleads-not-guilty-us-charges/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">denied</a> any of the fraud charges against him.</p>
<p>SBF is due in court again on October 2nd when his trial begins, and he faces an eight-count criminal charge. These include wire fraud and misuse of customers&#8217; funds. If found guilty, the once-admired &#8216;crypto hero&#8217; faces up to 115 years in federal prison.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-halt-operations-japan/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-415-million-hack/">FTX Identifies $415 Million Hack amongst Recoverable $5.5 Billion Digital Assets</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-415-million-hack/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase to Halt Operations in Japan Following Crypto Underperformance</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-halt-operations-japan/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-halt-operations-japan/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 11:57:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brian armstrong]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=232995</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-halt-operations-japan/">Coinbase to Halt Operations in Japan Following Crypto Underperformance</a></p>
<p>Coinbase says that its customers in Japan have a 1-month deadline to withdraw all holdings, as operations would cease after that. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-halt-operations-japan/">Coinbase to Halt Operations in Japan Following Crypto Underperformance</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-halt-operations-japan/">Coinbase to Halt Operations in Japan Following Crypto Underperformance</a></p>
<p>According to recent reports, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase Global Inc</a> (NASDAQ: COIN) is halting operations in Japan due to volatile market conditions. The leading American crypto exchange also <a href="https://www.coinbase.com/blog/halting-operations-in-japan" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a> it would conduct a “complete review of our business in [Japan].”</p>
<p>Coinbase, which promised to make the transition in Japan as smooth as possible, also said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“We want to assure you that we have segregated the Japanese Yen and crypto assets of our customers in custody in compliance with the regulations, and we are committed to ensuring that all our customers can withdraw their assets at their earliest convenience.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Following the suspension of operations, Coinbase Japan customers have until February 16th to pull out their fiat and crypto holdings. According to the leading crypto exchange, customers can withdraw their crypto holdings to various available options. These alternatives include other Virtual Assets Service Providers, Coinbase Wallet, or any other self-hosted wallet of the customer’s choice. In addition, clients can liquidate their portfolio and withdraw the resulting fiat sum to a domestic bank account.</p>
<p>Coinbase also warned that it would convert any remaining crypto, on or after February 17th, to yen. Furthermore, the exchange could send any remaining cash to a guaranty account at the Legal Affairs Bureau in the succeeding month.</p>
<h2>Coinbase Intent to Pull Out of Japan Underscores Bleak Crypto Market Situation</h2>
<p>Coinbase’s decision to halt operations in Japan comes on the heels of a similar move made by fellow US exchange <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/kraken/">Kraken</a> in the country. Less than a month ago, Kraken <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/kraken-stop-operations-japan/">announced</a> that it would cease operations in Japan by January as part of its cost-cutting measures. At the time of the announcement, the San Francisco-based company cited a weak global crypto market as a reason. Coinbase’s own cessation of operations in Japan due to a digital asset slump also underscores the industry’s present state of affairs.</p>
<p>The Coinbase-Japan development also comes after the exchange <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-layoff-crypto-meltdown/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">cut down</a> its global headcount by 20% to preserve cash. Last week, Coinbase chief executive officer <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/brian-armstrong/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Brian Armstrong</a> explained the need for the substantial staff layoff. In his opinion, the exchange had to improve its odds of surviving in an <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a>-triggered “stress test scenario.” Referring to the FTX collapse and subsequent crypto crunch as a “black eye for the industry,” Armstrong suggested the worst still lay ahead. In his own estimations:</p>
<blockquote><p>“We may not have seen the last of it &#8211; there will be increased scrutiny on various companies in the space to make sure that they’re following the rules. Long term, that’s a good thing. But short term, there’s still a lot of market fear.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Most of the crypto market woes, which characterized much of last year, have also crossed over into the new year. These include waning investor appetite for digital assets, soaring interest rates, and fears of a full-blown global economic recession. Several investors have already fled riskier assets such as crypto and tech stocks. This trend has resulted in mass selloffs of said assets, inadvertently setting them downward.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/dogecoin-doge-carbon-footprint-reduce/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-halt-operations-japan/">Coinbase to Halt Operations in Japan Following Crypto Underperformance</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-halt-operations-japan/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dogecoin DOGE Sees Its Carbon Footprint Reduce by 25%, Here’s Why</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/dogecoin-doge-carbon-footprint-reduce/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/dogecoin-doge-carbon-footprint-reduce/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 11:36:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[doge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogecoin (doge)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[shib]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[shiba inu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[shiba inu (shib)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=232989</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/dogecoin-doge-carbon-footprint-reduce/">Dogecoin DOGE Sees Its Carbon Footprint Reduce by 25%, Here&#8217;s Why</a></p>
<p>DOGE may have been particularly focused on environmental sustainability - one of the most topical issues of the blockchain industry.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/dogecoin-doge-carbon-footprint-reduce/">Dogecoin DOGE Sees Its Carbon Footprint Reduce by 25%, Here&#8217;s Why</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/dogecoin-doge-carbon-footprint-reduce/">Dogecoin DOGE Sees Its Carbon Footprint Reduce by 25%, Here&#8217;s Why</a></p>
<p>Recent <a href="https://forexsuggest.com/global-impact-of-cryptocurrency-trading/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">research</a> from Forex Suggest has shown that Dogecoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/dogecoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">DOGE</a>) was able to reduce its carbon footprint by a whopping 25% in just a year. DOGE was the only meme coin to achieve this feat in 2022.</p>
<p>Carbon footprint remains a key metric for mainstream adoption and over the years, several debates have risen over the high energy demands of some networks. That was one of the main reasons why billionaire <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/tesla/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tesla</a> CEO <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/elon-musk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Elon Musk</a> took a stance against accepting Bitcoin BTC payments for his Tesla products. Instead, he opted for Dogecoin and <a href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1392974251011895300?t=Zx33JB2nJBnO8gECn7lkZQ&amp;s=19" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">noted</a> that the &#8220;silly joke&#8221; coin was a better alternative for transactions.</p>
<p>Now with the combined proactive efforts of Musk, developers, and the broader Dogecoin community, DOGE reportedly shed its annual carbon emissions by 25%. That is, it produced 1,063 tons of emissions in 2022 as opposed to the 1,423 tons released in the previous year.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Ethereum was by far, the most successful in reducing its carbon emissions in 2022. The network <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/merge-ethereum-proof-of-stake/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">transitioned</a> to a proof-of-stake consensus mechanism in September, causing its energy consumption to reduce greatly.</p>
<h2>Dogecoin DOGE Tipped as Viable Financial Instrument for 2023</h2>
<p>Owing to the reduced carbon footprint and robust support from its very large community, Dogecoin has now positioned itself as one of the best choices of financial instruments in 2023.</p>
<p>Its performance for the year was also encouraging. As most top assets of the crypto markets bled out in 2022, DOGE held its own, outperforming them throughout the year-long bear market.</p>
<p>The memecoin was the third best-performing coin from the top 10 list.  It came closely behind XRP and BNB who took the first and second spots respectively.</p>
<p>Perhaps the most interesting part of DOGE&#8217;s amazing year is that it also outperformed its biggest rival, Shiba Inu SHIB. SHIB on the other hand had its focus set on building a layer-2 network and taking its metaverse ambitions a notch higher.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/deloitte-audit-usdc-issuer-circle/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/dogecoin-doge-carbon-footprint-reduce/">Dogecoin DOGE Sees Its Carbon Footprint Reduce by 25%, Here&#8217;s Why</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/dogecoin-doge-carbon-footprint-reduce/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Deloitte Set to Audit USDC Issuer Circle</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/deloitte-audit-usdc-issuer-circle/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/deloitte-audit-usdc-issuer-circle/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Babafemi Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 11:20:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[circle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[deloitte]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mastercard]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stripe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[usd coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[usdc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[visa]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=232792</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/deloitte-audit-usdc-issuer-circle/">Deloitte Set to Audit USDC Issuer Circle</a></p>
<p>Circle reassured the USDC holders and the general public that it remained committed to transparency.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/deloitte-audit-usdc-issuer-circle/">Deloitte Set to Audit USDC Issuer Circle</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/deloitte-audit-usdc-issuer-circle/">Deloitte Set to Audit USDC Issuer Circle</a></p>

<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/usd-coin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">USDC</a> issuer, Circle, has announced that it will be audited by Deloitte in the future instead of Grant Thornton. According to the firm, its last audit covers 2019,2020, and 2021 and has been filed publicly with the Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>). The statement formed part of the <a href="https://6778953.fs1.hubspotusercontent-na1.net/hubfs/6778953/PDFs/2301StateofUSDCEconomy_Web.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">state of the USDC economy report</a>, which it released on Tuesday.</p>
<h2>Deloitte May Be the First</h2>
<p>Since the collapse of FTX, there has been an increased call for the transparency of crypto companies. This has led many of the firms to publish Proof of Reserves and also to perform external audits. However, in December, reports emerged that none of the Big 4 accounting firms (Deloitte, Ernst &amp; Young, KPMG, and PricewaterhouseCoopers) was willing to involve themselves.</p>
<p>Likewise, accounting firms like Mazars Group and Armanino halted auditing services for their crypto clients last month. Mazars, which audited <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a>, Crypto.com, and KuCoin ceased its services due to public sentiment. Consequently, there&#8217;s been a concern that mainstream accounting firms will not be able to provide the necessary audits to retain and restore investor confidence in crypto companies.</p>
<p>Thus, the announcement of Deloitte as Circle’s new auditor has sparked excitement among cryptocurrency enthusiasts. <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/circle/">Circle</a> also reassured the USDC holders and the general public that it remained committed to transparency. It stated that it will continue to provide open and timely reporting of how the firm reduces risk and maintains liquidity in its reserve.</p>
<h2>Stablecoins Are the Next Big Thing</h2>
<p>Circle CEO <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/jeremy-allaire/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Jeremy Allaire</a> believes that stablecoins like USDC represent the thing among crypto assets. He noted a need for a “shift in the utility value phase of blockchains and programmable composable always-on money.”</p>
<p>He noted that embracing stablecoins has nothing to do with competing with the traditional financial system. Rather, Allaire stated that it was about doing what the traditional system could not do.</p>
<p>Specifically, he highlighted the potential to reduce costs expended on payments. He also highlighted the growing interest of merchants in the evolution. Allaire shared that traditional payment providers like <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/mastercard/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Mastercard</a>, Stripe, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/visa-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Visa</a>, and Checkout.com were already partnering with the firm to make this happen.</p>
<p>Recognizing the potential of stablecoins, the US Congress is also set to pass a stablecoin legislation.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-information-crypto-miners/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/deloitte-audit-usdc-issuer-circle/">Deloitte Set to Audit USDC Issuer Circle</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/deloitte-audit-usdc-issuer-circle/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Here’s How US SEC Released Personal Information of Crypto Miners during Investigation</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-information-crypto-miners/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-information-crypto-miners/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 11:14:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gemini]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[genesis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[green]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[us sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=232973</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-information-crypto-miners/">Here&#8217;s How US SEC Released Personal Information of Crypto Miners during Investigation</a></p>
<p>The SEC has reportedly violated its own privacy act while disclosing information of miners on the Green blockchain network. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-information-crypto-miners/">Here&#8217;s How US SEC Released Personal Information of Crypto Miners during Investigation</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-information-crypto-miners/">Here&#8217;s How US SEC Released Personal Information of Crypto Miners during Investigation</a></p>
<p>During their recent investigation, the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) reportedly leaked the names and email addresses of all the crypto miners connected to the blockchain firm Green.</p>
<p>On Tuesday, January 17, the Washington Examiner <a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/technology/sec-official-accidentally-leaks-personal-information-of-crypto-community" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reported</a> that the SEC unintentionally included 650 names and email addresses of miners during its email communication with Green. As a result, it left the blockchain&#8217;s nodes vulnerable to hacks. Since then, the securities regulator has been reaching out to Green users regarding their purchases of the blockchain firm&#8217;s products. The SEC website notes:</p>
<blockquote><p>“The Privacy Act of 1974 [&#8230;] prohibits the disclosure without consent of information about individuals that the federal government maintains in a system of records. If we store information about you in a system of records from which we retrieve that information by personal identifier [&#8230;] we will safeguard your information in accordance with the Privacy Act.”</p></blockquote>
<p>While hackers have been always targeting centralized exchanges for getting their customer information, such unintentional leaks by government officials haven&#8217;t appeared in the past.</p>
<p>Post major collapse during the crypto winter of 2022, the US SEC has turned aggressive in its approach to the crypto crackdown. The securities regulator has executed several crackdowns over the last year and critics have often called out the agency for taking a “regulation by enforcement” approach.</p>
<p>Last month, the SEC also involved itself in the case of the collapse of the crypto exchange FTX alleging the violation of the anti-fraud provision of the securities laws.</p>
<h2>SEC&#8217;s Growing Attention in Crypto</h2>
<p>The US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has been putting up growing attention to the developments taking place in the crypto market recently. The crypto mining firms have been on their radar as they face severe headwinds due to the collapse of the crypto market last year.</p>
<p>In the latest development, the SEC has charged both &#8211; Genesis and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/gemini/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Gemini</a> &#8211; over the allegations of violating the securities laws through the sale of unregistered securities.</p>
<p>“Today’s charges build on previous actions to make clear to the marketplace and the investing public that crypto lending platforms and other intermediaries need to comply with our time-tested securities laws. Doing so best protects investors. It promotes trust in markets. It’s not optional. It’s the law,&#8221; they <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-genesis-gemini-securities/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">noted</a>.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-developments-watch-out-for-2023/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-information-crypto-miners/">Here&#8217;s How US SEC Released Personal Information of Crypto Miners during Investigation</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-information-crypto-miners/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Developments to Watch Out for in 2023</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-developments-watch-out-for-2023/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-developments-watch-out-for-2023/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andy Watson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 11:08:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth 2.0]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum 2.0]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nft]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=232895</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-developments-watch-out-for-2023/">Crypto Developments to Watch Out for in 2023</a></p>
<p>While not on a massive scale yet, 2023 saw crypto take more steps into mass adoption.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-developments-watch-out-for-2023/">Crypto Developments to Watch Out for in 2023</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-developments-watch-out-for-2023/">Crypto Developments to Watch Out for in 2023</a></p>
<p>The past year has been a massive year for cryptocurrencies once again. There have been several highs and huge breakthroughs, as well as a few lows. However, 2023 can be seen as a year in which crypto took another step forward.</p>
<p>Whether you want to <a href="https://www.oanda.com/us-en/trading/cryptocurrencies/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">trade cryptocurrency</a>, invest, or simply want a new way to buy and use services and products, some of these developments are set to transform the world of crypto in 2023 and beyond.</p>
<h2>Ethereum 2.0</h2>
<p><a href="https://www.forbes.com/uk/advisor/investing/cryptocurrency/what-is-ethereum-2/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Ethereum 2.0</a> is the next stage of Ethereum that was “finalized” a little while ago. ETH 2.0 wasn’t a singular release but rather a change that has happened over the past few years. One of the biggest changes it has brought is incredible transaction speed.</p>
<p>One of the most frustrating problems is the time it takes for transactions and crypto trades to be processed; ETH 2.0 has revolutionized transaction speeds by allowing up to 100,000 transactions a second. While this is only part of the Ethereum evolution, it is set to have a broad effect across many crypto-based systems.</p>
<h2>El Salvador</h2>
<p>One of the biggest hurdles crypto has faced over the past few years is the lack of mass adoption. While some companies have begun accepting crypto as payment, it hasn’t reached the level of being a recognized currency in a country.</p>
<p>El Salvador took the step to recognize <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> as a legal tender, and while it hasn’t been without hiccups, it shows that adoption at this size is possible. This has been seen as the first step towards adoption globally.</p>
<h2>Machankura</h2>
<p>Africa has fallen behind the rest of the world in terms of crypto-adoption simply due to the lack of internet access, computers, and smartphones. However, a developer in Africa has created a ground-breaking solution for this problem.</p>
<p>Machankura is an app for non-smartphones that allows users to trade cryptocurrencies, namely Bitcoin. The platform works over text messages and eliminates the need for the internet, as mobile access is the only thing necessary.</p>
<h2>Rise of DeFi</h2>
<p>DeFi, or decentralized finance, is the combination of traditional financial systems and the blockchain. Using smart contracts and the blockchain, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-decentralized-finance-defi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">DeFi</a> enables us to send money at lightning speed with no intermediaries.</p>
<p>DeFi also eliminates all the fees associated with banking and instead uses a peer-to-peer system. DeFi uses automated machines, which replace what a bank would do altogether.</p>
<h2>NFTs</h2>
<p>NFTs have been on a rollercoaster over the past couple of years. Many people view them as a scam or a way for the rich to hide their wealth; while this is true in some cases, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NFTs</a> have a lot more versatility than you may think.</p>
<p>NFTs can offer a lot for multiple industries, including gaming. Developers want players to own what they earn in a game. Fortnite is a great example; skins don’t have any real value but turning them into NFTs allows them to be traded and earn their owner&#8217;s real money.</p>
<h2>Wider Adoption</h2>
<p>While not on a massive scale yet, 2023 saw <a href="https://medium.com/@cuemby/the-mass-adoption-of-cryptocurrency-in-countries-why-is-it-happening-and-how-is-it-possible-c25954e20228" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">crypto take more steps into mass adoption</a>. Businesses across the globe are allowing customers to use cryptocurrency to buy goods or services they provide.</p>
<p>Regulation is also part of the adoption process. With crypto regulations becoming more and more talked about and common, mass adoption has quickly become a question of “when” and not “if.”</p>
<h2>Company Tokens</h2>
<p>Many companies and institutions have viewed coins like Bitcoin and Ethereum as being too unstable and unreliable in a way. Therefore, they have taken the step to create their own tokens instead of adapting existing ones.</p>
<p>This allows them to have more control over the value of said coins while still being part of the cryptocurrency blockchain ecosystem and allowing their customers to use crypto to buy products.</p>
<h2>Greater Protection</h2>
<p>After the recent FTX disaster, consumer protection has become a hot topic again. Part of regulating crypto will ensure crypto traders are better protected when buying and selling on platforms.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gameswift-casper-network-web3-0-gaming/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-developments-watch-out-for-2023/">Crypto Developments to Watch Out for in 2023</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-developments-watch-out-for-2023/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>GameSwift and Casper Network Partner to Boost Web 3.0 Gaming</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/gameswift-casper-network-web3-0-gaming/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/gameswift-casper-network-web3-0-gaming/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 10:55:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gaming News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[casper network]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[GameSwift]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web3]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=232550</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gameswift-casper-network-web3-0-gaming/">GameSwift and Casper Network Partner to Boost Web 3.0 Gaming</a></p>
<p>While existing users Casper Network and GameSwift have been enjoying unique offerings from their individual ecosystems, the partnership of both networks will offer additional value that will greatly improve their gaming experience.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gameswift-casper-network-web3-0-gaming/">GameSwift and Casper Network Partner to Boost Web 3.0 Gaming</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gameswift-casper-network-web3-0-gaming/">GameSwift and Casper Network Partner to Boost Web 3.0 Gaming</a></p>
<p><a href="https://gameswift.io/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">GameSwift</a>, a Web3.0 gaming ecosystem and infrastructure service provider has announced it has entered into a strategic partnership with Layer-1 blockchain protocol, Casper Network. According to a Press Release shared with Coinspeaker, the partnership is mutually beneficial and will bring a whole new opportunity to users in both communities.</p>
<p>GameSwift has been awarded a grant by the Casper Network, and it will be integrating its infrastructure into the Casper Network. Casper Network is a<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/how-to-stake-in-cryptocurrency/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"> Proof-of-Stake</a> (PoS) protocol that is <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/casper-network-cspr-token-volatility/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">specifically designed</a> to power mainstream adoption of some of Web 3.0’s most demanded features.</p>
<p>It has the needed substrate to help scale GameSwift and upon the integration, Casper users and wallet owners can connect to the gaming protocol and gain access to all of its hosted gaming titles.</p>
<p>In the current world of Web 3.0 gaming, there are several intricacies involved including the custody of in-game assets, and the connection to decentralized wallets, all of which to this point have not been made user-friendly. The GameSwift and Casper Network collaboration seeks to resolve some of these key challenges such as wallet connection and all the drudgery associated with accessing and transferring assets to play blockchain games will be automatically eliminated.</p>
<p>With both platforms innovators in the Web3 space in their own rights, the partnership will also see them enjoy technical expertise from each other, especially in the aspect of scaling to onboard the next billion users into the Web3 gaming world.</p>
<h2>Casper Is a Perfect Fit for GameSwift</h2>
<p>GameSwift as a Web3.0 gaming service provider is composed of four key pillars including Chain, Web3 Infrastructure, Platform, and Gaming Studio. Each of these pillars is crucial to the ecosystem.GameSwift&#8217;s original infrastructure facilitates implementing and using blockchain technology for game developers and players.</p>
<p>The protocol is secured by the Polygon Layer-2 network, making its alliance with Casper Network. Casper Network made its debut as one of the most energy-efficient blockchain protocols and with its low energy footprint, it will help GameSwift advance its mission to stay fully Carbon neutral.</p>
<p>While existing users of both Casper Network and GameSwift have been enjoying unique offerings from their individual ecosystems, the partnership of both networks will offer additional value that will greatly improve their gaming experience. New users entering the world of Web 3.0 gaming will also find the integration and its associated capabilities a major improvement in easing the drudgery involved in playing blockchain games, especially, if they have tried other platforms prior to experiencing GameSwift.</p>
<p>Both protocols are committed to maximizing the unique offering of this partnership and will be making further announcements the near term.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/roblox-jumps-december-2022-metrics/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gameswift-casper-network-web3-0-gaming/">GameSwift and Casper Network Partner to Boost Web 3.0 Gaming</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/gameswift-casper-network-web3-0-gaming/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>