<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
>

<channel>
	<title>CoinCu News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://coincu.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coincu.com</link>
	<description>Coin and Crypto Infomation Update</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 07:33:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/cropped-Screen-Shot-2022-05-31-at-14.56.39-32x32.png</url>
	<title>CoinCu News</title>
	<link>https://coincu.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Amount Of Crypto Venture Capital Investment In June Was Only $520M: Report</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/199649-crypto-venture-capital-investment-in-june/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Harold]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 05:59:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto venture capital]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gensyn AI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hashkey Capital]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mythical Games]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shima Capital]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[VC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=199649</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Venture capital investment in crypto companies has decreased by more than 70% in the last year, according to statistics provided by crypto analytics source RootData.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>Venture capital investment in crypto companies has dropped by over 70% in the past year.</em></li>



<li><em>In June 2023, only $520 million was raised by 83 crypto projects, making it the lowest month for financing so far.</em></li>



<li><em>Infrastructure, CeFi, and gaming were the top three categories receiving funding, with Coinbase Ventures being the most active VC firm in the space.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Venture capital investment in crypto companies has decreased by more than 70% in the last year, according to statistics provided by crypto analytics source <a href="https://www.rootdata.com/dashboard" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">RootData</a>.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-116.png"><img decoding="async" width="959" height="639" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-116.png" alt="image 116" class="wp-image-199653" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-116.png 959w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-116-300x200.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-116-768x512.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-116-750x500.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 959px) 100vw, 959px" title="The Amount Of Crypto Venture Capital Investment In June Was Only $520M: Report 1"></a></figure></div>


<p>The digital asset market raised $1.81 billion in 149 rounds of funding in June 2022, whereas just 83 projects raised $520 million in June this year, the lowest month for financing thus far.</p>



<p>According to RootData, the infrastructure category topped the way with $213 million in financing for 26 projects in June. This is still a drop of almost 50% from May when 28 projects received $410 million. The category was won by Gensyn AI, a UK-based business, which received $43 million in a Series A investment headed by a16z.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-117.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="457" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-117-1024x457.png" alt="image 117" class="wp-image-199654" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-117-1024x457.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-117-300x134.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-117-768x343.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-117-1536x686.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-117-2048x914.png 2048w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-117-750x335.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-117-1140x509.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="The Amount Of Crypto Venture Capital Investment In June Was Only $520M: Report 2"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"><em>Source: RootData</em></figcaption></figure></div>


<p>CeFi (centralized finance) received $101 million in funding, accounting for approximately 20% of total financing. Gaming came in third with $62 million, with more than half of it going to Mythical Games, which received $37 million in Series C1. In that order, DeFi and NFTs finish up the list of categories.</p>



<p>Coinbase Ventures is the most active VC, having participated in 71 rounds this year, according to the site, followed by Hashkey Capital and Shima Capital, which funded 54 and 49 startups, respectively. The once-promising crypto asset class has taken a back seat to other assets, notably artificial intelligence.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large is-resized"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-118-1024x457.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-118-1024x457.png" alt="image 118" class="wp-image-199655" width="1024" height="457" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-118-1024x457.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-118-300x134.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-118-768x343.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-118-1536x686.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-118-2048x914.png 2048w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-118-750x335.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-118-1140x509.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="The Amount Of Crypto Venture Capital Investment In June Was Only $520M: Report 3"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"><em>Source: RootData</em></figcaption></figure></div>


<p>During the last year, Ethereum has had 1,826 projects financed, whereas Polygon has seen 1,076 rounds. When the money was broken down by location, the United States got 34% of the total, the largest of any nation on the list.</p>



<p>According to <a href="https://coincu.com/199477-vcs-crypto-funding-in-june-hits-lowest-2-years/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">WuBlockchain&#8217;s monthly report</a>, there were 83 public investments by crypto VCs in June, a 14% decrease from May (97 projects) and a 44% decrease year on year (149 projects as of June 2022). In June, the infrastructure category accounted for around 31% of financed projects, DeFi for approximately 18%, CeFi for approximately 8%, and NFT/GameFi for approximately 20%.</p>



<p>Venture investors have continued a trend that started in 2022, despite controversies in the cryptocurrency business. The news of regulatory uncertainty, market downturns, and extraordinary collapses pushed venture investors out of the business.</p>



<p>The SEC filed two cases against the two biggest cryptocurrency exchanges in the market, Binance and Coinbase, in early June, shaking the cryptocurrency business and wiping out billions of dollars in assets of SEC billionaires in this field. Moreover, with the Fed still debating rate rises, venture capital companies may be less interested in investing in a very risky sector.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER: </em></strong><em>The information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>



<p>Join us to keep track of news:&nbsp;<a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Harold</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Coincu</strong> <strong>News</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-115-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>What Is Average True Range (ATR)?</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/199639-what-is-average-true-range-atr/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Annie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 05:24:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Knowledge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ATR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Average True Range]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technical Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=199639</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Average True Range (ATR) is a technical analysis indicator used to measure the volatility or the degree of price movement in a financial instrument, such as stocks, commodities, or currencies, over a specific period of time. ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">What Is Average True Range?</h2>


<div class="wp-block-image is-style-default">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-112.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="874" height="558" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-112.png" alt="What Is Average True Range (ATR)?" class="wp-image-199645" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-112.png 874w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-112-300x192.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-112-768x490.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-112-750x479.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 874px) 100vw, 874px" title="What Is Average True Range (ATR)? 4"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>Average True Range (ATR) is a technical analysis indicator used to measure the volatility or the degree of price movement in a financial instrument, such as stocks, commodities, or currencies, over a specific period of time. It was developed by J. Welles Wilder and introduced in his book &#8220;New Concepts in Technical Trading Systems.&#8221;</p>



<p>The ATR calculates the average range between the high and low prices of an asset over a given number of periods. It considers any gaps between consecutive periods and incorporates these into the calculation. The ATR is typically presented as a value or a percentage of the asset&#8217;s current price.</p>



<p>Traders and analysts use the ATR to gain insights into the potential volatility and range of price movement for an asset. A higher ATR value suggests greater volatility, while a lower ATR value indicates lower volatility. Traders may use the ATR to determine stop-loss levels, set profit targets, or identify potential breakout points.</p>



<p>To calculate the ATR, the following steps are generally followed:</p>



<ol>
<li>Calculate the true range (ATR) for each period. The true range is the greatest of the following three values:
<ul>
<li>The difference between the current period&#8217;s high and low prices.</li>



<li>The absolute value of the difference between the current period&#8217;s high and the previous period&#8217;s close.</li>



<li>The absolute value of the difference between the current period&#8217;s low and the previous period&#8217;s close.</li>
</ul>
</li>



<li>Determine the average true range (ATR) over the desired number of periods by calculating the moving average of the true range values. Typically, a 14-day period is commonly used, but this can be adjusted based on the trader&#8217;s preference or the characteristics of the asset being analyzed.</li>
</ol>



<p>The ATR is a useful tool for assessing volatility and making informed trading decisions. However, it should be used in conjunction with other technical indicators and fundamental analysis to form a comprehensive trading strategy.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Importance of ATR</h2>


<div class="wp-block-image is-style-default">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-110.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="602" height="345" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-110.png" alt="What Is Average True Range (ATR)?" class="wp-image-199643" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-110.png 602w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-110-300x172.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" title="What Is Average True Range (ATR)? 5"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>The Average True Range (ATR) is an important tool for traders and analysts due to its several key benefits and applications:</p>



<ol>
<li>Volatility Measurement: ATR provides a reliable measure of price volatility. By understanding the level of volatility in an asset, traders can adjust their trading strategies accordingly. High ATR values indicate higher volatility, suggesting larger price swings and potentially increased risk. Conversely, low ATR values indicate lower volatility, implying more stable price movements.</li>



<li>Stop Loss Placement: ATR helps traders determine appropriate stop-loss levels for their trades. By setting stop-loss orders based on the ATR, traders can account for the natural fluctuations in price and avoid being prematurely stopped out by minor price movements. Wider stop-loss levels can be set for assets with higher ATR, while tighter levels can be used for low-volatility assets.</li>



<li>Position Sizing: ATR can assist traders in determining the appropriate position size for their trades. By considering the ATR value, traders can adjust their position sizes based on their risk tolerance and the level of volatility in the market. Higher ATR values may warrant smaller position sizes to limit potential losses, while lower ATR values may allow for larger position sizes.</li>



<li>Trend Identification: ATR can be used to identify periods of increasing or decreasing volatility, which can be indicative of changes in market trends. A rising ATR may suggest a strengthening trend or an upcoming breakout, while a declining ATR may indicate a weakening trend or a period of consolidation. Traders can use this information to make informed decisions about entering or exiting positions.</li>



<li>Breakout Strategies: ATR is often employed in breakout trading strategies. Breakouts occur when prices move beyond established support or resistance levels. Traders can use the ATR to set appropriate entry points for breakout trades. By incorporating the ATR into their strategies, traders can adjust their entry levels based on the current volatility, potentially improving their chances of capturing significant price moves.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">How To Calculate ATR? </h2>


<div class="wp-block-image is-style-default">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-111.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="576" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-111-1024x576.png" alt="What Is Average True Range (ATR)?" class="wp-image-199644" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-111-1024x576.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-111-300x169.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-111-768x432.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-111-750x422.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-111-1140x641.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-111.png 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="What Is Average True Range (ATR)? 6"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>The Average True Range (ATR) is calculated using the following steps:</p>



<ol>
<li>Calculate the True Range (TR) for each period:<ul><li>TR = max(high &#8211; low, abs(high &#8211; previous close), abs(low &#8211; previous close))</li></ul>The True Range is determined by taking the highest value among three calculations: a) The difference between the high and low prices of the current period. b) The absolute value of the difference between the high of the current period and the previous close. c) The absolute value of the difference between the low of the current period and the previous close.</li>



<li>Determine the Average True Range (ATR) over the desired number of periods:<ul><li>ATR = Moving Average(TR, n)</li></ul>The ATR is calculated by taking the moving average of the True Range values over a specific number of periods (n). The most commonly used period is 14, but you can adjust it based on your preference or the characteristics of the asset being analyzed.</li>
</ol>



<p>To illustrate the calculation, let&#8217;s consider a hypothetical example using daily price data for a stock:</p>



<p>Day 1: High = $50, Low = $45, Close = $47 Day 2: High = $48, Low = $42, Close = $45 Day 3: High = $52, Low = $47, Close = $50</p>



<p>Calculating the True Range (TR) for each day:</p>



<ul>
<li>Day 1: TR = max(50 &#8211; 45, abs(50 &#8211; 47), abs(45 &#8211; 47)) = 5</li>



<li>Day 2: TR = max(48 &#8211; 42, abs(48 &#8211; 45), abs(42 &#8211; 45)) = 6</li>



<li>Day 3: TR = max(52 &#8211; 47, abs(52 &#8211; 50), abs(47 &#8211; 50)) = 5</li>
</ul>



<p>Now, let&#8217;s calculate the Average True Range (ATR) over a 3-day period:</p>



<ul>
<li>ATR = (5 + 6 + 5) / 3 = 5.33</li>
</ul>



<p>So, the ATR for this stock over the 3-day period is approximately 5.33.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">What Is a Good Average True Range?</h2>


<div class="wp-block-image is-style-default">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-113.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="538" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-113-1024x538.png" alt="What Is Average True Range (ATR)?" class="wp-image-199646" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-113-1024x538.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-113-300x158.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-113-768x403.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-113-1536x806.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-113-2048x1075.png 2048w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-113-750x394.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-113-1140x599.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="What Is Average True Range (ATR)? 7"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>Average True Range (ATR) value is subjective and can vary depending on factors such as the trading style, time frame, and the specific asset being analyzed. There is no universally defined threshold for what constitutes a &#8220;good&#8221; ATR.</p>



<p>Instead, the interpretation of Average True Range values is relative to the context of the asset and the trading strategy employed. Generally, a higher ATR indicates greater volatility and larger price swings, which may be desirable for traders seeking more significant profit potential but may also entail increased risk. Conversely, a lower Average True Range suggests lower volatility and more stable price movements, which may be preferred by traders seeking a more conservative approach with potentially smaller gains or losses.</p>



<p>Different assets exhibit varying levels of volatility, and what may be considered a high or low Average True Range value for one asset may be different for another. Additionally, the desired ATR value may also depend on the trading timeframe. For example, a higher Average True Range may be suitable for short-term traders aiming to capitalize on intraday price fluctuations, while a lower Average True Range may be preferable for long-term investors looking for more stable trends.</p>



<p>Traders often assess the ATR in relation to the asset&#8217;s price and historical ATR values. By comparing the current Average True Range to past Average True Range readings, traders can gain insights into whether the current volatility levels are relatively high or low compared to historical norms.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Interpretation of ATR</h2>


<div class="wp-block-image is-style-default">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-114.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="600" height="400" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-114.png" alt="What Is Average True Range (ATR)?" class="wp-image-199647" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-114.png 600w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-114-300x200.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" title="What Is Average True Range (ATR)? 8"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>The Average True Range (ATR) can be interpreted in several ways to gain insights into the volatility and potential price movement of an asset. Here are a few common interpretations:</p>



<ol>
<li>Volatility Levels: A higher ATR value suggests higher volatility, indicating larger price swings and potentially increased risk. Traders who prefer more active and volatile markets may find higher ATR values favorable, as they offer greater profit potential. Conversely, lower ATR values indicate lower volatility and more stable price movements, which may be preferred by conservative traders or investors.</li>



<li>Stop Loss Placement: ATR can be used to determine appropriate stop-loss levels for trades. By setting stop-loss orders based on multiples of the ATR, traders can account for the natural fluctuations in price and avoid being stopped out by minor price movements. For example, a trader might set a stop loss at 2 times the ATR below the entry price to provide a buffer against normal price volatility.</li>



<li>Trend Strength: Changes in the Average True Range can indicate shifts in trend strength. Increasing Average True Range values may suggest a strengthening trend or an upcoming breakout, as higher volatility often accompanies strong price movements. On the other hand, decreasing ATR values may indicate a weakening trend or a period of consolidation, as lower volatility may indicate a lack of market conviction.</li>



<li>Range Expansion and Contraction: Average True Range can help identify periods of range expansion or contraction. When the ATR is rising, it indicates an increase in price volatility and the potential for larger price moves. This expansion may signal the start of a new trend or an impending breakout. Conversely, a declining ATR suggests a contraction in price volatility, indicating a period of reduced price swings or consolidation.</li>



<li>Comparative Analysis: Traders can compare the current Average True Range to past ATR readings to gain insights into whether the current volatility levels are relatively high or low compared to historical norms. This can help in assessing whether the asset is exhibiting abnormal or extreme volatility. Additionally, comparing the ATR of different assets can help traders identify which instruments are currently exhibiting higher or lower volatility, assisting in portfolio diversification decisions.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Benefits of Using Average True Range</h2>



<p>Using the Average True Range (ATR) in trading and analysis offers several benefits, including:</p>



<ol>
<li>Volatility Measurement: Average True Range provides a quantitative measure of price volatility. It helps traders assess the magnitude of price fluctuations in an asset over a specific period. By understanding the level of volatility, traders can adjust their trading strategies, position sizing, and risk management techniques accordingly.</li>



<li>Stop Loss Placement: Average True Range assists in setting appropriate stop-loss levels for trades. By incorporating the ATR, traders can place stop-loss orders at levels that account for the typical price volatility of the asset. This helps avoid setting stop-loss levels that are too tight and easily triggered by normal price fluctuations, as well as setting stop-loss levels that are too wide and expose traders to excessive risk.</li>



<li>Position Sizing: ATR aids in determining the appropriate position size for trades. Traders can use the ATR to calculate the potential risk and reward of a trade and adjust their position sizes accordingly. Higher ATR values may warrant smaller position sizes to limit potential losses, while lower ATR values may allow for larger position sizes.</li>



<li>Trend Identification: ATR can assist in identifying periods of increasing or decreasing volatility, which can be indicative of changes in market trends. Rising ATR may suggest a strengthening trend or an upcoming breakout, while declining ATR may indicate a weakening trend or a period of consolidation. Traders can use this information to make informed decisions about entering or exiting positions based on the evolving market conditions.</li>



<li>Breakout Strategies: ATR is often employed in breakout trading strategies. Breakouts occur when prices move beyond established support or resistance levels. By incorporating the ATR into breakout strategies, traders can adjust their entry levels based on the current volatility. This allows them to adapt their strategies to the prevailing market conditions and potentially increase the effectiveness of their breakout trades.</li>



<li>Risk Management: ATR assists in risk management by providing an objective measure of price volatility. It helps traders in determining appropriate levels of risk based on the current market conditions. By considering the ATR, traders can align their risk tolerance with the potential volatility of the asset, allowing for more effective risk management and trade decision-making.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Drawbacks of Using Average True Range</h2>



<p>While the Average True Range (ATR) is a useful tool for measuring volatility and making trading decisions, it is important to be aware of its limitations and potential drawbacks:</p>



<ol>
<li>Lagging Indicator: ATR is a lagging indicator because it relies on historical price data. It calculates volatility based on past price movements, which means it may not provide real-time or future predictions of volatility. Traders should be aware that ATR reflects historical volatility and may not accurately capture sudden changes or shifts in market conditions.</li>



<li>Lack of Directional Bias: ATR measures volatility but does not provide information about the direction of price movement. It does not indicate whether prices will move up or down, making it necessary to use ATR in conjunction with other technical analysis tools to identify potential trends or market conditions.</li>



<li>Not Suitable for All Strategies: While ATR can be beneficial for certain trading strategies, it may not be applicable or effective for all trading styles. Some strategies may require more precise timing or rely on other indicators that provide more specific signals for trade entries and exits. Traders should consider their individual trading approach and the suitability of ATR within their strategy.</li>



<li>Sensitivity to Outliers: ATR considers the highest and lowest prices within each period, including any outliers that may not be representative of the typical price range. Extreme price movements or gaps can significantly impact the ATR calculation, potentially skewing the results and leading to less reliable volatility measurements.</li>



<li>Interpretation Challenges: Determining what constitutes a &#8220;good&#8221; or &#8220;appropriate&#8221; ATR value can be subjective and vary based on the asset being analyzed, the time frame, and the trader&#8217;s risk tolerance. There is no universal threshold for ATR, and the interpretation of its values requires context and experience.</li>



<li>Lack of Contextual Information: ATR alone may not provide sufficient information for making trading decisions. It is important to consider other factors such as market trends, support and resistance levels, and fundamental analysis to form a comprehensive view of the market. ATR should be used in conjunction with other indicators and analysis techniques to enhance decision-making.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">How To Use Average True Range in Technical Analysis</h2>



<p>The Average True Range (ATR) can be used in technical analysis in various ways to assist traders in making informed trading decisions:</p>



<ol>
<li>Volatility Assessment: ATR provides a measure of price volatility. Traders can use the ATR to assess the current level of volatility in an asset. Higher ATR values indicate higher volatility, suggesting larger price swings and potentially increased risk. Lower ATR values indicate lower volatility, implying more stable price movements. This information helps traders adapt their trading strategies and risk management techniques accordingly.</li>



<li>Stop Loss Placement: ATR can aid in determining appropriate stop-loss levels for trades. By incorporating the ATR, traders can set stop-loss orders at levels that account for the typical price volatility of the asset. One common approach is to use a multiple of the ATR to set stop-loss levels. For example, a trader may choose to set a stop-loss order at 2 times the ATR below the entry price to allow for a reasonable buffer against normal price fluctuations.</li>



<li>Position Sizing: ATR assists in determining the appropriate position size for trades. By considering the ATR, traders can calculate the potential risk and reward of a trade. A higher ATR may warrant a smaller position size to limit potential losses, while a lower ATR may allow for a larger position size. This helps align position sizes with the level of volatility and risk associated with the asset.</li>



<li>Breakout Trading: ATR is often utilized in breakout trading strategies. Breakouts occur when prices move beyond established support or resistance levels. Traders can use the ATR to set entry points for breakout trades. By incorporating the ATR, traders can adjust their entry levels based on the current volatility. This can help identify potential breakouts that have higher chances of significant price moves.</li>



<li>Trend Analysis: Changes in the ATR can provide insights into trend strength. Increasing ATR values may indicate a strengthening trend or an upcoming breakout, as higher volatility often accompanies strong price movements. Conversely, decreasing ATR values may indicate a weakening trend or a period of consolidation, as lower volatility may suggest a lack of market conviction. Traders can use the ATR alongside other technical indicators to identify and confirm trends.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Average True Range (ATR) Is a Versatile Trading Tool</h2>



<p>Average True Range (ATR) is a versatile trading tool that offers several applications and benefits in technical analysis. Here are some key reasons why ATR is considered a versatile tool:</p>



<ol>
<li>Volatility Measurement: ATR quantifies the volatility of an asset by measuring the price range over a specific period. It provides traders with a numerical value that represents the average volatility, allowing them to gauge the potential price movements and adjust their trading strategies accordingly.</li>



<li>Risk Management: ATR assists in risk management by helping traders determine appropriate stop-loss levels and position sizes. By factoring in the ATR, traders can set stop-loss orders at levels that align with the asset&#8217;s volatility, avoiding getting stopped out prematurely by normal price fluctuations. Additionally, ATR helps in determining position sizes by considering the potential risk associated with an asset&#8217;s volatility.</li>



<li>Entry and Exit Points: ATR is valuable for identifying optimal entry and exit points. Traders can use ATR-based indicators or ATR bands to establish entry levels that align with the asset&#8217;s volatility. For example, a trader may wait for a price breakout that exceeds a certain multiple of the ATR to confirm a significant move before entering a trade. Similarly, ATR can help in identifying potential reversal points or profit-taking levels.</li>



<li>Trend Identification: ATR aids in identifying trends and trend strength. Rising ATR values often indicate increasing volatility and potentially stronger trends, while decreasing ATR values may suggest a loss of momentum or a period of consolidation. Traders can use the ATR in combination with other trend-following indicators to confirm trends and make informed trading decisions.</li>



<li>Range Expansion and Contraction: ATR is helpful for recognizing periods of range expansion and contraction. When the ATR is rising, it suggests an increase in volatility and potential larger price moves, indicating a period of range expansion. Conversely, a declining ATR suggests reduced volatility and potential range contraction, indicating a period of consolidation. Traders can adjust their strategies accordingly to suit the market conditions.</li>



<li>Indicator Confirmation: ATR can be used in conjunction with other technical indicators to confirm signals or provide additional insights. For example, ATR can be combined with moving averages to identify potential trend reversals or used alongside oscillators to validate overbought or oversold conditions.</li>
</ol>



<p>The versatility of ATR lies in its ability to measure volatility, assist in risk management, identify trends, determine entry and exit points, and provide confirmation for other indicators. Traders can adapt and apply ATR to various trading styles, timeframes, and markets to enhance their decision-making and optimize trading strategies.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Conclusion</h2>



<p>Average True Range (ATR) is a powerful tool in technical analysis that provides valuable insights into price volatility and potential price movements. Its versatility makes it applicable to various trading strategies and timeframes.</p>



<p id="block-643c4ba8-b40b-4525-9a96-f280dbfbeb9d"><strong><em>DISCLAIMER:&nbsp;</em></strong><em>The Information on this&nbsp;website&nbsp;is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>



<p id="block-522ef498-a505-4d0b-9a0d-b2e5cca12111">Join us to keep track of news:&nbsp;<a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right" id="block-4fa7c042-0908-4ee5-9ff4-91607eb34413"><strong>Annie</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right" id="block-84ea04e6-519a-4165-8e39-faa42e0200e5"><strong>Coincu</strong>&nbsp;<strong>New</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/What-Is-Average-True-Range-ATR-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>BaseFEX Reviews: Crypto Derivatives Exchange That Puts Traders First?</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/199618-basefex-reviews-crypto-derivatives-exchange/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Annie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 04:37:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange Reviews]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BaseFEX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Derivatives Exchange]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=199618</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[BaseFEX is a crypto derivatives exchange that specializes in futures trading. Currently, it only offers Bitcoin futures trading, but it allows traders to engage in highly-leveraged contracts for different cryptocurrencies valued up to 100x times. These include perpetual swap contracts for BTC (Bitcoin), ETH (Ethereum), BCH (Bitcoin Cash), XRP (Ripple), BNB (Binance Coin), and EOS [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>BaseFEX is a crypto derivatives exchange that specializes in futures trading. Currently, it only offers Bitcoin futures trading, but it allows traders to engage in highly-leveraged contracts for different cryptocurrencies valued up to 100x times. </p>


<div class="wp-block-image is-style-default">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-103.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="601" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-103-1024x601.png" alt="BaseFEX Reviews: Crypto Derivatives Exchange That Puts Traders First?" class="wp-image-199627" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-103-1024x601.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-103-300x176.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-103-768x451.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-103-1536x902.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-103-750x440.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-103-1140x669.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-103.png 2006w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="BaseFEX Reviews: Crypto Derivatives Exchange That Puts Traders First? 9"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>These include perpetual swap contracts for BTC (Bitcoin), ETH (Ethereum), BCH (Bitcoin Cash), XRP (Ripple), BNB (Binance Coin), and EOS Electro-Optical System). All profits and losses on BaseFEX trading are paid in Bitcoin and USDT. However, BaseFEX is looking to expand its services by offering leveraged contracts for other cryptocurrencies and altcoins. This will provide traders with more options and a greater range of investment opportunities. By expanding its portfolio, BaseFEX hopes to attract more traders and investors to its platform and establish itself as a leading player in the crypto derivatives market.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">What Is BaseFEX?</h2>


<div class="wp-block-image is-style-default">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-105.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="770" height="508" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-105.png" alt="BaseFEX Reviews: Crypto Derivatives Exchange That Puts Traders First?" class="wp-image-199629" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-105.png 770w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-105-300x198.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-105-768x507.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-105-750x495.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 770px) 100vw, 770px" title="BaseFEX Reviews: Crypto Derivatives Exchange That Puts Traders First? 10"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>BaseFEX is a cryptocurrency derivatives exchange platform. It provides traders with the ability to trade various cryptocurrency futures contracts with leverage. BaseFEX offers a range of features and tools for trading, including a user-friendly interface, advanced trading charts, risk management options, and a customizable trading experience.</p>



<p>BaseFEX is its focus on offering high leverage for trading. Leverage allows traders to multiply their exposure to the price movements of the underlying cryptocurrency without requiring them to hold the full value of the contract. This can potentially amplify profits but also carries higher risks.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">How Does BaseFEX Work?</h2>


<div class="wp-block-image is-style-default">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-104.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="705" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-104-1024x705.png" alt="BaseFEX Reviews: Crypto Derivatives Exchange That Puts Traders First?" class="wp-image-199628" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-104-1024x705.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-104-300x207.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-104-768x529.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-104-1536x1058.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-104-2048x1411.png 2048w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-104-750x517.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-104-1140x785.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="BaseFEX Reviews: Crypto Derivatives Exchange That Puts Traders First? 11"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>BaseFEX is a cryptocurrency derivatives exchange that operates on a user-friendly online platform: </p>



<ol>
<li>Registration: To begin trading on BFEX, users need to create an account by completing the registration process. This typically involves providing personal information and agreeing to the platform&#8217;s terms of service.</li>



<li>Deposit: After registering, users need to deposit funds into their BFEX account. BFEX supports deposits in cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin (BTC) or Ethereum (ETH).</li>



<li>Trading Interface: Once the account is funded, users can access the trading interface. The interface displays various trading pairs and futures contracts available for trading. Users can choose the desired trading pair and contract based on their preferences.</li>



<li>Leverage: BFEX allows traders to use leverage, which means they can open positions that are larger than the amount of funds they have in their account. Leverage amplifies both profits and losses, so traders should exercise caution and understand the risks involved.</li>



<li>Placing Orders: Traders can place different types of orders on BFEX, including market orders, limit orders, stop orders, and more. These orders allow traders to specify the desired price at which they want to enter or exit a position.</li>



<li>Risk Management: BFEX provides various risk management tools to help traders manage their positions effectively. These tools may include features like stop-loss orders and take-profit orders, which allow users to automatically close positions at predetermined price levels.</li>



<li>Trading Execution: Once an order is placed, BFEX executes the trade based on the market conditions and the order parameters. The order may be filled immediately if the market conditions allow, or it may remain open until the specified conditions are met.</li>



<li>Profits and Losses: As the market price of the chosen cryptocurrency futures contract fluctuates, traders can make profits or losses. Traders can monitor their positions and account balance in real-time on the BFEX platform.</li>



<li>Withdrawals: If traders wish to withdraw their funds from BFEX, they can request a withdrawal to their designated cryptocurrency wallet. The withdrawal process usually involves a security verification step to ensure the safety of the funds.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Features of BaseFEX</h2>


<div class="wp-block-image is-style-default">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-106.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="573" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-106-1024x573.png" alt="BaseFEX Reviews: Crypto Derivatives Exchange That Puts Traders First?" class="wp-image-199630" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-106-1024x573.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-106-300x168.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-106-768x429.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-106-1536x859.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-106-2048x1145.png 2048w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-106-750x419.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-106-1140x637.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="BaseFEX Reviews: Crypto Derivatives Exchange That Puts Traders First? 12"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>BaseFEX offers several features that cater to the needs of cryptocurrency traders:</p>



<ol>
<li>Leverage Trading: BFEX provides high leverage options, allowing traders to amplify their exposure to cryptocurrency futures contracts. Traders can potentially generate higher profits by using leverage, but it&#8217;s important to note that it also carries higher risk.</li>



<li>Diverse Range of Cryptocurrency Futures: BFEX supports a wide range of cryptocurrency futures contracts, including popular cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH), and others. Traders can choose from various trading pairs and contract durations to suit their trading strategies.</li>



<li>User-Friendly Trading Interface: BFEX offers an intuitive and user-friendly trading interface, making it accessible for both novice and experienced traders. The interface provides real-time market data, advanced charting tools, and order placement options to facilitate efficient trading.</li>



<li>Advanced Trading Tools: BFEX equips traders with advanced trading tools and features to enhance their trading experience. These tools may include customizable charts, technical analysis indicators, risk management options, and order types such as market orders, limit orders, and stop orders.</li>



<li>Security Measures: BFEX prioritizes the security of user funds and employs industry-standard security measures. These measures may include encrypted data transmission, two-factor authentication (2FA), cold storage for cryptocurrencies, and regular security audits.</li>



<li>Risk Management Tools: BFEX provides risk management tools to help traders mitigate potential losses. These tools may include stop-loss orders, which allow traders to set a specific price level at which their positions will be automatically closed to limit losses.</li>



<li>Competitive Fee Structure: BFEX offers a competitive fee structure for traders. The platform typically charges trading fees based on the trading volume and may have different fee tiers for different levels of trading activity.</li>



<li>Responsive Customer Support: BFEX has a customer support team that can assist users with inquiries and issues related to the platform. They aim to provide timely and helpful support to ensure a smooth trading experience.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Pros and Cons</h2>


<div class="wp-block-image is-style-default">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-107.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="600" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-107-1024x600.png" alt="BaseFEX Reviews: Crypto Derivatives Exchange That Puts Traders First?" class="wp-image-199631" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-107-1024x600.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-107-300x176.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-107-768x450.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-107-1536x901.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-107-2048x1201.png 2048w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-107-750x440.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-107-1140x668.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="BaseFEX Reviews: Crypto Derivatives Exchange That Puts Traders First? 13"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>

<div class="wp-block-image is-style-default">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-108.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="595" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-108-1024x595.png" alt="BaseFEX Reviews: Crypto Derivatives Exchange That Puts Traders First?" class="wp-image-199632" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-108-1024x595.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-108-300x174.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-108-768x446.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-108-1536x892.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-108-2048x1189.png 2048w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-108-750x436.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-108-1140x662.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="BaseFEX Reviews: Crypto Derivatives Exchange That Puts Traders First? 14"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>Pros:</p>



<ol>
<li>Leverage Trading: BFEX offers high leverage options, allowing traders to amplify their potential profits by trading with borrowed funds.</li>



<li>Wide Range of Cryptocurrencies: BFEX supports a diverse selection of cryptocurrencies, providing traders with various options for trading futures contracts.</li>



<li>User-Friendly Interface: BFEX&#8217;s user-friendly interface makes it accessible for both experienced and novice traders. It offers intuitive navigation, advanced charting tools, and order placement options.</li>



<li>Risk Management Tools: BaseFEX provides risk management features like stop-loss orders, enabling traders to manage their risk exposure and protect themselves from significant losses.</li>



<li>Security Measures: BaseFEX emphasizes the security of user funds and employs measures such as encryption, 2FA, and cold storage to safeguard customer assets.</li>



<li>Competitive Fees: BaseFEX aims to offer competitive fee structures for trading, making it potentially cost-effective for active traders.</li>
</ol>



<p>Cons:</p>



<ol>
<li>Leverage Risks: While leverage can amplify potential profits, it also increases the risk of losses. Trading with leverage requires careful risk management and can result in substantial losses if not used responsibly.</li>



<li>Limited Availability: BaseFEX&#8217;s availability might be limited in certain regions. It&#8217;s important to check if the platform is accessible in your jurisdiction before attempting to use it.</li>



<li>Regulatory Considerations: Cryptocurrency derivatives trading is subject to regulatory oversight in various jurisdictions. Traders should be aware of the legal and regulatory implications of engaging in such activities in their respective countries.</li>



<li>Volatility and Market Risk: The cryptocurrency market is highly volatile, which can result in rapid price fluctuations. Traders should be prepared for significant price swings and understand the potential risks associated with trading in a volatile market.</li>



<li>Technical Issues: Like any online platform, BaseFEX may encounter technical issues, such as system outages or delays. These issues can disrupt trading activities and potentially lead to missed opportunities or inconveniences.</li>



<li>Learning Curve: Trading on BaseFEX requires a certain level of understanding of cryptocurrency markets, derivatives trading, and risk management strategies. Novice traders may need to invest time and effort in learning these concepts before engaging in active trading.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">BaseFEX Fees</h2>


<div class="wp-block-image is-style-default">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-109.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="800" height="800" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-109.png" alt="BaseFEX Reviews: Crypto Derivatives Exchange That Puts Traders First?" class="wp-image-199633" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-109.png 800w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-109-300x300.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-109-150x150.png 150w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-109-768x768.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-109-75x75.png 75w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-109-350x350.png 350w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-109-750x750.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 800px) 100vw, 800px" title="BaseFEX Reviews: Crypto Derivatives Exchange That Puts Traders First? 15"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>BaseFEX charges fees for various services and transactions on its platform. Here is a general overview of the fees you may encounter when using BaseFEX:</p>



<ol>
<li>Trading Fees: BaseFEX charges trading fees for executed trades on the platform. The fee structure is typically based on a tiered system, where the fee percentage decreases as your trading volume increases. The specific fee percentages may vary depending on the trading pair and contract type. It&#8217;s recommended to visit the BaseFEX website or consult their fee schedule for detailed information on current trading fees.</li>



<li>Funding Fees: When depositing or withdrawing funds from your BaseFEX account, you may encounter funding fees. These fees are typically associated with cryptocurrency transactions and are subject to network fees and market conditions. The specific fees can vary depending on the cryptocurrency being deposited or withdrawn.</li>



<li>Overnight Funding Fees: BaseFEX may charge overnight funding fees for holding leveraged positions overnight. These fees are calculated based on the size of the position and the funding rate of the particular contract. The funding rate is influenced by market demand and can vary from positive to negative. Positive funding rates result in traders receiving payments, while negative funding rates result in traders paying fees.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">BaseFEX Customer Service</h2>



<p>BaseFEX provides customer support services to assist users with inquiries and issues related to the platform. Here is an overview of BaseFEX&#8217;s customer service options:</p>



<ol>
<li>Support Tickets: Users can submit support tickets through the BaseFEX website or platform. By submitting a support ticket, users can describe their issue or inquiry in detail and receive a response from the BaseFEX support team.</li>



<li>Email Support: BaseFEX offers email support for users who prefer to communicate via email. Users can send their questions or concerns to the designated support email address provided by BaseFEX. The support team will respond to the email inquiries as promptly as possible.</li>



<li>Live Chat: BaseFEX features a live chat support option, allowing users to engage in real-time conversations with the customer support team. Live chat can be accessed through the BaseFEX website or platform. This option enables users to receive immediate assistance for urgent matters or time-sensitive inquiries.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Conclusion</h2>



<p>BaseFEX is a cryptocurrency derivatives exchange platform that offers traders the ability to trade a variety of cryptocurrency futures contracts with leverage. It provides a user-friendly interface, a wide range of cryptocurrencies to trade, and risk management tools such as stop-loss orders. BaseFEX emphasizes security measures to protect user funds and offers competitive fee structures.</p>



<p>However, it&#8217;s important to consider the potential risks associated with trading on BaseFEX or any other cryptocurrency derivatives exchange. Leverage trading can amplify both profits and losses, and the cryptocurrency market is highly volatile. It&#8217;s crucial to have a good understanding of trading concepts, risk management strategies, and the specific terms and conditions of BaseFEX before engaging in trading activities.</p>



<p id="block-643c4ba8-b40b-4525-9a96-f280dbfbeb9d"><strong><em>DISCLAIMER:&nbsp;</em></strong><em>The Information on this&nbsp;website&nbsp;is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>



<p id="block-522ef498-a505-4d0b-9a0d-b2e5cca12111">Join us to keep track of news:&nbsp;<a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right" id="block-4fa7c042-0908-4ee5-9ff4-91607eb34413"><strong>Annie</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right" id="block-84ea04e6-519a-4165-8e39-faa42e0200e5"><strong>Coincu</strong>&nbsp;<strong>New</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BaseFEX-Reviews-Crypto-Derivatives--1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Whale Makes Significant Deposit of 4.62 Million RDNT Tokens on Binance</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/199584-whale-makes-deposit-of-462-million-rdnt/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tommy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 04:31:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[deposit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[investment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[RDNT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Whale]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=199584</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Whale deposits 4.62M RDNT tokens at Binance, incurring a loss despite token value surge]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong> </p>



<ul>
<li>Whale deposits 4.62M RDNT tokens at Binance, incurring a loss despite token value surge. </li>



<li>Whale had been accumulating RDNT tokens over two months, investing 1.55M USDC.</li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>According to <a href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1675693681825951744" data-type="URL" data-id="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1675693681825951744" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Lookonchain</a>, a huge whale address transferred 4.62 million RDNT  to Binance today after the price of increased.</strong></h5>



<figure class="wp-block-gallery has-nested-images columns-default is-cropped wp-block-gallery-1 is-layout-flex">
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-94.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="904" height="510" data-id="199597" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-94.png" alt="RDNT" class="wp-image-199597" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-94.png 904w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-94-300x169.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-94-768x433.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-94-750x423.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 904px) 100vw, 904px" title="Whale Makes Significant Deposit of 4.62 Million RDNT Tokens on Binance 16"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"><em>Source: Radiant Capital</em></figcaption></figure>
</figure>



<p></p>



<p>A large investor, known as a &#8220;whale,&#8221; has recently made a deposit of 4.62 million RDNT tokens (equivalent to 1.4 million dollars) at cryptocurrency exchange Binance. This deposit suffered a loss even though the value of the token had increased earlier that day.</p>



<p>It appears that this whale had been accumulating tokens for the past two months, spending a total of 1.55 million USDC to purchase the 4.62 million RDNT tokens.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-gallery has-nested-images columns-default is-cropped wp-block-gallery-3 is-layout-flex">
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-102.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="558" data-id="199625" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-102-1024x558.png" alt="RDNT" class="wp-image-199625" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-102-1024x558.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-102-300x163.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-102-768x418.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-102-1536x837.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-102-750x409.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-102-1140x621.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-102.png 1946w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Whale Makes Significant Deposit of 4.62 Million RDNT Tokens on Binance 17"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"><em>Source: CoinmarketCap</em></figcaption></figure>
</figure>



<p>These purchases were made through a platform called Odos Protocol, and the average price paid per token was $0.3353. </p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">A whale deposited 4.62M <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24RDNT&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener">$RDNT</a> ($1.4M) to <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Binance?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener">#Binance</a> at a loss after the <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24RDNT&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener">$RDNT</a> price rose today.<br><br>This whale spent 1.55M <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24USDC&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener">$USDC</a> to buy 4.62M <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24RDNT&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener">$RDNT</a> at an average price of $0.3353 on <a href="https://twitter.com/odosprotocol?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener">@odosprotocol</a> over the past 2 months.<br><br>If he sells, he will lose ~$157K.<a href="https://t.co/qfPWMRE9m3" target="_blank">https://t.co/qfPWMRE9m3</a> <a href="https://t.co/pvw8b7rI5J" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/pvw8b7rI5J</a></p>&mdash; Lookonchain (@lookonchain) <a href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1675693681825951744?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener">July 3, 2023</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>Despite the loss incurred through the recent deposit, it is unclear whether the whale plans to sell their RDNT tokens. If they were to do so at current market prices, they would face a loss of approximately $157,000. However, there may be other factors at play that influence the whale&#8217;s decision to hold onto their tokens or sell them at a later time.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER: The Information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></strong></p>



<p>Join us to keep track of news:&nbsp;<a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p>Website: <a href="https://coincu.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">coincu.com</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Tommy</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Coincu News</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ban-sao-cua-Noi-dung-doan-van-ban-cua-ban-1-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>ShapeShift Reviews: Your Multi-Chain Crypto Home Base?</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/199586-shapeshift-reviews-your-multi-chain-crypto/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Annie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 03:59:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange Reviews]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Multi-Chain Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ShapeShift]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=199586</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[ShapeShift is known for its simple and secure approach to cryptocurrency trading, offering users the ability to swap cryptocurrencies quickly and privately without the need for an account. What Is ShapeShift? ShapeShift is a popular cryptocurrency exchange platform that allows users to quickly and easily trade one cryptocurrency for another without the need for creating [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>ShapeShift is known for its simple and secure approach to cryptocurrency trading, offering users the ability to swap cryptocurrencies quickly and privately without the need for an account.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image is-style-default">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-96.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="477" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-96-1024x477.png" alt="ShapeShift Reviews: Your Multi-Chain Crypto Home Base?" class="wp-image-199607" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-96-1024x477.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-96-300x140.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-96-768x357.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-96-1536x715.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-96-2048x953.png 2048w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-96-750x349.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-96-1140x531.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="ShapeShift Reviews: Your Multi-Chain Crypto Home Base? 18"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">What Is ShapeShift?</h2>


<div class="wp-block-image is-style-default">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-98.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="512" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-98-1024x512.png" alt="ShapeShift Reviews: Your Multi-Chain Crypto Home Base?" class="wp-image-199609" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-98-1024x512.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-98-300x150.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-98-768x384.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-98-360x180.png 360w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-98-750x375.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-98-1140x570.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-98.png 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="ShapeShift Reviews: Your Multi-Chain Crypto Home Base? 19"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>ShapeShift is a popular cryptocurrency exchange platform that allows users to quickly and easily trade one cryptocurrency for another without the need for creating an account or undergoing a lengthy registration process. It was founded in 2014 by Erik Voorhees and has gained recognition in the crypto community for its simplicity and privacy-focused approach.</p>



<p>ShapeShift is its ability to facilitate instant cryptocurrency swaps. Users can select the cryptocurrency they want to convert and the cryptocurrency they want to receive, and ShapeShift will execute the trade at the current exchange rate. ShapeShift supports a wide range of cryptocurrencies, making it convenient for users to exchange various digital assets.</p>



<p>ShapeShift is its non-custodial nature. Unlike traditional exchanges, ShapeShift does not hold user funds in its platform. Instead, it enables direct peer-to-peer transactions between users&#8217; wallets, allowing for increased security and control over their assets. This also means that ShapeShift does not require users to create an account or provide personal information, enhancing privacy and anonymity.</p>



<p>ShapeShift has evolved over time and introduced additional features to its platform. This includes the ShapeShift API, which allows developers to integrate ShapeShift functionality into their own applications, and ShapeShift Membership, a subscription-based program that offers benefits such as higher trading limits and rewards.</p>



<p>ShapeShift underwent a significant change in 2021, transitioning from its original model to a decentralized exchange (DEX) known as ShapeShift DAO. As a DEX, ShapeShift DAO operates on a blockchain network, enabling users to trade cryptocurrencies in a decentralized manner while maintaining control over their funds.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">How Does ShapeShift Work?</h2>


<div class="wp-block-image is-style-default">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-97.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="513" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-97-1024x513.png" alt="ShapeShift Reviews: Your Multi-Chain Crypto Home Base?" class="wp-image-199608" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-97-1024x513.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-97-300x150.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-97-768x385.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-97-1536x770.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-97-2048x1027.png 2048w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-97-360x180.png 360w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-97-750x376.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-97-1140x572.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="ShapeShift Reviews: Your Multi-Chain Crypto Home Base? 20"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>ShapeShift works as a cryptocurrency exchange platform that allows users to trade one cryptocurrency for another in a quick and straightforward manner. Here&#8217;s an overview of how SS typically operates:</p>



<ol>
<li>Selection of Cryptocurrencies: Users start by selecting the cryptocurrencies they want to exchange. SS supports a wide range of cryptocurrencies, including popular ones like Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH), Ripple (XRP), and many others.</li>



<li>Input of Receiving Address: Users provide the wallet address where they want to receive the converted cryptocurrency. This address must correspond to the selected cryptocurrency.</li>



<li>Confirmation of Transaction Details: SS displays the exchange rate and the amount of cryptocurrency that will be received based on the current market rate. Users review and confirm the transaction details before proceeding.</li>



<li>Sending the Initial Cryptocurrency: Users initiate the trade by sending the initial cryptocurrency they want to exchange to a unique deposit address provided by SS. This can be done by scanning a QR code or manually entering the address.</li>



<li>Verification of Transaction: SS monitors the blockchain network to confirm the receipt of the initial cryptocurrency. Once the transaction is verified, SS proceeds to the next step.</li>



<li>Sending the Converted Cryptocurrency: After the verification, SS sends the converted cryptocurrency to the receiving wallet address specified by the user. The transaction is executed at the current exchange rate provided at the beginning of the process.</li>



<li>Transaction Completion: Once the converted cryptocurrency is sent, the transaction is considered complete. Users can verify the transaction on the blockchain network by checking the receiving wallet address.</li>
</ol>



<p>ShapeShift operates as a non-custodial exchange, meaning it does not hold user funds or require user accounts. Users maintain control over their wallets and private keys throughout the exchange process, which enhances security and privacy. However, it also means that ShapeShift does not offer features like account balances or transaction history.</p>



<p>ShapeShift provides a user-friendly interface on its website and also offers an API for developers to integrate its functionality into their own applications. By simplifying the cryptocurrency exchange process and emphasizing user control and privacy, ShapeShift aims to provide a convenient solution for users seeking to swap cryptocurrencies efficiently.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Features of ShapeShift</h2>


<div class="wp-block-image is-style-default">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-99.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="600" height="240" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-99.png" alt="ShapeShift Reviews: Your Multi-Chain Crypto Home Base?" class="wp-image-199610" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-99.png 600w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-99-300x120.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" title="ShapeShift Reviews: Your Multi-Chain Crypto Home Base? 21"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>ShapeShift offers several features that make it a popular choice for users looking to exchange cryptocurrencies quickly and conveniently. Here are some key features of ShapeShift:</p>



<ol>
<li>Instant Cryptocurrency Exchange: SS enables instant cryptocurrency exchanges, allowing users to trade one cryptocurrency for another in a seamless manner. The exchange is executed at the current market rate, providing users with immediate access to the desired cryptocurrency.</li>



<li>Wide Range of Supported Cryptocurrencies: SS supports a vast selection of cryptocurrencies, including major coins like Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH), Litecoin (LTC), and many others. This extensive range of supported cryptocurrencies offers users flexibility and options for their trading needs.</li>



<li>Non-Custodial Nature: SS operates as a non-custodial exchange, which means it does not hold user funds or require users to create accounts. Users maintain control over their wallets and private keys throughout the exchange process, enhancing security and privacy.</li>



<li>Simple and User-Friendly Interface: SS is designed with simplicity in mind, providing a user-friendly interface that makes it easy for both beginners and experienced users to navigate and execute cryptocurrency exchanges. The platform focuses on streamlining the exchange process and removing unnecessary complexities.</li>



<li>Privacy and Anonymity: SS prioritizes user privacy by not requiring any personal information during the exchange process. Users can trade cryptocurrencies without the need for account creation or identity verification, enhancing anonymity.</li>



<li>ShapeShift API: SS offers an API (Application Programming Interface) that allows developers to integrate ShapeShift&#8217;s exchange functionality into their own applications or platforms. This enables developers to leverage ShapeShift&#8217;s infrastructure to offer cryptocurrency exchange services to their users.</li>



<li>ShapeShift DAO: SS has transitioned into a decentralized exchange (DEX) known as ShapeShift DAO. As a DEX, ShapeShift DAO operates on a blockchain network and provides users with decentralized trading capabilities.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Pros and Cons</h2>


<div class="wp-block-image is-style-default">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-100.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="508" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-100-1024x508.png" alt="ShapeShift Reviews: Your Multi-Chain Crypto Home Base?" class="wp-image-199611" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-100-1024x508.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-100-300x149.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-100-768x381.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-100-1536x762.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-100-2048x1017.png 2048w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-100-360x180.png 360w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-100-750x372.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-100-1140x566.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="ShapeShift Reviews: Your Multi-Chain Crypto Home Base? 22"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>Pros of ShapeShift:</p>



<ol>
<li>Instant Exchanges: SS facilitates instant cryptocurrency exchanges, allowing users to quickly swap one digital asset for another without delays or waiting for order matching.</li>



<li>Wide Range of Supported Cryptocurrencies: SS supports a vast selection of cryptocurrencies, giving users access to a diverse range of digital assets for trading.</li>



<li>Non-Custodial and Privacy-Focused: SS operates as a non-custodial exchange, meaning users retain control of their funds and private keys throughout the exchange process. It also prioritizes user privacy by not requiring user accounts or personal information.</li>



<li>User-Friendly Interface: SS provides a user-friendly interface that simplifies the exchange process, making it accessible to both novice and experienced cryptocurrency users.</li>



<li>ShapeShift DAO: SS&#8217;s transition into a decentralized exchange (ShapeShift DAO) allows users to trade cryptocurrencies in a decentralized manner, contributing to the principles of decentralization and blockchain technology.</li>
</ol>



<p>Cons of ShapeShift:</p>



<ol>
<li>Lack of Advanced Trading Features: SS focuses on simplicity and instant exchanges, which means it lacks advanced trading features commonly found on traditional exchanges, such as order books, limit orders, and advanced charting tools.</li>



<li>Lack of Account Features: As a non-custodial exchange, SS does not offer user accounts, balances, or transaction history. This may be a limitation for users who prefer a more comprehensive overview of their trading activities.</li>



<li>Limited Customer Support: SS&#8217;s customer support options are limited compared to traditional exchanges. As a decentralized platform, the support channels may not offer the same level of responsiveness or availability.</li>



<li>Transaction Fees: SS charges fees for cryptocurrency exchanges, and while they are typically included in the exchange rate, they can be higher compared to some traditional exchanges. Users should consider the fees associated with each transaction.</li>



<li>Market Volatility: The instantaneous nature of SS&#8217;s exchanges exposes users to market volatility. The exchange rate may fluctuate during the confirmation process, resulting in slightly different amounts of the converted cryptocurrency.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">How to Trade on ShapeShift?</h2>



<p>To trade on ShapeShift, follow these general steps:</p>



<ol>
<li>Select the Cryptocurrencies: Start by deciding which cryptocurrencies you want to trade. SS supports a wide range of cryptocurrencies, so you have various options to choose from.</li>



<li>Choose the Trading Method: SS offers different ways to trade, depending on your preferences and needs. You can trade directly on the ShapeShift website, use SS&#8217;s API to integrate trading functionality into your own application, or access SS through third-party wallets or platforms that have integrated SS.</li>



<li>Provide Receiving Address: Specify the wallet address where you want to receive the converted cryptocurrency. Make sure to input the correct address for the specific cryptocurrency you wish to receive.</li>



<li>Input Sending Address: Provide the wallet address from which you will send the initial cryptocurrency you want to exchange. Double-check the address to ensure accuracy.</li>



<li>Confirm Transaction Details: Review the exchange rate and the amount of the converted cryptocurrency you will receive. Ensure that the details are correct before proceeding.</li>



<li>Initiate the Trade: Send the initial cryptocurrency to the unique deposit address provided by SS. This can be done by scanning a QR code or manually entering the address. Make sure to send the exact amount required to complete the trade.</li>



<li>Monitor the Transaction: Track the progress of your transaction. SS will verify the transaction on the blockchain network and proceed with the exchange once the initial cryptocurrency is received.</li>



<li>Receive the Converted Cryptocurrency: Once the initial transaction is confirmed, SS will send the converted cryptocurrency to the specified receiving address. The cryptocurrency will be transferred to your wallet.</li>



<li>Verify the Transaction: Check your receiving wallet address to ensure that the converted cryptocurrency has been successfully deposited.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">ShapeShift Fees</h2>



<p>ShapeShift charges fees for its cryptocurrency exchange services. The fee structure of ShapeShift can vary depending on the cryptocurrencies being traded and other factors. Here are some key points to understand about ShapeShift fees:</p>



<ol>
<li>Trading Fees: SS&#8217;s trading fees are included in the exchange rate provided at the beginning of the transaction. The fees are typically calculated as a percentage of the transaction amount and can vary based on market conditions and the specific cryptocurrencies being exchanged.</li>



<li>Network Fees: In addition to trading fees, SS passes on the network fees associated with the blockchain networks used for cryptocurrency transactions. These network fees are required to process and validate transactions on the respective blockchain networks.</li>



<li>Fee Calculation: SS&#8217;s fees are integrated into the exchange rate to provide users with a transparent and simplified trading experience. This means that the exchange rate you see at the beginning of the transaction already includes the applicable fees, so you don&#8217;t need to calculate them separately.</li>



<li>Fee Disclosure: SS provides transparent fee disclosure during the transaction process. Before confirming the trade, you will see the exchange rate and the resulting amount of the converted cryptocurrency, which includes the fees.</li>



<li>Fee Estimation: SS&#8217;s website and API provide fee estimation tools that allow users to get an estimate of the trading fees for a particular transaction before initiating the trade. This can help users plan their trades and understand the cost implications.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">ShapeShift App</h2>


<div class="wp-block-image is-style-default">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-101.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="534" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-101-1024x534.png" alt="ShapeShift Reviews: Your Multi-Chain Crypto Home Base?" class="wp-image-199612" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-101-1024x534.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-101-300x156.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-101-768x401.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-101-1536x801.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-101-2048x1068.png 2048w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-101-750x391.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-101-1140x595.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="ShapeShift Reviews: Your Multi-Chain Crypto Home Base? 23"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>ShapeShift had a mobile app available for both iOS and Android devices. The ShapeShift app provided users with a convenient way to access and manage their cryptocurrency exchanges on the go. However, it&#8217;s important to note that the availability and features of the ShapeShift app may have evolved or changed since then, and I recommend checking the official ShapeShift website or app store for the most up-to-date information on the ShapeShift app.</p>



<ol>
<li>Cryptocurrency Trading: The SS app likely allows users to trade one cryptocurrency for another directly from their mobile devices. Users can select the cryptocurrencies they want to exchange, input the necessary addresses, and complete the transactions.</li>



<li>Wallet Integration: The app may integrate with users&#8217; cryptocurrency wallets, allowing them to securely store and manage their digital assets within the app. This integration simplifies the process of initiating trades and accessing funds for exchanges.</li>



<li>Account Management: The SS app might offer features for managing user accounts, such as viewing transaction history, checking balances, and monitoring the status of ongoing trades.</li>



<li>Price Tracking and Alerts: SS app users may have access to real-time cryptocurrency price tracking, enabling them to stay updated on market trends. Additionally, the app might provide price alerts to notify users of significant price movements or specific price targets.</li>



<li>Security Features: ShapeShift likely incorporates security measures in its app, such as encryption, two-factor authentication (2FA), and biometric authentication (e.g., fingerprint or face recognition) to ensure the safety of user accounts and transactions.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">ShapeShift Security</h2>



<p>ShapeShift places a strong emphasis on security to protect user funds and personal information. Here are some of the security measures and practices employed by ShapeShift:</p>



<ol>
<li>Non-Custodial Model: SS operates as a non-custodial exchange, which means that it does not hold user funds. Users retain control over their wallets and private keys throughout the exchange process. This reduces the risk of hacking or theft from centralized exchange wallets.</li>



<li>Two-Factor Authentication (2FA): SS offers optional two-factor authentication as an extra layer of security. Users can enable 2FA using authenticator apps, such as Google Authenticator or Authy, to provide an additional verification step during account access.</li>



<li>Secure Communication: ShapeShift employs encryption protocols, including HTTPS (Hypertext Transfer Protocol Secure), to ensure secure communication between users&#8217; devices and the ShapeShift platform. This helps protect sensitive data from unauthorized access.</li>



<li>Wallet Integration: SS allows users to use their own cryptocurrency wallets for trading. By utilizing existing wallets, users can leverage the security features of their preferred wallet providers, such as hardware wallets or secure software wallets.</li>



<li>Privacy-Focused: SS respects user privacy and does not require users to create accounts or provide personal information during the exchange process. This reduces the risk of data breaches and protects user anonymity.</li>



<li>Ongoing Security Audits: SS conducts regular security audits and assessments to identify and address potential vulnerabilities. This helps ensure that the platform maintains a robust security posture and stays up to date with the latest security best practices.</li>



<li>Bug Bounty Program: ShapeShift operates a bug bounty program, encouraging security researchers and the wider community to report any security vulnerabilities they discover. This allows ShapeShift to address potential issues promptly and reward those who contribute to the platform&#8217;s security.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Conclusion</h2>



<p>ShapeShift caters to users who prioritize simplicity, privacy, and instant exchanges. It is important for users to conduct their own research and understand the fees, risks, and features associated with ShapeShift before engaging in cryptocurrency trading.</p>



<p id="block-643c4ba8-b40b-4525-9a96-f280dbfbeb9d"><strong><em>DISCLAIMER:&nbsp;</em></strong><em>The Information on this&nbsp;website&nbsp;is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>



<p id="block-522ef498-a505-4d0b-9a0d-b2e5cca12111">Join us to keep track of news:&nbsp;<a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right" id="block-4fa7c042-0908-4ee5-9ff4-91607eb34413"><strong>Annie</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right" id="block-84ea04e6-519a-4165-8e39-faa42e0200e5"><strong>Coincu</strong>&nbsp;<strong>New</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ShapeShift-Reviews-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>AzukiDAO&#8217;s Lawsuit With Founder Zagabond To Recover 20,000 ETH Get Support</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/199572-azukidaos-lawsuit-zagabond-founder/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Foxy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 03:49:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[NFTs News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[# Cryptocurrencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[#Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Azuki]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Azuki Elementals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AzukiDAO]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[rug pull]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sue]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Zagabond]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=199572</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Jeremy Cahen founder of NFT marketplace Not Larva Labs, said he would help the AzukiDAO take legal action against co-founder Azuki Zagabond.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>The founder of Not Larva Labs said he has evidence of the Zagabond scam created by Azuki, and he is willing to testify in court.</em></li>



<li><em>AzukiDAO proposes to hire a lawyer to recover 20,000 ETH from the founder of Zagabond and sue the project.</em></li>



<li><em>So far, the vote has exceeded the majority to pass it.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Jeremy Cahen (Twitter nickname PAULY), founder of NFT marketplace Not Larva Labs, said he would happily help the Azuki community take legal action against co-founder Azuki Zagabond.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-90.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="655" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-90-1024x655.png" alt="AzukiDAO&#039;s Lawsuit With Founder Zagabond To Recover 20,000 ETH Get Support" class="wp-image-199588" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-90-1024x655.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-90-300x192.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-90-768x491.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-90-1536x982.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-90-750x480.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-90-1140x729.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-90.png 1681w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="AzukiDAO&#039;s Lawsuit With Founder Zagabond To Recover 20,000 ETH Get Support 24"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>Jeremy Cahen also said that Zagabond and his team fraudulently appropriated more than $100,000,000 from the community. Jeremy would love to testify in court about all this, and I have full personal information about many of the team members involved in these scams.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">I will gladly aid the Azuki community in their legal actions against <a href="https://twitter.com/ZAGABOND?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener">@ZAGABOND</a>.<br><br>He is a pathological liar and serial criminal and I and my colleagues and I spent over a year tracking him down to recover $3,000,000 USDC worth of funds that he defrauded.<br><br>He and his team have… <a href="https://t.co/kqSA7jA6hy" target="_blank">https://t.co/kqSA7jA6hy</a></p>&mdash; PAULY (@Pauly0x) <a href="https://twitter.com/Pauly0x/status/1675583611561443329?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener">July 2, 2023</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>Not Larva Labs founder&#8217;s endorsement of AzukiDAO after the community proposed hiring an attorney to assist the community in recovering 20,000 ETH from Zagabond and suing it yesterday.</p>



<p>Specific content includes: hiring a lawyer to file a lawsuit against Zagabond, the founder of Azuki, accusing the organization of having many Rug projects; withdrawing 20,000 ETH issued by Elementals from the team and distributing it to the DAO to promote the growth of the entire Azuki community and provide rewards and incentives for artists, content creators, and builder. So far, the vote has exceeded the majority to pass it.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-92.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="818" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-92-1024x818.png" alt="AzukiDAO&#039;s Lawsuit With Founder Zagabond To Recover 20,000 ETH Get Support" class="wp-image-199593" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-92-1024x818.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-92-300x240.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-92-768x613.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-92-1536x1226.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-92-750x599.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-92-1140x910.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-92.png 1721w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="AzukiDAO&#039;s Lawsuit With Founder Zagabond To Recover 20,000 ETH Get Support 25"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>Azuki Dao provides financial support for 20000E Dao. Funds will be used to help us organize a Study Group for the Lawsuit. The proposed voting deadline is July 3. It is known that AzukiDAO and 20000E DAO were founded by members and former owners of the Azuki community, not the official Azuki group.</p>



<p>Ahead of the news on May 10, 2022, the founder of the Azuki team, ZAGABOND.ETH, <a href="https://mirror.xyz/0x1Cb8332607fba6A780DdE78584AD3BFD1eEB1E40/yG8rI1lpQGLPhZch0kjxYRjKTtA9rAL51zg-ZrURyAc" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">admitted</a> in a mirror post that the Azuki team has operated three projects CryptoPhunks, Tendies, and CryptoZunks, in the past year.</p>



<p>At the heart of the controversy is their supposed strategy of &#8216;pulling the rug&#8217;, used in the &#8220;Azuki Elementals&#8221; casting process. The move deeply upset the staunch holders of the project.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-91.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="576" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-91-1024x576.png" alt="AzukiDAO&#039;s Lawsuit With Founder Zagabond To Recover 20,000 ETH Get Support" class="wp-image-199591" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-91-1024x576.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-91-300x169.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-91-768x432.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-91-750x422.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-91-1140x641.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-91.png 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="AzukiDAO&#039;s Lawsuit With Founder Zagabond To Recover 20,000 ETH Get Support 26"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>Originating from the launch of Azuki&#8217;s new series, &#8220;Azuki Elementals&#8221;. The series sold out in less than 20 minutes for 2 ETH each, raising an impressive $38 million.</p>



<p>Many issues surfaced during the launch, from grievances about the short 10-minute time period for Mint being whitelisted to site overload leading to Mint errors and duplications &#8211; overduplication of features between the original Azuki and the new Azuki Elementals. Investors expressed concern about the potential dilution of the first-generation Azuki&#8217;s value. The controversy escalated when the project team reportedly moved 20,000 ETH shortly after the launch.</p>



<p>The event was marred with allegations of unfair behavior and the dizzying price drop of the original Azuki collection, which <a href="https://coincu.com/199468-azuki-nft-floor-price-dropped-54-last-7-days/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">plummeted</a> from over 17 ETH just a week ago to just 5.8 ETH.</p>



<p id="block-643c4ba8-b40b-4525-9a96-f280dbfbeb9d"><strong><em>DISCLAIMER:&nbsp;</em></strong><em>The Information on this&nbsp;website&nbsp;is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>



<p id="block-522ef498-a505-4d0b-9a0d-b2e5cca12111">Join us to keep track of news:&nbsp;<a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right" id="block-4fa7c042-0908-4ee5-9ff4-91607eb34413"><strong>Foxy</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right" id="block-84ea04e6-519a-4165-8e39-faa42e0200e5"><strong>Coincu</strong>&nbsp;<strong>News</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Thumb-2023-Foxy-47-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Market Overview Last Week From June 26th To July 2nd</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/199564-market-overview-from-june-26th-to-july-2nd/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[David]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 03:44:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[# Cryptocurrencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[#Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[#marketoverview]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[#Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=199564</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The market overview provides an overview of the cryptocurrency market from June 26th to July 2nd. It includes comprehensive updates and analyses of the market trends and movements during this period. The market overview covers a range of topics, such as the performance of major cryptocurrencies, the impact of news events on the market, and [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The market overview provides an overview of the cryptocurrency market from June 26th to July 2nd. It includes comprehensive updates and analyses of the market trends and movements during this period. The market overview covers a range of topics, such as the performance of major cryptocurrencies, the impact of news events on the market, and the overall sentiment of investors. By examining these factors in detail, the market overview aims to provide readers with a deeper understanding of the current state of the cryptocurrency market and the factors that are driving its movements.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Quick look market overview about big news!</strong></h2>



<p>Binance&#8217;s L2 opBNB network is currently running on the testnet. There is a lot of information about this airdrop with the slogan that if you missed BNB in 2017, you should not miss this one, although Binance has announced that there is no airdrop. The way to do it is similar to other L2s, by going to the faucet token testnet and experiencing it.</p>



<p>Binance Labs announces the results of the 5th Incubation Program, consisting of 5 projects receiving investment out of 12 selected for review: Bracket Labs, DappOS, Kryptoskatt, Mind Network, and zkPass. More than 900 projects were registered for the 5th incubation round, but only 12 were selected for review. Finally, only 5 projects were invested in, showing the program&#8217;s strict requirements. Binance Labs also revealed that the 6th incubation round is about to open for registration. Interested projects should follow Binance&#8217;s Twitter for the latest updates.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-gallery has-nested-images columns-default is-cropped wp-block-gallery-5 is-layout-flex">
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-03_10-25-00.jpg"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="578" data-id="199579" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-03_10-25-00-1024x578.jpg" alt="Market Overview - Binance news
" class="wp-image-199579" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-03_10-25-00-1024x578.jpg 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-03_10-25-00-300x169.jpg 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-03_10-25-00-768x433.jpg 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-03_10-25-00-750x423.jpg 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-03_10-25-00-1140x643.jpg 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-03_10-25-00.jpg 1383w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Market Overview Last Week From June 26th To July 2nd 27"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">Market overview &#8211; Binance news</figcaption></figure>
</figure>



<p>MicroStrategy has just bought an additional 12,333 $BTC. The average estimated price of this amount of $BTC is $28,136, meaning that the fund currently has a profit of ~$27.6M.</p>



<p>The chairman of the Fed said that interest rates could be raised two more times. Some macroeconomic news from last week: The PCE inflation index decreased to 3.8%, much lower than the estimated 4.6%. Core PCE is at 4.6%, lower than the estimated 4.7%.</p>



<p>SEC said: &#8220;BTC ETF applications are not yet complete,&#8221; causing the price of BTC to drop to 29,500 in the middle of the week. Some updates on Bitcoin Spot ETF:</p>



<p>Fidelity, Wisdomtree, Invesco/Galaxy, and VanEck have all amended their proposals for Bitcoin Spot ETF and submitted new versions to the SEC.</p>



<p>ArkInvest also revised its proposal, but only the current version was modified. This means that the SEC did not return the proposal, so over time, if an ETF is approved, Cathie Wood ArkInvest will be the first company.</p>



<p>All proposals state that they: &#8220;expect to participate in a monitoring agreement with Coinbase, Inc.&#8221;</p>



<p>Bitwise also revised its proposal but did not include any sharing agreement language.</p>



<p>Companies are working very quickly.</p>



<p>BlackRock has not yet revised its text, and on the Nasdaq website, BlackRock&#8217;s proposal is still listed as &#8220;pending.&#8221;</p>



<p>It is important to note that the SEC has not made any official announcements, and all information we hear is from the Wall Street Journal.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Market overview &#8211;</strong> <strong>Celsius will begin liquidating its altcoins into BTC and ETH to repay its creditors!</strong></h2>



<figure class="wp-block-gallery has-nested-images columns-default is-cropped wp-block-gallery-7 is-layout-flex">
<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-03_10-25-05.jpg"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="631" height="513" data-id="199580" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-03_10-25-05.jpg" alt="photo 2023 07 03 10 25 05" class="wp-image-199580" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-03_10-25-05.jpg 631w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-03_10-25-05-300x244.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 631px) 100vw, 631px" title="Market Overview Last Week From June 26th To July 2nd 28"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">Market overview &#8211; Celsius</figcaption></figure>
</figure>



<p>The sale begins on July 1st, and some tokens include:</p>



<p>CEL &#8211; $100 million (CEL&#8217;s current market cap is $37 million) </p>



<p>MATIC &#8211; $58 million </p>



<p>ADA &#8211; $28 million </p>



<p>LINK &#8211; $20 million </p>



<p>LTC &#8211; $19 million </p>



<p>BCH &#8211; $15.7 million</p>



<p>So Celsius&#8217; debtors and customers will soon receive their compensation!</p>



<p>Polynetwork has been hacked again. Previously, it was involved in a nearly $600M incident. This time, $42 billion was minted, mostly on Chain Metis. Details:</p>



<ul>
<li>99,999,184 BNB and 10 billion BUSD were issued on Metis.</li>



<li>999.8127 SHIB was issued on Heco, 87,579,118 COW and 999,998,434 OOE, 636,643,868 STACK, 88,640,563 GM,2,175,053 03 were issued on Polygon.</li>



<li>378,028,371 STACK, 82,854,568 XTM, 11,026,341 SPAY, issued 89,383,712 GM on Avalanche, 8,882,911 METIS, 926,160,132 DOV, 978,102,855 SLD.</li>



<li>And other assets were issued on BSC.</li>
</ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Market overview &#8211; Some significant unlocking periods in July.</strong></h2>



<figure class="wp-block-gallery has-nested-images columns-default is-cropped wp-block-gallery-9 is-layout-flex">
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-03_10-25-08.jpg"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="586" data-id="199581" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-03_10-25-08-1024x586.jpg" alt="photo 2023 07 03 10 25 08" class="wp-image-199581" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-03_10-25-08-1024x586.jpg 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-03_10-25-08-300x172.jpg 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-03_10-25-08-768x440.jpg 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-03_10-25-08-750x429.jpg 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-03_10-25-08-1140x653.jpg 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-03_10-25-08.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Market Overview Last Week From June 26th To July 2nd 29"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">Market overview &#8211; Tokens unlocked</figcaption></figure>
</figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Market overview &#8211;</strong> <strong>Update some macro events that may affect crypto in July.</strong></h2>



<p> <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f4cc.png" alt="📌" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> 1:00 6/7: FOMC Meeting &#8211; High impact </p>



<p><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f4cc.png" alt="📌" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> 19:15 6/7: ADP Non-farm &#8211; Medium impact</p>



<p> <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f4cc.png" alt="📌" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> 19:30 6/7: US Unemployment Claims &#8211; Medium impact</p>



<p> <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f4cc.png" alt="📌" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> 21:00 6/7: ISM Services PMI &#8211; Medium impact </p>



<p><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f4cc.png" alt="📌" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> 19:30 7/7: Non-farm Payrolls &#8211; High impact </p>



<p><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f4cc.png" alt="📌" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> 19:30 12/7: US CPI Release &#8211; High impact </p>



<p><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f4cc.png" alt="📌" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> 19:30 13/7: US PPI Release &#8211; Fairly high impact </p>



<p><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f4cc.png" alt="📌" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> 19:30 18/7: US Retail Sales &#8211; Fairly high impact </p>



<p><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f4cc.png" alt="📌" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> 1:00 27/7: FED Interest Rate Decision &#8211; High impact </p>



<p><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f4cc.png" alt="📌" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> 19:30 27/7: US GDP Release &#8211; High impact </p>



<p><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f4cc.png" alt="📌" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> 19:30 28/7: US Core PCE &#8211; Fairly high impact.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Market overview &#8211; Trend analysis for this week!</strong></h2>



<p>The trend will likely be POW coins due to next year&#8217;s halving event. Market overview &#8211; Here are some Pow coins in the BTC ecosystem that are frequently mentioned:</p>



<p>$STX &#8211; BTC Layer 2, smart contracts; $BCH &#8211; BTC fork; $RIF &#8211; identity &amp; storage; $T &#8211; tBTC, a merger between $KEEP and $NU; $HARD &#8211; lending &amp; borrowing BTC, KAVA eco; $REN &#8211; defi BTC; $BADGER &#8211; defi for BTC; $PNT &#8211; ptokens for BTC; $ALEX: Dex of $STX $SOV: Smartcontract, Lending, Borrowing; $PCX: BTC Layer2 omniBTC; $ORD: Dex $ML: BTC layer2 (high inflation); $LBTC: Lighting Bitcoin; $BC: Old Bitcoin; BRC20 $ORDI, $VMPX, $PEPEBRC, $MEMEBRC, $PIZABRC, $TRAC, $BIOP, $BSVBRC &#8230;</p>



<p>This year is the year of Cex fud, so let&#8217;s take a look at Dex</p>



<figure class="wp-block-gallery has-nested-images columns-default is-cropped wp-block-gallery-11 is-layout-flex">
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="661" data-id="199582" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-03_10-25-12-1024x661.jpg" alt="photo 2023 07 03 10 25 12" class="wp-image-199582" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-03_10-25-12-1024x661.jpg 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-03_10-25-12-300x194.jpg 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-03_10-25-12-768x496.jpg 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-03_10-25-12-750x484.jpg 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-03_10-25-12-1140x736.jpg 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-03_10-25-12.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Market Overview Last Week From June 26th To July 2nd 30"><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">Market overview &#8211; DEX trading volume</figcaption></figure>
</figure>



<p>DEX trading <a href="https://coincu.com/198147-may-the-ethereum-price-reach-2000-again/" data-type="URL" data-id="https://coincu.com/198147-may-the-ethereum-price-reach-2000-again/">volume on Ethereum </a>is currently the highest, followed by Arbitrum, BNB Chain, and Polygon.</p>



<p>Since Arbitrum launched its token, it has been relatively quiet, with much Fud about the foundation selling tokens. With this volume, there may be many gems in this ecosystem soon.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER:&nbsp;</em></strong><em>The information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>



<p>Join us to keep track of news:&nbsp;<a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong><em>David</em></strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong><em>Coincu News</em></strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/c7dec957c25c12024b4d-1024x731.jpg" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/jpeg" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shakepay Reviews: The Easiest Way For Canadians To Buy And Earn Bitcoin?</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/199561-shakepay-reviews-canadians-to-buy-earn-bitcoin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Annie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 03:35:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange Reviews]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buy And Earn Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shakepay]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shakepay Reviews]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=199561</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Shakepay is a Canadian-based cryptocurrency platform and mobile application that offers a user-friendly and convenient way for users to buy, sell, and manage cryptocurrencies. With its intuitive interface, Shakepay simplifies the process of entering the world of cryptocurrencies, particularly for Canadian users. Shakepay&#8217;s key features include the ability to buy and sell cryptocurrencies using Canadian [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Shakepay is a Canadian-based cryptocurrency platform and mobile application that offers a user-friendly and convenient way for users to buy, sell, and manage cryptocurrencies. </p>


<div class="wp-block-image is-style-default">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-86.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="616" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-86-1024x616.png" alt="image 86" class="wp-image-199573" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-86-1024x616.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-86-300x181.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-86-768x462.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-86-1536x924.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-86-2048x1232.png 2048w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-86-750x451.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-86-1140x686.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Shakepay Reviews: The Easiest Way For Canadians To Buy And Earn Bitcoin? 31"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>With its intuitive interface, Shakepay simplifies the process of entering the world of cryptocurrencies, particularly for Canadian users.</p>



<p>Shakepay&#8217;s key features include the ability to buy and sell cryptocurrencies using Canadian dollars (CAD), instant transfers between Shakepay users, the SP Card for cryptocurrency spending, and a secure cryptocurrency wallet. The platform emphasizes security by implementing measures like encryption, two-factor authentication, and cold storage for funds.</p>



<p>While Shakepay has its strengths, such as its user-friendly interface and instant transfers, there are also some limitations to consider. Shakepay has a limited selection of cryptocurrencies available for trading, and it is currently only accessible to Canadian residents. The platform charges fees for transactions and services, which users should take into account when using the platform.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">What Is Shakepay?</h2>


<div class="wp-block-image is-style-default">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Shakepay.jpeg"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="535" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Shakepay-1024x535.jpeg" alt="Shakepay" class="wp-image-199574" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Shakepay-1024x535.jpeg 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Shakepay-300x157.jpeg 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Shakepay-768x401.jpeg 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Shakepay-750x392.jpeg 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Shakepay-1140x596.jpeg 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Shakepay.jpeg 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Shakepay Reviews: The Easiest Way For Canadians To Buy And Earn Bitcoin? 32"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>Shakepay is a Canadian-based cryptocurrency platform and mobile application that allows users to buy, sell, and trade cryptocurrencies. It was founded in 2015 with the goal of making it easier for people to enter the world of cryptocurrencies. SP provides a user-friendly interface and a seamless experience for buying and selling cryptocurrencies, particularly Bitcoin and Ethereum.</p>



<p>One of the key features of Shakepay is its ability to simplify the process of purchasing cryptocurrencies using Canadian dollars (CAD). Users can link their bank accounts to the SP app and easily transfer funds to buy cryptocurrencies. SP also supports instant fund transfers between Shakepay users, making it convenient for friends or family members to send and receive cryptocurrencies.</p>



<p>Shakepay offers a cryptocurrency wallet where users can securely store their digital assets. The platform prioritizes security and implements various measures, such as multi-factor authentication and cold storage, to protect users&#8217; funds.</p>



<p>Shakepay also offers a Shakepay Card, which is a prepaid Visa card linked to users&#8217; Shakepay accounts. This card allows users to spend their cryptocurrencies at any merchant that accepts Visa, both online and offline. When making a purchase, the Shakepay Card automatically converts the selected cryptocurrency into the local currency, providing a seamless spending experience.</p>



<p>Shakepay aims to provide a user-friendly and accessible platform for Canadians to enter the world of cryptocurrencies, facilitating the buying, selling, and spending of digital assets.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">How Does Shakepay Work?</h2>


<div class="wp-block-image is-style-default">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-87.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="633" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-87-1024x633.png" alt="image 87" class="wp-image-199576" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-87-1024x633.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-87-300x185.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-87-768x475.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-87-1536x949.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-87-2048x1266.png 2048w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-87-750x464.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-87-1140x705.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Shakepay Reviews: The Easiest Way For Canadians To Buy And Earn Bitcoin? 33"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>Shakepay works as a cryptocurrency platform and mobile application that simplifies the process of buying, selling, and spending cryptocurrencies. Here&#8217;s an overview of how Shakepay works:</p>



<ol>
<li>Account Creation: To get started with SP, users need to download the SP mobile app from the App Store or Google Play Store. After installing the app, users can create an account by providing their personal information and completing the verification process.</li>



<li>Funding the Account: Once the account is set up, users can link their bank accounts to the SP app. This allows them to transfer funds from their bank account to their SP account in Canadian dollars (CAD). The linked bank account is used to deposit and withdraw funds.</li>



<li>Buying and Selling Cryptocurrencies: With funds in their SP account, users can buy cryptocurrencies, primarily Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH). SP offers a simple interface where users can enter the amount of cryptocurrency they wish to purchase and confirm the transaction. The app will display the current exchange rate and any associated fees. Selling cryptocurrencies follows a similar process, where users can choose to sell their digital assets and receive the proceeds in CAD.</li>



<li>Cryptocurrency Wallet: SP provides a built-in cryptocurrency wallet where users can securely store their digital assets. The wallet supports multiple cryptocurrencies, allowing users to hold and manage different tokens in one place. SP implements security measures, such as two-factor authentication and cold storage, to safeguard users&#8217; funds.</li>



<li>Sending and Receiving Cryptocurrencies: SP allows users to send and receive cryptocurrencies to and from other SP users instantly. Users can simply enter the recipient&#8217;s Shakepay username or scan a QR code to initiate a transfer. This feature makes it convenient for friends or family members to send and receive cryptocurrencies within the SP ecosystem.</li>



<li>Shakepay Card: SP offers a prepaid Visa card known as the SP Card. This card is linked to users&#8217; SP accounts and allows them to spend their cryptocurrencies at any merchant that accepts Visa. When making a purchase, the selected cryptocurrency is automatically converted into the local currency at the current exchange rate, providing a seamless spending experience.</li>



<li>Security and Compliance: SP places a strong emphasis on security and compliance. It employs industry-standard security measures, including encryption, multi-factor authentication, and cold storage for cryptocurrency storage. SP is also regulated by the Financial Transactions and Reports Analysis Centre of Canada (FINTRAC) as a Money Services Business (MSB), ensuring compliance with applicable regulations and Know Your Customer (KYC) requirements.</li>
</ol>



<p>Shakepay simplifies the process of buying, selling, and spending cryptocurrencies by providing a user-friendly interface, instant fund transfers, a secure wallet, and the Shakepay Card for easy cryptocurrency spending.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Features of Shakepay</h2>


<div class="wp-block-image is-style-default">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-88.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="506" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-88-1024x506.png" alt="image 88" class="wp-image-199577" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-88-1024x506.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-88-300x148.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-88-768x380.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-88-1536x759.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-88-2048x1013.png 2048w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-88-750x371.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-88-1140x564.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Shakepay Reviews: The Easiest Way For Canadians To Buy And Earn Bitcoin? 34"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>Shakepay offers several features that make it a popular choice for users looking to buy, sell, and manage cryptocurrencies:</p>



<ol>
<li>Buy and Sell Cryptocurrencies: SP allows users to easily buy and sell cryptocurrencies, including Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH), and others. Users can fund their SP accounts using Canadian dollars (CAD) via bank transfers and initiate transactions with competitive pricing.</li>



<li>Shakepay Card: Shakepay offers a prepaid Visa card called the SP Card, which is linked to users&#8217; SP accounts. The card allows users to spend their cryptocurrencies at any merchant that accepts Visa, both online and offline. When making a purchase, the selected cryptocurrency is automatically converted into the local currency, facilitating seamless spending.</li>



<li>Instant Fund Transfers: SP enables instant transfers of funds between Shakepay users. Users can send and receive cryptocurrencies instantly, making it convenient for peer-to-peer transactions or splitting bills among friends and family.</li>



<li>ShakeSats: ShakeSats is a unique feature of SP that allows users to buy and hold satoshis, which are smaller units of Bitcoin. ShakeSats enables users to accumulate small amounts of Bitcoin over time, contributing to the growing adoption and interest in cryptocurrencies.</li>



<li>Cryptocurrency Wallet: SP provides a secure and user-friendly cryptocurrency wallet for storing digital assets. The wallet supports various cryptocurrencies, offering users a convenient way to manage and hold their tokens. SP implements security measures, such as two-factor authentication and cold storage, to protect users&#8217; funds.</li>



<li>Auto-Buy: SP offers an Auto-Buy feature that allows users to set up recurring purchases of cryptocurrencies. Users can schedule automatic purchases at specified intervals, such as daily, weekly, or monthly, helping them to consistently invest in cryptocurrencies.</li>



<li>Shakepay Referral Program: SP has a referral program that rewards users for inviting others to join the platform. Users can earn referral bonuses in Bitcoin for each successful referral, contributing to their cryptocurrency holdings.</li>



<li>Security and Compliance: SP prioritizes the security of user funds and personal information. It employs robust security measures, including encryption, two-factor authentication, and cold storage. SP is also compliant with Canadian regulations as a registered Money Services Business (MSB) and follows Know Your Customer (KYC) procedures.</li>



<li>User Support: SP provides customer support to assist users with any questions or issues they may encounter. Users can reach out to the SP support team via email or in-app chat for prompt assistance.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Pros and Cons</h2>



<p>Pros of Shakepay:</p>



<ol>
<li>User-Friendly Interface: SP offers a user-friendly interface that makes it easy for beginners to navigate and use the platform for buying, selling, and managing cryptocurrencies.</li>



<li>Convenience: SP simplifies the process of buying and selling cryptocurrencies, particularly for Canadian users. It allows users to link their bank accounts, facilitating easy fund transfers and eliminating the need for complex deposit methods.</li>



<li>Instant Transfers: SP enables instant transfers of cryptocurrencies between Shakepay users, providing a convenient way to send and receive digital assets quickly.</li>



<li>Shakepay Card: The SP Card allows users to spend their cryptocurrencies at any merchant that accepts Visa, both online and offline. This feature provides flexibility and convenience for cryptocurrency holders to use their funds in everyday transactions.</li>



<li>Security Measures: SP implements robust security measures, including encryption, two-factor authentication, and cold storage, to protect users&#8217; funds and personal information. It is also regulated as a Money Services Business (MSB), ensuring compliance with relevant regulations.</li>



<li>Cryptocurrency Wallet: SP provides a built-in cryptocurrency wallet where users can securely store their digital assets. The wallet supports multiple cryptocurrencies, making it convenient for users to manage and hold their tokens in one place.</li>



<li>ShakeSats: SP&#8217;s ShakeSats feature allows users to accumulate small amounts of Bitcoin over time, making it accessible for users to participate in the world of cryptocurrencies.</li>
</ol>



<p>Cons of Shakepay:</p>



<ol>
<li>Limited Cryptocurrency Selection: SP primarily focuses on Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH) for buying and selling. While these are the most popular cryptocurrencies, users looking for a wider range of altcoins may find the selection limited.</li>



<li>Availability: SP is currently available only to Canadian residents. Users from other countries are unable to access and use the platform.</li>



<li>Limited Payment Options: SP primarily supports bank transfers as the funding method, which may be restrictive for users who prefer alternative payment methods like credit cards or PayPal.</li>



<li>Exchange Fees: SP charges fees for cryptocurrency transactions, including buying, selling, and converting cryptocurrencies. While the fees are competitive, they still represent an additional cost for users.</li>



<li>Customer Support: While SP offers customer support, some users have reported delays in response times or difficulties in getting their issues resolved promptly.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Shakepay Fees</h2>


<div class="wp-block-image is-style-default">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-89.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="565" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-89-1024x565.png" alt="image 89" class="wp-image-199578" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-89-1024x565.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-89-300x166.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-89-768x424.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-89-1536x847.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-89-2048x1130.png 2048w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-89-750x414.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-89-1140x629.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Shakepay Reviews: The Easiest Way For Canadians To Buy And Earn Bitcoin? 35"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p><br>Shakepay charges fees for various transactions and services on its platform. Here is an overview of the main fees associated with Shakepay:</p>



<ol>
<li>Trading Fees: SP charges trading fees when buying or selling cryptocurrencies. The fee structure is based on a percentage of the transaction amount and varies depending on the type of transaction (buy or sell) and the cryptocurrency being traded. The exact fee percentages can be found on the Shakepay website or within the app.</li>



<li>Conversion Fees: Shakepay applies conversion fees when converting between different cryptocurrencies within the platform. The conversion fee is a percentage-based fee applied to the transaction amount</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Shakepay Customer Service</h2>



<p>Shakepay provides customer service to assist users with any inquiries or issues they may encounter. Here are some ways to access Shakepay&#8217;s customer service:</p>



<ol>
<li>In-App Chat: The primary method to reach Shakepay&#8217;s customer service is through the in-app chat feature. Users can access the chat by logging into their SP account on the mobile app and navigating to the &#8220;Support&#8221; section. From there, they can initiate a chat conversation with a SP representative.</li>



<li>Email Support: Users can also contact SP&#8217;s customer service via email. They can send an email to <a href="mailto:support@shakepay.com">support@shakepay.com</a> with their questions or concerns, and a SP representative will respond to their query.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Conclusion</h2>



<p>Shakepay is a reputable and reliable platform for individuals in Canada who want to engage with cryptocurrencies. It provides a seamless user experience, prioritizes security, and offers features like the Shakepay Card to enable cryptocurrency spending. Users should carefully consider their needs and preferences to determine if Shakepay aligns with their requirements for buying, selling, and managing cryptocurrencies.</p>



<p id="block-643c4ba8-b40b-4525-9a96-f280dbfbeb9d"><strong><em>DISCLAIMER:&nbsp;</em></strong><em>The Information on this&nbsp;website&nbsp;is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>



<p id="block-522ef498-a505-4d0b-9a0d-b2e5cca12111">Join us to keep track of news:&nbsp;<a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right" id="block-4fa7c042-0908-4ee5-9ff4-91607eb34413"><strong>Annie</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right" id="block-84ea04e6-519a-4165-8e39-faa42e0200e5"><strong>Coincu</strong>&nbsp;<strong>New</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Shakepay-Reviews-The-Easiest-Way-For--1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>PolyNetwork Hacked Possibly Due To Stealing 3/4 Of Admin&#8217;s Private Key: Report</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/199559-polynetwork-hacked-due-to-stealing-private-key/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Foxy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 03:11:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[# Cryptocurrencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[#Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Admin&#039;s Private Key]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dedaub]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[polynetwork]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stealing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=199559</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Research by security firm Dedaub said that the root cause of PolyNetwork attack could be the theft of three-quarters of the administrator's private key.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>Security firm Dedaub reckons that three-quarters of an administrator&#8217;s private key being stolen led to the carnage on PolyNetwork.</em></li>



<li><em>However, the cause could be Rug Pull or offline software running on three of the four admins was compromised.</em></li>



<li><em>The Poly team has paused their EthCrossChainManager smart contract on several chains, notably Metis, BSC, and Ethereum.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Research by security firm Dedaub said that the root cause of PolyNetwork attack could be the theft of three-quarters of the administrator&#8217;s private key.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-84.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="538" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-84-1024x538.png" alt="PolyNetwork Hacked Possibly Due To Stealing 3/4 Of Admin&#039;s Private Key: Report" class="wp-image-199568" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-84-1024x538.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-84-300x158.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-84-768x403.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-84-750x394.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-84-1140x599.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-84.png 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="PolyNetwork Hacked Possibly Due To Stealing 3/4 Of Admin&#039;s Private Key: Report 36"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>Security firm Dedaub stated in a blog post that the root cause of the attack on the PolyNetwork cross-chain interaction protocol was not a logic error in the smart contract but most likely 3/4 errors in smart contracts. Poly Administrator&#8217;s private key has been stolen or misused.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Poly chain hack technical postmortem explains how the signature scheme of the cross-chain bridge was used as intended in smart contract Merkle verifier.<br><br>It is presumed the keeper private keys were compromised (or misused).<a href="https://t.co/EXwSedk9cD" target="_blank">https://t.co/EXwSedk9cD</a></p>&mdash; Dedaub (@dedaub) <a href="https://twitter.com/dedaub/status/1675627338371874816?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener">July 2, 2023</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>Dedaub also mentioned that it took PolyNetwork seven hours to respond to the attack, while the attacker orchestrated several transactions across multiple chains to take advantage of this. So far, there is no clear evidence that the private keys were stolen. It could be Rug Pull, or maybe offline software running on three of the four admins was compromised.</p>



<p>Suppose Poly developers confirm that the attack is linked to a compromised signing key. In that case, it raises questions about the applicability of a centralized cross-chain bridge that controls a lot of money.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-85.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="512" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-85-1024x512.png" alt="PolyNetwork Hacked Possibly Due To Stealing 3/4 Of Admin&#039;s Private Key: Report" class="wp-image-199569" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-85-1024x512.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-85-300x150.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-85-768x384.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-85-1536x768.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-85-360x180.png 360w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-85-750x375.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-85-1140x570.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-85.png 2048w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="PolyNetwork Hacked Possibly Due To Stealing 3/4 Of Admin&#039;s Private Key: Report 37"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>The attack also showed less-than-perfect monitoring of the Poly group of the underlying bridge. If the protocol has been established with a rapid monitoring solution, this will significantly reduce the response time and potentially save some affected money.</p>



<p>It was reported yesterday that hackers had released over a dozen assets across several chains through Poly Network, worth $35 billion. The Poly team <a href="https://coincu.com/199536-polynetwork-57-assets-10-blockchains-affected/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">has paused</a> their EthCrossChainManager smart contract on several chains, most notably on Metis, BSC, and Ethereum.</p>



<p>There are reports that the attackers have transferred more than $5 million in cryptocurrencies on chains like Ethereum.</p>



<p>This is not the first time PolyNetwork has been hacked. Previously on August 10, 2021, caused more than $600 million in damage, but fortunately, the amount was refunded.</p>



<p id="block-643c4ba8-b40b-4525-9a96-f280dbfbeb9d"><strong><em>DISCLAIMER:&nbsp;</em></strong><em>The Information on this&nbsp;website&nbsp;is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>



<p id="block-522ef498-a505-4d0b-9a0d-b2e5cca12111">Join us to keep track of news:&nbsp;<a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right" id="block-4fa7c042-0908-4ee5-9ff4-91607eb34413"><strong>Foxy</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right" id="block-84ea04e6-519a-4165-8e39-faa42e0200e5"><strong>Coincu</strong>&nbsp;<strong>News</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Thumb-2023-Foxy-46-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Report SEC Chairman Gary Gensler Resigned Is It True?</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/199551-sec-chairman-gary-gensler-resigned-is-it-true/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Foxy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 02:35:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[# Cryptocurrencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[#Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gary Gensler]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Resigned]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rumor]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=199551</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A fake website recently started spreading rumors that SEC Chairman Gary Gensler has resigned, but that is not true.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>Recently a report has begun to spread rumors that SEC Chairman Gary Gensler has resigned.</em></li>



<li><em>However, SEC PR told FOX reporters that Gensler would not step down.</em></li>



<li><em>President Gary Gensler is on a full-blown assault on the crypto industry, most notably the recent lawsuit with Binance and Coinbase.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>A fake website recently started<a href="https://www.thecryptoalert.com/post/sec-sources-confirm-gary-gensler-resignation" target="_blank" rel="noopener"> spreading rumors </a>that SEC Chairman Gary Gensler has resigned, but that is not true.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-81.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="576" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-81-1024x576.png" alt="Report SEC Chairman Gary Gensler Resigned Is It True?" class="wp-image-199554" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-81-1024x576.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-81-300x169.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-81-768x432.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-81-750x422.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-81-1140x641.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-81.png 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Report SEC Chairman Gary Gensler Resigned Is It True? 38"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>The site publishes only a few articles. Some crypto bloggers are also spreading this rumor. In it, one of the sources reporting Gensler&#8217;s resignation is the CoinDesk website. CoinDesk cited an unnamed source as saying that Gensler resigned immediately. However, CoinDesk later updated its story to say that the source was mistaken and Gensler did not leave.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-80.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="900" height="182" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-80.png" alt="Report SEC Chairman Gary Gensler Resigned Is It True?" class="wp-image-199553" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-80.png 900w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-80-300x61.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-80-768x155.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-80-750x152.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 900px) 100vw, 900px" title="Report SEC Chairman Gary Gensler Resigned Is It True? 39"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">Fake reports are spread</figcaption></figure></div>


<p>After the rumor spread, FOX Business Network (FBN) reporter Charles Gasparino attempted to get an answer from SECGov, and as expected, its media department announced that Gary Gensler was not resigning.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Breaking: As expected <a href="https://twitter.com/SECGov?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener">@SECGov</a> PR says <a href="https://twitter.com/GaryGensler?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener">@GaryGensler</a> is not resigning</p>&mdash; Charles Gasparino (@CGasparino) <a href="https://twitter.com/CGasparino/status/1675650578657992704?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener">July 2, 2023</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>At the beginning of June, the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) launched two major legal actions against two leading cryptocurrency exchanges, Binance and Coinbase, accusing the exchanges of violating the US securities laws.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-82.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="788" height="443" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-82.png" alt="Report SEC Chairman Gary Gensler Resigned Is It True?" class="wp-image-199555" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-82.png 788w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-82-300x169.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-82-768x432.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-82-750x422.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 788px) 100vw, 788px" title="Report SEC Chairman Gary Gensler Resigned Is It True? 40"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>At the heart of this attack is Gary Gensler, who was appointed SEC chairman in February 2021. Gensler today looks like <a href="https://coincu.com/193410-sec-chair-gary-gensler-warns-crypto-frenzy/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">the crypto industry&#8217;s worst enemy</a>, putting out what sounds like a complete negation of the entire point of the existence of cryptocurrencies.</p>



<p>Having said that, since his first year as head of the SEC, Gensler has consistently believed that most cryptocurrencies fit the definition of securities and crypto exchanges. Cryptocurrency needs to be registered with the SEC, and stablecoins are &#8220;poker chips&#8221; to gamble on cryptocurrencies that pose systemic economic risks.</p>



<p>At the same time, Gensler said in testimony before Congress that the US government and Congress should develop more definitive rules for cryptocurrencies.</p>



<p>However, contrary to this argument, Coinbase has always made the point that the SEC has been deliberately dodging the requirement to make specific regulations for the crypto industry and many other companies in the industry for a long time. However, the crypto companies is still accused of non-compliance.</p>



<p id="block-643c4ba8-b40b-4525-9a96-f280dbfbeb9d"><strong><em>DISCLAIMER:&nbsp;</em></strong><em>The Information on this&nbsp;website&nbsp;is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>



<p id="block-522ef498-a505-4d0b-9a0d-b2e5cca12111">Join us to keep track of news:&nbsp;<a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right" id="block-4fa7c042-0908-4ee5-9ff4-91607eb34413"><strong>Foxy</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right" id="block-84ea04e6-519a-4165-8e39-faa42e0200e5"><strong>Coincu</strong>&nbsp;<strong>News</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Thumb-2023-Foxy-45-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
