<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 18:57:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Ethereum’s Vitalik Buterin Talks on Privacy with Stealth Addresses</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ethereum-buterin-stealth-addresses/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ethereum-buterin-stealth-addresses/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 14:50:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stealth Addresses]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vitalik Buterin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=233580</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ethereum-buterin-stealth-addresses/">Ethereum’s Vitalik Buterin Talks on Privacy with Stealth Addresses</a></p>
<p>Vitalik pointed out that there has been no viable stealth address solution thus far, even though it offers a more functional and comprehensive privacy solution when compared to the now-sanctioned crypto mixer Tornado Cash.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ethereum-buterin-stealth-addresses/">Ethereum’s Vitalik Buterin Talks on Privacy with Stealth Addresses</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ethereum-buterin-stealth-addresses/">Ethereum’s Vitalik Buterin Talks on Privacy with Stealth Addresses</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/vitalik-buterin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Vitalik Buterin</a>, the co-founder and the most popular figure behind the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a> blockchain network has <a href="https://vitalik.ca/general/2023/01/20/stealth.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">shared insights</a> on the use of stealth addresses as a viable way to maintain true privacy on blockchain networks.</p>
<p>In a blog post tagged “An incomplete guide to stealth addresses,” the blockchain developer highlighted how maintaining privacy has been more vital at this time. According to him, every transaction carried out on the blockchain registers different data that places the sender’s affairs right up for the public to see.</p>
<p>While he noted that there has been a series of proposed solutions, he considers stealth addresses as one that may be viable for the Ethereum blockchain in the long term if developmental work is put into it.</p>
<p>Describing how stealth addresses work, he used two hypothetical names, Alice and Bob. He said this technology can help Alice send Bob some money to Bob and Bob on the other hand can use the addresses to shield his identity as the recipient of the funds which could be an asset or a <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Non-Fungible Token</a> (NFT).</p>
<p>While he pointed out that the Stealth addresses are often generated by either Alice or Bob but it is often controlled by the receiver. Per his note;</p>
<p>“Bob generates and keeps secret a spending key, and uses this key to generate a stealth meta-address. He passes this meta-address to Alice (or registers it on ENS). Alice can perform a computation on this meta-address to generate a stealth address belonging to Bob. She can then send any assets she wants to send to this address, and Bob will have full control over them. Along with the transfer, she publishes some extra cryptographic data (an ephemeral pubkey) on-chain that helps Bob discover that this address belongs to him.”</p>
<p>Vitalik pointed out that there has been no viable stealth address solution thus far, even though it offers a more functional and comprehensive privacy solution when compared to the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-treasury-sanctions-tornado-cash/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">now-sanctioned</a> crypto mixer Tornado Cash.</p>
<h2>Vitalik Buterin on the Future of Privacy</h2>
<p>In his view, developers will launch more functional products that are usable when they focus optimally on developing stealth addresses that can be implemented easily.</p>
<p>“Basic stealth addresses can be implemented fairly quickly today, and could be a significant boost to practical user privacy on Ethereum,” he said, adding that “They do require some work on the wallet side to support them. That said, it is my view that wallets should start moving toward a more natively multi-address model [&#8230;] for other privacy-related reasons as well.”</p>
<p>He pointed out that there are some challenges that may be experienced including longer-term usability issues. Rather than get discouraged, Vitalik said he is optimistic that these can be addressed over time.</p>
<p>“In the longer term, these problems can be solved, but the stealth address ecosystem of the long term is looking like one that would really heavily depend on zero-knowledge proofs.”</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/big-banks-rival-apple-pay-paypal/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ethereum-buterin-stealth-addresses/">Ethereum’s Vitalik Buterin Talks on Privacy with Stealth Addresses</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ethereum-buterin-stealth-addresses/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Big Banks Unveil Payment Wallet to Rival Apple Pay &amp; PayPal</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/big-banks-rival-apple-pay-paypal/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/big-banks-rival-apple-pay-paypal/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 14:44:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FinTech News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bank of america]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[goldman sachs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jpmorgan chase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mastercard]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[paypal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[visa]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[wells fargo]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=233570</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/big-banks-rival-apple-pay-paypal/">Big Banks Unveil Payment Wallet to Rival Apple Pay &#038; PayPal</a></p>
<p>A host of big banks in America are collaborating on a payment wallet to facilitate debit &#038; credit-driven online retail transactions. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/big-banks-rival-apple-pay-paypal/">Big Banks Unveil Payment Wallet to Rival Apple Pay &#038; PayPal</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/big-banks-rival-apple-pay-paypal/">Big Banks Unveil Payment Wallet to Rival Apple Pay &#038; PayPal</a></p>
<p>Several big American banks are <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/banks-plan-payment-wallet-to-compete-with-paypal-apple-pay-11674433472" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reportedly</a> planning a payment wallet to facilitate online shopping. These banks include<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/wells-fargo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"> Wells Fargo</a> (NYSE: WFC), <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/bank-of-america/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bank of America</a> (NYSE: BAC), <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/jpmorgan-chase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">JPMorgan Chase</a> (NYSE: JPM), and four other financial institutions. According to the Wall Street Journal, the group’s planned digital wallet service could compete with PayPal and Apple Pay.</p>
<p>As it stands, the big banks’ payment wallet has yet to have an official name. Regardless, Early Warning Services LLC will manage the digital payment. EWC LLC is a bank-owned company that operates the money transfer platform Zelle. Despite any perceived similarities between Zelle and the upcoming payment feature, the banks’ initiative will operate separately from Zelle.</p>
<h2>Takeaways from Upcoming Big Banks Digital Wallet Initiative</h2>
<p>The rollout of the new payment feature will begin in the second half of the year. This development implies that shoppers would soon be able to pay at merchants’ online checkout with debit and credit card-linked wallets. Furthermore, the wallet will launch with <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/visa-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Visa Inc</a> (NYSE: V) and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/mastercard/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Mastercard</a> (NYSE: MA) debit and credit cards. However, the facilitators of the card launch also reached out about the initiative to other card networks to gauge interest. These include Illinois-based financial services company and Discover Bank operator Discover Financial Services (NYSE: DFS).</p>
<p>A host of financially-driven platforms are responsible for the said service rollout. They include PNC Financial Services Group Inc (NYSE: PNC), US Bancorp (NYSE: USB), and Truist Financial Corp (NYSE: TFC). The bank consortium is still finetuning details of the digital payment’s customer experience. The process likely involves consumers typing their emails on a merchant’s checkout page. The merchant would then ping Early Warning Services to track its back-end connections to banks. The EWS process aims to identify which of the consumers’ cards is loadable to the wallet. Following this process, consumers could choose which card to use or opt out altogether.</p>
<p>Upon rollout, the banks expect to enable up to 150 million debit and credit cards within the wallet. Furthermore, usage eligibility stems from up-to-date payments on cards used online in recent years. In addition, US consumers who qualify for the cards upon their launch already have an email address and phone number.</p>
<h2>Traditional Banks Acknowledge Fintech &amp; Tech Threats</h2>
<p>According to inside sources, the stated goal of competing with PayPal Holdings (NASDAQ: PYPL) and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/apple-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Apple</a> (NASDAQ: AAPL) is practical. The involved banks worry they might lose control of their customer relationships to the fintech mainstay and consumer electronics giant’s payment schemes. Apple, in particular, poses a credible threat and is steepening its presence in mainstream financial services. For example, the California-based multinational tech company works on a savings account with <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/goldman-sachs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Goldman Sachs</a> (NYSE: GS). In addition, Apple reportedly also plans to launch a buy now pay later (BNPL) offering at some point in the future.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/germany-anti-trust-investigation-paypal/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/big-banks-rival-apple-pay-paypal/">Big Banks Unveil Payment Wallet to Rival Apple Pay &#038; PayPal</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/big-banks-rival-apple-pay-paypal/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Germany’s Watchdog Launches Anti-Trust Investigation into PayPal</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/germany-anti-trust-investigation-paypal/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/germany-anti-trust-investigation-paypal/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 14:27:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FinTech News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Amazon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[facebook]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[google]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[paypal]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=233569</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/germany-anti-trust-investigation-paypal/">Germany&#8217;s Watchdog Launches Anti-Trust Investigation into PayPal</a></p>
<p>Germany's FOC regulator stated that PayPal's users of terms are causing a possible hindrance to its competitors which has led to an investigation. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/germany-anti-trust-investigation-paypal/">Germany&#8217;s Watchdog Launches Anti-Trust Investigation into PayPal</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/germany-anti-trust-investigation-paypal/">Germany&#8217;s Watchdog Launches Anti-Trust Investigation into PayPal</a></p>
<p>Payments giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">PayPal</a> could be in trouble as Germany&#8217;s antitrust watchdog launched an investigation into PayPal in order to examine whether the US online payment giant was using its position to restrict competition in the market.</p>
<h2>Investigation into PayPal</h2>
<p>Germany&#8217;s Federal Cartel Office (FCO) also noted that they would examine if the conditions set out in PayPal&#8217;s terms of use constitute a possible &#8220;hindrance of competitors and restriction of price competition&#8221;.</p>
<p>FCO noted that PayPal is the leading payment service in Germany but also the most expensive in the region. Speaking on the development, FCO president Andreas Mundt said:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We will now examine what market power PayPal has and to what extent online retailers are dependent on offering PayPal as a payment method&#8221;.</p></blockquote>
<p>Currently, the charges paid by sellers to use PayPal&#8217;s service start at 2.49 percent of the payment in addition to 0.35 euros per transaction. The FCO stated that traders aren&#8217;t allowed to offer their goods and services at lower prices if the customers choose a cheaper payment service. Besides, the traders cannot even express a preference for payment methods other than PayPal.</p>
<p>The FCO noted that this prevents rival services from entering the market while keeping the surcharges higher. Mundt <a href="https://www.reuters.com/legal/german-cartel-office-initiates-proceedings-against-paypal-2023-01-23/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">added</a> that such a situation keeps the customers at the receiving end because &#8220;ultimately they pay for these higher fees indirectly through the product price.&#8221;</p>
<p>The new legislation that arrived in 2021 gave Germany&#8217;s antitrust watchdog FCO sweeping powers for taking action against tech companies that are suspected of abusing their dominant market positions. As a result, the FCO has already opened proceedings against tech giants like <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/amazon/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Amazon</a>, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/google/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Google</a>, and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/facebook/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Facebook</a>.</p>
<h2>PayPal and Crypto</h2>
<p>During the crypto bull run of 2020-21, PayPal made its entry into the crypto space allowing users to buy and sell digital assets on the platform. Last month in December 2022, PayPal <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-crypto-luxembourg/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">launched</a> its crypto offering in Luxembourg making a push in the European Union.</p>
<p>Furthermore, PayPal is also looking to expand its crypto services in the market. In October 2022, the payments service provider started allowing its users to swap Bitcoin from the PayPal wallet to other digital wallets.</p>
<p>However, as PayPal continues to make a move in the crypto space, it has to keep in tune with the growing regulatory scrutiny in the sector.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/spotify-layoff-scheme-tech-downturn/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/germany-anti-trust-investigation-paypal/">Germany&#8217;s Watchdog Launches Anti-Trust Investigation into PayPal</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/germany-anti-trust-investigation-paypal/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Spotify Resorts to Fresh Layoff Scheme amid Tech Downturn</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/spotify-layoff-scheme-tech-downturn/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/spotify-layoff-scheme-tech-downturn/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 12:01:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alphabet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Amazon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[microsoft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[spotify]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=233490</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/spotify-layoff-scheme-tech-downturn/">Spotify Resorts to Fresh Layoff Scheme amid Tech Downturn</a></p>
<p>Following its October headcount reduction, Swedish streaming giant Spotify looks to another layoff round to remain profitable.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/spotify-layoff-scheme-tech-downturn/">Spotify Resorts to Fresh Layoff Scheme amid Tech Downturn</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/spotify-layoff-scheme-tech-downturn/">Spotify Resorts to Fresh Layoff Scheme amid Tech Downturn</a></p>
<p>According to reports, music streaming giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/spotify/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Spotify</a> (NYSE: SPOT) is <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-01-23/spotify-seen-cutting-staff-as-soon-as-this-week-to-cut-costs" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">planning</a> a staff layoff this week. The latest Spotify layoff comes amid the sustained economic slowdown and follows last October&#8217;s headcount reduction. At a 2022 investors&#8217; presentation, Spotify chief financial officer Paul Vogel admitted that times are hard. According to him: the Stockholm-based company is &#8220;clearly aware of the increasing uncertainty regarding the global economy.&#8221;</p>
<p>Although the company cut 38 employees in October 2022, it did not specify how many workers it would fire this time. Nonetheless, as last reported, Spotify had a staff force of roughly 9,800.</p>
<p>Spotify was also among tech companies seeking austerity measures to remain competitive and profitable. In October last year, the Swedish audio streaming and media services provider sacked 38 employees from its Gimlet Media and Parcast podcast studio. In addition, Spotify also shut down 11 original podcasts from its in-house studios to further lower costs. Some canceled podcasts include &#8216;How to Save a Planet,&#8217; &#8216;Crime Show,&#8217; and &#8216;Medical Murders&#8217;. Furthermore, affected staff of these discontinued podcast shows who were not fired, got reassigned to new shows.</p>
<h2>Spotify Layoff Comes despite Expansive Investments in Podcast Businesses</h2>
<p>Having invested heavily in acquiring podcast networks across the last three years, Spotify hit a rough patch last year. The company previously spent $1 billion in strategic business acquisitions of numerous audio broadcasting platforms. However, although Spotify had rights to shows like &#8216;Armchair Expert&#8217; and &#8216;The Joe Rogan Experience,&#8217; its shares dropped 66% in 2022. In addition, the Swedish music-streaming giant has reportedly failed to provide its investors returns. Nonetheless, Spotify&#8217;s board administration expects a profitable podcast business within the next one to two years.</p>
<p>In 2022, Spotify had a monthly active user base of more than 433 million.</p>
<p>Spotify, like many tech companies, onboarded several new employees during the pandemic. These hires were to handle the increased operational scale and service demand. However, since that pandemic era, the capital market, particularly tech stocks, has been in a tailspin. Throughout much of last year, investors shirked tech stocks and crypto assets in favor of more stable, safe-haven securities. These tech selloffs resulted in several industry players, including <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/amazon/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Amazon</a> (NASDAQ: AMZN), <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/microsoft-corporation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Microsoft</a> (NASDAQ: MSFT), and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/meta/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Meta</a> (NASDAQ: META), employing cost-cutting measures. In addition to conducting mass layoffs, some measures also entailed shutting down &#8216;non-essential&#8217; or &#8216;non-profitable&#8217; operational activities.</p>
<h2>Alphabet Downsizing</h2>
<p>On Friday, Google parent <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/alphabet-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Alphabet Inc</a> (NASDAQ: GOOGL) announced that it was <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alphabet-layoff-12000-employees/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">laying off</a> around 12,000 employees. According to the multinational tech conglomerate, this downsizing cuts across its global operations. Furthermore, Alphabet CEO <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/sundar-pichai/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Sundar Pichai</a> also explained that the mammoth layoff represents approximately 6% of the company&#8217;s workforce. Pichai also said despite the global scale of the retrenchment, its impact would be immediate in the United States.</p>
<p>However, the Alphabet chief executive remains optimistic about the company&#8217;s artificial intelligence (AI) investments.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cardano-protocol-recovers-nodes-offline/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/spotify-layoff-scheme-tech-downturn/">Spotify Resorts to Fresh Layoff Scheme amid Tech Downturn</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/spotify-layoff-scheme-tech-downturn/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano Protocol Recovers after More than 50% of Nodes Went Offline</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/cardano-protocol-recovers-nodes-offline/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/cardano-protocol-recovers-nodes-offline/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 11:56:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ada]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sol]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[solana]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=233549</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cardano-protocol-recovers-nodes-offline/">Cardano Protocol Recovers after More than 50% of Nodes Went Offline</a></p>
<p>The Cardano outage is not a new occurrence for some of the majority of Layer-1 protocols.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cardano-protocol-recovers-nodes-offline/">Cardano Protocol Recovers after More than 50% of Nodes Went Offline</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cardano-protocol-recovers-nodes-offline/">Cardano Protocol Recovers after More than 50% of Nodes Went Offline</a></p>
<p>The Cardano (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/cardano/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ADA</a>) protocol recorded a temporary outage on at least 50% of its nodes over the weekend <a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/cardano-recovers-from-an-outage-on-50-relay-and-block-producing-nodes" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">according</a> to reports from a number of its Stake Pool Operators (SPO). According to an update shared on the official Telegram page of the Cardano SPO, a yet-to-be-identified anomaly was responsible for the outage.</p>
<p>Despite the concerns that the outage caused, its impact was not so detrimental as almost all of the nodes recovered automatically. According to the update shared, the outage was experienced in blocks 8300569 and 8300570.</p>
<p>“This appears to have been triggered by a transient anomaly causing two reactions in the node, some disconnected from a peer, others threw an exception and restarted,” the post said, highlighting the details behind the outage.</p>
<p>The announcement also highlighted that these sorts of outages have been anticipated in the design of the protocol and that the nodes behaved just as expected. When the blocks were restored, production notably continued at a slower pace with the team confirming that the reduced movement can be likened to the regular delays that are often experienced when the nodes are in normal operations.</p>
<p>This sort of outage may be caused by a factor that may turn out to be a recurring one. In order to prevent such a situation, Input Output Global said it is investigating the root cause of the outage.</p>
<p>“We’re now investigating the root cause for this anomalous behavior and implementing further logging measures alongside our regular monitoring procedures,” stated the official announcement.</p>
<p>In a chart posted by Tom Stokes, the co-founder of Node Shark and a Cardano SPO, the node synchronization fell from 100% to a little above 40% for over 300 reporting nodes. When the nodes recovered, the sync did not go back to 100 as it was pegged at around 87%.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="474" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">A few hours ago over half of all <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Cardano?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Cardano</a> nodes went offline. This is why decentralization matters. <a href="https://t.co/NXDVyKy8ep">pic.twitter.com/NXDVyKy8ep</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Tom Stokes (@eUTxO_pro) <a href="https://twitter.com/eUTxO_pro/status/1616983286739529730?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 22, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2>Cardano and Layer-1 Offline Challenges</h2>
<p>The Cardano outage is not a new occurrence for some of the majority of Layer-1 protocols. Over the past few years, Solana (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/solana/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SOL</a>) has also <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/solana-suffers-another-outage-sol-price-15-down/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">gone offline</a> more than once, lending a lot of criticism to the so-called Ethereum-killer protocols.</p>
<p>There was a significant difference between the Cardano nodes outage and that of Solana and it is that when the latter went offline, it stayed down for about 48 hours. This has raised another notable highlight for Cardano proponents who gushed over the resilience of the protocol when compared to its peers.</p>
<p>&#8220;The real takeaway for me is how impressively resilient the Cardano network is. Something took down ~60% of nodes and the network recovered in a few minutes and continued producing blocks throughout,&#8221; Pi Lanningham, chief technology officer of Cardano-based decentralized exchange SundaeSwap, <a href="https://twitter.com/Quantumplation/status/1617106867557203975" target="_blank" rel="noopener">tweeted</a>.</p>
<p>The outage is not impacting the price of ADA as the digital currency only recorded a marginal loss of 0.83% over the past 24 hours to $0.3794. The coin is still up by 8.32% in the trailing 7-day period.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-charity-30000-web3-scholarships/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cardano-protocol-recovers-nodes-offline/">Cardano Protocol Recovers after More than 50% of Nodes Went Offline</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/cardano-protocol-recovers-nodes-offline/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Charity Has Plans to Offer Over 30,000 Web3 Scholarships in 2023</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-charity-30000-web3-scholarships/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-charity-30000-web3-scholarships/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 11:13:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance charity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web3]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=233520</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-charity-30000-web3-scholarships/">Binance Charity Has Plans to Offer Over 30,000 Web3 Scholarships in 2023</a></p>
<p>The Binance Charity Scholar Program (BCSP) will also offer Web3 courses allowing students to upskill without having to overcome unnecessary financial barriers. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-charity-30000-web3-scholarships/">Binance Charity Has Plans to Offer Over 30,000 Web3 Scholarships in 2023</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-charity-30000-web3-scholarships/">Binance Charity Has Plans to Offer Over 30,000 Web3 Scholarships in 2023</a></p>
<p>Crypto exchange <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a> is gearing up to bring greater educational opportunities in the rapidly emerging Web 3 space. As per the latest development, Binance Charity will be funding over 30,000 Web3 scholarships as part of the Binance Scholar Program.</p>
<p>The Binance Charity Scholar Program (BCSP) will also offer Web3 courses allowing students to upskill without having to overcome unnecessary financial barriers. In their <a href="https://www.binance.com/es/feed/post/171332" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">blog post</a> last week, Binance Charity explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>“We recognize that digital education and skills development can be out of reach for many, resulting in a blockchain industry that lacks diversity and talent. The Binance Scholar Program changes all that, covering the costs of tuition and course fees at some of the world’s leading universities, colleges and vocational training providers.”</p></blockquote>
<p>The blog post also adds that nearly 82,000 students have shown interest in becoming part of the next BCSP cohort. Some of the education partners for Binance include top institutions such as the University of Western Australia, the Frankfurt School of Finance &amp; Management in Germany, the University of Nicosia in Cyprus, and the Nigerian-based technology hub Utiva. Besides, France-based tuition-free training center Simplon has also shown interest in hosting some of BCSP&#8217;s events.</p>
<p>“The response to our Web3 education projects has been unprecedented, showing the keen appetite of so many people to learn about blockchain, De-Fi [sic], NFTs, coding, and much more,” said Helen Hai, Head of Binance Charity Foundation.</p>
<h2>The Binance Charity Scholar Program</h2>
<p>The BCSP serves as a platform offering interested individuals access to necessary skills. In addition to offering support with course fees, the program also involves the provision of offering work opportunities for individuals to seek experience.</p>
<p>For implementing BSP, Binance distributed nearly $2.2 million in BUSD to prominent educational institutions across multiple countries. Last year, Binance Charity partnered with and funded Nigerian-based tech school Utiva by offering Web3 education to 50,000 students.</p>
<p>Furthermore, BCSP has also formed a collaboration with the Ukrainian Ministry of Digital Transformation. This is to help all the Ukrainians who have lost their jobs due to the war with Russia.</p>
<p>Additionally, Binance Charity has also received partnership support from Binance Academy, the non-profit blockchain educational portal of Binance. Helen Hai also added: “We’re seeing interest from a diverse range of people, including a great ratio of women [&#8230;] With so many more education initiatives with amazing partners in the pipeline, we’ve never been more excited to build a more inclusive Web3 world&#8221;.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/aptos-apt-surges-100-week/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-charity-30000-web3-scholarships/">Binance Charity Has Plans to Offer Over 30,000 Web3 Scholarships in 2023</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-charity-30000-web3-scholarships/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Aptos (APT) Surges Nearly 100% in Week, Here’s Why</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/aptos-apt-surges-100-week/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/aptos-apt-surges-100-week/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 10:45:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apt price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[aptos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[aptos (apt)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[aptos nft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nft]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=233485</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/aptos-apt-surges-100-week/">Aptos (APT) Surges Nearly 100% in Week, Here&#8217;s Why</a></p>
<p>Overall, APT has now surged over 300% from its November lows, to reach a new all-time high.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/aptos-apt-surges-100-week/">Aptos (APT) Surges Nearly 100% in Week, Here&#8217;s Why</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/aptos-apt-surges-100-week/">Aptos (APT) Surges Nearly 100% in Week, Here&#8217;s Why</a></p>
<p>Ever since hitting its November lows of $3, Aptos (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/aptos/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">APT</a>) has seen an impressive amount of gains. Presently, the native token of the Aptos blockchain holds the position as the most profitable crypto asset of the week. This was after gaining more than 94% in the last seven days. Interestingly, however, nearly 80% of that increase took place over the last three days.</p>
<p>Overall, APT has now surged over 300% from its November lows, to reach a new all-time high of $14.4, per CoinMarketCap <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/aptos/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">data</a>.</p>
<h2>Why Is Aptos (APT) Surging?</h2>
<p>At the moment, it appears there&#8217;s no stopping the momentum of the APT price surge. Even more impressive is that the present bear market also looks to have no bearing on the token&#8217;s growth. So it might be important to understand the factors triggering its price surge.</p>
<p>Firstly,  the general <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-market-outlook-ethereum-orbeon-protocol-ready-to-thrive/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">crypto market</a> has been experiencing some sort of relief since the turn of the new year. So much so, that a large percentage of digital assets are now performing significantly better than they did for the most part of 2022. In line with this, APT has also seen its market capitalization rise by 31.2% since the beginning of the year. As of this publication, APT has a market capitalization of over $2.3 billion and sits comfortably as the 30th largest token with a valuation of $14 billion.</p>
<p>Additionally, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NFT</a> markets on Aptos appear to have also played a major part in its recent growth. This is according to what data from Aptos-based NFT marketplace Topaz suggests. Per the data, trading volumes and minimum prices of NFT projects are sky-high at the moment. For instance, NFT collections such as Aptomingos and Aptos Monkeys account for tens of thousands in trading volume within the past 24 hours alone.</p>
<p>Despite this trend, however, some experts still believe that<a href="https://twitter.com/LomahCrypto/status/1617052324513579010?t=JoJ-d4tUQ5FhERkIts569g&amp;s=19" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"> interest in Aptos NFTs</a> will surge even more. Therefore, it might be safe to say that the APT token may be looking to even surpass its new all-time high in the coming days.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/xrp-scam-gol-tv-twitter-account/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/aptos-apt-surges-100-week/">Aptos (APT) Surges Nearly 100% in Week, Here&#8217;s Why</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/aptos-apt-surges-100-week/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Scam Goes Too Far: Advertized on GOL TV Twitter Account</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/xrp-scam-gol-tv-twitter-account/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/xrp-scam-gol-tv-twitter-account/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sanaa Sharma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 10:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=233481</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/xrp-scam-gol-tv-twitter-account/">XRP Scam Goes Too Far: Advertized on GOL TV Twitter Account</a></p>
<p>Recently, another news of a clone of XRP, called the RP Classic (XRPC), has grabbed the attention of several investors. Many crypto participants are not aware of the suspicious activities of the XRPC token.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/xrp-scam-gol-tv-twitter-account/">XRP Scam Goes Too Far: Advertized on GOL TV Twitter Account</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/xrp-scam-gol-tv-twitter-account/">XRP Scam Goes Too Far: Advertized on GOL TV Twitter Account</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/xrp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">XRP</a> has had several cases of people imposing as Ripple-associated entities and enticing users with shabby money-making investment schemes that are not exactly supported by authorized contracts or regulatory supervision. In an event of bizarre Twitter account hacking,  the XRP scam was also advertised on the official Twitter account of GOL TV, an American Sports Broadcaster.</p>
<p>The most common form of counterfeit tactic is the wrong impersonation of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ripple-labs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ripple</a> Chief Executive Officer <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/brad-garlinghouse/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Brad Garlinghouse</a>. Several times, the hoaxers pose as Garlinghouse and present an extremely enticing investment opportunity, like the standard doubling of one&#8217;s money. People who accept the bait are then left with no recovery of money and essentially no way to go about retrieving it.</p>
<p>This XRP scam which can be seen on a number of platforms at an international level is becoming harder to investigate due to its persistently developing antics with each passing day. Fraudsters acquire new techniques by the day to keep up with the new methods of detection employed by some of the most prominent virtual asset exchanges, law enforcement bodies, and other regulatory authorities. The thieves are technically actors who use fake accounts, the wrongful manipulation of public emotions, misrepresentations of credentials, multi-level marketing schemes, complicated phishing networks, and more advanced approaches in performing deceitful actions that victimize innocent XRP holders.</p>
<p>While these techniques can seem elementary and not very alluring, innocent victims who have not come across such cases usually fall prey to them. It is, therefore, important to confirm from some reliable authority or source before investing any capital. Another tip is to never transfer money to another account that cannot be verified without considerable research.</p>
<p>Recently, another news of a clone of XRP, called the RP Classic (XRPC), has grabbed the attention of several investors. Many crypto participants are not aware of the suspicious activities of the XRPC token. It is also the third most searched asset on the crypto market data aggregator CoinMarketCap.</p>
<p>According to CoinMarketCap <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/xrp-classic-token/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">data</a>, XRPC is up by 442.185% for the past thirty days. However, there&#8217;s not much information about the token which has a contract that goes back to Binance&#8217;s BNB Chain. The project&#8217;s website claims that its mission is to devise solutions to make the crypto industry a better and safer place.</p>
<p>The project&#8217;s idea is divided into four phases with the ultimate one being able to launch its very own blockchain. While all this sounds promising, other articles on the vision part do raise some eyebrows about the token likely being a scam.</p>
<p>Moreover, despite what the name suggests, it has no association with Ripple&#8217;s XRP Ledger or its token. No contract on the XRP Ledger blockchain exists with an equivalent contract name to the project.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/musk-zero-ads-subscription-twitter/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/xrp-scam-gol-tv-twitter-account/">XRP Scam Goes Too Far: Advertized on GOL TV Twitter Account</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/xrp-scam-gol-tv-twitter-account/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Elon Musk Plans to Roll Out Zero Ads Subscription Model for Twitter</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/musk-zero-ads-subscription-twitter/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/musk-zero-ads-subscription-twitter/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 09:42:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tesla]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[twitter]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=233456</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/musk-zero-ads-subscription-twitter/">Elon Musk Plans to Roll Out Zero Ads Subscription Model for Twitter</a></p>
<p>Tesla CEO Elon Musk intimated plans to revamp Twitter ads, including a zero ads subscription option for interested users.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/musk-zero-ads-subscription-twitter/">Elon Musk Plans to Roll Out Zero Ads Subscription Model for Twitter</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/musk-zero-ads-subscription-twitter/">Elon Musk Plans to Roll Out Zero Ads Subscription Model for Twitter</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/elon-musk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Elon Musk</a> plans to implement a zero-ads subscription model on the popular microblogging platform <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/twitter/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Twitter</a>. The <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/tesla/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tesla</a> chief executive&#8217;s intent to revamp Twitter advertisement frequency and size is part of ongoing improvement processes at the company.</p>
<p>Commenting on his proposed higher-priced zero-ad subscription model development, Musk <a href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1616853475220156417?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1616855485294215168%7Ctwgr%5E50b62273a3c6ee8dbc2c1497d0a4da26d1c29ba7%7Ctwcon%5Es2_&amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.benzinga.com%2Fnews%2F23%2F01%2F30515436%2Felon-musk-says-twitter-will-offer-zero-ads-subscription-model" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Ads are too frequent on Twitter and too big. Taking steps to address both in coming weeks.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Musk also explained that Twitter supports its advertising partners via new code and algorithms. According to him, this development could enhance advertising strategy by making displaying peddled items more timely and relevant. In Musk&#8217;s own words:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We&#8217;re approaching [the advertising strategy]; how do we get the ad to be as close to content as possible? If you&#8217;re shown an opportunity to buy something you actually want, that&#8217;s great — that&#8217;s the content, you&#8217;re serving someone&#8217;s need.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>However, the outspoken billionaire businessman did not provide additional details on the scheme&#8217;s implementation steps or exact pricing.</p>
<h2>Musk to Diversify Twitter Revenue Streams</h2>
<p>Since acquiring Twitter in October, Musk has sought to diversify the platform&#8217;s business from advertising revenue. Earlier this month, the social media company also announced it would relax its cause-based advertising policy. In addition, Twitter is looking to align its ad policy with television and other media outlets.</p>
<p>Elon Musk also previously proposed <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/musk-twitter-blue-dogecoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">&#8220;Twitter Blue&#8221;</a> subscriptions as another avenue to earn revenue outside standard ads. This service model sees subscribers pay a monthly fee of $8 to get verified check marks on their profile pages. At the time, the Tesla CEO was open to accepting payment for Twitter Blue in Dogecoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/dogecoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">DOGE</a>).</p>
<p>Prior to Musk&#8217;s overhaul of Twitter Blue, the company reserved the right to confer said check marks.</p>
<h2>Twitter Ads on Decline since Acquisition by Elon Musk</h2>
<p>Twitter has seen a remarkable decline in advertising activities and subsequent revenue since Musk took over the company. Numerous high-profile companies have pulled back from the site, pausing promotions, amid concern regarding its moderation policies. Companies that halted ads on Twitter include <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/general-motors/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">General Motors Corporation</a> (NYSE: GM) and Oreo Cookie maker Mondelez International Inc (NASDAQ: MDLZ). At the time, Musk addressed the cessations, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;I understand if [advertisers] want to kind of, you know, give it a minute and kind of see how things are evolving. But really, you know, the best way to see how things are evolving is just use Twitter.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>This advertising pause arguably also plays favorably into Musk&#8217;s overarching agenda for the company&#8217;s revenue streams. He previously stated that he did not want Twitter to become a &#8220;free-for-all hellscape.&#8221;</p>
<p>Twitter recently relaxed a three-year ban on political advertising as part of its continued policy transition. Furthermore, the social media company reportedly cut around 40 of its advertising data scientists and engineers at the turn of the year.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/genesis-bankruptcy-first-hearing/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/musk-zero-ads-subscription-twitter/">Elon Musk Plans to Roll Out Zero Ads Subscription Model for Twitter</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/musk-zero-ads-subscription-twitter/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Genesis Bankruptcy Case Scheduled for First Hearing on January 23rd </title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/genesis-bankruptcy-first-hearing/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/genesis-bankruptcy-first-hearing/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 09:39:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dcg]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[genesis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[genesis global capital]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=233469</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/genesis-bankruptcy-first-hearing/">Genesis Bankruptcy Case Scheduled for First Hearing on January 23rd </a></p>
<p>The bankruptcy hearing for embattled crypto lender Genesis commences today at a New York Southern District court. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/genesis-bankruptcy-first-hearing/">Genesis Bankruptcy Case Scheduled for First Hearing on January 23rd </a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/genesis-bankruptcy-first-hearing/">Genesis Bankruptcy Case Scheduled for First Hearing on January 23rd </a></p>
<p>According to <a href="https://www.justice.gov/ust-regions-r02/page/file/1563331/download" target="_blank" rel="noopener">court filings</a>, the first hearing for the bankruptcy case of crypto lender Genesis Capital will occur on January 23rd. The documents state that a judge of the US Bankruptcy Court for the Southern District of New York will preside over the case.</p>
<h2>Genesis Hearing Breakdown</h2>
<p>As the first step in Genesis’ bankruptcy hearing, the court will deliberate a number of decisions. These include whether to accept the requested Chapter 11 relief by Genesis Global Holdco and two of its lending business subsidiaries. These business subsidiaries, collectively known as Genesis Capital, are Genesis Global Capital and Genesis Asia Pacific.</p>
<p>The companies also requested a joint administration of the cases. Under the dictates of Chapter 11 bankruptcy, companies can propose reorganization plans to creditors while continuing business operations.</p>
<p>The United States Trustee would appoint a committee for unsecured creditors as part of the bankruptcy proceedings. This committee would also have the right to demand that the affected companies be consulted and apprised before making important decisions. In addition, the same due consultation process also applies to the said companies to participate in any reorganization plans. According to the court filings, the committee selection usually comprises twenty of the largest unsolicited creditors.</p>
<h2>The Bankruptcy</h2>
<p>Genesis <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/genesis-files-bankruptcy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">filed for bankruptcy protection</a> on January 19th, citing liabilities of up to $10 billion. The crypto lender’s insolvency came amid the latest <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-exchange-files-for-bankruptcy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX-fueled contagion</a> in the crypto space. <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a> went down in early November with around $175 million of Genesis’ crypto investment which hit the crypto lender hard. A few days after the Bahamian crypto exchange’s collapse, Genesis Global Capital suspended withdrawals on its platform. At the time, the company intimated the next steps it would take following the withdrawal suspension, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>“We have hired the best advisors in the industry to explore all possible options. Next week, we will deliver a plan for the lending business. We’re working tirelessly to identify the best solutions for the lending business, including, among other things, sourcing new liquidity.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Despite its January 2023 bankruptcy filing, two of Genesis’ subsidiaries remained unaffected. Still operating, as usual, are Genesis’ outfit offering derivatives and custody services as well as its Global Trading division. Commenting on a likely headway for Genesis amid its insolvency crisis, Paul Aronzon, an independent director at the company, explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>“We have crafted a deliberate process and roadmap through which we believe we can reach the best solution for clients and other stakeholders. We look forward to advancing our dialogue with DCG and our creditors’ advisors as we seek to implement a path to maximize value and provide the best opportunity for our business to emerge well-positioned for the future.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Genesis also said that it expects to have adequate funds left to repay its unstructured creditors at the end of the restructuring process. Furthermore, the company’s Chapter 11 plan also seeks a global resolution of all claims. In addition, Genesis also looks to create a trust that will distribute assets to creditors.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-coinbase-ethereum-shanghai/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/genesis-bankruptcy-first-hearing/">Genesis Bankruptcy Case Scheduled for First Hearing on January 23rd </a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/genesis-bankruptcy-first-hearing/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>