<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 22:29:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Crypto exchange Bitget responds on regulatory moves: &#8216;the industry&#8217;s broad reach are well appreciated&#8217;</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-exchange-bitget-appreciates-regulatory-moves-to-advance-the-industry/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 22:29:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[exchanges]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-exchange-bitget-appreciates-regulatory-moves-to-advance-the-industry/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways Regulatory agencies globally have been rolling out frameworks to guide the cryptocurrency market. Europe recently approved the MiCA guideline, while Hong Kong is set to release its crypto regulatory framework soon. Crypto exchange Bitget said it supports all regulations designed to advance the cryptocurrency industry.&#160; Cryptocurrency regulation begins to take shape globally The [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-exchange-bitget-appreciates-regulatory-moves-to-advance-the-industry/">Crypto exchange Bitget responds on regulatory moves: &#8216;the industry&#8217;s broad reach are well appreciated&#8217;</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Regulatory agencies globally have been rolling out frameworks to guide the cryptocurrency market.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Europe recently approved the MiCA guideline, while Hong Kong is set to release its crypto regulatory framework soon.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Crypto exchange Bitget said it supports all regulations designed to advance the cryptocurrency industry.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr">Cryptocurrency regulation begins to take shape globally</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The past few months have been interesting for the cryptocurrency industry in terms of regulation. Despite the ongoing bear market, regulators around the world have been busy rolling out regulatory frameworks for the crypto sector.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In the United States, the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has stated that the existing securities laws in the US cover cryptocurrencies and no new laws are needed.</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, that is not the case in the United States. In Europe, the European Union has chosen to adopt MiCA, or Markets in Crypto Assets, to regulate the cryptocurrency industry.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Earlier this month, finance ministers in Europe unanimously&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/can-mica-rules-help-the-struggling-cryptocurrency-industry/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>voted in favour of MiCA</u></a>.The law is expected to come into effect in 2024 and will regulate how the crypto market operates.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Hong Kong is expected to&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/hong-kong-to-release-crypto-framework-next-month-bloomberg/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>release its cryptocurrency framework</u></a> soon. Once that happens, companies seeking to offer services in Hong Kong will need to apply for and get licenses from the commission.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The The International Organization of Securities Commissions (IOSCO) also&nbsp;<a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/watchdog-proposes-first-set-global-rules-crypto-sector-2023-05-23/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>opened up its policy recommendations</u></a> for crypto and digital asset markets for public comment earlier this week.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitget supports market regulation</h2>
<p dir="ltr">With regulation coming from various parts of the globe, crypto companies have been making changes to ensure they operate in line with these frameworks.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Crypto exchange Bitget is one of the crypto exchanges that continues to strive to operate according to the set regulations.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">While commenting on the recent regulatory efforts, Bitget&rsquo;s Managing Director Gracy Chen said;&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;Bitget, as a pioneer in the crypto-based fintech revolution and a highly innovative solution, welcomes all forms of regulation. We believe such regulations can help position the industry on a defined path for growth, protect consumers, and assist in combating cyber crimes. We believe that digital currency and its underlying technology have the power to bolster financial innovation and economic growth.</em></p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>Based on this, the moves from IOSCO, the European Union, and Hong Kong to advance the industry&rsquo;s broad reach are well appreciated. They will serve as a major basis for other countries to build their own regulations as well.</em></p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>Our brand is committed to embracing regulation and implementing a comprehensive set of risk control and anti-money laundering procedures.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitget has become one of the leading cryptocurrency exchanges in the world and currently processes more than $500 million in daily trading volume.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The crypto exchange is headed by Gracy Chen, a leader specialising in the growth and execution of global market strategies. She has been a metaverse and crypto enthusiast since 2014 and has now become a prominent figure in the industry.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-exchange-bitget-appreciates-regulatory-moves-to-advance-the-industry/">Crypto exchange Bitget responds on regulatory moves: &#8216;the industry&#8217;s broad reach are well appreciated&#8217;</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>SUI price dips below $1, BTC, ETH struggle as crypto market shrinks 2.6%</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/sui-price-dips-below-1-btc-eth-struggle-as-crypto-market-shrinks-2-6/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 20:20:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/sui-price-dips-below-1-btc-eth-struggle-as-crypto-market-shrinks-2-6/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Sui (SUI) fell below $1, while Bitcoin and Ethereum dropped below key levels at $26,500 and $1,800 respectively. Altcoins were selling off on Wednesday as the global cryptocurrency market cap dropped to $1.15 trillion, down 2.6% at the time of writing. A confluence of headwinds, including the uncertainty around the US debt ceiling talks and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sui-price-dips-below-1-btc-eth-struggle-as-crypto-market-shrinks-2-6/">SUI price dips below $1, BTC, ETH struggle as crypto market shrinks 2.6%</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Sui (SUI) fell below $1, while Bitcoin and Ethereum dropped below key levels at $26,500 and $1,800 respectively.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Altcoins were selling off on Wednesday as the global cryptocurrency market cap dropped to $1.15 trillion, down 2.6% at the time of writing.</li>
<li dir="ltr">A confluence of headwinds, including the uncertainty around the US debt ceiling talks and possible default were likely triggers.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">The price of Sui (SUI) fell below $1 on Wednesday as the broader <a href="https://coinjournal.net/cryptocurrencies/"><u>cryptocurrency market</u></a> continued to sell-off after recent declines catalysed by macroeconomic news events.</p>
<p dir="ltr">At the time of writing, SUI traded at $0.97, about 7.6% down in the past 24 hours and -16% over the past seven days. The token&rsquo;s daily trading volume was just over $235 million, up 115% from a day earlier as selling pressure mounted.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Today&rsquo;s declines for Sui sees its price below the dollar for the first time since its token launch for trading on exchanges. On 3 May 2023, SUI reached its all-time high price of $2.16. At the current value, its down nearly 55%.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Crypto market shrinks 2.6% as BTC, ETH and altcoins struggle</h2>
<p dir="ltr">As SUI fell to its lowest price level so far, the sentiment around crypto did not help the global cryptocurrency market cap. According to data from market data aggregator CoinGecko, the total crypto market cap was down 2.6% in the past 24 hours at the time of writing, hovering around $1.15 trillion.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Crypto markets were also down as <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/"><u>Bitcoin (BTC)</u></a> price retreated towards $26k amid continuing uncertainty in the financial market. The benchmark cryptocurrency&rsquo;s market cap was $508 billion, down 3.7% from a day earlier.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/"><u>Ethereum</u></a> also struggled to maintain recent upside momentum, with ETH price trading at $1,789 and about 3.3% down in the past 24 hours.</p>
<p dir="ltr">ETH and BTC both hit year-to-date highs above the psychological levels of $2,000 and $30,000 respectively. However, a confluence of headwinds, including regulatory uncertainty have catalysed declines that threaten further rot to critical support zones.</p>
<p dir="ltr">At the moment, another downward trigger is the uncertainty around the US debt ceiling talks and possible default. <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/stocks/"><u>Stocks</u></a> were down on Wednesday as a result of investor jitters.</p>
<p dir="ltr">All the top 10 <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/altcoins/"><u>altcoins</u></a> were also down, including XRP and Litecoin that have had some upside in recent weeks. Crypto analysts say further declines could spell danger for the market. Michael van de Poppe <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoMichNL/status/1661377154704199681" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>shared</u></a> such an outlook.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sui-price-dips-below-1-btc-eth-struggle-as-crypto-market-shrinks-2-6/">SUI price dips below $1, BTC, ETH struggle as crypto market shrinks 2.6%</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance CEO says “it’s a big deal” after China broadcast crypto on state TV</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-ceo-says-its-a-big-deal-after-china-broadcast-crypto-on-state-tv/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-ceo-says-its-a-big-deal-after-china-broadcast-crypto-on-state-tv/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 18:13:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[China]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-ceo-says-its-a-big-deal-after-china-broadcast-crypto-on-state-tv/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao says China&#8217;s state TV crypto broadcast is &#8220;a big deal.&#8221;&#160; He notes that previous coverage has historically been bullish for crypto. His comments come as Bitcoin price struggled to stay above $26k on Wednesday. Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao, popularly known as CZ, says China broadcasting a crypto segment on state broadcaster [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-ceo-says-its-a-big-deal-after-china-broadcast-crypto-on-state-tv/">Binance CEO says “it’s a big deal” after China broadcast crypto on state TV</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao says China&rsquo;s state TV crypto broadcast is &ldquo;a big deal.&rdquo;&nbsp;</li>
<li dir="ltr">He notes that previous coverage has historically been bullish for crypto.</li>
<li dir="ltr">His comments come as Bitcoin price struggled to stay above $26k on Wednesday.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/binance/">Binance</a> CEO Changpeng Zhao, popularly known as CZ, says China broadcasting a <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/">crypto</a> segment on state broadcaster China Central Television is &ldquo;a big deal&rdquo; and that such broadcasts have previously coincided with a subsequent uptick in crypto prices.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to CZ, the broadcast has &ldquo;Chinese speaking communities buzzing,&rdquo; given how such coverage of Bitcoin have ended with crypto price rallying.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;It&rsquo;s a big deal. The Chinese speaking communities are buzzing,&rdquo; he <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1661391542504902664" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">tweeted</a> on Wednesday. &ldquo;<em>Historically, coverages like these led to bull runs</em>.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">He however, noted that his comments do not mean that the &ldquo;<em>past predicts the future</em>.&rdquo; The Binance CEO, who is one of the biggest crypto proponents in the world, added a disclaimer that his remarks did not constitute financial advice.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitcoin features in Chinese TV broadcast</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The referenced <a href="https://t.co/2wcArnPI93" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">broadcast</a> shows a Bitcoin ATM in the increasingly crypto-friendly Hong Kong. The crypto teller machine also shows a bitcoin logo and a &ldquo;Buy Bitcoins&rdquo; inscription. The TV segment also featured commentary on NFTs.</p>
<p dir="ltr">But it should be remembered that China banned bitcoin (again) in 2021.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As highlighted <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-bulls-tap-hong-kong-news-to-test-key-resistance/">here</a> on Tuesday, <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">Bitcoin price</a> rose briefly to touch the $27,500 resistance area as Hong Kong announced retail investors would from 1 June be able to buy and trade bitcoin and Ethereum on regulated exchanges.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Experts hailed Hong Kong&rsquo;s Securities and Futures Commission (SFC)&rsquo;s announcement as a potential game changer for crypto adoption. The framework comes as Hong Kong looks to position itself as a leading crypto and blockchain hub, while at the same time offering guidelines and rules that target greater protection for consumers.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin has not had a major reaction to the latest China related news, and was struggling to remain above $26k as at 1:50 pm ET on Wednesday. According to data from CoinGecko, BTC was perched at $26,300, down 3.2% in the past 24 hours.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-ceo-says-its-a-big-deal-after-china-broadcast-crypto-on-state-tv/">Binance CEO says “it’s a big deal” after China broadcast crypto on state TV</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-ceo-says-its-a-big-deal-after-china-broadcast-crypto-on-state-tv/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>ARPA, IRIS, CREAM, BEL Waves prices rise as BTC retreats</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/arpa-iris-cream-bel-waves-prices-rise-as-btc-retreats/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/arpa-iris-cream-bel-waves-prices-rise-as-btc-retreats/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 17:51:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/arpa-iris-cream-bel-waves-prices-rise-as-btc-retreats/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin and most cryptocurrencies were deeply in the red on Wednesday. The same was true in the stock market, where the Dow Jones and Nasdaq retreated. Several altcoins like ARPA, CREAM, IRIS, and Waves soared. Cryptocurrencies and stocks slumped hard on Wednesday as concerns about the debt ceiling continued.&#160;Bitcoin remained below the support at $27,000 [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/arpa-iris-cream-bel-waves-prices-rise-as-btc-retreats/">ARPA, IRIS, CREAM, BEL Waves prices rise as BTC retreats</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin and most cryptocurrencies were deeply in the red on Wednesday.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The same was true in the stock market, where the Dow Jones and Nasdaq retreated.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Several altcoins like ARPA, CREAM, IRIS, and Waves soared.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Cryptocurrencies and stocks slumped hard on Wednesday as concerns about the debt ceiling continued.&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/"><u>Bitcoin</u></a> remained below the support at $27,000 while the Dow Jones and the Nasdaq 100 indices retreated by more than 1%. Safe havens like the US dollar index (DXY) jumped.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Debt ceiling crisis continues</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The main catalyst for the ongoing sell-off in the stocks, commodities, and cryptocurrencies market is the ongoing debt ceiling issue. Democrats and Republicans have failed to reach an agreement on how to handle the crisis.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, there are concerns that the two sides will not reach an&nbsp;<a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/freeze-or-cut-spending-fight-is-main-event-in-debt-ceiling-talks-3ffccb?mod=hp_lead_pos1"><u>agreement</u></a> before the June 1 deadline. However, most analysts and experts in negotiations believe that these talks will go to the wire as the two sides seek concessions.</p>
<p dir="ltr">A default of the American government would have a major implication around the world since it holds over $31 trillion in debt. It would lead to a major crash of key assets like stocks and bonds. Also, it would lead to a jump in the unemployment rate.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The soaring US debt is one reason why many people allocate their cash to safe havens like gold and Bitcoin to a small extent. However, historically, these assets tend to drop when there is an elevated risk. For example, BTC and gold plunged in March 2020 as the world was moving into lockdown.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Several altcoins are rising</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Not all cryptocurrencies are slipping. Data compiled by Binance shows that ARPA price has jumped by over 74% in the past 24 hours, making it the best performer in the industry. This rally happened as the token trended in key social media platforms like Twitter and StockTwits. There is a likelihood that the developers will launch the mainnet soon.</p>
<p dir="ltr">CREAM, the token for Cream Finance, jumped by more than 15% while Bella Protocol jumped by 12%. PIVX and IRIS prices jumped by more than 10% in the past 24 hours. The parabolic moves of most of these tokens was not driven by any news in the ecosystems. It also happened in a low-volume environment, signaling that it could be part of a pump and dump.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Meanwhile,&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/waves/"><u>Waves</u></a> price drifted upwards after an association of South Korean exchanges removed it from a cautionary list. As a result, several exchanges decided to restart offering the coin. Also, the platform partnered with Pyth Network, an oracle platform that competes with Chainlink.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Are you ready for a revolution in Tsunami oracles world? &#128640;</p>
<p>Meet our new partners <a href="https://twitter.com/PythNetwork?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@PythNetwork</a>, who will be providing real-time pricing for our new oracles. Over 200 different assets in their account, can you imagine the power?</p>
<p>Welcome aboard and get ready, Tsunami is coming!&#127754; <a href="https://t.co/2GuqwCxhGs">https://t.co/2GuqwCxhGs</a> <a href="https://t.co/2r8WafEsEU">pic.twitter.com/2r8WafEsEU</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Tsunami Exchange &#127754; (1 &#10141; 2) (@ExchangeTsunami) <a href="https://twitter.com/ExchangeTsunami/status/1661344808261021699?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">May 24, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/arpa-iris-cream-bel-waves-prices-rise-as-btc-retreats/">ARPA, IRIS, CREAM, BEL Waves prices rise as BTC retreats</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/arpa-iris-cream-bel-waves-prices-rise-as-btc-retreats/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>USDT’s total supply nears all-time high: will cryptos like Metacade rally higher?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/usdts-total-supply-nears-all-time-high-will-cryptos-like-metacade-rally-higher/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/usdts-total-supply-nears-all-time-high-will-cryptos-like-metacade-rally-higher/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 16:41:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/usdts-total-supply-nears-all-time-high-will-cryptos-like-metacade-rally-higher/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways USDT&#8217;s total market cap is close to its all-time high of $84.1 billion. Tether&#8217;s recovery could see the broader crypto market embark on a rally again. Metacade could be one of the biggest winners thanks to the project&#8217;s huge potential.&#160; The cryptocurrency market has been in a bearish cycle since 2021, with the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/usdts-total-supply-nears-all-time-high-will-cryptos-like-metacade-rally-higher/">USDT’s total supply nears all-time high: will cryptos like Metacade rally higher?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">USDT&rsquo;s total market cap is close to its all-time high of $84.1 billion.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Tether&rsquo;s recovery could see the broader crypto market embark on a rally again.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Metacade could be one of the biggest winners thanks to the project&rsquo;s huge potential.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">The cryptocurrency market has been in a bearish cycle since 2021, with the prices of most coins and tokens down by more than 50% from their all-time highs.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, the market sentiment has improved this year, with Bitcoin and other major cryptocurrencies up by over 40% year-to-date.</p>
<p dir="ltr">One of the biggest positives this year is the recovery of USDT, the stablecoin issued by Tether. USDT remains the largest stablecoin in the world in terms of market cap, and its recovery could spell excellent times ahead for the cryptocurrency market.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Does USDT&rsquo;s recovery signal an upcoming bull cycle, and should investors take the opportunity to purchase cryptocurrencies like Metacade?&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">USDT&rsquo;s total market cap crosses $83 billion</h2>
<p dir="ltr">USDT, the world&rsquo;s leading stablecoin by market cap, has almost recovered from the bear market jitters.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The total market cap of USDT recently crossed $83 billion, which is just below the all-time high of &nbsp;$84.1 billion reached on May 10, 2022. According to the data obtained from Coinmarketcap, USDT&rsquo;s total market cap crossed the $83.5 billion mark earlier today, indicating that the stablecoin is doing as well as it did during the most recent bull cycle.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What does Tether&rsquo;s recovery mean for the cryptocurrency market?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Tether&rsquo;s recovery is an excellent development for the broader cryptocurrency market. It comes following numerous regulatory uncertainties and the banking crisis in the United States.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The collapse of the Silicon Valley Bank severely affected the market cap of USDT&rsquo;s nearest competitor, Circle&rsquo;s USDC. Due to the crisis in the US, the supply of rival USDC has declined from nearly $47 billion to $27.8 billion</p>
<p dir="ltr">With USDT now close to its all-time high, a liquidity crisis in the cryptocurrency space might not be something investors worry about.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Data provider Kaiko revealed that the rising USDT isn&rsquo;t tied to an increase in trading volumes. The firm stated that;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;The data doesn&rsquo;t show any notable increase in USDT market share (as measured by trade volume) relative to other stablecoins over the past few months, in large part due to Binance&rsquo;s promotion of TUSD as an alternative to BUSD.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p dir="ltr">The firm further stated that the increase in USDT could be because of offshore trading among market-making firms and whales.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How does this affect projects like Metacade?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">USDT&rsquo;s recovery will be a boost for the broader cryptocurrency market. Historically, Bitcoin has performed well when there is an increase in the total USDT supply.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">With USDT now close to its all-time high again, it could benefit Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">MCADE, the native token of the<a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=invezz&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=investment_opportunity"><u>&nbsp;Metacade</u></a> ecosystem, could be one of the biggest winners if the market rallies.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade has performed well over the past seven days despite the broader crypto market recording slight losses. At press time, the price of Metacade stands at $0.02111, down by 1% over the last 24 hours. The token is up by more than 5% from the low of $0.01954 recorded over the weekend.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Despite its recent positive performance, MCADE is down by 53% from its all-time high price of $0.04569. This could represent an excellent buying opportunity for investors.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade has huge potential in the GameFi ecosystem, making it one of the tokens investors could consider. It is a web3 project on the Ethereum blockchain, with the team currently working on launching a play-to-earn ecosystem that allows users to enjoy new web3 experiences.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">What&nbsp;<a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=invezz&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=investment_opportunity"><u>Metacade</u></a> hopes to achieve is to allow players to be able to play, connect, build, and earn seamlessly. The team is working to also turn Metacade into a decentralised autonomous organisation (DAO) by next year, ensuring that the project is truly decentralised.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Should you buy Metacade now?</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=invezz&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=investment_opportunity"><u>Metacade</u></a> is a relatively new project, and its token price is down by more than 50% from its all-time high. This implies that MCADE could be trading at a discount.</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, the major investment decision regarding MCADE should be based on the potential of the project. As stated above, Metacade hopes to change the way the P2E model works by introducing new web3 experiences for the users.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The development team is already working on its P2E ecosystem after raising $16 million in the recently concluded presale event. The token has also launched on Uniswap, MEXC, and BitMart, and the team is working to get it listed on other leading cryptocurrency exchanges.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/usdts-total-supply-nears-all-time-high-will-cryptos-like-metacade-rally-higher/">USDT’s total supply nears all-time high: will cryptos like Metacade rally higher?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/usdts-total-supply-nears-all-time-high-will-cryptos-like-metacade-rally-higher/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitfinex and Chile’s OrionX partner to accelerate crypto adoption in Latin America</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitfinex-and-chiles-orionx-partner-to-accelerate-crypto-adoption-in-latin-america/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitfinex-and-chiles-orionx-partner-to-accelerate-crypto-adoption-in-latin-america/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 15:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitfinex]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitfinex-and-chiles-orionx-partner-to-accelerate-crypto-adoption-in-latin-america/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways Bitfinex has entered a strategic partnership with OrionX. The two companies will work towards accelerating cryptocurrency adoption in Latin America. OrionX is expanding its services to Mexico, Peru, and Colombia.&#160; Bitfinex announces a strategic partnership with OrionX Bitfinex, a state-of-the-art digital asset trading platform, announced on Wednesday, May 24th, that it has partnered [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitfinex-and-chiles-orionx-partner-to-accelerate-crypto-adoption-in-latin-america/">Bitfinex and Chile’s OrionX partner to accelerate crypto adoption in Latin America</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Bitfinex has entered a strategic partnership with OrionX.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The two companies will work towards accelerating cryptocurrency adoption in Latin America.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">OrionX is expanding its services to Mexico, Peru, and Colombia.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitfinex announces a strategic partnership with OrionX</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Bitfinex, a state-of-the-art digital asset trading platform, announced on Wednesday, May 24th, that it has partnered with the leading Chilean crypto firm Orionx.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to the press release shared with Coinjournal, the two entities will work together to promote financial freedom and inclusion throughout Latin America. &nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">While commenting on this&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>latest cryptocurrency news</u></a>, Paolo Ardoino, CTO at Bitfinex, said</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;We&rsquo;re excited to collaborate with Orionx as we look to expand our presence in Chile and across Latin America. This represents a major step forward in our efforts to harness the power of Bitcoin and decentralised technology to promote financial freedom and empower businesses that share our values. We look forward to working even more closely with the team at Orionx to support its growth and development going forward.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p dir="ltr">OrionX has been around since 2017 and has become one of the most promising cryptocurrency projects in Latin America. The company has evolved beyond its origins as a crypto exchange to become the region&rsquo;s first crypto bank offering users an expansive range of crypto-related services.</p>
<p dir="ltr">OrionX is now preparing to expand its services beyond Chile and enter new markets, including Peru, Mexico, and Colombia. The company expects to surpass a million users by 2024.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The partnership will allow Bitfinex to expand its presence in Latin America, indirectly reaching millions of users, and supporting common education programs for local universities. Last month, Bitfinex <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitfinex-sponsors-women-coding-bootcamp-in-paraguay/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>sponsored a coding bootcamp</u></a> in Paraguay dedicated exclusively to women</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">OrionX to benefit from Bitfinex&rsquo;s experience and network</h2>
<p dir="ltr">OrionX is set to benefit from Bitfinex&rsquo;s strong crypto trading expertise and network. Joel Vainstein, the co-founder of Orionx, stated that;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;Having a strategic collaboration with a company like Bitfinex will play a vital role in advancing our project in LATAM. We firmly believe that their involvement will provide a substantial impetus to our capital-raising activities. We are confident that their extensive experience and proven product portfolio will expedite our own product development and user base expansion, positioning us as the benchmark in the region.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitfinex&rsquo;s interest in Latin America comes as the crypto exchange seeks to increase its presence in the region. The crypto exchange seeks to provide financial services in the underbanked and unbanked regions of the world.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitfinex has played an active role in El Salvador over the past two years. The company is working closely alongside partners such as Mi Primer Bitcoin to promote financial education and support the growth of local businesses.</p>
<p>Last month, Bitfinex Securities El Salvador, a fully-regulated platform for issuing and trading tokenised assets, was&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitfinex-gets-license-to-operate-under-el-salvadors-new-crypto-law/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>granted El Salvador&rsquo;s first Digital Asset Service Provider licence</u></a> under the country&rsquo;s ground-breaking new Digital Assets Law.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitfinex-and-chiles-orionx-partner-to-accelerate-crypto-adoption-in-latin-america/">Bitfinex and Chile’s OrionX partner to accelerate crypto adoption in Latin America</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitfinex-and-chiles-orionx-partner-to-accelerate-crypto-adoption-in-latin-america/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tulipart.com Launches A Collection of Tulip NFTs Minted Daily over 7 Years</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/tulipart-com-launches-a-collection-of-tulip-nfts-minted-daily-over-7-years/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/tulipart-com-launches-a-collection-of-tulip-nfts-minted-daily-over-7-years/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire &#160;]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 15:05:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=140465</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Zug, Switzerland, May 24th, 2023, Chainwire Tulipart.com is a collection of 10,000 unique tulip NFTs. Over a period of 7 years, 4 Tulip NFTs will be minted every day until the goal of 10,000 is reached. Each Tulip NFT consists of six different components, which range from common to exclusive, making them more or less [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tulipart-com-launches-a-collection-of-tulip-nfts-minted-daily-over-7-years/">Tulipart.com Launches A Collection of Tulip NFTs Minted Daily over 7 Years</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Zug, Switzerland, May 24th, 2023, Chainwire</strong></p>
<p><a href="http://www.tulipart.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Tulipart.com</a> is a collection of 10,000 unique tulip NFTs. Over a period of 7 years, 4 Tulip NFTs will be minted every day until the goal of 10,000 is reached. Each Tulip NFT consists of six different components, which range from common to exclusive, making them more or less rare.</p>
<p>New Tulip NFTs aren&rsquo;t available for direct purchase; they are solely distributed to $LAND token holders via a lottery system. Participation involves holding and staking $LAND tokens. Staking a higher amount of $LAND tokens elevates the chances of acquiring a Tulip NFT each day.</p>
<p>$LAND tokens may be procured at no cost via the ongoing airdrop at <a href="http://Tulipart.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Tulipart.com</a>. Any Ethereum address holder can verify their participation eligibility. Ineligibility for the airdrop doesn&rsquo;t impede the opportunity to procure $LAND on Uniswap, effectively enhancing the probability of winning a Tulip NFT.</p>
<p><iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/48fPAzeqcLg?showinfo=0"></iframe></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>About Tulipart</strong></p>
<p>Tulipart.com is a cutting-edge platform fostering the innovation and creativity within the cryptocurrency and NFT landscapes. Based in Zug, Switzerland, a global hub for blockchain technology, Tulipart.com is the epicenter of a unique collection of 10,000 one-of-a-kind tulip NFTs, set to be minted over a period of seven years.</p>
<p>Those interested can visit <a href="http://www.tulipart.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Tulipart.com</a> to claim their $LAND tokens, stake them, and win a Tulip NFT.</p>
<ul>
<li>Tulipart website: <a href="http://www.tulipart.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">www.tulipart.com</a></li>
<li>Airdrop page: <a href="https://www.airdrop.com/tulip" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.airdrop.com/tulip</a></li>
<li>Opensea: <a href="https://opensea.io/collection/tulipart-1" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://opensea.io/collection/tulipart-1</a></li>
<li>Discord: <a href="https://discord.gg/h3xzdcHReN" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://discord.gg/h3xzdcHReN</a></li>
<li>Telegram: <a href="https://t.me/tulipart" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://t.me/tulipart</a></li>
<li>Tulipart logo: <a href="https://bit.ly/3GnTiif%C2%A0" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://bit.ly/3GnTiif&nbsp;</a></li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Contact</strong></p>
<p>Marketing, Giorgio Minguzzi, Tulip Art AG, giorgio.m@airdrop.com, +393472620489</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tulipart-com-launches-a-collection-of-tulip-nfts-minted-daily-over-7-years/">Tulipart.com Launches A Collection of Tulip NFTs Minted Daily over 7 Years</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/tulipart-com-launches-a-collection-of-tulip-nfts-minted-daily-over-7-years/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>AI Project TradeGDT soars in popularity, hits 10% of Bybit Derivatives Trading Volume in 4 Hours</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/ai-project-tradegdt-soars-in-popularity-hits-10-of-bybit-derivatives-trading-volume-in-4-hours/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/ai-project-tradegdt-soars-in-popularity-hits-10-of-bybit-derivatives-trading-volume-in-4-hours/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire &#160;]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 15:01:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=140439</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Singapore, Singapore, May 23rd, 2023, Chainwire Generative AI can create new content, such as images, videos, and text. With the help of deep learning algorithms like GANs (Generative Adversarial Networks), researchers are developing AI models that can generate realistic and original content. ChatGPT (Generative Pre-train Transformer) has elevated the AI trend and broadened the vision [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ai-project-tradegdt-soars-in-popularity-hits-10-of-bybit-derivatives-trading-volume-in-4-hours/">AI Project TradeGDT soars in popularity, hits 10% of Bybit Derivatives Trading Volume in 4 Hours</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Singapore, Singapore, May 23rd, 2023, Chainwire</strong></p>
<p>Generative AI can create new content, such as images, videos, and text. With the help of deep learning algorithms like GANs (Generative Adversarial Networks), researchers are developing AI models that can generate realistic and original content. ChatGPT (Generative Pre-train Transformer) has elevated the AI trend and broadened the vision of people toward AI, the conversation with ChatGPT is as human-like as it can be.</p>
<p>Trading has been one of the centerpieces of the financial markets and the broader economy. Trading helps to establish the market price of an asset, security and crypto itself. Trading also creates liquidity in the market by providing a mechanism for investors to buy and sell assets quickly and easily. Therefore the demand for AI in trading has never been higher, in crypto trading where everything happens at such a lightning pace, human productivity has been the limiting factor where evidence of increasing reliance on bot has been high. The revolution will be the implementation of AI that can be a better human with less emotion and productivity of a bot.</p>
<p>TradeGDT (Trading Generative Data Transformer) is an upgraded version of a big data quantitative trading bot combined with AI. By combining the ChatGPT plug-in, it can communicate with users more intelligently and flexibly. Users can communicate with TradeGDT to execute orders, and even prompt users to be alert to the pairing dynamics Information, and through AI pattern learning, TradeGDT can analyze and study user data, dynamic trade model, identify the profit model belonging to the trader, and then formulate a set of trading models for automation execution, while becoming the trader&rsquo;s AI smart trading assistant a better version of the trader itself.</p>
<p>TraderDAO team has been engaging in implementing AI in crypto trading since the start of 2022. TradeGDT has been proposed to cater for the demand of the crypto trading market. The TraderDAO team has been expanding and since gaining its team component that greatly accelerated the development of TradeGDT. With a very clear goal and commitment, TraderDAO has launched the MVP (Minimal Viable Product) to the market with close partnership to Bybit, and has hit the market with a bang which hits more than 10% ($330mil) Bybit 24 hour Trading Volume in 4 hours of their launch.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" src="https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/content_1684828120TqwKu5vYb9.jpg"></p>
<p>The trading volume was inspired by $POT, a trading fee sharing token in TraderDAO which acts as the AI data training incentive. Traders just need to perform trading to mint $POT and enjoy the fee sharing premium of the entire platform. The minting of each $POT requires a corresponding fee coming from trading fee rebate. Therefore, $POT is minted with 1:1 real yield asset backed, and the $POT treasury will grow bigger in value as the market continues to add new trades in, where these trades will provide data for AI pattern learning, powering the development of TradeGDT.</p>
<p>$POT is the utility token that incentivises AI training where the $HOT token is the governance token of TraderDAO. $HOT is deeply rooted in the heart of TradeGDT utility, the fuel that is burned off to use or operate all the coming functions and features of TradeGDT AI. TradeGDT will be traders&rsquo; smart trading assistance that revolutionize trading by improved decision making, increased efficiency, reduced risk, improved portfolio management, faster and more accurate trade execution. All the benefits with $HOT as the gas fee, fueling the path to trading revolution.</p>
<p>As the AI trend continues to make waves around all spaces, ChatGPT is moving in the forefront of the AI movement. TraderDAO AI TradeGDT could be the beginning of the AIFI (AI Finance) trend, with the past hype brough fort by DeFI and GameFI, AIFI has a far more bigger future with limitless potential, trading is the center to all crypto token value and&nbsp;with the combination of Trading and AI, TradeGDT could be the champion of the AIFI era.</p>
<h3>About TradeGPT</h3>
<p>TradeGDT is a groundbreaking AI project that is transforming the trading landscape. Our team comprises skilled engineers from renowned institutions like Cambridge and TsingHua, with over 5 years of experience in quant trading. With a diverse management team representing talents from Singapore, Malaysia, Taiwan, Hong Kong, and the UK, we foster innovation on a global scale.</p>
<p>At TradeGDT, we offer an advanced incubation platform designed to help traders develop their AI Trading Brain, providing valuable assistance in trading or allowing others to follow their successful strategies. By seamlessly integrating sophisticated Hidden Markov Models with user-fed trading data, TradeGDT evolves and adapts to each trader&rsquo;s unique trading patterns, precisely identifying the best entry opportunities for them.</p>
<p>The heart of our ecosystem lies in TraderDAO, a decentralized autonomous organization that continually provides invaluable trading data to TradeGDT. With the input from a community of over 10,000 active traders, our platform generates a more powerful AI Trading Brain, enabling traders to achieve superior results.</p>
<p><strong>Contact</strong></p>
<p>Maverick, TraderDAO, core@traderdao.ai, @mave121</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ai-project-tradegdt-soars-in-popularity-hits-10-of-bybit-derivatives-trading-volume-in-4-hours/">AI Project TradeGDT soars in popularity, hits 10% of Bybit Derivatives Trading Volume in 4 Hours</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/ai-project-tradegdt-soars-in-popularity-hits-10-of-bybit-derivatives-trading-volume-in-4-hours/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Router Protocol launches testnet for Router Chain</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/router-protocol-launches-testnet-for-router-chain/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 14:48:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/router-protocol-launches-testnet-for-router-chain/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways Router Protocol&#8217;s Router Chain launches on testnet. Router Chain aims to increase Web3 adoption by solving existing problems in cross-blockchain communications. The testnet is available on Ethereum (Goerli), Polygon (Mumbai), Avalanche (Fuji), Base, and BNB Chain blockchains.&#160; Router Protocol&#8217;s Router Chain launches on testnet Router Protocol, an infrastructure enterprise enabling communication between blockchains, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/router-protocol-launches-testnet-for-router-chain/">Router Protocol launches testnet for Router Chain</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Router Protocol&rsquo;s Router Chain launches on testnet.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Router Chain aims to increase Web3 adoption by solving existing problems in cross-blockchain communications.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The testnet is available on Ethereum (Goerli), Polygon (Mumbai), Avalanche (Fuji), Base, and BNB Chain blockchains.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr">Router Protocol&rsquo;s Router Chain launches on testnet</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://routerprotocol.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Router Protocol</a>, an infrastructure enterprise enabling communication between blockchains, announced on Wednesday, May 23rd, that it has launched the testnet of its Layer 1 blockchain.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In a press release shared with Coinjournal, Router Protocol revealed that the primary purpose of Router Chain is to increase Web3 adoption by solving existing problems in cross-blockchain communications, such as security, scalability, decentralization, and a lack of true-blue cross-chain dApps.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Router Chain grants developers numerous benefits, including;</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Infra-level Flexibility: With Router Chain, developers are no longer limited to a single type of bridging infrastructure. They can develop IDAPPS &ndash; apps that are interoperable by default &ndash; using Router&rsquo;s stateful infra (OmniChain framework) or stateless infra (CrossTalk framework), depending on their requirements.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Modular Security: With Router Chain, dApps have access to three layers of security &ndash; at the protocol level, bridge level, and application level. This implies that dApps can implement their own security measures on top of the baseline security model provided by the Router Chain.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">With Router Chain, developers also have access to other features such as;</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">MetaMask Compatibility</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Cross-chain Meta Transactions</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Acknowledgments and Refunds</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Decentralized Read Calls</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Transaction Batching</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Atomicity</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Expiry Timestamp</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr">Testnet launch supports five major blockchain networks</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The Router Protocol team added that testnet &nbsp;Mandara also allows external validators to participate in the network for the first time. This is an incredible milestone for the protocol as it makes it possible to achieve true decentralisation.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Router Protocol added that it has already started onboarding external validators, with a goal to onboard over 60 during testnet to secure its network.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The team revealed that the testnet launch supports five blockchain networks: Ethereum (Goerli), Polygon (Mumbai), Avalanche (Fuji), Base, and BNB Chain. Router Protocol would add support for the Near blockchain after the testnet launch.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">While commenting on this&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>latest cryptocurrency news</u></a>, Ramani Ramachandran, co-founder and CEO of Router Protocol, said;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;The testnet launch brings us a step closer to true blockchain interoperability. This is the first time users can interact with Router Chain in a multitude of ways and see the capabilities on full display. The days of siloed user and developer experiences across blockchains are numbered as we move closer to a Web3 experience with significant improvements in UX, infrastructure, security, and scalability.&rdquo;&nbsp;</em></p>
<p dir="ltr">Ravindra Kumar, Founder and CEO of Frontier, added that;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;IDAPPs hold the key to unlocking a decentralized future, where there are no barriers between blockchain networks. Cross-chain dApps are enabling us to transcend the limitations of individual blockchains, fostering collaboration, scalability, and true interoperability.&rdquo;&nbsp;</em></p>
<p>Router Protocol has been building despite the current bear market. In December 2022, Router Protocol announced that it had partnered with Circle&rsquo;s Cross-Chain Transfer Protocol&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/router-protocol-integrates-with-circle-to-make-usdc-interoperable/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>to make USD Coin (USDC) interoperable</u></a>.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/router-protocol-launches-testnet-for-router-chain/">Router Protocol launches testnet for Router Chain</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
