<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 19:10:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Ledger Launches Institutional-Grade Trading Network for Crypto Custody</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ledger-trading-network-crypto-custody/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ledger-trading-network-crypto-custody/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Marco T. Lanz]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 19:10:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blackrock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[invesco]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ledger]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[valkyrie]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[wisdomtree]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=260891</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ledger-trading-network-crypto-custody/">Ledger Launches Institutional-Grade Trading Network for Crypto Custody</a></p>
<p>Ledger launched an institutional-grade trading network to meet the risk management and regulatory requirements of institutions. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ledger-trading-network-crypto-custody/">Ledger Launches Institutional-Grade Trading Network for Crypto Custody</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ledger-trading-network-crypto-custody/">Ledger Launches Institutional-Grade Trading Network for Crypto Custody</a></p>
<p>On June 28th, crypto custody company Ledger announced the launch of &#8220;Ledger Enterprise TRADELINK&#8221;, a custodial trading network for institutions aiming to revolutionize this segment.</p>
<p>According to Ledger, the crypto wallet company has signed contracts with several partners to carry out its new project, which eliminates unnecessary complexities in the crypto market that are under scrutiny by regulators. Among the cryptocurrency companies and partners that have signed with Ledger are Bitstamp, Bitazza, CEX.IO, Coinsquare, Crypto.com, Damex, Flowdesk, Huobi, Uphold, NDAX, Wintermute, and YouHodler.</p>
<h2>Ledger Significantly Improves the Security and Speed of Transactions</h2>
<p>One of the most significant advantages of Ledger Enterprise TRADELINK is that it leverages end-to-end hardware security, providing 100% self-custody. This eliminates exposure to third parties and allows for asset recovery in case of emergencies. Moreover, it greatly reduces transaction times by 80%, optimizing trading strategies. The best part is that it doesn&#8217;t charge anything for transactions carried out on the platform.</p>
<p>Sebastien Badault, VP Enterprise at Ledger, stated in an <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/06/28/crypto-custody-firm-ledger-introduces-institutional-grade-trading-network/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">interview</a> with Coindesk that the company&#8217;s new solution connects custodians, OTC brokers (outside an exchange), and exchanges, eliminating regulatory risks that have recently caused havoc to cryptocurrency companies in the US.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the Ledger executive pointed out that the company is preparing to face an even more restrictive regulatory scenario in the crypto industry. Therefore, one way to mitigate operational risks is to align fund managers (individuals or companies managing other people&#8217;s money) with multiple custody partners (entities responsible for storing and safeguarding crypto assets).</p>
<p>&#8220;Looking ahead, there may be many more regulations regarding the ability to distribute your risks, so aligning fund managers with multiple custody partners will definitely be a major advantage.&#8221;</p>
<h2>US Regulators vs Crypto Industry</h2>
<p>Recently, the SEC sued the two largest cryptocurrency exchanges in the United States, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/judge-binance-motion-sec-statements/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a> and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-legal-measures-storm/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase</a>, for violating securities laws, which has generated fear among many investors due to the reach of both exchanges.</p>
<p>However, institutional investors do not feel threatened by the US Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>). Recently, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/blackrock-chance-spot-bitcoin-etf-approval/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BlackRock</a>, the world&#8217;s largest asset manager, filed an application to register a Bitcoin spot exchange-traded fund (ETF), restoring the hope for funds to reapply for their ETFs with the regulator.</p>
<p>The news of BlackRock&#8217;s Bitcoin ETF has sparked new applications from several major funds, such as WisdomTree, Invesco, and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/valkyrie-application-spot-bitcoin-etf/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Valkyrie</a>, which had previously received a resounding &#8220;no&#8221; from the SEC.</p>
<p>Therefore, Ledger&#8217;s new enterprise trading network could boost institutional trading, despite the regulatory uncertainty prompted by the SEC.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitpanda-pro-one-trading-funding/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ledger-trading-network-crypto-custody/">Ledger Launches Institutional-Grade Trading Network for Crypto Custody</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ledger-trading-network-crypto-custody/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitpanda Pro Morphs to One Trading after Closing Series A Funding Round with €30 Million</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitpanda-pro-one-trading-funding/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitpanda-pro-one-trading-funding/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 15:24:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitpanda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitpanda pro]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[one trading]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=260872</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitpanda-pro-one-trading-funding/">Bitpanda Pro Morphs to One Trading after Closing Series A Funding Round with €30 Million</a></p>
<p>One Trading intends to launch USD trading pairs, launch derivatives offerings, and announce new crypto listings including Bitcoin and Ethereum.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitpanda-pro-one-trading-funding/">Bitpanda Pro Morphs to One Trading after Closing Series A Funding Round with €30 Million</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitpanda-pro-one-trading-funding/">Bitpanda Pro Morphs to One Trading after Closing Series A Funding Round with €30 Million</a></p>
<p>After operating as one entity since 2019, Bitpanda and Bitpanda Pro have separated with the latter rebranding to One Trading following the successful closure of a Series A funding round with €30 million. According to the announcement, Bitpanda will retain a small stake in the new entity but will continue to operate independently in its future growth prospects.</p>
<p>Notably, the funding round that enabled the separation was led by Peter Thiel’s Valar Ventures and featured participation from MiddleGame Ventures, Speedinvest, Keyrock, and Wintermute Ventures. Onwards, the new entity will be led by Chief Executive Officer Josh Barraclough, who will lead the company toward greater achievements through regulated channels in Europe.</p>
<p>Already, One Trading is set to operate via MiFID Trading Venue License to enhance its Virtual Asset Service Provider (VASP) registration in Italy. Furthermore, the company aims at bridging the gap between retail and institutional customers in Europe amid mainstream cryptocurrency adoption.</p>
<p>“Since we first launched Bitpanda Pro, given its potential, we always knew and planned that its success would naturally make it evolve to become its own business,” Eric Demuth, CEO of Bitpanda, <a href="https://blog.bitpanda.com/en/bitpanda-pro-becomes-one-trading-after-completing-successful-series" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">noted</a>.</p>
<p>The relationship between Bitpanda &#8211; which was previously valued at about $4.1 billion &#8211; and On Trading will continue to stand, with the latter expected to support trading of the former’s native crypto token dubbed BEST.  Notably, the BEST coin is used to incentivize Bitpanda traders and holders through 15 percent annual rewards. Trading around € 0.37 on Wednesday, the BEST token is mostly viewed as a loyalty token with weekly payouts.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Following a successful Series A funding round, Bitpanda Pro is evolving into One Trading and becoming a separate company. While the Pro team was always quite independent, we share the belief that this is the logical next step in order for them to achieve their full potential.</p>
<p>— Bitpanda (@Bitpanda_global) <a href="https://twitter.com/Bitpanda_global/status/1673973978451329024?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 28, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2>One Trading Future</h2>
<p>The cryptocurrency market in Europe is expected to thrive further following the recent approval of the Markets in Crypto Assets (MiCA) regulation by the EU. However, individual state nations have taken the initiative to control the cryptocurrency market to ensure safe adoption and avoid instances similar to the FTX and Alameda Research implosion. Already, the leading global CEX Binance has experienced regulatory hurdles in different European countries including Belgium and Netherlands.</p>
<p>As a result, the One Trading team understands it will be a challenging time ahead amid global regulatory scrutiny. Most countries are working on individual crypto regulatory frameworks, which has significantly divided the entire industry. The team at Bitpanda intends to continue developing infrastructure for financial inclusion through an AI-focused Bitpanda.ai. Moreover, the rise of artificial intelligence around the world is expected to revolutionize cryptocurrency trading through AI bots that are more receptive to wide market data.</p>
<p>To begin with, One Trading intends to launch USD trading pairs, launch derivatives offerings, and announce new crypto listings including <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a>.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-relaunch-international-exchange/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitpanda-pro-one-trading-funding/">Bitpanda Pro Morphs to One Trading after Closing Series A Funding Round with €30 Million</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitpanda-pro-one-trading-funding/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>FTX in Talks to Relaunch Its International Crypto Exchange</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-relaunch-international-exchange/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-relaunch-international-exchange/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 14:37:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[john ray iii]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sam bankman-fried]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sbf]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=260826</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-relaunch-international-exchange/">FTX in Talks to Relaunch Its International Crypto Exchange</a></p>
<p>The possibility of FTX reopening its crypto exchange services under the new management has been tagged feasible by some industry observers.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-relaunch-international-exchange/">FTX in Talks to Relaunch Its International Crypto Exchange</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-relaunch-international-exchange/">FTX in Talks to Relaunch Its International Crypto Exchange</a></p>
<p>The <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">FTX derivatives exchange</a>, the bankrupt cryptocurrency trading platform, has recently unveiled its plans to revive its international crypto exchange, according to <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/ftx-begins-talks-on-reboot-as-managers-uncover-past-misconduct-38ad7e3c" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reports</a> by Wall Street Journal. This decision comes in the face of a tarnished reputation, as its bankruptcy caused a series of setbacks and challenges that have affected its standing in the market.</p>
<p>According to its CEO John Ray, the company remains determined to regain its position and rebuild trust among its users and the wider crypto community. John also noted that the decision to relaunch the international crypto exchange is a strategic move as the exchange seeks to address the issues that have plagued its reputation.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the beleaguered crypto exchange acknowledges that it has faced criticism and concerns from users regarding its previous operations, including issues related to security, customer support, and transparency. To ensure a successful relaunch, FTX has undertaken a comprehensive review of its internal processes and systems.</p>
<p>Additionally, the company has invested significant resources in strengthening its security infrastructure, enhancing its customer support capabilities, and implementing more transparent practices. Likewise, the bankrupt exchange aims to provide a secure and reliable platform that instills confidence in its users and demonstrates its commitment to their financial well-being.</p>
<p>As such, John Ray has started soliciting for interested parties to assist in restarting the FTX crypto exchange. Per the reports, any party or individual that wants to help finance or partake in the restructuring of FTX must submit its indication of interest to the company and its advisers latest by the end of this week.</p>
<p>Furthermore, FTX recognizes the importance of regulatory compliance in the crypto industry. The company is working to ensure its operations align with the evolving regulatory landscape. Not only is the bankrupt exchange determined to regain its standing in the market, but it is also determined to become a leader in the crypto industry by setting new standards for security, customer support, and innovation.</p>
<h2>FTX Successfully Recovers $7B in Funds amid Relaunch Plans</h2>
<p>In a report by the current FTX officials, it is evident that the former executives led by Sam Bankman-Fried (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/sam-bankman-fried/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SBF</a>) commingled users’ funds with corporate interest for months before <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-exchange-files-for-bankruptcy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">filing</a> a voluntary petition for relief under Chapter 11 of the United States Bankruptcy Code in the United States Bankruptcy Court for the District of Delaware on November 11, 2022.</p>
<p>However, FTX has <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-customer-funds-fbi-ryan-salame/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">recently</a> recovered about $7.3 billion in assets and is sending optimism to creditors and users of the platform whose funds remain locked. The attorney of the bankrupt exchange stated that FTX has been thinking about its future for the past months, and has been wondering what went wrong under the leadership of SBF.</p>
<p>Notably, the possibility of FTX reopening its crypto exchange services under the new management to help make customers whole again has been tagged feasible by some industry observers.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-commission-proposals-digital-euro/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-relaunch-international-exchange/">FTX in Talks to Relaunch Its International Crypto Exchange</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-relaunch-international-exchange/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>European Commission Publishes Proposals to Preserve Cash and Create Digital Euro Framework</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-commission-proposals-digital-euro/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-commission-proposals-digital-euro/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 14:17:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital euro]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eu commission]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=260785</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-commission-proposals-digital-euro/">European Commission Publishes Proposals to Preserve Cash and Create Digital Euro Framework</a></p>
<p>The European Commission's proposals for the use of cash and the digital Euro contain similar content as a draft bill leaked earlier in June.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-commission-proposals-digital-euro/">European Commission Publishes Proposals to Preserve Cash and Create Digital Euro Framework</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-commission-proposals-digital-euro/">European Commission Publishes Proposals to Preserve Cash and Create Digital Euro Framework</a></p>
<p>The European Union has published <a href="https://ec.europa.eu/commission/presscorner/detail/en/ip_23_3501" target="_blank" rel="noopener">proposals</a> that seek to preserve the use of cash in the region, while simultaneously setting a framework for the possible issuance of a digital euro. According to proposals by the European Commission, the aim is to ensure that banknotes and coins are still as accessible as ever while digital options are also supported.</p>
<p>The Commission said people in the EU have been transacting with euro coins and banknotes for over 20 years. While it wants this option to remain available, the publication notes that more people are now looking to digital payments. The European Commission stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>“While 60% of people surveyed would like to continue to have the option to use cash, an increasing number of people are choosing to pay digitally, using cards and applications issued by banks and other digital and financial firms. This trend was accelerated by the COVID-19 pandemic.”</p></blockquote>
<p>To cater to both sides of the divide, the Commission is proposing legislation that protects cash and also backs the digital Euro.</p>
<h2>EU Proposals on Cash and Digital Currency Functioning Simultaneously</h2>
<p>The first measure is a legislative proposal on the legal tender of Euro cash. This proposal is to “safeguard the role of cash”, ensuring its availability and acceptance as a means of payment.</p>
<p>The publication includes a second measure &#8211; a legislative proposal that creates a “legal framework for a possible digital Euro”. The European Commission notes that the digital Euro will complement coins and banknotes, and offer people an additional payment method. In addition, the digital Euro will be cheap, secure, and widely accepted. However, the Commission notes that it does not have the final say on digital Euro issuance.</p>
<p>“While today’s proposal &#8211; once adopted by the European Parliament and Council &#8211; would establish the legal framework for the digital Euro, it will ultimately be for the European Central Bank to decide if and when to issue the digital Euro,” explains the Commission.</p>
<p>The European Commission describes the digital Euro as a system that allows direct payments between devices, without an internet connection. These payments will ensure better data protection and privacy for users. The transactions will require less personal data than is necessary for card payments.</p>
<p>The proposals from the European Commission also states that the digital euro will be available from banks and registered payment service providers, with basic services free of charge. For financial inclusion, access to the digital Euro would not require bank accounts.</p>
<p>Furthermore, all merchants would have to accept digital euro payments. However, the law would exempt small merchants whose cost of setting up the required infrastructure would be high. The Commission also hopes that widespread use of the digital Euro would provide a basis for banks to create innovative solutions for customers.</p>
<h2>Leaked Euro Bill</h2>
<p>The provisions in the proposals for a digital Euro in the EU corroborate the specifics of a Digital Euro bill <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/leaked-digital-euro-bill-usability/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">leaked</a> last week. The draft bill to be proposed by the European Commission states that the digital Euro will support online payments, limit programmability, and run without interest or surcharges.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/kucoin-kyc-verification-users/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-commission-proposals-digital-euro/">European Commission Publishes Proposals to Preserve Cash and Create Digital Euro Framework</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-commission-proposals-digital-euro/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>KuCoin to Require KYC Verification for All Users Starting from July</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/kucoin-kyc-verification-users/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/kucoin-kyc-verification-users/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Babafemi Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 13:55:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cybersecurity News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bybit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[kucoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=260699</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/kucoin-kyc-verification-users/">KuCoin to Require KYC Verification for All Users Starting from July</a></p>
<p>KuCoin CEO noted that the increased adoption of cryptocurrency has pushed the number of related security issues higher.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/kucoin-kyc-verification-users/">KuCoin to Require KYC Verification for All Users Starting from July</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/kucoin-kyc-verification-users/">KuCoin to Require KYC Verification for All Users Starting from July</a></p>

<p>Leading cryptocurrency exchange KuCoin has <a href="https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20230628022769/en/KuCoin-Introduces-Compulsory-KYC-in-Move-to-Embrace-Regulation" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">introduced</a> additional checks to its <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/glossary/kyc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">KYC</a> verification process. In a bid to comply with global anti-money laundering regulations, the firm announced the KYC system upgrade on June 28. As part of the upgrade, all new users will have to complete mandatory identity checks from July 15. Without this, such users will not have access to the firm’s suite of products.</p>
<p>In the same manner, existing users will not be able to make deposits to the platform without additional verification. However, they will have access to other features like buying and selling, trading with less risk, and getting rewards.</p>
<p>According to KuCoin CEO, Johnny Lyu, the increased adoption of cryptocurrency has pushed the number of related security issues higher. He said:</p>
<blockquote>
<p>&#8220;As a globalized exchange, KuCoin closely monitors the crypto policies of various countries and respects compliance requirements, providing users with enhanced asset security.&#8221;</p>
</blockquote>
<p>  Likewise, Lyu noted that the new KYC verification progress will improve the company’s compliance will global regulations. He also stated that it would guarantee better protection for investors. At the time of the announcement, KuCoin had about 27 million registered accounts.</p>
<h2>KYC Verification Upgrade: Spreading Phenomenon</h2>
<p>KuCoin is not the only crypto exchange enhancing its KYC policy to comply with global regulations and prevent financial crimes. <a href="https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/cryptocurrency-anti-money-laundering-enforcement-2022-09-26/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">According to a Reuters report</a>, several exchanges have embraced similar policies in the face of enforcement actions by regulators for their AML compliance.</p>
<p>For example, Binance recently implemented stricter KYC measures for its users, limiting funds withdrawals and preventing access to its platform from specific countries. Also, Coinbase has partnered with law enforcement agencies and regulators to share customer data and transaction information. In May, Bybit also restricted non-KYC users from withdrawing more than 20,000 Tether.</p>
<p>With cyber criminals exploiting security lapses around on-chain assets, these moves show that the crypto exchanges understand the value of KYC for crypto and the risks of non-compliance. Katarzyna Kazimierczak-Mrowinska, the CEO of Authenteq, noted in the article for <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbesbusinesscouncil/2022/02/17/why-kyc-is-one-of-the-keys-to-cryptos-longevity/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Forbes</a> that by implementing KYC technology in a way that respects user privacy and security, we can create a more trustworthy and sustainable crypto ecosystem.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fintech-innoviti-25m-funding/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/kucoin-kyc-verification-users/">KuCoin to Require KYC Verification for All Users Starting from July</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/kucoin-kyc-verification-users/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Payment-Centric Fintech Startup Innoviti Sets Eyes on $25M Funding to Promote Business </title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fintech-innoviti-25m-funding/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fintech-innoviti-25m-funding/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 13:42:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FinTech News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investors News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[innoviti]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=260773</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fintech-innoviti-25m-funding/">Payment-Centric Fintech Startup Innoviti Sets Eyes on $25M Funding to Promote Business </a></p>
<p>Innoviti processes over $10 billion in transactions annually across more than 2,000 cities in India. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fintech-innoviti-25m-funding/">Payment-Centric Fintech Startup Innoviti Sets Eyes on $25M Funding to Promote Business </a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fintech-innoviti-25m-funding/">Payment-Centric Fintech Startup Innoviti Sets Eyes on $25M Funding to Promote Business </a></p>
<p>Innoviti Technologies, an Indian fintech startup, is exploring a fresh funding round that could potentially value the company at approximately $350 million, Bloomberg reported on June 28, citing people familiar with the matter.</p>
<p>According to the <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-06-28/fintech-firm-innoviti-said-to-seek-funds-at-350-million-value" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a>, the company seeks to raise around $25 million in the financing round to boost its business offerings and increase its market dominance.</p>
<p>The startup, backed by renowned venture capitalists including Catamaran Ventures, the investment arm of Infosys Ltd, was established in 2002 by Rajeev Agrawal to provide payment management solutions for businesses nationwide.</p>
<p>Last year, the company <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/elon-musk-new-funds-twitter/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">raised</a> $45 million in a series D round, which brought its total valuation to approximately $163 million as of November 2022. The payments-focused start-up firm is now planning a new round of funding that could increase its value and market position.</p>
<h2>Innoviti Plans to Expand Its Lending Business with New Funding</h2>
<p>In addition to the planned fundraising, Innoviti is considering the possibility of some early investors selling shares valued around $25 million as part of the funding round, people familiar with the matter told Bloomberg.</p>
<p>While the discussions are still in their early stages, the company has outlined plans to utilize the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/elon-musk-new-funds-twitter/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">funding</a> to expand its customer base and further develop its lending business by introducing new products. It is important to note that the details of the planned funding round are subject to change.</p>
<p>As one of the significant players in the fintech industry in India, Innoviti aims to leverage its current success to bolster its market presence. While the outcome of the intended funding round remains uncertain, the company&#8217;s strong support from prominent investors and its proven track record position it favorably for future growth.</p>
<p>The move comes at a time when several prominent startups in India are grappling with internal challenges and controversies. Byju&#8217;s, an education technology company, recently faced setbacks with the departure of its auditor and three board members within a week. The company is now working to reassure its investors by committing to the timely release of its long-delayed financials and reinforcing its accounting processes.</p>
<p>Another fintech firm, BharatPe, also found itself entangled in a scandal, as it initiated legal proceedings against one of its co-founders and his wife for alleged embezzlement and misappropriation of company funds.</p>
<h2>Innoviti Processes over $10 Billion in Transactions Annually</h2>
<p>According to the company&#8217;s website, Innoviti processes over $10 billion in transactions annually across more than 2,000 cities in India.</p>
<p>The firm was among India&#8217;s first digital lending platforms to provide short-term working capital to small and family-owned traders. As mentioned, the firm plans to further increase its lending business to serve more regional customers.</p>
<p>For over twenty years, Innoviti has been at the forefront of providing technology-driven payment solutions and cutting-edge point-of-sale terminals. Its unwavering commitment to innovation and customer-centricity has made it a trusted partner for businesses, offline merchants, and small retailers.</p>
<p>The company integrates its offerings into the existing payment ecosystem through strategic collaborations with banks and digital payment providers, delivering a seamless and efficient experience.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tencent-ant-foreigners-china/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fintech-innoviti-25m-funding/">Payment-Centric Fintech Startup Innoviti Sets Eyes on $25M Funding to Promote Business </a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fintech-innoviti-25m-funding/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tencent and Ant Group Open Up Mobile Payments to Foreigners in China</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tencent-ant-foreigners-china/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tencent-ant-foreigners-china/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 13:27:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FinTech News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ant group]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mastercard]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tencent]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[wepay]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=260783</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tencent-ant-foreigners-china/">Tencent and Ant Group Open Up Mobile Payments to Foreigners in China</a></p>
<p>The latest announcement means that Tencent and Ant want to allow visitors to make payments with different vendors in China.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tencent-ant-foreigners-china/">Tencent and Ant Group Open Up Mobile Payments to Foreigners in China</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tencent-ant-foreigners-china/">Tencent and Ant Group Open Up Mobile Payments to Foreigners in China</a></p>
<p>Foreigners can now easily pay for goods and services in China as payment giants <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/tencent/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tencent</a> and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ant-financial/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ant Group</a> said users can directly link international credit cards to their platforms. Therefore, tourists can connect their pay via the two dominant mobile pay apps- Tencent’s WeChat Pay and Ant Group’s Alipay. Over the years, China’s payment system has kept credit cards out of use, and this has been affecting foreign visitors. The entire country shifted towards a cashless society, relying heavily on digital and mobile payments.</p>
<p>Since mobile apps became the primary means of payment in China in the late 2010s, the mobile payment network has become inaccessible to foreign tourists. Hence, non-China residents find it difficult to make payments in many shops and restaurants. Most of these outlets opt for mobile payments other than credit cards or cash. As a result, many foreigners in China resorted to opening bank accounts in China to access the predominant mobile payment networks owned by Tencent and Ant Group.</p>
<h2>Tencent and Ant Group Allow Foreigners in China to Use International Credit Cards for Payments</h2>
<p>On Wednesday, Tencent Holdings announced that WeChat users overseas could begin to link their Visa-issued credit cards to their WeChat app starting from July. Meanwhile, financial services company <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/mastercard/">Mastercard</a> (NYSE: MA) made a similar call last week. The company said its cardholders can add their credit or debit cards to Alipay digital wallets. Before the latest developments with Tencent and Ant, the Chinese companies partnered with Visa and Mastercard in 2019 to enable using foreign cards on their platforms.</p>
<p>People who know the matter stated that the initiatives were reversed as China closed its borders during the global health crisis, and international visits to the country saw a setback. The plans are gradually returning to shape as the East Asian government reopens its borders to foreigners this year.</p>
<p>Notably, the 2019 partnership only was accessible to some overseas users and selected businesses. At the time, tourists from Hong Kong, Macau, and other countries spent $131 billion in mainland China just before the coronavirus pandemic. In December 2022, records showed that the number of online payment users in China was over 911 million.</p>
<p>The latest announcement means that Tencent and Ant are expanding their horizons by allowing visitors to make payments with different vendors in China. Tencent <a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/chinese-payment-giants-revive-effort-accept-foreign-credit-cards-2023-06-28/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">commented</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Our efforts to further open payment services to visitors coincide with the full resumption of travel and tourism to China, as well as major upcoming international events in the country scheduled this year.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Apart from foreigners who are largely impacted by China’s payment system, the elderly population, who are much less tech-savvy, are cut out as well.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-cloud-authorities-eu-ai/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tencent-ant-foreigners-china/">Tencent and Ant Group Open Up Mobile Payments to Foreigners in China</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tencent-ant-foreigners-china/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Google Cloud Reveals ‘Productive Conversations’ with Authorities in EU on AI Regulation</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-cloud-authorities-eu-ai/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-cloud-authorities-eu-ai/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 13:20:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cloud Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ai]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[google]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[google cloud]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=260729</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-cloud-authorities-eu-ai/">Google Cloud Reveals &#8216;Productive Conversations&#8217; with Authorities in EU on AI Regulation</a></p>
<p>The head of Google's cloud division has said the company's discussions with the EU will help create a "path forward" for AI development.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-cloud-authorities-eu-ai/">Google Cloud Reveals &#8216;Productive Conversations&#8217; with Authorities in EU on AI Regulation</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-cloud-authorities-eu-ai/">Google Cloud Reveals &#8216;Productive Conversations&#8217; with Authorities in EU on AI Regulation</a></p>
<p>Google is currently in productive talks with authorities in the European Union (EU) about artificial intelligence (AI) regulations. The company and EU regulators are having early discussions about designing safe AI technology.</p>
<p>Google Cloud CEO Thomas Kurian told <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/06/28/google-has-had-productive-talks-with-eu-on-ai-act-cloud-boss-says.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">CNBC</a> that the conversations are for the progress of the technology. Kurian also noted that the aim is to maximize AI opportunities despite its inherent risks:</p>
<blockquote><p>“We’re having productive conversations with the EU government. Because we do want to find a path forward…These technologies have risk, but they also have enormous capability that generate true value for people.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Kurian confirmed that Google Cloud is working on fixing several concerns the EU and other regions might have about AI. For instance, many regulators worry that it could become increasingly difficult to differentiate between human art or AI-generated art.</p>
<p>At the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ai-google-i-o-2023-conference/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Google I/0 2023 conference</a> in May, the tech giant announced a new feature that watermarks AI-generated images and includes metadata. In addition, Google said it would apply this feature to Google Workspace, the Bard chatbot, and Adobe Firefly. Interestingly, Microsoft also <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2023/05/23/microsoft-pledges-to-watermark-ai-generated-images-and-videos/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announced</a> a similar feature for AI-generated images and videos.</p>
<p>Last week, Google Cloud <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-cloud-anti-money-laundering-ai/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">launched</a> an AI feature focused on combating money laundering. The firm said it is ready to release the program following a successful trial with London-based banking giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/hsbc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">HSBC Holdings Plc</a> (NYSE: HSBC). Google designed the Anti Money Laundering AI feature to meet banking industry governance requirements. The program significantly reduced HSBC’s batch processing time and improved detection with increased accuracy.</p>
<h2>Regulator AI Concerns Google Should Address in the EU and Other Regions</h2>
<p>While many are in support, policymakers worldwide are skeptical about artificial intelligence for many reasons. Among other worries, EU policymakers believe that generative AI has enabled the mass production of content that could be detrimental to creatives. AI models are trained using data and information that, when used, could infringe on an artist’s or other creative’s copyright.</p>
<p>Recently, the EU Parliament <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/eu-parliament-ai-draft-act/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">passed an AI draft act</a> aimed at regulating the development, application, and growth of the technology. The act requires programs to label AI-generated content to reduce fake information. Kurian told CNBC:</p>
<blockquote><p>“We are providing tools, for example, to recognize if the content was generated by a model. And that is equally important as saying copyright is important, because if you can’t tell what was generated by a human or what was generated by a model, you wouldn’t be able to enforce it.”</p></blockquote>
<p>In addition to labeling AI content, the act protects users from undue surveillance. It would be unlawful for anyone to use AI for facial recognition or other kinds of potentially harmful targeting. The act would also disallow AI used for behavioral analysis or to predict criminal tendencies. Furthermore, the EU’s AI act kicks against any tools that can sway voter election decisions. In addition, Parliament would periodically review any further applications it may consider high risk.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/blackrock-chance-spot-bitcoin-etf-approval/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-cloud-authorities-eu-ai/">Google Cloud Reveals &#8216;Productive Conversations&#8217; with Authorities in EU on AI Regulation</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-cloud-authorities-eu-ai/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>BlackRock Has 50% Chance of Getting SEC’s Spot Bitcoin ETF Approval</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/blackrock-chance-spot-bitcoin-etf-approval/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/blackrock-chance-spot-bitcoin-etf-approval/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Temitope Olatunji]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 13:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funds & ETFs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blackrock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[grayscale]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=260735</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/blackrock-chance-spot-bitcoin-etf-approval/">BlackRock Has 50% Chance of Getting SEC&#8217;s Spot Bitcoin ETF Approval</a></p>
<p>The SEC may prefer to give BlackRock the approval because of its reputation. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/blackrock-chance-spot-bitcoin-etf-approval/">BlackRock Has 50% Chance of Getting SEC&#8217;s Spot Bitcoin ETF Approval</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/blackrock-chance-spot-bitcoin-etf-approval/">BlackRock Has 50% Chance of Getting SEC&#8217;s Spot Bitcoin ETF Approval</a></p>
<p>According to some Bloomberg analysts, BlackRock has a 50% chance of getting approval for its spot Bitcoin Exchange Traded Fund (ETF) from the Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>). On the other hand, they also speculated that Grayscale has a 70% chance of winning its ongoing legal case against the regulator.</p>
<p>Eric Balchunas made the comment about the two companies in a tweet after Elliott Stein, a senior litigation analyst for Bloomberg Intelligence, made some comments about them. In his statement, Stein mentioned that the odds for Grayscale increased from 40% to 70% after the last oral argument. According to him, it looks like the three judges were siding with Grayscale.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Another reason we give spot bitcoin ETF approval 50% chance is our senior legal analyst <a href="https://twitter.com/NYCStein?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@NYCStein</a> gives Grayscale a 70% chance of winning case against SEC, who could approve BlackRock&#8217;s ETF as way to save face using trusted &#8216;adult&#8217; TradFi cos &amp; stick it to Grayscale via <a href="https://twitter.com/JSeyff?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@JSeyff</a> <a href="https://t.co/pHydOcpuQo">pic.twitter.com/pHydOcpuQo</a></p>
<p>— Eric Balchunas (@EricBalchunas) <a href="https://twitter.com/EricBalchunas/status/1673685658538323968?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 27, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/grayscale/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Grayscale</a> legal issue with the SEC started last year after the regulator rejected its proposal to offer ETFs. With the outcome of the last court proceeding, Elliott thinks that the SEC could be preparing for a loss and looking for ways to reduce its effect or completely soften it by approving the Grayscale Spot Bitcoin ETF application before the court makes the final decision.</p>
<p>&#8220;Grayscale has a 70% chance of winning its lawsuit against the SEC over the company’s bid to convert the Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC) to a Bitcoin ETF, we believe,&#8221; Stein <a href="https://twitter.com/EricBalchunas/status/1673685658538323968" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">wrote</a>.</p>
<p>For <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/blackrock/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BlackRock</a>, the SEC may prefer to give it approval because of its reputation. The commission may prefer to consider a reputable traditional firm like BlackRock for ETF approval instead of Grayscale. Analysts say this gives the investment advisory company a 50% chance of getting its filing approved.</p>
<h2>Companies and Investors Are Looking into Bitcoin ETFs</h2>
<p>Many companies have been applying to offer <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-cryptocurrency-etf/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">crypto ETFs</a>, making it a trending topic in the crypto industry. If many of them get the approvals they seek, the digital asset market will be exposed to large companies and their clients. This could be positive for the crypto industry.</p>
<p>Even though the outcome of Grayscale’s case is not yet evident, the Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC) has continued to rise in price. The asset now sells for $19.47, breaking the $19.19 high it has on June 23. The price also represents the highest price it has had since May 2022.</p>
<p>Looking at the price of many other cryptocurrencies, it is obvious that many of them are far below their highest highs, and those that are doing well can only be said to be recovering from the effect of the elongated bear market. However, the price rise still shows investors&#8217; positive sentiments toward the product. The SEC’s approval may push the price higher in the short term.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-law-commission-digital-assets/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/blackrock-chance-spot-bitcoin-etf-approval/">BlackRock Has 50% Chance of Getting SEC&#8217;s Spot Bitcoin ETF Approval</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/blackrock-chance-spot-bitcoin-etf-approval/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>UK Law Commission Proposes Building Rules for Governing Digital Assets</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-law-commission-digital-assets/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-law-commission-digital-assets/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 13:06:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Law Commission]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=260738</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-law-commission-digital-assets/">UK Law Commission Proposes Building Rules for Governing Digital Assets</a></p>
<p>The UK Law Commission has submitted its proposal to the government to provide a comprehensive legal foundation for digital assets. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-law-commission-digital-assets/">UK Law Commission Proposes Building Rules for Governing Digital Assets</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-law-commission-digital-assets/">UK Law Commission Proposes Building Rules for Governing Digital Assets</a></p>
<p>As <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/crypto/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">crypto</a> adoption grows in the UK, lawmakers have started demanding a proper law base governing digital assets. The UK Law Commission has proposed having proper crypto rules to make the country a global hub for digital assets and non-fungible tokens.</p>
<p>In a report on Wednesday, June 28, the independent panel of the Law Commission noted that the long-awaited recommendations “aim to provide a comprehensive legal foundation for digital assets, which will allow these new technologies to flourish, enabling a diverse range of market participants to interact with and benefit from them”. The UK government has now to decide further whether to adopt the recommendations of the Law Commission.</p>
<p>Last year in April, the UK Treasury announced a similar goal of making the UK the global crypto hub. Judge Geoffrey Vos has suggested that prioritizing updates to the English and Welsh legal system could make it the preferred option for the crypto sector, further enhancing the attractiveness of the UK.</p>
<p>As the digital asset market and technology evolve, there has been an increase in legal uncertainty. The UK government is aware of this and is actively seeking ways to maintain its global leadership and position as a hub for digital assets, despite strong competition from other countries.</p>
<h2>UK Law Commission Seeks Clarification on Digital Assets</h2>
<p>The UK Law Commission has also asked the government when digital assets can be classified as money under the existing rules, or be used as collateral. The Commission also argued that the market participants should have the legal tools to provide “new ways to take security over crypto-tokens and tokenized securities&#8221;.</p>
<p>Professor Sarah Green, the Law Commissioner for Commercial and Common Law, explained the need for changes in the digital asset space in the UK. She <a href="https://www.lawcom.gov.uk/new-recommendations-for-reform-and-development-of-the-law-on-digital-assets-to-secure-uks-position-as-global-crypto-hub/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">said</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“The use and importance of digital assets has grown significantly in the law few years. The flexibility of the common law means that the legal system in England and Wales is well-placed to adapt to this rapid growth. Our recommendations for reform and development of the law, therefore, seek to solidify the legal foundation for digital assets. We also aim to ensure that the private law in England and Wales remains a dynamic, globally competitive and flexible tool that enables further technological innovation.”</p></blockquote>
<p>The panel also recommended creating laws to officially recognize a separate category of personal property specifically for digital assets. This would help provide better support and accommodation for digital assets within the legal framework.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/voyager-digital-1-1m-legal-fees/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-law-commission-digital-assets/">UK Law Commission Proposes Building Rules for Governing Digital Assets</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-law-commission-digital-assets/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4070 metric#misses=41 metric#hit-ratio=99.0 metric#bytes=1098166 metric#prefetches=197 metric#store-reads=19 metric#store-writes=2 metric#store-hits=203 metric#store-misses=2 metric#sql-queries=34 metric#ms-total=88.81 metric#ms-cache=4.65 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.2325 metric#ms-cache-ratio=5.2 -->