<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>CoinGape</title>
	<atom:link href="https://coingape.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coingape.com/</link>
	<description>CoinGape - 24*7 Crypto Updates</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 03:12:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/14183030/cropped-CoinGape_logo-32x32.png</url>
	<title>CoinGape</title>
	<link>https://coingape.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Coinbase Slaps A Lawsuit Compelling the SEC to Respond to Rulemaking Petition</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/coinbase-slaps-a-lawsuit-to-compel-the-sec-to-respond-to-rulemaking-petition/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 03:12:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulation News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase vs SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=146128</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>On Monday, April 24, US&#8217;s largest crypto trading platform Coinbase (NASDAQ: COIN) recently filed a lawsuit against the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) to compel the regulator to respond to a rulemaking petition filed by Coinbase last year. In the lawsuit filed with the federal court in Philadelphia, Coinbase argued that the SEC hasn&#8217;t <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/coinbase-slaps-a-lawsuit-to-compel-the-sec-to-respond-to-rulemaking-petition/" title="Coinbase Slaps A Lawsuit Compelling the SEC to Respond to Rulemaking Petition"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/coinbase-slaps-a-lawsuit-to-compel-the-sec-to-respond-to-rulemaking-petition/">Coinbase Slaps A Lawsuit Compelling the SEC to Respond to Rulemaking Petition</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/16155103/coinbase-sec.jpeg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong, CLO Grewal Sold COIN Stocks Ahead Of US SEC Action" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p>On Monday, April 24, US&#8217;s largest crypto trading platform Coinbase (NASDAQ: COIN) recently filed a lawsuit against the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) to compel the regulator to respond to a rulemaking petition filed by Coinbase last year.</p>
<p>In the lawsuit filed with the federal court in Philadelphia, Coinbase argued that the SEC hasn&#8217;t been prompt or reasonable in providing a response. Coinbase&#8217;s rulemaking petition submitted last year asks the SEC to write regulations explaining how securities laws are applicable to digital assets.</p>
<p>Besides, Coinbase also wants the SEC to engage in a formal notice-and-comment process, which would allow the public to weigh in. In an <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/coinbase-takes-jab-at-sec-with-lawsuit-over-rule-petition-1.1911616" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">interview</a> with Bloomberg, Coinbase’s Chief Legal Officer Paul Grewal said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Not only have we been waiting for many, many months, but there’s been a campaign of enforcement that the SEC has embarked upon in parallel&#8221;.</p></blockquote>
<p>Apart from Coinbase, several crypto firms like Ripple and others have complained that the SEC hasn&#8217;t provided any clarity on crypto regulations.</p>
<p>Over the last few months, SEC chair Gary Gensler has been reiterating that most digital assets are securities. In a separate comment, the SEC chair also said that the existing rules are clear and the crypto firms just refuse to follow them.</p>
<h3>Coinbase and SEC Rift Widens</h3>
<p>The recent action from Coinbase is likely to widen its rift with the securities regulator going ahead. Last month, the crypto exchange followed up on its petition with a comment submitted to the agency seeking more regulatory clarity with SEC&#8217;s view on staking services. This service allows users to earn rewards in exchange for allowing their tokens to be used in transactions on the blockchain.</p>
<p>However, the crypto exchanges faced a <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/coinbase-takes-jab-at-sec-with-lawsuit-over-rule-petition-1.1911616" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Wells Notice</a> from the securities regulator in return for this. The notice signals that the SEC plans to sue Coinbase over a range of alleged violations. Over the years, crypto exchange Coinbase has positioned itself as the most compliant crypto exchange. Besides, it has also shown intentions to work closely with the regulators.</p>
<p>Coinbase&#8217;s Grewal said that if the SEC believes crypto doesn&#8217;t need separate rules, it should respond to the petition accordingly. This would also give Coinbase the opportunity to challenge the assessment in court. He added:</p>
<blockquote><p>“What the SEC chair is doing is depriving the third branch — the US courts — from a chance to exercise their authority to evaluate whether he got it right or he got it wrong”.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/coinbase-slaps-a-lawsuit-to-compel-the-sec-to-respond-to-rulemaking-petition/">Coinbase Slaps A Lawsuit Compelling the SEC to Respond to Rulemaking Petition</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/16155103/coinbase-sec.jpeg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>More Delay In Ripple Lawsuit Judgement? This Could Be The Reason</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/more-delay-in-ripple-lawsuit-judgement-this-could-be-the-reason/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Anvesh Reddy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 02:35:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulation News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Securities and Exchange Commission]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=146127</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto News: The intense grilling of US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) Chair Gary Gensler before the House Financial Services Committee came as a welcome move for the crypto market. In fact, the criticism Gensler faced during the hearing could act as a validation of long pending demand for regulatory clarity in the crypto market <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/more-delay-in-ripple-lawsuit-judgement-this-could-be-the-reason/" title="More Delay In Ripple Lawsuit Judgement? This Could Be The Reason"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/more-delay-in-ripple-lawsuit-judgement-this-could-be-the-reason/">More Delay In Ripple Lawsuit Judgement? This Could Be The Reason</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/23152921/ripple-sec.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="ripple sec XRP news lawsuit" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p><strong>Crypto News</strong>: The intense grilling of US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) Chair Gary Gensler before the House Financial Services Committee came as a welcome move for the <a href="https://coingape.com/markets/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">crypto market</a>. In fact, the criticism Gensler faced during the hearing could act as a validation of long pending demand for regulatory clarity in the crypto market space. The lawmakers not only questioned the status quo but also sought Gensler&#8217;s opinion on the legal framework behind crypto assets.</p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/bitcoin-price-100k-kendrick-prediction" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>Top Bank’s 2024 Bitcoin Price Prediction Stirs Up Market, But Can It Really Happen?</strong></a></p>
<p>Several Congressmen expressed the need for immediate resolution to the regulatory issues surrounding trade of cryptocurrencies in the United States. Hence, it is possible that Gensler could face more of such Congressional hearings in that pursuit. But whether such hearings will further delay outcome from the legal route in crypto related lawsuits remains to be seen.</p>
<h2>Ripple Lawsuit Summary Judgement Delay</h2>
<p>After the ruling in the Ripple Vs SEC lawsuit in March 2022, experts have been predicting that the Summary Judgement could be out any time before May 6, 2020, which marks a 60 days period. However, it is highly unpredictable as to when Judge Analisa Torres gives out the judgement, especially after the Gary Gensler Congressional hearing led to a widespread debate in the mainstream. XRP influencer Mr Huber <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/Leerzeit/status/1650517409499959305?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener">said</a> there could be many more Congressional hearings of the SEC Chair before the Summary Judgement ruling.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;I think it is likely that there will be several more congressional hearings of Gensler and his successor before Torres even starts working on her Summary Judgement ruling.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Overall, the Congressional hearing&#8217;s impact on Court rulings cannot be overruled, in favor of Ripple and the 76,000 XRP holders.</p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/binance-news-support-for-floki-inu-meme-season-incoming/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>Binance.US Sparks Optimism As It Lists Floki (FLOKI), Is A Meme Season In The Making?</strong></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/more-delay-in-ripple-lawsuit-judgement-this-could-be-the-reason/">More Delay In Ripple Lawsuit Judgement? This Could Be The Reason</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/23152921/ripple-sec.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Multiple Dormant Bitcoin Whales Awaken; What Does It Mean?</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/crypto-news-bitcoin-price-dormant-whales-awaken/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Anvesh Reddy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 02:03:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=146126</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto News: Even as Bitcoin price dropped for three consecutive days last week, dormant whales re-activated their addresses containing massive amounts of cryptocurrency. Generally, this trend is associated with a corresponding price surge for the asset. However, this could also be seen as the big whales trying to cash out at current price anticipating a <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/crypto-news-bitcoin-price-dormant-whales-awaken/" title="Multiple Dormant Bitcoin Whales Awaken; What Does It Mean?"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/crypto-news-bitcoin-price-dormant-whales-awaken/">Multiple Dormant Bitcoin Whales Awaken; What Does It Mean?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/13143034/bitcoin.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="bitcoin news crypto" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p><strong>Crypto News</strong>: Even as <a href="https://coingape.com/price/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin price</a> dropped for three consecutive days last week, dormant whales re-activated their addresses containing massive amounts of cryptocurrency. Generally, this trend is associated with a corresponding price surge for the asset. However, this could also be seen as the big whales trying to cash out at current price anticipating a bear run in days to come. Nevertheless, BTC price is still at the highest level in the last 12 months and hence the bear run case may also be justified.</p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/binance-news-support-for-floki-inu-meme-season-incoming" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>Binance.US Sparks Optimism As It Lists Floki (FLOKI), Is A Meme Season In The Making?</strong></a></p>
<p>Meanwhile, the Spent Output Profit Ratio (SOPR) for long term Bitcoin holders shows high confidence in a price rise. On chain data <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://cryptoquant.com/insights/quicktake/64466eec10b8f142c0af3263-Long-term-holder-sopr-suggests-that-we-are-in-a-recovery-phase" target="_blank" rel="noopener">suggests</a> that BTC investors who have been holding since 5 months are currently in realized losses but what follows is a recovery period. Overall, this is a good sign for long term, despite potential for volatility in the short term.</p>
<h2>Dormant Bitcoin Whales Awaken</h2>
<p>Over the last one week, at least three big whale addresses made huge transfers, effectively activating the addresses after 10 years, in separate transactions. Such an address registered a transfer of 6,071 BTC after a long gap of 9.3 years. Similarly, two other whale addresses <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/whale_alert/status/1650456202432720899?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener">transferred</a> over 1,000 BTC separately, despite Bitcoin price maintaining sideways movement after consistent drop. In a latest, Whale Alert reported that:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;A dormant address containing 1,000 BTC ($27,456,958) has just been activated after 12.0 years!&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Interestingly, several Ethereum (ETH) and XRP whale transactions were also registered around the same time.</p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/bitcoin-price-100k-kendrick-prediction" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>Top Bank’s 2024 Bitcoin Price Prediction Stirs Up Market, But Can It Really Happen?</strong></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/crypto-news-bitcoin-price-dormant-whales-awaken/">Multiple Dormant Bitcoin Whales Awaken; What Does It Mean?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/13143034/bitcoin.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>MATIC Price Prediction: Polygon Price at Crucial Support Plots a 50% Rally; Enter Today?</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/markets/matic-price-prediction-polygon-price-at-crucial-support-plots-a-50-rally-enter-today/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brian Bollinger]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 20:01:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MATIC price prediction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon (MATIC)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[RSI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?post_type=markets&#038;p=146125</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>MATIC Price Prediction: In the weekly time frame chart, the Polygon coin shows its prices have been respecting two rising trendlines which reveals the formation of a broadening channel pattern. The most common outcome of this pattern is it triggers a significant downfall upon the breakdown of its support trendline. However, there are other criteria <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/markets/matic-price-prediction-polygon-price-at-crucial-support-plots-a-50-rally-enter-today/" title="MATIC Price Prediction: Polygon Price at Crucial Support Plots a 50% Rally; Enter Today?"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/markets/matic-price-prediction-polygon-price-at-crucial-support-plots-a-50-rally-enter-today/">MATIC Price Prediction: Polygon Price at Crucial Support Plots a 50% Rally; Enter Today?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="720" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/30224735/Polygon-blockchain-13.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="MATIC Price Prediction" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><a href="https://coingape.com/polygon-matic-price-prediction/">MATIC Price Prediction:</a> In the weekly time frame chart, the Polygon coin shows its prices have been respecting two rising trendlines which reveals the formation of a broadening channel pattern. The most common outcome of this pattern is it triggers a significant downfall upon the breakdown of its support trendline. However, there are other criteria the traders must consider before entering the coin under the influence of this channel pattern.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Key Points </span></h2>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">In theory, the increasing gap between the channel’s trendline reflects the increasing indecisiveness and uncertainty among participants.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Multiple support level accumulated at $1 support indicates a higher possibility for an upcoming bullish reversal </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The intraday trading volume in the MATIC is $318.5 Million, indicating a 15% loss.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><img decoding="async" class="alignnone" src="https://s3.tradingview.com/snapshots/j/jyrS6o6X.png" alt="MATIC Price Prediction" width="1946" height="1104" />Source-</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Tradingview</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Amid the recent sell-off in the crypto market, the <a href="https://coingape.com/price/polygon/#:~:text=The%20live%20Polygon%20price%20today,in%20the%20last%2024%20hours.">MATIC price</a> has plunged back to the channel pattern’s support trendline. Moreover, along with the trendline at $1 psychological support, this level is also near the 50% Fibonacci retracement level and 100-day EMA slope.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">These accumulated supports create a strong launchpad for coin buyers to sustain at a higher price. If buyers manage to hold above the rising trendline, the prices are likely to witness a bullish reversal and trigger a bull cycle within the pattern.</span></p>
<blockquote><p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/new-upcoming-binance-listing/">15 New Cryptocurrencies In Upcoming Binance Listing For 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A possible target for this reversal could be the last swing high of $1.5, indicating a potential target of 50%.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Anyhow the ongoing bullish rally will prolong until the pattern’s support trendline is intact, as a breakdown below it will invalidate the bullish thesis and signal the resumption of the prior downtrend.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Technical Indicators</span></h2>
<p><b>Exponential Moving Average:</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> with the recent downfall, the MATIC price dipped below the 20-and-50 <a href="https://coingape.com/education/exponential-moving-average-how-to-leverage-it-in-crypto-market/">EMAs</a> after two months.</span></p>
<p><b>RSI: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">The daily <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/rsi-relative-strength-index/">RSI slope</a> nosedived below the midline indicating the rising negative sentiment among market participants.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">MATIC Coin Price Intraday Levels</span></h2>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Spot rate: $0.99</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Trend:  Bearish</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Volatility: Low</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Resistance levels- $1.07 and $1.24</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Support levels- $1 and $0.94</span></li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/markets/matic-price-prediction-polygon-price-at-crucial-support-plots-a-50-rally-enter-today/">MATIC Price Prediction: Polygon Price at Crucial Support Plots a 50% Rally; Enter Today?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/30224735/Polygon-blockchain-13.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Top Bank&#8217;s 2024 Bitcoin Price Prediction Stirs Up Market, But Can It Really Happen?</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/bitcoin-price-100k-kendrick-prediction/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pratik Bhuyan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 20:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=146120</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>On Monday, April 24, the prominent banking institution, Standard Chartered, claimed that the much-hyped &#8220;crypto winter&#8221; had eventually come to an end, and further predicted that the world&#8217;s first decentralized currency &#8212; Bitcoin &#8212; may reach the price of $100,000 by the end of 2024. Despite the fact that forecasts of sky-high valuations have been <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/bitcoin-price-100k-kendrick-prediction/" title="Top Bank&#8217;s 2024 Bitcoin Price Prediction Stirs Up Market, But Can It Really Happen?"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/bitcoin-price-100k-kendrick-prediction/">Top Bank&#8217;s 2024 Bitcoin Price Prediction Stirs Up Market, But Can It Really Happen?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="900" height="540" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/25010846/bitcoin-1.png" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Bitcoin price" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p>On Monday, April 24, the prominent banking institution, Standard Chartered, claimed that the much-hyped &#8220;<a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/crypto-winter-2/">crypto winter</a>&#8221; had eventually come to an end, and further predicted that the world&#8217;s first decentralized currency &#8212; <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> &#8212; may reach the price of $100,000 by the end of 2024. Despite the fact that forecasts of sky-high valuations have been quite regular after previous rallies in Bitcoin&#8217;s price, there are a number of elements that are strongly motivating this particular prognosis, according to Standard Chartered&#8217;s head of digital assets research Geoff Kendrick. In November of 2020, a Citi analyst predicted that the <a href="https://coingape.com/price/bitcoin">price of Bitcoin</a> may reach as high as $318,000 by the end of the year 2022. However, at $16,500, the flagship crypto asset was closed out for the year down roughly 65%. So the question is, will this too turn out to be another dud or finally come true?</p>
<h2>Bitcoin&#8217;s Bullish Factors</h2>
<p>The most recent crisis to hit the banking industry in the United States has lately sparked a price boom in Bitcoin and indirectly re-established its primary use case &#8220;as a decentralized, trustless, and scarce digital asset,&#8221; according to the bank. Additionally, Kendrick pointed out a number of other parameters which he thinks would fuel the price of Bitcoin which includes the fact that the <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/federal-reserve-system/">Federal Reserve</a> would no longer be raising interest rates, the fact that the supply bitcoin would be halved again, and that regulatory benefits making into UK and USA would finally be realized.</p>
<p><em><strong>Read More: <a title="Do Kwon’s Latest Move Against U.S. SEC Could Be Game Changing, But Is It Enough?" href="https://coingape.com/do-kwo-latest-move-sec-game-changer/" rel="bookmark">Do Kwon’s Latest Move Against U.S. SEC Could Be Game Changing, But Is It Enough?</a></strong></em></p>
<p>According to Standard Chartered, the fact that the Federal Reserve of the United States is drawing closer to the conclusion of its cycle of interest rate hikes should be favorable for risk assets in general. Bitcoin, being the king of risk assets, tends to benefit from such a development. Moreover, its increasing connection to the Nasdaq stock market at the present time suggests that the leading cryptocurrency  should trade even better if risk assets were to improve more generally. However, Bitcoin&#8217;s ability to trade higher during bad periods for risk assets does not preclude it from doing so.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin&#8217;s Upcoming Halving</h2>
<p>The uniqueness of Bitcoin lies in its code. The coding behind the largest cryptocurrency by <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/market-capitalization/">market cap</a> is designed to ensure that the rate of supply expansion slows down over time. And it’s these in-built <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/bitcoin-halving-2/">halving events</a> that have lent an impact on the price of Bitcoin previously. Because the source code is publicly available, simple calculations determine that the reward for a Bitcoin block is halved every 210,000 blocks, which is equivalent to around once in every four years.</p>
<p>When looking at historical information, we can see that the spot price of bitcoin has climbed by 1,263% between the 2016 and 2020 halvings.  If the current trends continue as they are, the price of bitcoin will reach $120,263 on the 23rd of March in 2024 which is in line with Kendrick&#8217;s Bitcoin price prediction.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter wp-image-146123 size-full" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/25010308/S7xz2k0f_548d5ea6d7f39df10ce98d47614af67a569204f6af4e526df49d668bc8a95774.png" alt="Bitcoin price" width="1280" height="598" /></p>
<p>On Sunday , the price of Bitcoin dipped below $27,000 for a short period of time as the broader <a href="https://coingape.com/markets/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">crypto market</a> continued its decline for five consecutive days. As things stand, Bitcoin’s price is currently exchanging hands at $27,348 which represents a drop of 0.43% over the past 24 hours in comparison to a loss of 7.47% recorded over the past seven days.</p>
<p><em><strong>Also Read: <a title="Binance.US Sparks Optimism As It Lists Floki (FLOKI), Is A Meme Season In The Making?" href="https://coingape.com/binance-news-support-for-floki-inu-meme-season-incoming/" rel="bookmark">Binance.US Sparks Optimism As It Lists Floki (FLOKI), Is A Meme Season In The Making?</a></strong></em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/bitcoin-price-100k-kendrick-prediction/">Top Bank&#8217;s 2024 Bitcoin Price Prediction Stirs Up Market, But Can It Really Happen?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/25010846/bitcoin-1.png" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Floki Price Skyrocketed 75% Today; Is This Rally Sustainable for New Buyers?</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/markets/floki-price-skyrocketed-75-today-is-this-rally-sustainable-for-new-buyers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brian Bollinger]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 18:29:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Floki Inu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FLOKI Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?post_type=markets&#038;p=146122</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Today, the Floki coin price witnessed a significant inflow and shows a 75% hike. This massive rise could be associated with the recent listing announcement of Floki in the California-based Binance exchange and also becoming the official partner of the Asian Badminton Championship 2023. This event could allow Floki to show its utility to numerous <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/markets/floki-price-skyrocketed-75-today-is-this-rally-sustainable-for-new-buyers/" title="Floki Price Skyrocketed 75% Today; Is This Rally Sustainable for New Buyers?"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/markets/floki-price-skyrocketed-75-today-is-this-rally-sustainable-for-new-buyers/">Floki Price Skyrocketed 75% Today; Is This Rally Sustainable for New Buyers?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/01120714/Floki-Inu.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Today, the Floki coin price witnessed a significant inflow and shows a 75% hike. This massive rise could be associated with the recent <a href="https://coingape.com/binance-news-support-for-floki-inu-meme-season-incoming/">listing announcement</a> of Floki in the California-based Binance exchange and also becoming the official partner of the Asian Badminton Championship 2023. This event could allow Floki to show its utility to numerous investors and present its brand in front of a massive crowd. Amid this rally, the coin price breached a crucial monthly resistance of $0.000042, offering an entry opportunity to potential buyers.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Key points: </span></h2>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">A daily candle closing at $0.000042 resistance will offer buyers a significant footing to prolong the bullish rally.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">A bullish breakout backed by tremendous high volume indicates the buyers’ conviction to achieve higher price levels</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The intraday trading volume in the Floki coin is $116 Million, indicating a 903% gain.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><img decoding="async" class="alignnone" src="https://s3.tradingview.com/snapshots/6/62WcRY8Q.png" alt="Floki Price" width="1946" height="1104" />Source- </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Tradingview</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Over the past six weeks, the Floki coin price resonated in a fixed range spread from $0.000042 to $0.000027 level. In the daily time chart, this consolidation revealed the formation of a double bottom pattern. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Pointing to this pattern’s core concept, the setup indicates strong sustainability for Floki&#8217;s price at $0.000027 base support which allows buyers to replenish bullish momentum. Moreover, the announcement of Floki to be an official partner of the Asian Badminton Championship 2023 has grabbed the attention of several investors fueling the ongoing intraday growth.</span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">The 2023 Badminton Asia Championship is just around the corner, from April 25-30 in Dubai, UAE at the Sheikh Rashid Bin Hamdan Indoor Hall. </p>
<p>Powered by <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/FLOKI?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#FLOKI</a>, its set to introduce the <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24FLOKI&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$FLOKI</a> brand to 600+ million households in Asia.</p>
<p>Buy tickets here:<a href="https://t.co/VVNuSY24a8">https://t.co/VVNuSY24a8</a> <a href="https://t.co/yD3nNUItvI">pic.twitter.com/yD3nNUItvI</a></p>
<p>&mdash; FLOKI (@RealFlokiInu) <a href="https://twitter.com/RealFlokiInu/status/1650143630143766529?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">April 23, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">With today’s 75% price jump, the Floki price gave a decisive breakout from the $0.000042 neckline resistance of the double bottom pattern. Concerning the fast-moving price action, the new investors should form a candle closing above $0.000042 to confirm a breakout opportunity. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In the coming days, if the price shows sustainability above the breakout level, the buyers are likely to raise the coin’s market value 35% higher to hit $0.000057.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On a contrary note, the daily closing below $0.000042 may hint at the continuation of a sideways trend.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Technical Indicator</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><strong>Relative Strength Index:</strong> The daily <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/rsi-relative-strength-index/">RSI slope</a> surge above the midline reflects the rising bullish sentiment among traders.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><strong>Exponential Moving Average:</strong> A potential bullish crossover between the 20-and-50-day <a href="https://coingape.com/education/exponential-moving-average-how-to-leverage-it-in-crypto-market/">EMA</a> will add an extra edge to long buyers.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Floki Coin Price Intraday Levels</span></h2>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Spot rate: $0.0000249</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Trend: Bullish</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Volatility: High</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Resistance levels- $0.000047 and $0.000057</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Support levels- $0.0000427 and $0.0000328</span></li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/markets/floki-price-skyrocketed-75-today-is-this-rally-sustainable-for-new-buyers/">Floki Price Skyrocketed 75% Today; Is This Rally Sustainable for New Buyers?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/01120714/Floki-Inu.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Whales Buy XRP Dip; Moves 180 Mln XRP</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/xrp-news-whales-buy-xrp-dip-moves-180-mln-xrp/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ashish Kumar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 17:44:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple vs SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC vs Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Xrp price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=146107</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>XRP News: Ripple’s native crypto, XRP is trading under increased selling pressure losing its gain registered over the past week. XRP price is down by more than 11% in the last 7 days. However, this dip has allowed the crypto whales to add accumulate more XRP tokens. Also Read: Ripple Moving Out Of U.S. After <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/xrp-news-whales-buy-xrp-dip-moves-180-mln-xrp/" title="Crypto Whales Buy XRP Dip; Moves 180 Mln XRP"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/xrp-news-whales-buy-xrp-dip-moves-180-mln-xrp/">Crypto Whales Buy XRP Dip; Moves 180 Mln XRP</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/24151009/XRP-DUMP-1.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="XRP News Ripple price lawsuit SEC" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p><strong>XRP News:</strong> Ripple’s native crypto, XRP is trading under increased selling pressure losing its gain registered over the past week. <a href="https://coingape.com/price/xrp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">XRP price</a> is down by more than 11% in the last 7 days. However, this dip has allowed the crypto whales to add accumulate more XRP tokens.</p>
<p><strong>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/ripple-moving-out-of-u-s-after-coinbase-ceo-drops-hint/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ripple Moving Out Of U.S. After Coinbase CEO Drops Hint?</a></strong></p>
<h2>108 Mln XRP On The Move</h2>
<p>As per the data provided by WhaleAlert, crypto whales have moved around 180 million XRP (approx worth $82 million) in multiple transactions over the past 24 hours. The biggest transaction recorded by the tracker has been of moving 108.9 million XRP tokens (approx worth $50 million) among unknown wallets.</p>
<p>XRP price has dropped by over 2% in the last 24 hours. This dip has allowed crypto whales to accumulate 42 million XRP tokens in a single transaction. More than $19.34 million worth of XRP tokens were bought from the Bitso <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/crypto-exchange-2/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">crypto exchange</a>.</p>
<p>However, whales were also caught dumping XRP tokens amid the price drop. As per the data, 28 million XRP tokens (approx worth $13 million) were moved by a whale wallet to the Bitstamp crypto exchange. <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/xrp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>Read More XRP News Here&#8230;</strong></a></p>
<p><strong>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/ripple-exec-opts-for-eus-progressive-crypto-laws-as-xrp-case-verdict-closes-in/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ripple Exec Opts For EU’s Progressive Crypto Laws As XRP Case Verdict Closes In</a></strong></p>
<p>It is important to note that XRP price is still in flagging green indexes maintaining a gain of around 7% in the last 30 days. XRP is trading at an average price of $0.454, at the press time. Its 24-hour trading volume is up by 74% to stand at $1.2 billion.</p>
<p>XRP price has been stagnant over the past 2 years as <a href="https://coingape.com/xrp-lawsuit-ripples-fight-over-fair-notice-extends/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ripple Labs and its executives are facing a legal tussle</a> launched by U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). However, XRP has managed to gain around 33% on the year to date (YTD) basis.</p>
<p><strong>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/xrp-news-sec-losing-grip-on-supreme-court-case-will-this-help-ripple/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC Losing Grip On Supreme Court Case; Will This Help Ripple?</a></strong></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/xrp-news-whales-buy-xrp-dip-moves-180-mln-xrp/">Crypto Whales Buy XRP Dip; Moves 180 Mln XRP</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/24151009/XRP-DUMP-1.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Do Kwon&#8217;s Latest Move Against U.S. SEC Could Be Game Changing, But Is It Enough?</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/do-kwo-latest-move-sec-game-changer/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pratik Bhuyan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 16:35:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Do Kwon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[luna]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Securities and Exchange Commission]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terra]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terra (LUNA)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=146103</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>According to recent court documents, the attorneys for Do Kwon, the founder of the defunct cryptocurrency issuer Terraform Labs, have asked a United States court to dismiss charges levied against him by the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). This comes after the legal team representing Kwon alleged that the regulatory body lacked the legal jurisdiction <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/do-kwo-latest-move-sec-game-changer/" title="Do Kwon&#8217;s Latest Move Against U.S. SEC Could Be Game Changing, But Is It Enough?"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/do-kwo-latest-move-sec-game-changer/">Do Kwon&#8217;s Latest Move Against U.S. SEC Could Be Game Changing, But Is It Enough?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="840" height="560" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/24215348/Do-Kwon.v21.webp" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="do kwon" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p>According to recent court documents, the attorneys for <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/do-kwon/">Do Kwon</a>, the founder of the defunct cryptocurrency issuer Terraform Labs, have asked a United States court to dismiss charges levied against him by the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). This comes after the legal team representing Kwon alleged that the regulatory body lacked the legal jurisdiction to purse their lawsuit.</p>
<h2>Do Kwon&#8217;s Legal Tussle</h2>
<p>U.S. law enforcement accused Kwon of defrauding <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/cryptocurrency/">cryptocurrency</a> investors in a 12-page indictment that was made public later last month. According to the lawsuit Kwon deceived &#8220;individuals about aspects of the Terra blockchain, including its technology and the extent to which it had been adopted by users.&#8221;</p>
<p><em><strong>Read More: <a title="Ripple Moving Out Of U.S. After Coinbase CEO Drops Hint?" href="https://coingape.com/ripple-moving-out-of-u-s-after-coinbase-ceo-drops-hint/" rel="bookmark">Ripple Moving Out Of U.S. After Coinbase CEO Drops Hint?</a></strong></em></p>
<p>However, in response, Kwon&#8217;s attorneys <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://www.courtlistener.com/docket/66820843/29/securities-and-exchange-commission-v-terraform-labs-pte-ltd/" rel="nofollow">argued</a> that the SEC was unable to prove that it had personal jurisdiction over Kwon because the products referenced by the regulator were &#8220;available to the world and not directed at persons in the United States.&#8221; The allegations that have been hurled against them are categorically refuted throughout the 47-page report.</p>
<h2>Terra Calls UST A Currency</h2>
<p>In addition, the biggest ace in the hole is the <a href="https://coingape.com/terras-ust-peg-was-maintained-artificially-not-by-algorithm/">UST stablecoin</a>, which the Kwon legal team contends is a currency and not a security. As a result, the Kwon team concludes that the collapse of the Terra ecosystem falls outside of its jurisdiction. While the SEC argues that UST is a security because it could be used to buy LUNA, the Kwon team was quoted as saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>The SEC has not previously asserted that something is a security merely because it can be used to buy something else the SEC calls a security.</p></blockquote>
<p>Although this has come as a shocker to the financial watchdog, it will still be an uphill task for Kwon&#8217;s lawyers to prove that UST is in fact a currency and not an unregistered crypto security as deemed by the regulators.</p>
<p>Kwon is still being investigated for criminal fraud by authorities in the United States, and in South Korea, as he&#8217;s currently accused of violating laws governing financial markets. Both nations have put forward requests to have the former executive extradited to their jurisdictions so that they can initiate rightful legal proceedings.</p>
<p>In the wake of this news, the price of LUNA gained by 3.11% in the past 1 hour in contrast to an increase of 2.07% recorded over the past 24 hours. It is currently exchanging hands at $1.38 at the time of writing.</p>
<p><em><strong>Also Read: <a title="Binance.US Sparks Optimism As It Lists Floki (FLOKI), Is A Meme Season In The Making?" href="https://coingape.com/binance-news-support-for-floki-inu-meme-season-incoming/" rel="bookmark">Binance.US Sparks Optimism As It Lists Floki (FLOKI), Is A Meme Season In The Making?</a></strong></em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/do-kwo-latest-move-sec-game-changer/">Do Kwon&#8217;s Latest Move Against U.S. SEC Could Be Game Changing, But Is It Enough?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/24215348/Do-Kwon.v21.webp" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>LUNC News: Terra Classic Projects To Burn Millions of LUNC, Key Proposals Passed</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/lunc-news-terra-classic-projects-to-burn-millions-of-lunc-key-proposals-passed/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Varinder Singh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 16:25:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LUNC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LUNC price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terra]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terra Classic]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=146110</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Terra Luna Classic community welcomed another project onto the network by approving a key parameter change proposal. The proposal will not only abroad this new project, but enable other projects to build on the Terra Luna Classic blockchain. Proposal 11477 “Increase MaxContractSize to upload code” submitted by TerraPoker to increase of key on Cosmos <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/lunc-news-terra-classic-projects-to-burn-millions-of-lunc-key-proposals-passed/" title="LUNC News: Terra Classic Projects To Burn Millions of LUNC, Key Proposals Passed"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/lunc-news-terra-classic-projects-to-burn-millions-of-lunc-key-proposals-passed/">LUNC News: Terra Classic Projects To Burn Millions of LUNC, Key Proposals Passed</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1280" height="720" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/23210244/lunc-1-1-e1671875694694.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="LUNC News: Terra Classic Projects To Burn Millions of LUNC, Key Proposals Passed" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" srcset="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/23210244/lunc-1-1-e1671875694694.jpg 1280w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/23210244/lunc-1-1-e1671875694694-300x169.jpg 300w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/23210244/lunc-1-1-e1671875694694-768x432.jpg 768w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/23210244/lunc-1-1-e1671875694694-1224x689.jpg 1224w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/23210244/lunc-1-1-e1671875694694-678x381.jpg 678w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/23210244/lunc-1-1-e1671875694694-150x84.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1280px) 100vw, 1280px" /><p>The Terra Luna Classic community welcomed another project onto the network by approving a key parameter change proposal. The proposal will not only abroad this new project, but enable other projects to build on the Terra Luna Classic blockchain.</p>
<p>Proposal 11477 “Increase MaxContractSize to upload code” submitted by TerraPoker to increase of key on Cosmos Wasm MaxContractSize to 819200 from 614400 is passed. This will allow the protocol to upload its contract on the chain and contribute to the LUNC burn campaign.</p>
<p>TerraPoker in a <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/TP_TerraPoker/status/1650384169757999105" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">tweet</a> on April 24 appreciated the community for supporting the project to launch on the Terra Classic chain. The project will <span class="css-901oao css-16my406 r-poiln3 r-bcqeeo r-qvutc0">provide the poker game with </span><span class="r-18u37iz">LUNC</span><span class="css-901oao css-16my406 r-poiln3 r-bcqeeo r-qvutc0"> soon and promises to burn 10% of the rake fees collected.</span></p>
<p>The adjustment in contract size will not only welcome Terra Poker into the Terra Classic ecosystem, but also allow other protocols to join and help developers build better solutions.</p>
<p>The proposal has received 60% of votes in favor, while 31% voted &#8220;No&#8221; and 8% voted &#8220;Abstain.&#8221; The current sentiment in the LUNC community suggests the proposal will increase utility on the chain and boost LUNC burn. Thus, major validators including Allnodes, LUNC DAO, TerraCVita, Interstake, and JESUSisLORD supported the project.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, validator <strong>Allnodes</strong> has <a href="https://coingape.com/lunc-news-allnodes-supports-terra-rebels-controversial-terra-classic-proposal/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">supported the controversial Proposal 11479</a> by the <strong>Terra Rebels</strong> developer group, passing the proposal to fund $37,593 worth of LUNC tokens for running Rebel Station Infrastructure for 3 months.</p>
<h2>Another Project on Terra Classic Burned 11.79 million LUNC</h2>
<p>While TerraPoker aims to burn millions of LUNC tokens, some projects such as Cremation Coin are already contributing large LUNC burns, with total net LUNC burn of over 344 million.</p>
<p>However, another project called <strong>GenesisX50</strong> has <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://finder.terra.money/classic/tx/AD3F617167E9A6289CB7CAF150132B613077B6633C4627599321A45C87EDF763" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">burned</a> <strong>11,799,000 LUNC</strong> in a single transaction. The project has now burned 13 million LUNC in total as part of its native GSX50 token burns.</p>
<p>Moreover, LUNC DAO has burned 1.44 LUNC tokens as part of the weekly burn plan. The validator has burned over 457 million LUNC in total.</p>
<p><strong>Also Read: <a title="Permanent Link to Binance Adds Bitcoin, Shiba Inu, Dogecoin, Stablecoins To Liquid Swap" href="https://coingape.com/binance-adds-bitcoin-shiba-inu-dogecoin-stablecoins-to-liquid-swap" target="_blank" rel="bookmark noopener">Binance Adds Bitcoin, Shiba Inu, Dogecoin, Stablecoins To Liquid Swap</a></strong></p>
<h2>LUNC Price Remains Under Pressure</h2>
<p>South Korean District Court <a href="https://coingape.com/lunc-news-luna-is-not-a-security-declares-s-korean-court/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">rejected the prosecutors&#8217; office claims</a> that Terra LUNA or Terra Classic LUNC are securities. Moreover, the court also dismissed the state’s appeal of confiscating Terraform Labs co-founder Daniel Shin.</p>
<p>However, LUNC price remains under pressure as Terra Luna Classic community <a href="https://coingape.com/lunc-news-core-developers-edward-kim-zaradar-leave-joint-l1-task-force/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">facing a minor crisis</a> as core developers <strong>Ed Kim</strong> and <strong>Tobias “Zaradar” Andersen </strong>left the Joint L1 Task Force developer team.</p>
<p><a href="https://coingape.com/price/terra-luna-classic" target="_blank" rel="noopener">LUNC price</a> fell 1% in the last 24 hours, with the price currently trading at $0.00011. The 24-hour low and high are $0.000108 and $0.000111, respectively.</p>
<p><strong>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/just-in-bone-shibaswap-bone-arbdoge-ai-aidoge-pump-10-on-okx-listing" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bone ShibaSwap (BONE), ArbDoge AI (AIDOGE) Pump 10% On OKX Listing</a></strong></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/lunc-news-terra-classic-projects-to-burn-millions-of-lunc-key-proposals-passed/">LUNC News: Terra Classic Projects To Burn Millions of LUNC, Key Proposals Passed</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/23210244/lunc-1-1-e1671875694694-1224x689.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bybit Introduces Compulsory KYC in Move Toward Full Compliance</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/bybit-introduces-compulsory-kyc-in-move-toward-full-compliance/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Godfrey Benjamin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 16:11:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bybit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Compliance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[KYC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=146105</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>ByBit is pushing for greater compliance and is demanding related compliance from its users. In a recent update to its terms, users of all the exchange’s products and services are expected to have completed at least the first level of the trading platform’s Know-Your-Customers (KYC) procedures before May 8th 2023.  Starting from 8 May, 2023, <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/bybit-introduces-compulsory-kyc-in-move-toward-full-compliance/" title="Bybit Introduces Compulsory KYC in Move Toward Full Compliance"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/bybit-introduces-compulsory-kyc-in-move-toward-full-compliance/">Bybit Introduces Compulsory KYC in Move Toward Full Compliance</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="627" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/24214033/Bybit.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p><span style="font-weight: 400">ByBit is pushing for greater compliance and is demanding related compliance from its users. In a recent update to its terms, users of all the exchange’s products and services are expected to have </span><a rel='nofollow'  href="https://www.bybit.com/en-US/help-center/s/article/Individual-KYC-FAQ"><span style="font-weight: 400">completed</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> at least the first level of the trading platform’s Know-Your-Customers (KYC) procedures before May 8th 2023. </span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Starting from 8 May, 2023, Identity Verification of at least Lv.1 will be mandatory for all Bybit products and services. Existing users who have not completed Identity Verification as of 8 May, 2023 will only be allowed to close existing open positions or orders, return loans, or…</p>
<p>&mdash; Wu Blockchain (@WuBlockchain) <a href="https://twitter.com/WuBlockchain/status/1650487377268477953?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">April 24, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">If by the end of the stipulated date, existing users have not completed the identity verification process at Level 1 (Lv.1), they would be limited to only closing existing open positions or orders, returning loans, or withdrawing.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">&#8220;Any new trading activities will be restricted. Once the Identity Verification is completed, existing users can continue to use Bybit products and services,&#8221; Bybit posted.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">According to the Dubai-headquartered cryptocurrency exchange, KYC is a requirement for financial service providers that clients must fulfill. It is conducted to &#8220;verify the identity, suitability and risks involved, in order to minimize the risk to the respective account.&#8221; </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Notably, the KYC process is in levels and the higher the level, the higher the offerings available to a user, especially for withdrawals.</span></p>
<h2><b>Enhanced Functionalities for Bybit Verified KYC Users</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Users who do not undergo the KYC process are limited to a withdrawal of about 20,000 Tether (USDT) or less daily. On the other hand, those who complete Lv.1, can access as much as 1 million USDT daily. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">While the KYC Lv.2 users have a daily withdrawal limit of less than or equal to 2 million USDT. These withdrawal limits are basically for those on the non-VIP level. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Therefore, those on the several VIP levels are entitled to higher daily withdrawal limits. It goes as high as 12 million USDT. As Bybit is seeing tremendous growth and in its <a href="https://coingape.com/bybit-launches-new-futures-contracts-to-expand-its-derivatives-offerings/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">product offering</a>, so also is its need to become compliant in order to stay on the good side of the law. With the new compliance move, the exchange is created a bed that can shield it from regulatory purge in the near future.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Bybit’s key competitors particularly those in the United States including Coinbase and Paxos have all made it to the list of exchanges billed for sanctioning after Kraken </span><a href="https://coingape.com/kraken-starts-withdrawing-all-staked-ethereum-eth-amid-us-sec-pressure/"><span style="font-weight: 400">paid</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> a $32 million fine for some of its products.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">While Bybit serves other markets, the KYC push will give it a </span><a href="https://coingape.com/breaking-osc-bans-kucoin-settlement-agreement-with-bybit-approved/"><span style="font-weight: 400">more competitive edge</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> to explore more markets beyond its current operational range.</span></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/bybit-introduces-compulsory-kyc-in-move-toward-full-compliance/">Bybit Introduces Compulsory KYC in Move Toward Full Compliance</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/24214033/Bybit.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance.US Sparks Optimism As It Lists Floki (FLOKI), Is A Meme Season In The Making?</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/binance-news-support-for-floki-inu-meme-season-incoming/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pratik Bhuyan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 15:52:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BinanceUS]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FLOKI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Floki Inu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=146111</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Binance News: Days after recognizing Shiba Inu&#8217;s full potential as a result of an internal review and its subsequent delisting from the Binance&#8217;s experimental &#8220;innovation zone&#8221;, the U.S. arm of the world&#8217;s largest crypto exchange announced that it will offer Floki (FLOKI) &#8212; another flagship cryptocurrency from the memecoin genre. Binance Lists Floki (FLOKI) On <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/binance-news-support-for-floki-inu-meme-season-incoming/" title="Binance.US Sparks Optimism As It Lists Floki (FLOKI), Is A Meme Season In The Making?"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/binance-news-support-for-floki-inu-meme-season-incoming/">Binance.US Sparks Optimism As It Lists Floki (FLOKI), Is A Meme Season In The Making?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="720" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/24200934/5184.webp" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="binance news" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p><strong>Binance News: </strong>Days after recognizing Shiba Inu&#8217;s full potential as a result of an internal review and its subsequent delisting from the Binance&#8217;s experimental &#8220;innovation zone&#8221;, the U.S. arm of the world&#8217;s largest <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/crypto-exchange-2/">crypto exchange</a> announced that it will offer <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/floki-inu/">Floki (FLOKI)</a> &#8212; another flagship cryptocurrency from the memecoin genre.</p>
<h2>Binance Lists Floki (FLOKI)</h2>
<p>On Monday, April 24, the California-based <a href="https://coingape.com/blog/binance-exchange-review/">Binance exchange</a> notified its millions of users about the upcoming Floki listing which would initially be paired with both USD and USDT support. The trading for the token is said to go live tomorrow, April 25, 2023 at 5 a.m. PDT / 8 a.m. EDT. However, according to the announcement, the deposit function for FLOKI tokens are currently enabled for users to fund their crypto accounts.</p>
<p><em><strong>Read More: <a title="Ripple Moving Out Of U.S. After Coinbase CEO Drops Hint?" href="https://coingape.com/ripple-moving-out-of-u-s-after-coinbase-ceo-drops-hint/" rel="bookmark">Ripple Moving Out Of U.S. After Coinbase CEO Drops Hint?</a></strong></em></p>
<p>In the wake of this Binance news, the upcoming <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/meme-cryptocurrency/">meme cryptocurrency</a> &#8212; which is currently valued at $345 million &#8212; rose by nearly 6.1% in the past one hour while registering gains of roughly 25% in the past one hour. At the time of writing, the price of FLOKI is presently exchanging hands at $0.000035.</p>
<h2>Is A Meme Season Coming?</h2>
<p>As <a href="https://coingape.com/binance-adds-bitcoin-shiba-inu-dogecoin-stablecoins-to-liquid-swap/">reported</a> by CoinGape earlier today, Binance has created seven new liquidity pools for crypto including <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a>, Shiba Inu, and <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/dogecoin">Dogecoin</a> in response to the growing demand for such cryptocurrencies. Moreover, emerging memecoins like Bone ShibaSwap (BONE), ArbDoge AI (AIDOGE) pumped more than 10% on news of a <a href="https://coingape.com/just-in-bone-shibaswap-bone-arbdoge-ai-aidoge-pump-10-on-okx-listing/">major exchange listing</a> today.</p>
<p>As a direct consequence of this, many in the crypto community are speculating of an impending memecoin rally where market participants anticipate higher retail engagement as an increasing number of exchanges provide support for these <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/altcoins/">altcoins</a>. However, such price movements are heavily dependent on Bitcoin and a further decline from its current levels of $27K would turn out to be devastating for the larger <a href="https://coingape.com/markets/?utm_source=menubar">crypto market</a>.</p>
<p><em><strong>Also Read: <a title="This AI-Powered Alternative To Stripe, PayPal Becoming Popular For Crypto Payments" href="https://coingape.com/near-protocol-ai-crypto-payment-alternative-stripe-paypal/" rel="bookmark">This AI-Powered Alternative To Stripe, PayPal Becoming Popular For Crypto Payments</a></strong></em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/binance-news-support-for-floki-inu-meme-season-incoming/">Binance.US Sparks Optimism As It Lists Floki (FLOKI), Is A Meme Season In The Making?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/24200934/5184.webp" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Polkadot Price Prediction: DOT Price Sees 12% Rise if Buyers Hold this Key Support, But There’s More</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/markets/polkadot-price-prediction-dot-price-sees-12-rise-if-buyers-hold-key-support/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brian Bollinger]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 15:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dot]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polkadot Price Prediction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?post_type=markets&#038;p=146114</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Polkadot Price Prediction: In the daily time frame chart, the Polkadot price shows the formation of an inverted head and shoulder pattern. This famous trend reversal pattern is often spotted at the market bottom and offers early opportunities to go long. Amid the ongoing selling in the crypto market, the coin price is still shaping <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/markets/polkadot-price-prediction-dot-price-sees-12-rise-if-buyers-hold-key-support/" title="Polkadot Price Prediction: DOT Price Sees 12% Rise if Buyers Hold this Key Support, But There’s More"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/markets/polkadot-price-prediction-dot-price-sees-12-rise-if-buyers-hold-key-support/">Polkadot Price Prediction: DOT Price Sees 12% Rise if Buyers Hold this Key Support, But There’s More</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="675" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/25024335/shutterstock_1849145665-e1682349362923.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Polkadot (DOT) Price" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" srcset="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/25024335/shutterstock_1849145665-e1682349362923.jpg 1200w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/25024335/shutterstock_1849145665-e1682349362923-300x169.jpg 300w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/25024335/shutterstock_1849145665-e1682349362923-768x432.jpg 768w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/25024335/shutterstock_1849145665-e1682349362923-678x381.jpg 678w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/25024335/shutterstock_1849145665-e1682349362923-150x84.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Polkadot Price Prediction: In the daily time frame chart, the <a href="https://coingape.com/price/polkadot/#:~:text=DOT%20Price%20Trends%20%3A,trading%20volume%20of%20%24194%2C926%2C034%20USD.">Polkadot price</a> shows the formation of an inverted head and shoulder pattern. This famous trend reversal pattern is often spotted at the market bottom and offers early opportunities to go long. Amid the ongoing selling in the crypto market, the coin price is still shaping the third portion of the pattern, trying to sustain at higher chart levels. Here’s how this pattern may further influence the future trend of DOT prices.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Key Points:</span></h2>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Completion of the inverted head and shoulder pattern could drive the DOT price 80% higher than the current price</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">A potential bearish crossover between the 20-and-50-day EMA may prolong the current correction phase</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The 24-hour trading volume in the Polkadot coin is $165.5 Million, indicating a 49% gain.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><img decoding="async" class="alignnone" src="https://s3.tradingview.com/snapshots/d/DEkeRDD6.png" alt="Polkadot Price Prediction" width="1946" height="1104" />Source-</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Tradingview</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On April 18th, the Polkadot price turned down from the long-coming resistance trendline of an inverted head and shoulder and triggered a new correction phase. As a result, the coin price tumbled 16.9% to plunge to local support of $5.76-$5.66.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The negative sentiment in the market might have created this slight detour, but until the prices show sustainability above the $5.76 or $5.3 support, the bullish setup will remain intact. By the press time, the DOT price traded at the $5.9 mark but the lower price rejection candles observed in the last few days projects a higher possibility for price reversal.</span></p>
<blockquote><p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/top-crypto-copy-trading-platforms/">Top Crypto Copy Trading Platforms For 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This potential reversal may push the price 12% higher to hit the aforementioned resistance trendline. Under the influence of this pattern, the buyers should eventually breach this dynamic resistance. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In an ideal bullish scenario, a breakout above the trendline may set the DOT price for an 80% rally to hit $10.8.</span></p>
<h2><b>Technical Analysis</b></h2>
<p><b>Bollinger Band:</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> the DOT price wavering at the lower band of the <a href="https://coingape.com/education/bollinger-band/">Bollinger band indicator</a> increases the possibility of a bullish reversal.</span></p>
<p><b>RSI:</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> The daily <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/rsi-relative-strength-index/">RSI slope</a> took a sharp dive into the bearish territory indicating a negative sentiment in the market.</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Resistance levels- $6 and $6.6</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Support levels- $5.6 and $5.3</span></li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/markets/polkadot-price-prediction-dot-price-sees-12-rise-if-buyers-hold-key-support/">Polkadot Price Prediction: DOT Price Sees 12% Rise if Buyers Hold this Key Support, But There’s More</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/25024335/shutterstock_1849145665-e1682349362923.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>China&#8217;s Big CBDC Plan: Digital Yuan For Europe Trade</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/chinas-big-cbdc-plan-digital-yuan-for-europe-trade/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Anvesh Reddy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 15:19:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[China CBDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=146113</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>China&#8217;s Belt and Road initiative, the project aimed at improving regional co-operation through better connectivity, is one of the most ambitious infrastructure plans globally. While the initiative is purely physical and involves improving road connectivity, the country&#8217;s digital infrastructure plans for cross border trade could change the face of international payments in the commercial space. <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/chinas-big-cbdc-plan-digital-yuan-for-europe-trade/" title="China&#8217;s Big CBDC Plan: Digital Yuan For Europe Trade"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/chinas-big-cbdc-plan-digital-yuan-for-europe-trade/">China&#8217;s Big CBDC Plan: Digital Yuan For Europe Trade</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="630" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/11125858/0F4774CFCF2532A67926524653EC6B978C640E56A830BFE0179C6B943F364DED.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="China&#039;s Digital Yuan" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p>China&#8217;s Belt and Road initiative, the project aimed at improving regional co-operation through better connectivity, is one of the most ambitious infrastructure plans globally. While the initiative is purely physical and involves improving road connectivity, the country&#8217;s digital infrastructure plans for cross border trade could change the face of international payments in the commercial space. This is because the initiative connects stakeholders from around 150 countries.</p>
<p>Also Read: <a rel='nofollow'  href="http://coingape.com/binance-adds-bitcoin-shiba-inu-dogecoin-stablecoins-to-liquid-swap" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>Binance Adds Bitcoin, Shiba Inu, Dogecoin, Stablecoins To Liquid Swap</strong></a></p>
<h2>Digital Yuan For China&#8217;s Belt And Road Initiative</h2>
<p>China&#8217;s logistics hubs just began promoting the digital Yuan (e-CNY) for usage in cross border trade, as per a report in the South China Morning Post. This could be huge as the Belt and Road initiative was in 2022 already covering 30% of the country&#8217;s import export global trade. Hence, this could be seen as potentially largest digital currency usage project so far globally. Earlier, CoinGape <a href="https://coingape.com/rbi-india-digital-rupee-launch-cities-cbdc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a> that India&#8217;s central bank, the Reserve Bank of India (RBI), began implementing the digital rupee pilot for settlement of secondary market transactions.</p>
<p>Xuzhou, a well connected city in China&#8217;s Jiangsu, laid out a plan to promote the digital Yuan for trade purpose in 21 countries across Europe and Asia, besides taxes and utility services. The city&#8217;s authorities said the larger plan is to support the Belt and Road Initiative with e-CNY. Another city, Changshu, will pay government employees using digital Yuan.</p>
<p>However, this may not help the cause of <a href="https://coingape.com/markets/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">crypto market</a> as the central bank digital currency (CBDC) projects operate outside the blockchain ecosystem. In fact, the CBDC market could potentially hamper cryptocurrency space both financially as well as in regulatory aspect.</p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/binance-adds-bitcoin-shiba-inu-dogecoin-stablecoins-to-liquid-swap" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>Binance Adds Bitcoin, Shiba Inu, Dogecoin, Stablecoins To Liquid Swap</strong></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/chinas-big-cbdc-plan-digital-yuan-for-europe-trade/">China&#8217;s Big CBDC Plan: Digital Yuan For Europe Trade</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/11125858/0F4774CFCF2532A67926524653EC6B978C640E56A830BFE0179C6B943F364DED.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>DOGE Price Prediction: This Key Level will Determine if Dogecoin Price could Rise 24% or Tumble 10%</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/markets/doge-price-prediction-key-level-determine-if-dogecoin-price-rise-24-or-drop-10/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brian Bollinger]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 14:05:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOGE Price Prediction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin (DOGE)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[EMA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?post_type=markets&#038;p=146109</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>DOGE Price Prediction: April month has been a roller coaster ride for Dogecoin prices where it showed huge price swings but no commitment to a specific direction. Despite uncertain behavior, the coin price breached a long-coming resistance trendline on April 3rd offering an early sign for trend reversal. As of now, the buyers retest the breached <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/markets/doge-price-prediction-key-level-determine-if-dogecoin-price-rise-24-or-drop-10/" title="DOGE Price Prediction: This Key Level will Determine if Dogecoin Price could Rise 24% or Tumble 10%"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/markets/doge-price-prediction-key-level-determine-if-dogecoin-price-rise-24-or-drop-10/">DOGE Price Prediction: This Key Level will Determine if Dogecoin Price could Rise 24% or Tumble 10%</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/26113813/dogecoin1.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="dogecoin DOGE price crypto news" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p><i><span style="font-weight: 400;"><a href="https://coingape.com/doge-price-prediction/">DOGE Price Prediction</a>: </span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">April month has been a roller coaster ride for Dogecoin prices where it showed huge price swings but no commitment to a specific direction. Despite uncertain behavior, the coin price breached a long-coming resistance trendline on April 3rd offering an early sign for trend reversal. As of now, the buyers retest the breached trendline as a potential support to drive a sustained recovery rally.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Key Points</span></h2>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">A potential breakout above $0.08 will encourage the Dogecoin price to a 24% rally</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">A breakdown below the support trendline will undermine the bullish thesis</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The 24-hour trading volume in the Dogecoin coin is $1.16 Billion, indicating a 46% gain.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><img decoding="async" src="https://s3.tradingview.com/snapshots/5/5WPLw5A0.png" alt="TradingView Chart" />Source-Tradingview </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Amid the recent sell-off in the crypto market, the <a href="https://coingape.com/price/dogecoin/">Dogecoin price</a> witnessed a 16.7% loss since last week&#8217;s high of $0.095 and plugged to the current market value of $0.079. As a result, the coin plummeted below the local support of $0.084-0.0793 but found immediate support at the aforementioned trendline.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The daily chart showcasing lower price rejection candles at flipped trendline indicates buyers are obtaining strong support from this dynamic slope. On a contrary note, the recently breached $0.084 horizontal level may act as significant resistance causing the Dogecoin price to wobble in a narrow range.</span></p>
<blockquote><p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/new-upcoming-binance-listing/">15 New Cryptocurrencies In Upcoming Binance Listing For 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If market sentiment improves and the DOGE price gives a daily candle closing above $0.084, the memecoin will get back on the recovery track. The potential breakout may lead the price to 24% higher to rechallenge the $0.1 psychological mark.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On a contrary note, a breakdown below the support trendline will encourage SHIB price for longer correction.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Technical indicators</span></h2>
<p><b>MACD: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">The increasing gap between the falling <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/macd-moving-average-convergence-divergnece/">MACD</a>(Blue) and signal(orange) line indicate aggressive selling pressure in the market.</span></p>
<p><b>EMAs: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">the daily <a href="https://coingape.com/education/exponential-moving-average-how-to-leverage-it-in-crypto-market/">EMAs</a>(20, 50, 100, and 200) moving just above the coin price reflect the buyers will face multiple resistance in a recovery attempt.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Dogecoin Price Intraday Levels</span></h2>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Spot rate: $0.079</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Trend: Bullish</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Volatility: High</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Resistance levels- $0.08 and $0.085</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Support levels- $0.071 and $0.0628</span></li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/markets/doge-price-prediction-key-level-determine-if-dogecoin-price-rise-24-or-drop-10/">DOGE Price Prediction: This Key Level will Determine if Dogecoin Price could Rise 24% or Tumble 10%</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/26113813/dogecoin1.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Unveils ChatGPT Powered AI Chatbot</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/web-stories/binance-unveiled-ai-powered-chatbot-sensei/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Coingape Staff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 13:36:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?post_type=web-story&#038;p=146094</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[		<div class="wp-block-web-stories-embed alignnone">
			<a href="https://coingape.com/web-stories/binance-unveiled-ai-powered-chatbot-sensei/">
									<img
						src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/24183140/binance_has_announced_sensei_720.jpg"
						width="360"
						height="600"
						alt="Binance Unveils ChatGPT Powered AI Chatbot"
																			sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"
												loading="lazy"
						decoding="async"
					/>
								</a>
		</div>
		]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[		<div class="wp-block-web-stories-embed alignnone">
			<a href="https://coingape.com/web-stories/binance-unveiled-ai-powered-chatbot-sensei/">
									<img
						src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/24183140/binance_has_announced_sensei_720.jpg"
						width="360"
						height="600"
						alt="Binance Unveils ChatGPT Powered AI Chatbot"
																			sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"
												loading="lazy"
						decoding="async"
					/>
								</a>
		</div>
		]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/24183140/binance_has_announced_sensei_720.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Elon Musk Picks Battle With Twitter’s Famous Troll Dril</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/web-stories/elon-musk-picks-battle-with-famous-troll-dril/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jai Pratap]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 13:31:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?post_type=web-story&#038;p=146098</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[		<div class="wp-block-web-stories-embed alignnone">
			<a href="https://coingape.com/web-stories/elon-musk-picks-battle-with-famous-troll-dril/">
									<img
						src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/24185811/Elon-Musk-Picks-Battle-With-Twitters-Famous-Troll-Dril.jpg"
						width="360"
						height="600"
						alt="Elon Musk Picks Battle With Twitter’s Famous Troll Dril"
																			sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"
												loading="lazy"
						decoding="async"
					/>
								</a>
		</div>
		]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[		<div class="wp-block-web-stories-embed alignnone">
			<a href="https://coingape.com/web-stories/elon-musk-picks-battle-with-famous-troll-dril/">
									<img
						src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/24185811/Elon-Musk-Picks-Battle-With-Twitters-Famous-Troll-Dril.jpg"
						width="360"
						height="600"
						alt="Elon Musk Picks Battle With Twitter’s Famous Troll Dril"
																			sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"
												loading="lazy"
						decoding="async"
					/>
								</a>
		</div>
		]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/24185811/Elon-Musk-Picks-Battle-With-Twitters-Famous-Troll-Dril.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple Moving Out Of U.S. After Coinbase CEO Drops Hint?</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/ripple-moving-out-of-u-s-after-coinbase-ceo-drops-hint/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ashish Kumar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 12:28:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple vs SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC vs Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC vs Ripple Labs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Xrp price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=146051</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ripple News: Crypto firms based in the United States are reportedly seeking to relocate due lack of market guidance provided by the financial regulators. Coinbase, the U.S. biggest crypto exchange’s executive recently tipped off moving offshore, however, several developments are hinting that Ripple Labs might also be considering leaving the U.S. Also Read: Ex SEC <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/ripple-moving-out-of-u-s-after-coinbase-ceo-drops-hint/" title="Ripple Moving Out Of U.S. After Coinbase CEO Drops Hint?"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/ripple-moving-out-of-u-s-after-coinbase-ceo-drops-hint/">Ripple Moving Out Of U.S. After Coinbase CEO Drops Hint?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/18190911/ripple.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="ripple ceo XRP lawsuit update news" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p><strong>Ripple News:</strong> Crypto firms based in the United States are reportedly seeking to relocate due lack of market guidance provided by the financial regulators. Coinbase, the U.S. biggest <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/cryptocurrency-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">crypto exchange</a>’s executive recently<a href="https://coingape.com/coinbase-ceo-meets-sec-amid-moving-offshore-reports/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"> tipped off moving offshore</a>, however, several developments are hinting that Ripple Labs might also be considering leaving the U.S.</p>
<p><strong>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/crypto-news-ex-sec-chief-warns-of-more-crypto-lawsuits-ahead/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ex SEC Chief Warns Of More Crypto Lawsuits Ahead; Which Exchange Can Be Next?</a></strong></p>
<h2>Ripple Consider To Move Offshore?</h2>
<p>Ripple Labs and its executives are involved in the long running legal battle with the <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/securities-and-exchange-commission/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">U.S SEC</a>. It is expected that a verdict in the XRP lawsuit will lead the crypto industry toward regulatory clarity around crypto assets. Meanwhile, <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://ripple.com/careers/all-jobs/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Ripple’s recent job postings</a> have left the crypto community confused.</p>
<p>As per Ripple’s Career posting page, the firm is offering around 66 roles in the firm. It is important to note that 46 postings are offered outside the United States. Meanwhile, 6 of the open roles offered in the U.S. are several kinds of internships. However, Ripple CEO Brad Galinghouse have earlier stated that they will move outside if they lose the legal battle against the SEC.</p>
<p>It is expected that the recent job posting might be a part of Ripple’s expansion as Garlinghouse and the team seems to be much more confident of winning the crucial XRP case after recent court verdicts.</p>
<p><strong>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/lunc-news-luna-is-not-a-security-declares-s-korean-court/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">LUNA Is Not A Security, Declares S.Korean Court; Will US SEC Follow?</a></strong></p>
<p>U.S. watchdogs, Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) have recently picked up the pace by suing the crypto exchanges and lenders like Kraken, Bittrex and Gemini.</p>
<p>However, Brian Armstrong, Coinbase CEO is reportedly considering moving its head offices offshore. He stated that anything is on the table while in conversation with the ex UK Chancellor of the Exchequer George Osborne.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/ripple-moving-out-of-u-s-after-coinbase-ceo-drops-hint/">Ripple Moving Out Of U.S. After Coinbase CEO Drops Hint?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/18190911/ripple.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Just-In: Bone ShibaSwap (BONE), ArbDoge AI (AIDOGE) Pump 10% On OKX Listing</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/just-in-bone-shibaswap-bone-arbdoge-ai-aidoge-pump-10-on-okx-listing/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Varinder Singh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 12:28:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bone ShibaSwap]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto listing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OKX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[shiba inu]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=146084</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto exchange OKX on Monday announced the results of the special voting event held by the exchange to decide which meme coins should be listed. As per the voting tallies, the OKX crypto exchange will list ArbDoge AI (AIDOGE) and Bone ShibaSwap (BONE). Traders immediately reacted to the recent announcement, causing Bone ShibaSwap (BONE) and <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/just-in-bone-shibaswap-bone-arbdoge-ai-aidoge-pump-10-on-okx-listing/" title="Just-In: Bone ShibaSwap (BONE), ArbDoge AI (AIDOGE) Pump 10% On OKX Listing"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/just-in-bone-shibaswap-bone-arbdoge-ai-aidoge-pump-10-on-okx-listing/">Just-In: Bone ShibaSwap (BONE), ArbDoge AI (AIDOGE) Pump 10% On OKX Listing</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/09190843/shibarium-bone.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Bone ShibaSwap (BONE), ArbDoge AI (AIDOGE) Pump 10% On OKX Listing" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p>Crypto exchange OKX on Monday announced the results of the special voting event held by the exchange to decide which meme coins should be listed. As per the voting tallies, the OKX crypto exchange will list ArbDoge AI (AIDOGE) and Bone ShibaSwap (BONE).</p>
<p>Traders immediately reacted to the recent announcement, causing Bone ShibaSwap (BONE) and AIDOGE prices to skyrocket by 10%.</p>
<h2>OKX Listing Bone ShibaSwap (BONE) and ArbDoge AI (AIDOGE)</h2>
<p>Crypto exchange OKX in a <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/okx/status/1649376601971347456" target="_blank" rel="noopener">tweet</a> on April 24 announced that the results of the special voting event for 5 meme token projects are out. ArbDoge AI (AIDOGE) and BONE ShibaSwap (BONE) have received maximum deposit votes. Users voted to list their favorite meme coin from ArbDoge AI (AIDOGE), BONE ShibaSwap (BONE), Bonk (BONK), Optimus AI (OPTI), and Pepe (PEPE).</p>
<p>The spot trading for BONE and AIDOGE will open tomorrow April 25 at 6:00 AM UTC. The crypto community reacted positively to the announcement by OKX. Other projects such as BONK, OPTI, and PEPE received few votes due to new projects and low trading volumes.</p>
<p>Moreover, <span class="css-901oao css-16my406 r-poiln3 r-bcqeeo r-qvutc0">users can withdraw their coins used for deposit voting of </span><span class="r-18u37iz">AIDOGE</span><span class="css-901oao css-16my406 r-poiln3 r-bcqeeo r-qvutc0">, </span><span class="r-18u37iz">BONE</span><span class="css-901oao css-16my406 r-poiln3 r-bcqeeo r-qvutc0">, </span><span class="r-18u37iz">BONK</span><span class="css-901oao css-16my406 r-poiln3 r-bcqeeo r-qvutc0">, </span><span class="r-18u37iz">OPTI</span><span class="css-901oao css-16my406 r-poiln3 r-bcqeeo r-qvutc0">, and </span><span class="r-18u37iz">PEPE</span><span class="css-901oao css-16my406 r-poiln3 r-bcqeeo r-qvutc0"> on April 26 from 10:00 AM UTC onwards.</span></p>
<p><strong>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/binance-adds-bitcoin-shiba-inu-dogecoin-stablecoins-to-liquid-swap" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance Adds Bitcoin, Shiba Inu, Dogecoin, Stablecoins To Liquid Swap</a></strong></p>
<h2>Listed Meme Coins Rally</h2>
<p>The <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/shibarium" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Shibarium&#8217;s</a> gas token BONE rallied over 10% in a few hours, with the BONE price currently trading at $1.10. The 24-hour low and high are $1.008 and $1.115, respectively. Furthermore, the trading volume jumped over 50%, indicating an increase in interest among traders.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, ArbDoge AI (AIDOGE) is trading at $0.000000000312, up nearly 10% in the last 24 hours. The 24-hour low and high are $0.000000000268 and $0.000000000332, respectively. ArbDoge AI is not a project but an experiment in the Arbitrum ecosystem. Thus, investors should be cautious as trading in such crypto assets involves significant risk and may incur partial or full loss of invested capital.</p>
<p><strong>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/rich-dad-poor-dad-author-gold-price-bet-bitcoin-rally-robert-kiyosaki" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Rich Dad Poor Dad Author’s Gold Price Bet; Bitcoin Rally Soon?</a></strong></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/just-in-bone-shibaswap-bone-arbdoge-ai-aidoge-pump-10-on-okx-listing/">Just-In: Bone ShibaSwap (BONE), ArbDoge AI (AIDOGE) Pump 10% On OKX Listing</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/09190843/shibarium-bone.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>3 Best Altcoins to Hold Despite Market FUD Rises</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/markets/3-best-altcoins-to-hold-despite-market-fud-rises/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brian Bollinger]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 12:23:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance coin Price Prediction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polkadot Price Prediction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[solana price prediction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?post_type=markets&#038;p=146090</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From Mid-April, the crypto market witnessed a significant sell-off which initiated a correction phase in the majority of major cryptocurrencies. This retracement was triggered when the Leading cryptocurrency Bitcoin failed to sustain above the $30000 price level. Anyhow, with the overall market trend bullish, interested traders can refer to the following coins as they show <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/markets/3-best-altcoins-to-hold-despite-market-fud-rises/" title="3 Best Altcoins to Hold Despite Market FUD Rises"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/markets/3-best-altcoins-to-hold-despite-market-fud-rises/">3 Best Altcoins to Hold Despite Market FUD Rises</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1600" height="1120" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/09224431/altcoins3.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Cryptocurrency Price Prediction Today" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">From Mid-April, the crypto market witnessed a significant sell-off which initiated a correction phase in the majority of major cryptocurrencies. This retracement was triggered when the Leading cryptocurrency <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> failed to sustain above the $30000 price level. Anyhow, with the overall market trend bullish, interested traders can refer to the following coins as they show a strong chart setup to undermine the bearish momentum in the near future.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Binance coin(BNB)</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><img decoding="async" src="https://s3.tradingview.com/snapshots/0/0jtZjOJU.png" alt="TradingView Chart" />Source- Tradingview </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In the weekly time frame chart, the Binance coin price shows the formation of a <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/symmetrical-triangle-pattern/">symmetrical triangle pattern.</a> Under the influence of this pattern, the asset price resonated between two converging trendlines showcasing a steady sideways trend.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The coin price coiling narrow within the triangle is bound to break either of the given trendlines and trigger a direction rally. As of now, the <a href="https://coingape.com/price/binance-coin/">BNB price</a> trades at $329.8 with an intraday loss of 0.27%. Amid the recent sell-off in the market, the coin price turned down from the overhead resistance trendline is likely to hit the lower one.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Until the lower trendline is intact, the BNB holders are safe from a massive downfall, however, a breakout above the resistance trendline is needed to start a new recovery rally.</span></p>
<blockquote><p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/new-upcoming-binance-listing/">15 New Cryptocurrencies In Upcoming Binance Listing For 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Solana </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">(SOL)</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><img decoding="async" src="https://s3.tradingview.com/snapshots/a/ApKR2Bw3.png" alt="TradingView Chart" />Source- Tradingview </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On April 11th, the<a href="https://coingape.com/price/solana/"> Solana coin price</a> gave a massive breakout from a long-coming resistance trendline. After facing intense selling pressure at this dynamic resistance a breakout above was a sign of trend reversal.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">However, with the increasing <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/fud/">FUD</a> in the market, the Solana price shows a minor pullback and retests the breached trendline as potential support. If the coin price shows sustainability above the trendline, it would mean the market sentiment shifted from selling on rallies to buying in dips.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Thus, the post-retest rally may drive the SOL price to a high of $37.75 mark.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Polkadot (DOT)</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><img decoding="async" src="https://s3.tradingview.com/snapshots/k/kuffXP4J.png" alt="TradingView Chart" />Source- Tradingview </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In the weekly time frame chart, the Polkadot coin shows one of the famous trend reversal patterns called inverted head and shoulder. This pattern consists of a long swing low called the head and two minor swing longs called the shoulders.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Currently, the <a href="https://coingape.com/price/polkadot/">DOT price</a> trades at $5.95 and shapes the right shoulder pattern of the pattern. Despite the rising selling pressure in the market, if the coin price manages to sustain above local support of $5.7, this pattern will encourage the altcoin to breach the overhead neckline resistance at $6.5</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In ideal bullish conditions, a breakout of the resistance trendline may drive the DOT price to a high of $10.8</span></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/markets/3-best-altcoins-to-hold-despite-market-fud-rises/">3 Best Altcoins to Hold Despite Market FUD Rises</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/09224431/altcoins3.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>John Oliver Explores Crypto Collapse In Latest Episode</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/web-stories/john-oliver-explores-crypto-collapse-in-latest-episode/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jai Pratap]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 12:06:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?post_type=web-story&#038;p=146085</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[		<div class="wp-block-web-stories-embed alignnone">
			<a href="https://coingape.com/web-stories/john-oliver-explores-crypto-collapse-in-latest-episode/">
									<img
						src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/24173407/John-Oliver-Takes-On-Crypto-In-Latest-Episode-Of-Last-Week-Tonight.jpg"
						width="360"
						height="600"
						alt="John Oliver Explores Crypto Collapse In Latest Episode"
																			sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"
												loading="lazy"
						decoding="async"
					/>
								</a>
		</div>
		]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[		<div class="wp-block-web-stories-embed alignnone">
			<a href="https://coingape.com/web-stories/john-oliver-explores-crypto-collapse-in-latest-episode/">
									<img
						src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/24173407/John-Oliver-Takes-On-Crypto-In-Latest-Episode-Of-Last-Week-Tonight.jpg"
						width="360"
						height="600"
						alt="John Oliver Explores Crypto Collapse In Latest Episode"
																			sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"
												loading="lazy"
						decoding="async"
					/>
								</a>
		</div>
		]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/24173407/John-Oliver-Takes-On-Crypto-In-Latest-Episode-Of-Last-Week-Tonight.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
