<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 14:31:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>US SEC Reviewing All Recent Spot Bitcoin ETF Applications</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-sec-spot-bitcoin-etf-applications/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-sec-spot-bitcoin-etf-applications/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 14:31:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funds & ETFs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blackrock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[spot bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[spot btc etf]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=263401</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-sec-spot-bitcoin-etf-applications/">US SEC Reviewing All Recent Spot Bitcoin ETF Applications</a></p>
<p>The US SEC has started reviewing all the spot Bitcoin ETF filings re-submitted by all applicants along with a "surveillance sharing" clause.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-sec-spot-bitcoin-etf-applications/">US SEC Reviewing All Recent Spot Bitcoin ETF Applications</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-sec-spot-bitcoin-etf-applications/">US SEC Reviewing All Recent Spot Bitcoin ETF Applications</a></p>
<p>The US Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) has started reviewing all the spot Bitcoin ETF applications that it received over the last month, starting with BlackRock&#8217;s.</p>
<p>The regulator recently released documents for public consultations, but the official review process will begin once the filings are published in the federal register. The SEC is seeking comments on the ETF applications from Cboe, including those from Wise Origin, WisdomTree, VanEck, Invesco Galaxy, and ARK 21Shares. Additionally, the SEC is also seeking comments on BackRock&#8217;s iShares Bitcoin Trust, which was filed on Nasdaq.</p>
<p>BlackRock&#8217;s request to offer a Bitcoin ETF has been officially added to the Securities and Exchange Commission&#8217;s records for review. This is a significant step forward for the highly anticipated Bitcoin-related proposal.</p>
<p>BlackRock&#8217;s application has prompted a new wave of optimism in the crypto market. It also triggered some additional filings for spot Bitcoin ETF from other financial players in the market.</p>
<p>After the SEC expressed concerns about BlackRock&#8217;s initial application, the company submitted a revised version that included a &#8220;surveillance sharing&#8221; clause. This clause would involve monitoring of crypto exchange Coinbase and reporting any potentially illegal activities. Following BlackRock&#8217;s lead, other companies such as Valkyrie, Fidelity, and ARK Invest also updated their applications to include a similar provision.</p>
<h2>Why a Spot Bitcoin ETF Will Be a Game-Changer?</h2>
<p>A spot Bitcoin ETF is a type of investment that tracks the value of Bitcoin without needing to own the actual cryptocurrency. It can be traded on a traditional stock exchange. While there is already a Bitcoin ETF based on Bitcoin futures, a spot ETF linked to the current price of Bitcoin is highly desired in the industry. However, the SEC has been resistant to approving such an ETF in the past, which has been seen as a significant setback.</p>
<p>Now that BlackRock&#8217;s application is on the SEC&#8217;s official calendar, it will be published in the Federal Register. This publication will initiate a 21-day period for the public to provide comments on the application.</p>
<p>In an interview with CNBC last week, BlackRock CEO Larry Fink <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/07/14/blackrock-has-a-responsibility-to-democratize-investing-including-in-crypto-larry-fink-says.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We believe we have a responsibility to democratize investing. We’ve done a great job, and the role of ETFs in the world is transforming investing. And we’re only at the beginning of that. We are working with our regulators because, as in any new market, if BlackRock’s name is going to be on it, we’re going to make sure that it’s safe and sound and protected.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Read other <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/crypto/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">crypto news</a> on Coinspeaker.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/threads-twitter-active-user-base/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-sec-spot-bitcoin-etf-applications/">US SEC Reviewing All Recent Spot Bitcoin ETF Applications</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-sec-spot-bitcoin-etf-applications/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Meta’s Threads Already Has One-Fifth of Twitter’s Weekly Active User Base</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/threads-twitter-active-user-base/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/threads-twitter-active-user-base/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 14:27:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Meta]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[threads]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[twitter]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=263409</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/threads-twitter-active-user-base/">Meta’s Threads Already Has One-Fifth of Twitter’s Weekly Active User Base</a></p>
<p>The number of downloads and general user base Threads has pulled since launch is expanding and has already surpassed that of Twitter rivals.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/threads-twitter-active-user-base/">Meta’s Threads Already Has One-Fifth of Twitter’s Weekly Active User Base</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/threads-twitter-active-user-base/">Meta’s Threads Already Has One-Fifth of Twitter’s Weekly Active User Base</a></p>
<p>Meta’s new microblogging Twitter rival Threads now has 20% of Twitter’s weekly active user base since <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-threads-app-goes-live/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">launching</a> earlier this month. The Threads user base is also 86 times more than that of another Twitter rival, Truth Social.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.data.ai/en/insights/market-data/threads-crosses-150m-downloads/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">According</a> to intelligence platform data.ai, Threads also hit 100 million users within the first few days of its launch. In seven days, Threads downloads grossed over 150 million worldwide, 5.5 times faster than the second-fastest app to do so &#8211; Pokemon GO. According to data.ai, the third fastest app to hit the 150-million milestone is Call of Duty: Mobile, taking 106 days.</p>
<p>The intelligence firm also provided more information about Threads’ user base. Data.ai says that so far, India has the largest market share of Threads downloads at 33%, followed by Brazil at 22%. Others are the United States (16%), Mexico (8%), and Japan (5%).</p>
<h2>Threads User Base Can Expect Changes and New Features</h2>
<p>Meta recently <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2023/07/13/instagram-threads-update-brings-ios-17-support-among-other-small-improvements/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">launched</a> a new update for the Threads iOS app, including bug fixes, added features, and support for the new iOS 17 public beta. However, the new changes are minor features many may not quickly notice. Some of these include expanding profile pictures and double-tapping the search tab to start a search.</p>
<p>Instagram software engineer Cameron Roth has commented on a few changes users can expect. For instance, Roth said Threads would add alt text, a feature that adds descriptive text to photos, and a tag that lets people see whether or not they’re following a particular account. Furthermore, Roth promised a following feed and a desktop version. However, the desktop might come much later.</p>
<p>Instagram head Adam Mosseri also <a href="https://www.threads.net/@mosseri/post/Cujq4SpNhHz" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announced a few</a> changes. In addition to the following feed, Mosseri said the Threads user base can expect an edit button and a post search. He admitted that the team was “clearly way out over our skis on this” and had been more focused on fixing bugs than prioritizing obvious missing features.</p>
<h2>The Threads and Twitter Rivalry</h2>
<p>Meta launched Threads right when Twitter users seemed willing to try alternatives. Users were looking to sidestep Twitter following several changes, including introducing a viewing limit. Owner Elon Musk <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bluesky-record-traffic-twitter/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">announced</a> earlier this month that verified accounts could only access 6,000 posts a day, with unverified users at 600 and new unverified accounts at 300, to prevent data scraping. Musk eventually announced an upward review of the limits.</p>
<p>Following the announcement, Jack Dorsey-backed Twitter rival Bluesky saw record traffic which began to affect its performance as more people signed up. Bluesky eventually suspended sign-ups until the next day.</p>
<p>Twitter has now sent a <a href="https://cdn.sanity.io/files/ifn0l6bs/production/27109f01431939c8177d408d3c9848c3b46632cd.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">letter</a> to Meta accusing the company of “systematic, willful, and unlawful misappropriation of Twitter’s trade secrets and other intellectual property”. According to Musk’s attorney Alex Spiro, Meta intentionally employed former Twitter employees knowing they had access to Twitter’s trade secrets and other confidential information. Interestingly, Meta co-founder Mark Zuckerberg <a href="https://twitter.com/finkd/status/1676747594460962817" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">posted</a> his first tweet in 11 years shading Twitter.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/1inch-price-up-altcoin-recovery/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/threads-twitter-active-user-base/">Meta’s Threads Already Has One-Fifth of Twitter’s Weekly Active User Base</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/threads-twitter-active-user-base/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>1inch Price Up Over 50% in Past Week amid Altcoins’ Recovery and Heightened Trading Volume</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/1inch-price-up-altcoin-recovery/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/1inch-price-up-altcoin-recovery/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 14:10:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[1inch]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=263402</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/1inch-price-up-altcoin-recovery/">1inch Price Up Over 50% in Past Week amid Altcoins’ Recovery and Heightened Trading Volume</a></p>
<p>The activities in the 1INCH protocol are expected to remain high, particularly due to increased altcoin FOMO.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/1inch-price-up-altcoin-recovery/">1inch Price Up Over 50% in Past Week amid Altcoins’ Recovery and Heightened Trading Volume</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/1inch-price-up-altcoin-recovery/">1inch Price Up Over 50% in Past Week amid Altcoins’ Recovery and Heightened Trading Volume</a></p>
<p>The 1inch (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/1inch/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">1INCH</a>) market has recorded a sudden spike in daily traded volume amid the recent altcoin rally triggered by the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/xrp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">XRP</a> case. Notably, the multi-chain decentralized exchange (DEX) price aggregator, 1inch protocol has seen its daily traded volume up by a factor of more than 212 percent in the past 24 hours to about $645 million. Consequently, its market valuation gained about 7 percent to about $434 million on Monday and its price traded at around 46 cents. According to the latest crypto market data, the 1INCH token price was up more than 51 percent in the past five days despite the recent altcoin pullback.</p>
<h2>Closer Look at 1INCH Market Outlook</h2>
<p>The 1INCH market is heavily <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/07/17/1inch-token-surges-58-as-daily-trading-volume-spikes-to-20-month-high-investor-moves-37m-to-binance/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">bolstered</a> by the positive fundamentals and the speculative aspect of the cryptocurrency industry. Combining both aspects makes 1INCH extremely bullish in the long term. Moreover, the 1INCH protocol helps crypto users swap assets between different chains with the best prices securely. Additionally, the 1INCH protocol provides users with a safe crypto wallet that ultimately helps them swap through the best routes with enhanced liquidity.</p>
<p>According to the protocol’s official website, 1INCH protocol has about 383 liquidity sources, having facilitated more than $286 billion in traded volume from more than 4.5 million total wallets. Through fetching different price oracles from various decentralized exchanges, 1INCH protocol then analyzes the data in a bid to provide its customers with the best and most reliable routes with the smallest fees to swap the assets.</p>
<p>The recent meteoric rise in the 1INCH network is evidently visible through the increased open interest, up more than 138 percent in the past 24 hours to about $143 million. With increased volatility, trading volume, and open interest, 1INCH liquidations are expected to remain high in the coming days.</p>
<p>Furthermore, more than $4.2 million was liquidated in the 1INCH market in the last 24 hours, according to the latest market data provided by Coinglass. Amid the heightened on-chain activity, 1INCH whales were spotted depositing on centralized exchanges including Binance, perhaps to take some profits after a considerable rally.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="474" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Note that a <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/1INCH?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#1INCH</a> investor deposited 7M <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/1INCH?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#1INCH</a> ($3.88M) into <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Binance?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Binance</a> just now after the price of <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/1INCH?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#1INCH</a> rose.<a href="https://t.co/evi8W1swDw">https://t.co/evi8W1swDw</a> <a href="https://t.co/WzlhogyO2q">pic.twitter.com/WzlhogyO2q</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Lookonchain (@lookonchain) <a href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1680867399090962439?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 17, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The activities in the 1INCH protocol are expected to remain high, particularly due to increased altcoin FOMO. Moreover, the recent SEC vs Ripple summary judgment ruling largely vindicated not only XRP but also the entire altcoin industry. Furthermore, the SEC is now faced with the task of identifying which crypto transactions are investment contracts in a bid to classify them as securities.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the 1INCH community will have a chance to hear directly from the team leaders who will participate in the ETH Global Paris hackathon on July 21-23.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gnosis-product-offerings-crypto-spending/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/1inch-price-up-altcoin-recovery/">1inch Price Up Over 50% in Past Week amid Altcoins’ Recovery and Heightened Trading Volume</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/1inch-price-up-altcoin-recovery/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gnosis Launches New Product Offerings to Aid Self-Custodial Crypto Spending</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/gnosis-product-offerings-crypto-spending/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/gnosis-product-offerings-crypto-spending/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 12:54:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto payments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gnosis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gnosis card]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gnosis pay]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[visa]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=263365</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gnosis-product-offerings-crypto-spending/">Gnosis Launches New Product Offerings to Aid Self-Custodial Crypto Spending</a></p>
<p>Gnosis is keen on showcasing to the entire world how Web 3.0 can be used to bridge the gap between self-custodial crypto wallets and traditional payment methods.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gnosis-product-offerings-crypto-spending/">Gnosis Launches New Product Offerings to Aid Self-Custodial Crypto Spending</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gnosis-product-offerings-crypto-spending/">Gnosis Launches New Product Offerings to Aid Self-Custodial Crypto Spending</a></p>
<p>Gnosis, a popular blockchain project among developers, is set to release a pair of new product offerings. The sidechain to Ethereum revealed on Monday that it would be launching what it calls the &#8216;Gnosis Pay&#8217; and &#8216;Gnosis Card&#8217;.</p>
<p>According to the announcement, the Gnosis Card will be a debit card that will be directly connected to a user’s on-chain account. The card, according to the project, uses the Visa payment system, and will initially launch in the UK and the EU. However, there are plans to also extend the offering to other regions including Brazil, Mexico, Singapore, and Hong Kong.</p>
<p>Gnosis Pay, on the other hand, will operate as a layer 2 to the Gnosis chain itself. That is, the new decentralized payment network will usher in an era of faster and cheaper transactions than what was previously obtainable.</p>
<p>Speaking about Gnosis Pay, Stefan George, who is the chief technology officer (CTO) <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/07/17/gnosis-lets-crypto-users-make-everyday-purchases-from-wallets-with-visa/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">says</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“From a user experience point of view, it&#8217;s exactly the same experiences everyone&#8217;s used to but under the hood of using crypto to settle your payments.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Gnosis Pay will be launching at the major Ethereum community conference EthCC in Paris. However, according to Gnosis’s co-founder Dr. Friederike Ernst, the ultimate aim is to take the system even beyond the crypto community.</p>
<h2>Gnosis Seeks to Ease the Burden of Spending in Crypto</h2>
<p>For long, the crypto industry has often been condemned as being exclusive to only crypto enthusiasts and advocates.  This is although its underlying technology has been tipped to have the potential of benefitting the broader society.</p>
<p>To this end, Gnosis is keen on showcasing to the entire world how Web 3.0 can be used to bridge the gap between self-custodial crypto wallets and traditional payment methods such as Visa.</p>
<p>It might be noteworthy that there has been an unprecedented rise in the number of users using self-custodial wallets such as MetaMask and Ledger. That is especially since <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-exchange-files-for-bankruptcy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">the implosion of FTX</a> last November.</p>
<p>But despite this increasing popularity, real-world spending of assets in self-custody continues to pose a major challenge. In line with this challenge, Ernst also said partly:</p>
<blockquote><p>“We’re trying to erase this bit by bit so people can use their real-world money in crypto and use their crypto to pay for things in the real world.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Read other <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/crypto/blockchain-news/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">blockchain news</a> on Coinspeaker.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/zksync-era-proof-boojum/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gnosis-product-offerings-crypto-spending/">Gnosis Launches New Product Offerings to Aid Self-Custodial Crypto Spending</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/gnosis-product-offerings-crypto-spending/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>zkSync Era Announces New Proof System Boojum</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/zksync-era-proof-boojum/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/zksync-era-proof-boojum/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 12:48:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[boojum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stark]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[zksync]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[zksync era]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=263379</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/zksync-era-proof-boojum/">zkSync Era Announces New Proof System Boojum</a></p>
<p>In an official announcement, zkSync highlighted the properties attributed to Boojum, which includes PLONK-style arithmetization.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/zksync-era-proof-boojum/">zkSync Era Announces New Proof System Boojum</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/zksync-era-proof-boojum/">zkSync Era Announces New Proof System Boojum</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a> layer-2 zkSync Era has released a new high-performance proof system called Boojum for radical decentralization. zkSync took to Twitter to announce the proof system on the 17th of July, noting that it is an upgrade that will cause zkSync to change to a proof system backed by STARK. In addition, the newly-launched system will offer upgraded performance as it runs on consumer-grade hardware.</p>
<h2>zkSync Era Unveils Boojum Upgrade</h2>
<p>zkSync is committed to building a secure, permissionless, and affordable blockchain network that will advance personal freedom universally. The Alpha version of zkSync Era went live in March with a SNARK-based system, and the network has had significant activity. The total value locked is $577 million in addition to 23,750,000 transactions over the past 30 days. Also, 9,735 source-code-verified smart contracts are on record. The Boojum upgrade will not cause disruptions as zkSync is designed to allow cryptographic upgrades without regenesis. In other words, users and developers are assured of no disturbance as the network deploys cryptographic upgrades. After working backstage on a cryptographic upgrade, zkSync is now transitioning to Boojum.</p>
<p>“Boojum is the name of our Rust-based cryptographic library, which we use to implement the upgraded version of the ZK circuits for zkSync Era and the ZK Stack. The name Boojum was inspired by Lewis Carroll&#8217;s poem &#8220;The Hunting of the Snark&#8221;, where the Boojum represents the most fearsome kind of Snark.”</p>
<p>In an <a href="https://zksync.mirror.xyz/HJ2Pj45EJkRdt5Pau-ZXwkV2ctPx8qFL19STM5jdYhc" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">official announcement</a>, zkSync highlighted the properties attributed to Boojum, which includes PLONK-style arithmetization. This is the process that converts general computation into mathematical forms. As such, the ZK circuits “are simpler to write relative to some alternative formalisms, making the system easier to develop, audit, maintain, and upgrade”.</p>
<h2>More on the Upgrade</h2>
<p>Speaking further about Boojum, zkSync also referred to the FRI commitment scheme, which is a major component that contributes to the network’s efficiency. In addition, the ‘efficiency of “boring” parts of the system’. According to zkSync, it offers parallelized witness generation with Boojum. There is also an efficient development process if users change the circuit structure and pick different types of gates. Users can include their custom gate types in various fashions.</p>
<p>Basically, Boojum leveraged foundation papers on STARK, FRI, and DEEP-FRI to provide its two major selling points. They are world-class performance and the ability to reduce hardware requirements for decentralization.</p>
<p>The zkSync team has been developing Boojum for months, beginning with the designing stage. After then, the team moved to the testing stage, after which it shifted to Prime Time. zkSync assured that it will further audit and ensure the network&#8217;s security ahead of the full deployment of Boojum.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-bitcoin-miners-halving/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/zksync-era-proof-boojum/">zkSync Era Announces New Proof System Boojum</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/zksync-era-proof-boojum/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>JPMorgan Shows Hurdles Ahead for Bitcoin Miners as Halving Is Getting Closer</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-bitcoin-miners-halving/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-bitcoin-miners-halving/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 12:36:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin halving]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin miners]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jpmorgan]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=263362</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-bitcoin-miners-halving/">JPMorgan Shows Hurdles Ahead for Bitcoin Miners as Halving Is Getting Closer</a></p>
<p>The report highlights that the rapid growth in the Bitcoin hashrate is unlikely to continue at the same pace after the halving event.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-bitcoin-miners-halving/">JPMorgan Shows Hurdles Ahead for Bitcoin Miners as Halving Is Getting Closer</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-bitcoin-miners-halving/">JPMorgan Shows Hurdles Ahead for Bitcoin Miners as Halving Is Getting Closer</a></p>
<p>As the next <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> (BTC) halving event approaches, analysts at American investment banking giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/jpmorgan-chase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">JPMorgan Chase &amp; Co</a> (NYSE: JPM), led by Nikolaos Panigirtzoglou, recently highlighted its challenges for miners.</p>
<p>In a recent <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/07/17/next-bitcoin-halving-event-could-be-a-stress-test-for-miners-jpmorgan/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a>, the analysts noted that the hashrate for Bitcoin has recently reached new all-time highs. This surge in hashrate signifies the escalating competition among miners as they gear up for the next halving event <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-halving-2024-1-year-away/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">expected</a> in the second quarter of 2024.</p>
<h2>Challenges for Bitcoin Miners</h2>
<p>The report points out that the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/bitcoin-halving-2024-what-you-need-to-know/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">event</a> will decrease the block reward from 6.25 BTC to 3.125 BTC. This reduction will directly impact miners’ revenues, as they will earn fewer Bitcoin for their mining efforts. Consequently, miners will face a decline in their income, which raises concerns about the profitability and sustainability of mining operations.</p>
<p>Additionally, the report highlights that the reduction in issuance rewards effectively increases Bitcoin&#8217;s production cost. This is because, miners must cover their operational expenses, such as equipment, electricity, and maintenance, with a smaller number of Bitcoin.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the analysts emphasized that miners with lower electricity costs are expected to have an easier time sustaining their operations, while those with higher power costs may face challenges after the halving event is over.</p>
<p>Specifically, JPMorgan estimates that a 1% per kilowatt hour (kWh) change in electricity cost can lead to a $4,300 change in the production cost of Bitcoin. After the halving, this sensitivity is expected to double to $8,600, thus increasing the vulnerability of higher-cost miners.</p>
<p>The bank also highlights the rising competition among Bitcoin miners, reflected in the steep rise in the hashrate. The hashrate represents the total computational power dedicated to mining Bitcoin, and its increase indicates intensified competition within the mining industry.</p>
<p>As miners anticipate the halving event, more mining rigs are being deployed to capture a larger share of the diminishing block rewards. This influx of computational power contributes to the overall hashrate growth.</p>
<h2>Hashrate Post-halving Event</h2>
<p>The report highlights that the rapid growth in the Bitcoin hashrate is unlikely to continue at the same pace after the halving event. The analysts emphasized that without a sustained rise in the Bitcoin price above its production cost or a significant increase in transaction fees, the growth in the hashrate may be offset by the reduction in issuance rewards.</p>
<p>The potential slowdown in hashrate growth post-halving has implications for the mining ecosystem. If the Bitcoin price does not rise sufficiently or transaction fees do not increase significantly, miners may face profitability challenges. This scenario could lead to some miners exiting the market, particularly those with higher production costs or less efficient operations as we saw with <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/core-scientific-bankruptcy-mining/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">series of bankruptcies</a> last year</p>
<p>It is worth noting that the relationship between hashrate, Bitcoin price, and transaction fees is dynamic and susceptible to change. A persistent rise in the Bitcoin price or a considerable increase in transaction fees may encourage miners to continue investing in processing power, hence promoting hashrate growth.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/elon-musk-twitter-negative-cash-flow/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-bitcoin-miners-halving/">JPMorgan Shows Hurdles Ahead for Bitcoin Miners as Halving Is Getting Closer</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-bitcoin-miners-halving/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Elon Musk Confirms Twitter’s Negative Cash Flow amidst 50% Plunge in Ad Revenue</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/elon-musk-twitter-negative-cash-flow/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/elon-musk-twitter-negative-cash-flow/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 12:31:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[spacex]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tesla]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[twitter]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=263360</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/elon-musk-twitter-negative-cash-flow/">Elon Musk Confirms Twitter&#8217;s Negative Cash Flow amidst 50% Plunge in Ad Revenue</a></p>
<p>Insufficient earnings on Twitter suggest that the platform's advertising revenue may not have rebounded as quickly as previously anticipated.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/elon-musk-twitter-negative-cash-flow/">Elon Musk Confirms Twitter&#8217;s Negative Cash Flow amidst 50% Plunge in Ad Revenue</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/elon-musk-twitter-negative-cash-flow/">Elon Musk Confirms Twitter&#8217;s Negative Cash Flow amidst 50% Plunge in Ad Revenue</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/elon-musk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Elon Musk</a>, the CEO of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/tesla/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tesla</a> and SpaceX, who also holds the position of CTO at Twitter, recently revealed the social media platform&#8217;s ongoing negative cash flow and the weight of its debt burden. Musk cited a 50% drop in advertising revenue and a significant debt burden as the reasons behind Twitter&#8217;s ongoing cash flow challenges.</p>
<p>Responding to a tweet about potential recapitalization options, the billionaire entrepreneur emphasized the need for Twitter to achieve positive cash flow before pursuing other endeavors. He further revealed that the popular social media platform he acquired for $44 billion did not witness the expected increase in advertising revenue in June but expressed some optimism for July.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="474" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">We’re still negative cash flow, due to ~50% drop in advertising revenue plus heavy debt load. Need to reach positive cash flow before we have the luxury of anything else.</p>
<p>&mdash; Elon Musk (@elonmusk) <a href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1680082007873953794?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 15, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Musk also said that July showed more promise in advertising revenue while acknowledging that Twitter Spaces and the audio chat feature are currently generating costs without bringing revenue to the company.</p>
<p>The new development highlights the ongoing struggle to achieve positive cash flow at <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/twitter/">Twitter</a>, despite aggressive cost-cutting measures implemented since Musk&#8217;s acquisition of the company in October.</p>
<h2>Twitter Faces Annual Interest Payments of $1.5 Billion</h2>
<p>Since taking over Twitter, the Tesla CEO has implemented significant changes, including staff reductions and adjustments to content moderation policies. The billionaire wasted no time implementing a substantial <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-employees-new-round-layoffs/">workforce reduction</a>, cutting 75% of Twitter&#8217;s global employees following the deal&#8217;s completion.</p>
<p>The move aimed to streamline operations and reduce costs. In addition to the workforce reduction, Musk revealed that Twitter has successfully slashed its projected non-debt expenditures from $4.5 billion to $1.5 billion for 2023. Moreover, the acquisition deal came with a substantial debt burden for Twitter. Due to the debt, the platform now faces annual interest payments of approximately $1.5 billion, adding further strain to its financial situation.</p>
<p>A New York Times <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2022/11/22/technology/elon-musk-twitter-cost-cutting.html">report</a> also disclosed that Musk failed to settle hundreds of thousands of dollars in outstanding bills owed to travel vendors. The company&#8217;s executives accumulated these expenses before the official acquisition in 2022.</p>
<p>Despite the cost-cutting measures and workforce restructuring, Twitter continues to grapple with negative cash flow. The social media platform has faced challenges with advertisers reducing or halting their ad spending due to concerns relating to content moderation and uncertainty about Twitter&#8217;s future.</p>
<h2>Elon Musk Anticipates Twitter to Become Cash Flow Positive</h2>
<p>Insufficient earnings on Twitter suggest that the platform&#8217;s advertising revenue may not have rebounded as quickly as previously anticipated. In an interview with the BBC in April, Musk indicated that most advertisers had returned to the platform, and he expected Twitter to become cash flow positive within the second quarter.</p>
<p>To address the issues of poor advertising revenue and other financial challenges at Twitter, Musk appointed <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/linda-yaccarino/">Linda Yaccarino,</a> a former NBCUniversal marketing executive, as Twitter&#8217;s new CEO. Yaccarino&#8217;s background in advertising is expected to prioritize the revitalization of Twitter&#8217;s ad business.</p>
<p>As such, the new CEO has outlined plans to focus on video, creator, and commerce partnerships and has engaged in early discussions with various entities, including political and entertainment figures, payments services, and news and media publishers.</p>
<p>Last week, Twitter announced a revenue-sharing program for selected content creators. However, some users expressed disappointment at the program&#8217;s limited scope, which is currently only available to Twitter Blue verified subscribers who meet certain criteria.</p>
<p>The program distributes a portion of the ad revenue generated from ads placed in replies to tweets. Several influencers and creators, including controversial figures like Andrew Tate, have revealed that they received payments through this program.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/treasury-yields-decline-us-global-economy/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/elon-musk-twitter-negative-cash-flow/">Elon Musk Confirms Twitter&#8217;s Negative Cash Flow amidst 50% Plunge in Ad Revenue</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/elon-musk-twitter-negative-cash-flow/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Treasury Yields Decline as Investors Remain Cautious about US and Global Economy</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/treasury-yields-decline-us-global-economy/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/treasury-yields-decline-us-global-economy/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 12:16:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[treasury]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[treasury yield]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=263350</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/treasury-yields-decline-us-global-economy/">Treasury Yields Decline as Investors Remain Cautious about US and Global Economy</a></p>
<p>Treasury Yields are falling further due to general uncertainty in the market regarding interest rates and monetary policies.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/treasury-yields-decline-us-global-economy/">Treasury Yields Decline as Investors Remain Cautious about US and Global Economy</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/treasury-yields-decline-us-global-economy/">Treasury Yields Decline as Investors Remain Cautious about US and Global Economy</a></p>
<p>Treasury yields in the US have fallen on Monday following cautious sentiments from investors about the state of the economy. The decline in US Treasury Yields suggests investors are worried about monetary policy as they anticipate official economic data.</p>
<p>The 10-year Treasury Yield, as of 5:40 am ET was at 3.787%, lower by 3 basis points. As of press time, the yield has fallen further to 3.775. A similar plunge was recorded in the 2-year Treasury, which was lower by 2 basis points at 4.725%</p>
<p>Last week, official data showed that the consumer price index rose by 0.2% compared to the month before, and was the lowest rise since March 2021. Figures from the consumer price index and other key economic data would likely sway the Fed’s decision on monetary policy in one way or the other.</p>
<p>Rising prices and inflation have caused the Fed to consistently increase interest rates. Over the last 11 meetings, the Fed has increased the interest rate 10 times. Now, projections have it that the <a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/amp/story/treasury-yields-fall-further-after-cooling-inflation-data-639e2360?mod=rates-market-data" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">probability</a> the Fed will increase interest rates again is 92.4%. The market projection puts the rate at 5.25%-5.5%, with the Fed likely increasing the rate on July 26.</p>
<h2>China’s Influence</h2>
<p>Several global factors may also be preventing the Treasury Yields from rising. The state of the global economy is in question for many reasons, including data from China. Although the Chinese economy climbed 6.3% year-over-year (YoY) in Q2, the climb was lower than the expected 7.1%. <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/jpmorgan-chase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">JPMorgan</a> also reduced its growth expectation for China to 5% from 5.5%, after cutting the country’s growth from 5.9% earlier. According to JPMorgan economists, instability in the housing market is a serious factor. They said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Since 2Q, housing market weakness has intensified in both demand (related to weak income expectations and weak house price expectations) and supply (weak incentive for private developers to buy new land and start new projects) sides. This points at a major challenge for policymakers of how to balance the long-term goal of economic transformation and near-term objective of growth stabilization.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Last month, several other Wall Street banks <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/goldman-sachs-growth-outlook-china/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">cut their outlook</a> on growth in China. Goldman Sachs, Bank of America, Standard Chartered, UBS, and Nomura, all posted reduced forecasts for the country’s growth.</p>
<h2>Treasury Yields Have Been Fluctuating</h2>
<p>As most of the world battles inflation and dwindling economies, the US has been no different as Treasury Yields have been wavering. Last month, CoinSpeaker <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/treasury-yields-interest-rate-hike/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a> that the 2-year Treasury Yield lost 4 basis points to 4.656%, lower than it now is. The same report also put the 10-year Treasury yield at 3.808%.</p>
<p>In the previous month, negotiations regarding the US debt ceiling significantly <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-treasury-yields-congress-debt-ceiling/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">affected</a> the 10-year and 2-year Treasury yields. At one time, the 10-year yield fell by 10 basis points to 3.719%, while the 2-year yield lost 7 basis points and hit 4.514%</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fsb-regulatory-framework-crypto/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/treasury-yields-decline-us-global-economy/">Treasury Yields Decline as Investors Remain Cautious about US and Global Economy</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/treasury-yields-decline-us-global-economy/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>FSB Finalizes Global Regulatory Framework for Crypto</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fsb-regulatory-framework-crypto/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fsb-regulatory-framework-crypto/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Darya Rudz]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 11:33:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Editor's Choice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[financial stability board]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fsb crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fsb crypto framework]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fsb crypto regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[luna]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[terra]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=263301</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fsb-regulatory-framework-crypto/">FSB Finalizes Global Regulatory Framework for Crypto</a></p>
<p>The aim of FSB was to provide a regulatory framework that would comply with the principle of "same activity, same risk, same regulation" and cover all possible risks related to crypto activity.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fsb-regulatory-framework-crypto/">FSB Finalizes Global Regulatory Framework for Crypto</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fsb-regulatory-framework-crypto/">FSB Finalizes Global Regulatory Framework for Crypto</a></p>
<p>The Financial Stability Board (FSB), an international body that oversees and advises on the global financial system, has come up with the final version of the global regulatory framework for crypto-asset activities. Basically, the <a href="https://www.fsb.org/wp-content/uploads/P170723-1.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">document</a> released by FSB consists of recommendations for companies involved in crypto activity, and these recommendations are divided into two parts:</p>
<ul>
<li>high-level recommendations for the regulation, supervision and oversight of crypto-asset activities and markets;</li>
<li>revised high-level recommendations for the regulation, supervision, and oversight of “global stablecoin” arrangements.</li>
</ul>
<p>The aim of FSB was to provide a regulatory framework that would comply with the principle of &#8220;same activity, same risk, same regulation&#8221; and cover all possible risks related to crypto activity. According to FSB, crypto-asset activities must be regulated based on their economic functions and the risks they pose.</p>
<p>In addition to recommendations, FSB has collaborated with sectoral standard-setting bodies (SSBs) and come up with a work plan to mitigate various risks that cryptos might pose. Those include AML/CFT, data privacy, cyber security, consumer and investor protection, market integrity, competition policy, and more.</p>
<p>FSB commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Final recommendations incorporate learnings from events of the past year in crypto-asset markets and feedback received during the FSB’s public consultation.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<div title="Page 10">
<div>
<div>
<p>Next, in September, the FSB and the IMF will deliver a joint report to the G20 that will synthesise the policy findings from work of the Funf on macroeconomic and monetary issues. Further, by the end of 2025, the FSB will review the status of the implementation of the recommendations at the jurisdictional level. In partnership with the IMF and the World Bank, the FSB will oversee applying the proposed standards in daily practice.</p>
<p>Aspects, where the work has already started, include multifunction crypto-asset intermediaries, banks’ stablecoin exposures and related activities, and tokenization.</p>
<h2>Need for Proper Risk Management</h2>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<p>How did FSB develop the crypto regulatory framework? At the beginning of 2022, the crypto market was turmoiled by a chain of events that led to a sharp decrease in crypto assets. The collapse of Terra (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/terra/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">LUNA</a>), the third largest cryptocurrency ecosystem after Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a>) and Ethereum (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ETH</a>) at that time, the bankruptcy of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ieo/platform/ftx/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX exchange</a>, the crash of the crypto hedge fund Three Arrows Capital (3AC), the banking crisis, and the global economic decline showed the need to predict and protect against the risks caused by high volatility of crypto-asset markets.</p>
<p>However, the approach to regulating crypto markets is different in the US, Europe, and Asia. Different jurisdictions have different views on what should be done with digital assets. In the case of the FSB, the framework provided calls for stricter regulation, but it does not cover all aspects of crypto-related activity. It does not include stablecoins and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-central-bank-digital-currency-cbdc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Central Bank Digital Currencies</a> (CBDCs), which are also important and popular tools offered by the industry.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nab-payments-crypto-exchanges/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fsb-regulatory-framework-crypto/">FSB Finalizes Global Regulatory Framework for Crypto</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fsb-regulatory-framework-crypto/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>NAB Blocks Payments to High-Risk Crypto Exchanges to Curb Scam Losses</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nab-payments-crypto-exchanges/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nab-payments-crypto-exchanges/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Babafemi Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 11:30:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cftc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nab]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=263043</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nab-payments-crypto-exchanges/">NAB Blocks Payments to High-Risk Crypto Exchanges to Curb Scam Losses</a></p>
<p>According to NAB executive for group investigations and fraud Chris Sheehan, they have observed many scammers using cryptocurrency platforms to launder stolen funds.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nab-payments-crypto-exchanges/">NAB Blocks Payments to High-Risk Crypto Exchanges to Curb Scam Losses</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nab-payments-crypto-exchanges/">NAB Blocks Payments to High-Risk Crypto Exchanges to Curb Scam Losses</a></p>

<p>National Australia Bank (NAB) will begin blocking payments to high-risk crypto exchanges in an effort to curb scam losses. NAB <a href="https://news.nab.com.au/news/scam-strategy-update/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announced</a> the ban on Monday. It noted that it was taking action to protect its customers from the risks associated with cryptocurrency.</p>
<h2>NAB’s Move Is Part of a Wider Trend</h2>
<p>According to the NAB, it has stopped over $270 million worth of customer payments between March and July using payment prompts. Insights from the NAB app show 12% of payments were abandoned when customers received a real-time payment prompt in the app.</p>
<p>Again, recent data from the Australian Financial Crimes Exchange showed that 50% of reported scam funds had cryptocurrency linkage. With over $1.5 billion lost to investment scams by Australians in 2022 and about $221 million of that to crypto scams the threat posed by scam losses is great.</p>
<p>Earlier this year, Westpac and the Commonwealth Bank reportedly halted payments to Binance. ANZ also noted that it would start preventing payment to particular high-risk crypto trading platforms. Thus, the move to block payment to crypto exchanges is the latest in a series of measures by Australian banks to restrict cryptocurrency transactions.</p>
<h2>Ban to Affect High-Risk Crypto Exchanges</h2>
<p>While the ban is expected to affect Binance, NAB did not identify any specific cryptocurrency exchanges, noting its approach will be “consistent with the industry”. However, the bank stated that it will affect “high-risk” platforms with more scam events.</p>
<p>According to NAB executive for group investigations and fraud Chris Sheehan, they have observed many scammers using cryptocurrency platforms to quickly launder stolen funds. “We want to make it as hard as possible for these criminals and reduce the impact on our customers,” he said.</p>
<h2>Multiplied Woes</h2>
<p>Meanwhile, a ban that affects Binance’s operations will only increase its woes in Australia. The Australian Securities and Investment Commission canceled its local derivatives license in April. Later in May, Binance lost its local banking partner Cuscal. The Australian regulator has also <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-australia-offices-raided/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reportedly</a> begun a probe into Binance&#8217;s operations in the country.</p>
<p>And it isn’t just Australia. Binance has come under fire in many of its operational jurisdictions in recent times. In the US, The Commodity Futures Trading Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/cftc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CFTC</a>) and the SEC have accused Binance of operating without proper license and improper handling of customer funds. In the Netherlands, the exchange was forced to withdraw after failing to secure a license. The company is also facing accusations of illegal operations in France.</p>
<p>Despite the regulatory assaults, Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao has reiterated the company’s commitment to regulation. He <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/blog/from-cz/binance-turns-6-8188278446020229815" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a> that they &#8220;are not just open but eager to collaborate with policymakers to shape the future of digital assets&#8221;.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-internal-email-layoff/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nab-payments-crypto-exchanges/">NAB Blocks Payments to High-Risk Crypto Exchanges to Curb Scam Losses</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nab-payments-crypto-exchanges/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4204 metric#misses=47 metric#hit-ratio=98.9 metric#bytes=1125220 metric#prefetches=210 metric#store-reads=25 metric#store-writes=4 metric#store-hits=217 metric#store-misses=8 metric#sql-queries=36 metric#ms-total=135.59 metric#ms-cache=6.16 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.2199 metric#ms-cache-ratio=4.5 -->