<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 23:11:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Investors eye Litecoin and Avalanche as Bitcoin leads outflows</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/investors-eye-litecoin-and-avalanche-as-bitcoin-leads-outflows/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/investors-eye-litecoin-and-avalanche-as-bitcoin-leads-outflows/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 23:11:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Avalanche News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/investors-eye-litecoin-and-avalanche-as-bitcoin-leads-outflows/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Litecoin, Avalanche see inflows even as crypto outflows hit 5th consecutive week Bitcoin represented most of the negative sentiment with $33 million worth of outflows. Germany lead in terms of regions with 73% of the total outflows. Litecoin and Avalanche recorded some investment products inflows last week, defying sentiment across the broader crypto investment products [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/investors-eye-litecoin-and-avalanche-as-bitcoin-leads-outflows/">Investors eye Litecoin and Avalanche as Bitcoin leads outflows</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Litecoin, Avalanche see inflows even as crypto outflows hit 5th consecutive week</li>
<li dir="ltr">Bitcoin represented most of the negative sentiment with $33 million worth of outflows.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Germany lead in terms of regions with 73% of the total outflows.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/litecoin/">Litecoin</a> and <a href="https://coinjournal.net/avalanche/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Avalanche</a> recorded some investment products inflows last week, defying sentiment across the broader crypto investment products market.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Indeed, the inflows into exchange traded funds and other products for LTC and AVAX mirrored a broader outlook for altcoins &ndash; except for Ethereum which recorded $1 million in outflows. <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/avalanche/">Avalanche</a> and Litecoin saw $0.7 million and $0.3 million respectively.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Elsewhere, Blockchain equity ETFs accounted for minor outflows of $2 million to see the second consecutive week of negativity.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitcoin sees $33 million in outflows</h2>
<p dir="ltr">According to <a href="https://blog.coinshares.com/volume-132-digital-asset-fund-flows-weekly-report-6877d104bbeb" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">data</a> from digital assets manager CoinShares, digital asset investment products saw outflows totaling $32 million for the week ending May 19. This represented the fifth consecutive week of outflows, with the total outflows over the past five weeks rising to $232 million, or 0.7% of total assets under management.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Volumes for the week were also down, totaling $900 million, or roughly 40% below 2023 average. Data shows volumes for the broader market across the leading trusted exchanges fell to their lowest level of $20 billion last week. It is the worst week in terms of volume since late-2020. As CoinJournal reported <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-and-ethereum-volumes-dry-up-amid-price-struggles/">here</a>, crypto volumes have dried up in recent months as prices struggled with sell-off fears.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The outflows in <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> of $33 million represented most of the negative sentiment, CoinShares data showed. This has been the trend over the last five weeks and was also replicated across short-bitcoin products.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Per CoinShares, short bitcoin products saw minor outflows of $1.3 million for the week. The total outflows for short BTC investment products now total $235 million for the last five weeks.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Germany dominated last week&rsquo;s outflows</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Regionally, Germany dominated the outflows, totaling $24 million, accounting for 73% of total weekly outflows. The US and Switzerland followed with $5 million and $3.3 million respectively. Meanwhile, Brazil and Canada saw minor inflows of $1.3 million and $2.2 million.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/investors-eye-litecoin-and-avalanche-as-bitcoin-leads-outflows/">Investors eye Litecoin and Avalanche as Bitcoin leads outflows</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/investors-eye-litecoin-and-avalanche-as-bitcoin-leads-outflows/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin and Ethereum volumes dry up amid price struggles</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-and-ethereum-volumes-dry-up-amid-price-struggles/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-and-ethereum-volumes-dry-up-amid-price-struggles/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 21:55:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Volatility]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-and-ethereum-volumes-dry-up-amid-price-struggles/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Amid price struggles, on-chain metrics show Bitcoin and Ethereum volumes have dried up. BTC volume has fallen from over $40 billion worth of trade to just above $11.4 billion while ETH volume declined from near $20 billion to about $4.6 billion. Bitcoin price is hovering near $26,800 while Ethereum price is currently just above $1,820. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-and-ethereum-volumes-dry-up-amid-price-struggles/">Bitcoin and Ethereum volumes dry up amid price struggles</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Amid price struggles, on-chain metrics show Bitcoin and Ethereum volumes have dried up.</li>
<li dir="ltr">BTC volume has fallen from over $40 billion worth of trade to just above $11.4 billion while ETH volume declined from near $20 billion to about $4.6 billion.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Bitcoin price is hovering near $26,800 while Ethereum price is currently just above $1,820.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">The cryptocurrency market continues to battle the negative flip seen in recent months. It&rsquo;s a scenario that has seen <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> and <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/">Ethereum</a> prices unable to reclaim key technical areas following a dearth of momentum in the past few weeks.</p>
<p dir="ltr">New on-chain data confirms these price action struggles via the trading volume for both coins. Altcoin volume has also really &ldquo;dried up,&rdquo; the data shows.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">BTC and ETH volume dry up as prices struggle</h2>
<p dir="ltr">According to on-chain data from Santiment the combined trading volumes of BTC and <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/eth/">ETH</a> are currently at their lowest level in over a year. The on-chain analytics platform also notes that the crypto mega caps are seeing the second lowest volume count in nearly four years.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>The largest assets in #crypto are seeing historically low levels of weekly trading volume. #Altcoin volume, in particular, has really dried up. When combining just $BTC &amp; $ETH volume, this is the 2nd lowest threshold we are seeing since September, 2019,&rdquo;&nbsp;</em>the platform noted.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">&#128201; The largest assets in <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/crypto?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#crypto</a> are seeing historically low levels of weekly trading volume. <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Altcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Altcoin</a> volume, in particular, has really dried up. When combining just <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24BTC&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$BTC</a> &amp; <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24ETH&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$ETH</a> volume, this is the 2nd lowest threshold we are seeing since September, 2019. <a href="https://t.co/1V2tPno7jD">https://t.co/1V2tPno7jD</a> <a href="https://t.co/tegItbDuen">pic.twitter.com/tegItbDuen</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Santiment (@santimentfeed) <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1660751080127619072?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">May 22, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">Looking at the latest data Santiment shared today, Bitcoin&rsquo;s 7-day average trading volume has fallen from over $40 billion in February to just over $11.4 billion in May. The decline has come as BTC price fell from its year-to-date highs above $31,000 &ndash; the price of bitcoin is currently hovering around $26,800.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As for Ethereum, the proof-of-stake network&rsquo;s 7-day average trading volume has fallen sharply from nearly $20 billion in April to just over $4.6 billion in May. Like Bitcoin, Ethereum trading volume has dried up over the past month as the hype around the Shapella upgrade died down and prices fell from above $2,100.</p>
<p dir="ltr">ETH/USD currently trades around $1,820, up by about 1.2% in the past 24 hours but in the red over the past 30 days by nearly 3%.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin and Ether seeing a decrease in trading volume could be a signal that investors are increasingly cautious as market uncertainty swirls. This outlook is exacerbated by the overall nerves around risky assets as inflation, interest rates and the US debt ceiling contribute to indecisiveness.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-and-ethereum-volumes-dry-up-amid-price-struggles/">Bitcoin and Ethereum volumes dry up amid price struggles</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-and-ethereum-volumes-dry-up-amid-price-struggles/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Privacy-focused blockchain Namada plans airdrop to Osmosis’ OSMO holders</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/privacy-focused-blockchain-namada-plans-airdrop-to-osmosis-osmo-holders/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/privacy-focused-blockchain-namada-plans-airdrop-to-osmosis-osmo-holders/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 19:09:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cosmos News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/privacy-focused-blockchain-namada-plans-airdrop-to-osmosis-osmo-holders/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Privacy-focused blockchain Namada developers are seeking to forge closer ties with the Osmosis protocol. Namada is planning to airdrop its planned NAM token to OSMO investors. Namada also seeks to roll out its method for protecting asset privacy on Osmosis. Christopher Goes, Co-Founder of Namada, an L1 multi-chain privacy-focused blockchain, has proposed a partnership with [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/privacy-focused-blockchain-namada-plans-airdrop-to-osmosis-osmo-holders/">Privacy-focused blockchain Namada plans airdrop to Osmosis’ OSMO holders</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Privacy-focused blockchain Namada developers are seeking to forge closer ties with the Osmosis protocol.</li>
<li>Namada is planning to airdrop its planned NAM token to OSMO investors.</li>
<li>Namada also seeks to roll out its method for protecting asset privacy on Osmosis.</li>
</ul>
<p>Christopher Goes, Co-Founder of Namada, an L1 multi-chain privacy-focused blockchain, has proposed a partnership with <a href="https://coinjournal.net/cosmos/what-is-cosmos/">Cosmos</a>-based Osmosis.</p>
<p>The collaboration between Namada and Osmosis in this capacity is intended to enrich the respective ecosystems and bring a raft of benefits, particularly to holders of <a href="https://coinjournal.net/osmosis/">$OSMO</a> tokens, stakers and LP&rsquo;ers who would be eligible for an upcoming Namada airdrop. According to Goes, the L1 blockchain platform is interested in allocating continuous public goods funding to a grants pool managed by the Osmosis Grants Program.</p>
<p>Goes is hopeful that Osmosis will pitch the idea seeing that Namada would bankroll the effort.</p>
<h2>Protecting asset privacy on Osmosis</h2>
<p>Namada is also planning to roll out &ldquo;shielded actions&rdquo; to protect asset privacy on Osmosis. The &ldquo;shielded actions&rdquo; would hide assets on Namada when not being used in trades on Osmosis.</p>
<p>Explaining how the shielded actions work, Goes said:</p>
<p><em>&ldquo;It would be pretty boring if you only had assets and couldn&rsquo;t do anything with them. So we expect that people want to go to Osmosis and decentralized exchanges on other chains to trade their assets.&rdquo;</em></p>
<h2>Airdropping tokens to OSMO holders</h2>
<p>Namada&rsquo;s Swiss-based nonprofit the Anoma Foundation will also set aside some of Namada&rsquo;s staking token NAM for airdrops to OSMO holders. However, this is expected to take place after Namada goes live.</p>
<p>Namada is yet to give exact timelines as it waits for feedback from the Osmosis community. Goes highlighted that he is waiting for the community&rsquo;s input and permission to continue with the proposal, which will be subject to an OSMO governance vote.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/privacy-focused-blockchain-namada-plans-airdrop-to-osmosis-osmo-holders/">Privacy-focused blockchain Namada plans airdrop to Osmosis’ OSMO holders</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/privacy-focused-blockchain-namada-plans-airdrop-to-osmosis-osmo-holders/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>TON launches $25 million accelerator for emerging projects</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/ton-launches-25-million-accelerator-for-emerging-projects/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 18:30:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/ton-launches-25-million-accelerator-for-emerging-projects/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Projects will receive between $50,000 and $250,000 from the $250 million Toncoin Fund. The program will offer partnership and mentorship support, with multiple leading firms available to projects. TON Accelerator Program will draw funding from the $250 million ecosystem fund dubbed TONcoin Fund. In crypto news today, The TON Foundation, the organisation behind the The [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ton-launches-25-million-accelerator-for-emerging-projects/">TON launches $25 million accelerator for emerging projects</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Projects will receive between $50,000 and $250,000 from the $250 million Toncoin Fund.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The program will offer partnership and mentorship support, with multiple leading firms available to projects.</li>
<li dir="ltr">TON Accelerator Program will draw funding from the $250 million ecosystem fund dubbed TONcoin Fund.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">In <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/">crypto news</a> today, The TON Foundation, the organisation behind the The Open Network (TON) blockchain, has announced a new $25 million accelerator program for emerging projects.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The program, called the TON Accelerator Program, will provide funding, mentorship, and other resources to help projects build in the TON ecosystem.</p>
<p dir="ltr">TON is a community created blockchain network that uses the technology designed by Telegram and has the native cryptocurrency <a href="https://coinjournal.net/toncoin/">Toncoin (TON)</a>.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">TON to offer upto $250k to each project</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The TON Accelerator Program, which is open to various types of projects, will see select teams receive between $50,000 and $250,000 in funding. TON looks to have particular focus on projects in the DeFi space, according to details shared on Monday.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The program&rsquo;s funding will come from the TONcoin Fund, a $250 million ecosystem fund launched to support developers and founders looking to build on TON.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/TONcoinFund?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#TONcoinFund</a>'s $250M commitment will boost key projects, focusing on <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/DeFi?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#DeFi</a>. </p>
<p>Offering $50-250k per project plus mentorship via partners like <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Gotbit?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Gotbit</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Web3Port?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Web3Port</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Tonstarter?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Tonstarter</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/TEB?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#TEB</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/CypherCapital?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#CypherCapital</a>. Excited to expand with more partners, drive <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Web3?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Web3</a> innovation, and attract global&hellip; <a href="https://t.co/QHYvKHtT9S">pic.twitter.com/QHYvKHtT9S</a></p>
<p>&mdash; TON &#128142; (@ton_blockchain) <a href="https://twitter.com/ton_blockchain/status/1660652193123389443?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">May 22, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">Projects will also benefit from mentorship provided by some of the top partners and investors within the TON community. These will include hedge fund and AI-powered market maker GotBit Markets; Web3-focused innovation platform Web3Port; and Tonstarter, the leading fundraising platform on TON.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Also key to the program will be South Korea based Web3 incubator Boom Labs and UAE-based multi-strategy #crypto investment firm Cypher Capital Group.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Justin Hyun, Head of Incubation and Growth at TON Foundation expressed delight at the launch of the accelerator program, noting in a statement that the funding is part of a crucial strategy of ensuring growth.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;This is the beginning of many different incubators which will be supported in the future. Funding forms part of our local hubs rollout strategy and our ecosystem will work to attract new developers as well as successful repeat founders, based across a variety of key global locations,&rdquo; Hyun added.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Projects set to be included in the initial selection will be those that participated in the Hack-a-TONx DoraHacks hackathon. The virtual hackathon ran for two months and involved DoraHacks, a leading hacker organisation.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to the TON Foundation, application for funding is open to all MVP-ready projects. Those projects with a proof-of-concept or prototype and are seeking initial technical support are encouraged to apply for early-stage grants.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ton-launches-25-million-accelerator-for-emerging-projects/">TON launches $25 million accelerator for emerging projects</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>STEPN (GMT) price rising on Apple Pay integration</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/stepn-gmt-price-rising-on-apple-pay-integration/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 17:59:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Apple]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/stepn-gmt-price-rising-on-apple-pay-integration/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>At press time, the price of STEPN (GMT) was $0.2922, after a 7.90% surge in the last 24 hours. STEPN has integrated Apple Pay into their platform. It is the first blockchain gaming app to integrate Apple Pay. STEPN (GMT) price has taken to the skies today after the STEPN team announced that they had [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/stepn-gmt-price-rising-on-apple-pay-integration/">STEPN (GMT) price rising on Apple Pay integration</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>At press time, the price of STEPN (GMT) was $0.2922, after a 7.90% surge in the last 24 hours.</li>
<li>STEPN has integrated Apple Pay into their platform.</li>
<li>It is the first blockchain gaming app to integrate Apple Pay.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://coinjournal.net/stepn/">STEPN (GMT) price</a> has taken to the skies today after the STEPN team announced that they had successfully integrated Apple Pay into the platform.</p>
<p>STEPN, a leading Web3 move and earn application, follows a dual-token model with a utility token called GST and a governance token called GMT, which is also tradable on the secondary market.</p>
<p>The GST token has an unlimited supply it is earned when a user/member makes movements. &nbsp;is the app&rsquo;s currency that is earned for movement. It has several burn mechanisms to avoid inflation; for example, it is used to mint or repair sneakers, level up sneakers, and upgrade gems.</p>
<p>The GMT token on the other hand is earned after users level up their sneakers to level 30.</p>
<h2>Buying STEPN products and upgrades using Apple Pay</h2>
<p>Following the integration, STEPN has become the first blockchain gaming application to integrate Apple Pay.</p>
<p>The move will allow users to leverage Apple Pay&rsquo;s simplicity, speed, and security when purchasing STEPN products and upgrades directly on the STEPN app. It will eliminate the need for connecting a separate cryptocurrency wallet thus streamlining the payment process and making it easier for the STEPN community members.</p>
<p>In a statement announcing the integration, Yawn Rong, the co-founder of Find Satoshi Lab (FSL), the Web3 development studio behind STEP said:</p>
<p><em>&ldquo;This integration opens us up to a whole new audience, making Web3 more accessible to the masses. It bridges the gap between Web2 and Web3 technologies in an unprecedented way. We believe this is a momentous step towards onboarding the next 100 million users to Web3 technology. With our experienced team, we are confident in our ability to make this a reality, as we have already scaled from thousands to millions of active users. We extend our sincere gratitude to Apple for their support.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p>STEPN is a pioneer in the move and earn apps and its Apple Pay integration is a major milestone as the team works on making Web3 technology accessible to all.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/stepn-gmt-price-rising-on-apple-pay-integration/">STEPN (GMT) price rising on Apple Pay integration</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>MetaMask does not collect taxes on crypto transactions- ConsenSys</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/metamask-does-not-collect-taxes-on-crypto-transactions-consensys/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/metamask-does-not-collect-taxes-on-crypto-transactions-consensys/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 12:34:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto wallets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/metamask-does-not-collect-taxes-on-crypto-transactions-consensys/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>ConsenSys says allegations about MetaMask as false The section in its terms referred to in allegations that MetaMask collects taxes on crypto only applies to given products and paid plans that the company offers, not MetaMask. The particular products and plans are also those that involve sales tax only. ConsenSys, the company behind the popular [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/metamask-does-not-collect-taxes-on-crypto-transactions-consensys/">MetaMask does not collect taxes on crypto transactions- ConsenSys</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">ConsenSys says allegations about MetaMask as false</li>
<li dir="ltr">The section in its terms referred to in allegations that MetaMask collects taxes on crypto only applies to given products and paid plans that the company offers, not MetaMask.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The particular products and plans are also those that involve sales tax only.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">ConsenSys, the company behind the popular MetaMask crypto wallet, has denied claims that it collects taxes on crypto transactions.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/">Ethereum</a> blockchain software firm says that the allegations are &ldquo;false&rdquo; and that it has not made any changes to its terms of service to reflect this.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">ConsenSys says allegations about MetaMask are false</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The uproar appears to have stemmed from a section of MetaMask&rsquo;s terms of service that states that the wallet retains &ldquo;<em>the right to withhold taxes as necessary</em>.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, in a <a href="https://twitter.com/ConsenSys/status/1660353688446050304" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Twitter thread</a> clarifying the T&amp;Cs, ConsenSys says that the section only applies to specific products and paid plans that the company offers. It does not apply to MetaMask.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">&#128226; We are aware of tweets circulating with inaccurate information about ConsenSys' terms of service. </p>
<p>Let's clarify one thing upfront: MetaMask does NOT collect taxes on crypto transactions and we have not made any changes to our terms to do so. </p>
<p>This claim is false.</p>
<p>&mdash; ConsenSys (@ConsenSys) <a href="https://twitter.com/ConsenSys/status/1660353688446050304?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">May 21, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>The tax section in our terms of service falls under the &ldquo;fees and payment&rdquo; section, and it exclusively pertains to products and paid plans offered by ConsenSys. For example, Infura has credit card developer subscriptions which include sales tax</em>,&rdquo; the statement noted.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Adding that it believed in transparency and accuracy of information shared with users, the company added:</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>Legal terminology can be complex, but it&rsquo;s crucial to emphasize that this section DOES NOT apply to MetaMask or any other products that don&rsquo;t involve sales tax</em>.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to ConsenSys, no user assets are withheld on the premise that the user failed to pay taxes. Compliance with all applicable tax laws when it comes to customer&rsquo;s assets is that user&rsquo;s responsibility, the firm clarified.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">User privacy and secutiry among users&rsquo; priority</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Questions about MetaMask&rsquo;s tax policies began to swirl as some Twitter users voiced concerns that the wallet service was working with law enforcement.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The claims have been that the wallet is helping tax authorities to track down those deemed not to have paid taxes on their crypto holdings.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In 2022, ConsenSys came under criticism over its collection of the IP addresses and other details of users&rsquo; personal data. But pointing to its privacy policy, ConsenSys said the issue only affected those using its API-based tool Infura.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Using the tool as the default remote procedure call (RPC) in MetaMask would see it collect the user&rsquo;s IP address as well as their Ethereum wallet address. However, using another RPC provider or Ethereum node in MetaMask meant no such data collection.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/metamask-does-not-collect-taxes-on-crypto-transactions-consensys/">MetaMask does not collect taxes on crypto transactions- ConsenSys</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/metamask-does-not-collect-taxes-on-crypto-transactions-consensys/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Securities Commission Malaysia (SC) orders Huobi Global to stop operations</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/securities-commission-malaysia-sc-orders-huobi-global-to-stop-operations/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 12:18:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Huobi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Huobi-token News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/securities-commission-malaysia-sc-orders-huobi-global-to-stop-operations/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The securities commission said Huobi was operating in the country without registration. The exchange was ordered to disable its website and mobile apps. Huobi was also ordered to cease circulating, publishing or sending advertisements to Malaysian investors. The Securities Commission Malaysia (SC) has today ordered Huobi Global cryptocurrency exchange to stop its operations in the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/securities-commission-malaysia-sc-orders-huobi-global-to-stop-operations/">Securities Commission Malaysia (SC) orders Huobi Global to stop operations</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>The securities commission said Huobi was operating in the country without registration.</li>
<li>The exchange was ordered to disable its website and mobile apps.</li>
<li>Huobi was also ordered to cease circulating, publishing or sending advertisements to Malaysian investors.</li>
</ul>
<p>The Securities Commission Malaysia (SC) has today ordered Huobi Global cryptocurrency exchange to stop its operations in the country.</p>
<p>The regulator told the exchange&rsquo;s CEO Leo Li to disable its website and mobile applications because the exchange was operating a digital asset exchange without registration. It also told Huobi Global to stop circulating, publishing or sending advertisements to Malaysian investors.</p>
<h2>Operating without registration from the SC</h2>
<p>The Malaysian SC accused the crypto exchange of operating a digital asset exchange without obtaining a registration from the regulator as a Recognized Market Operator, which is an offence under the Capital Markets and Services Act.</p>
<p>The regulator gave CEO Leon Li the task of ensuring that the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/">crypto exchange</a> adheres to the given directives.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the Securities Commission Malaysia (SC) also asked Malaysian investors using Huobi Global to cease using the exchanges platform, withdraw their assets, and close their accounts.</p>
<h2>Huobi Global rebranding</h2>
<p>In November 2022, Huobi Global underwent a rebranding after its acquisition by About Capital Buyout Fund the previous month.</p>
<p>As a result, a spokesperson of the company told a popular media outline that the order by the SC does not apply to the Huobi that operates under the rebrand but to the entity that is operating under the previous entity.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/securities-commission-malaysia-sc-orders-huobi-global-to-stop-operations/">Securities Commission Malaysia (SC) orders Huobi Global to stop operations</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto price predictions: Alchemy Pay, Render Token, SUI</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-predictions-alchemy-pay-render-token-sui/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-predictions-alchemy-pay-render-token-sui/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 12:14:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-predictions-alchemy-pay-render-token-sui/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrency prices were relatively mixed on Monday as focus shifted to the upcoming Federal Reserve minutes and the debt limit issue.&#160;Bitcoin dropped below $27,000 while Ethereum was trading at $1,813. This coin price prediction will look at what to expect in Alchemy Pay (ACH), SUI, and Render Token (RNDR). Alchemy Pay price prediction Alchemy Pay [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-predictions-alchemy-pay-render-token-sui/">Crypto price predictions: Alchemy Pay, Render Token, SUI</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Cryptocurrency prices were relatively mixed on Monday as focus shifted to the upcoming Federal Reserve minutes and the debt limit issue.&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/"><u>Bitcoin</u></a> dropped below $27,000 while Ethereum was trading at $1,813. This coin price prediction will look at what to expect in Alchemy Pay (ACH), SUI, and Render Token (RNDR).</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Alchemy Pay price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Alchemy Pay is a company that is providing payment solutions in the blockchain industry. ACH, its native token, has jumped by more than 275% from the lowest level in December, making it one of the best-performing tokens om the industry.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">It has lost momentum recently after it formed a triple-top pattern at $0.045 whose neckline was at $0.022. In price action analysis, this pattern is usually one of the most accurate bearish signs. It has also moved below the 25-day and 50-day exponential moving averages, signaling that bears are in control.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, despite the recent rebound, I suspect that the ACH price will have a bearish breakout in the coming days. This view will be confirmed if it moves below the important support at $0.0222. If this happens, Alchemy Pay will have a bearish breakout to the next support at $0.1700.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/04/22/1684757572411-1f221ce4-c872-40a1-8db9-9989de0e1928.png" style="width: 595px;height: 289.567px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="595" height="289.567"></p>
<h3 dir="ltr">How to buy ACH</h3>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    Binance.US</h3>

    <p>Binance.US provides secure and reliable access to the world&rsquo;s most popular cryptocurrencies, with some of the lowest fees in the industry.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/binance-us-crypto?guid=MTQwMjk1&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy ACH with Binance.US today            </a>
    </p><h3>
    Uphold</h3>

    <p>Uphold is a platform which has over 50 cryptocurrencies to choose from.

It's users can make crypto trades with a bank account, credit card or crypto debit card. It has variable fees and allows users to automate trades.

Users who are on Brave's internet browser can also earn BAT tokens based on their browsing habits.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/uphold-crypto?guid=MTQwMjk1&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy ACH with Uphold today            </a>
    </p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Render Token price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/render-token/"><u>Render Token</u></a> has been in a strong bullish trend in the past few months. Together with Alchemy, it is one of the top-performing cryptocurrencies in the world this year. The token jumped above the key resistance point at $2.2052, the highest point on February 7. This means it is invalidating the double-top pattern.</p>
<p dir="ltr">RNDR price has moved above the 25-day and 50-day exponential moving averages and the 61.8% Fibonacci Retraacement. The Relative Strength Index is approaching the overbought level. Therefore, while there are risks, there is a possibility that the token will continue rising in the coming days. If this happens, the Render will likely jump above $3.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/04/22/1684757572247-a98c2467-3f73-4df0-958a-ef2fae805a91.png" style="width: 574px;height: 278.923px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="574" height="278.923"></p>
<h3 dir="ltr">How to buy Render Token</h3>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    Binance.US</h3>

    <p>Binance.US provides secure and reliable access to the world&rsquo;s most popular cryptocurrencies, with some of the lowest fees in the industry.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/binance-us-crypto?guid=MTQwMjk1&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy RNDR with Binance.US today            </a>
    </p><h3>
    Swapzone</h3>

    <p>Swapzone is a crypto exchange aggregator that operates as a gateway between the cryptocurrency community and exchange services. Swapzone aims to provide a convenient interface, safe user flow, and crystal-clear data for users to find the best exchange rates among the whole cryptocurrency market.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/swapzone-crypto?guid=MTQwMjk1&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy RNDR with Swapzone today            </a>
    </p>
<h2 dir="ltr">SUI price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr">SUI is one of the newest cryptocurrencies in the world. It is a&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sui-iou-price-spikes-ahead-of-airdrop-mainnet-launch/"><u>blockchain project</u></a> that was created to challenge the likes of Ethereum and Solana. After soaring to an all-time high of $1.1700 earlier this month, the coin has plunged hard recently. It fell to a low of $1.0374 during the weekend.</p>
<p dir="ltr">On the 30-minute chart, SUI has moved below all the important support levels, including $1.1140 and $1.100. It has also dropped below the short-term moving averages while its volume has dipped. Therefore, the outlook of the SUI token is bearish, with the next support being at $1.0375.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/04/22/1684757570812-efd4a89f-7214-4eb7-b9fe-7778f256900a.png" style="width: 693px;height: 337.26px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="693" height="337.26"></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-predictions-alchemy-pay-render-token-sui/">Crypto price predictions: Alchemy Pay, Render Token, SUI</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-predictions-alchemy-pay-render-token-sui/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto exchange Hotbit shuts down</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-exchange-hotbit-shuts-down/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-exchange-hotbit-shuts-down/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 11:33:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-exchange-hotbit-shuts-down/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Hotbit has announced that it will be halting its operations as from 22 May 2023. The exchange cites the deterioration in operating conditions and the change in the cryptocurrency exchange trends among reasons for the decision. The exchange has asked its users to withdraw their funds before June 21, at 4:00 am UTC. Hotbit, a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-exchange-hotbit-shuts-down/">Crypto exchange Hotbit shuts down</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Hotbit has announced that it will be halting its operations as from 22 May 2023.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The exchange cites the deterioration in operating conditions and the change in the cryptocurrency exchange trends among reasons for the decision.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The exchange has asked its users to withdraw their funds before June 21, at 4:00 am UTC.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Hotbit, a <a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/">cryptocurrency exchange</a> that has been in operation for over 5 years, has announced that it will be shutting down all operations.</p>
<p dir="ltr">A <a href="https://hotbit.zendesk.com/hc/en-us/articles/14750194236823" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">notice</a> to customers from the exchange&rsquo;s team on Monday noted that operations would be halted as from 22 May 2023, at UTC 04:00. Users have been asked to withdraw their remaining assets before June 21, 2023 at UTC 04:00.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Why did Hotbit shut down?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The decision to halt activities is down to multiple factors, including the deterioration of operating conditions and the change in the cryptocurrency exchange trends.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">It's time to take a bow &#128583;<br>For 5 years and 4 months, the Hotbit team has been proud to participate in a wonderful crypto show with 5 million users. However, it is with great regret that we have made the decision to stop all CEX operations from May 22, UTC 04:00. We kindly ask all&hellip;</p>
<p>&mdash; Hotbit News (@Hotbit_news) <a href="https://twitter.com/Hotbit_news/status/1660496999458963458?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">May 22, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>After the Hotbit management team was forced to suspend operations for several weeks due to the investigation in August 2022 the industry has experienced a series of crises, including the collapse of FTX, bank crises causing USDC off-peg incidents, resulting in continuous outflows of funds from CEX users, including Hotbit, and deteriorating cash flow</em>,&rdquo; the announcement read.</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, Hotbit also suffered from a number of problems, including repeated <a href="https://thefintechtimes.com/crypto-fraud-continued-drastic-rise-in-2022-reveals-coinjournal/coinjournal-number-of-incidents/">cyber-attacks</a> and the exploitation of project vulnerabilities by malicious actors.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Hotbit was founded in 2017 and quickly became one of the most popular cryptocurrency exchanges in the world.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The exchange&rsquo;s shutdown comes at a time when the crypto industry is still navigating the negative impact of major collapses.</p>
<p dir="ltr">It&rsquo;s also within an environment where regulators have increasingly tightened their crackdown on the industry. The past few months have seen major players like Coinbase, Ripple and Binance take the lead in asking for greater clarity in regulation from US regulators.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-exchange-hotbit-shuts-down/">Crypto exchange Hotbit shuts down</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-exchange-hotbit-shuts-down/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
