<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 11:53:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Singapore Grants Blockchain.com Major Payment Institution License</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/singapore-blockchain-com-license/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/singapore-blockchain-com-license/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Temitope Olatunji]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 11:53:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain.com]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mas]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266123</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/singapore-blockchain-com-license/">Singapore Grants Blockchain.com Major Payment Institution License</a></p>
<p>The new MPI license makes it possible for Blockchain.com to offer regulated digital payment token services to institutions and accredited investors.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/singapore-blockchain-com-license/">Singapore Grants Blockchain.com Major Payment Institution License</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/singapore-blockchain-com-license/">Singapore Grants Blockchain.com Major Payment Institution License</a></p>
<p>On August 1, the Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS), the Singapore Central Bank, granted Blockchain.com a major payment institution (MPI) license. The crypto exchange is now able to provide accredited customers with digital payment token (DPT) services, thanks to this authorization.</p>
<p>The Monetary Authority of Singapore, the country&#8217;s financial regulator, defines a digital payment token as a digital representation of value that lacks physical form and is securely maintained by a blockchain. With this approval, Blockchain.com becomes the twelfth digital payment token (DPT) service provider in Singapore, alongside companies like <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-com-license-singapore/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Crypto.com</a>, Circle, Paxos, Independent Reserve, and Revolut.</p>
<p>The new MPI license grants the exchange approval to offer regulated digital payment token services to institutions and accredited investors in Singapore. This is coming after the company received in-principle approval from MAS last year.</p>
<p>Peter Smith, the CEO and Co-Founder of Blockchain.com, expressed his excitement about the approval, <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/blockchaincom-receives-major-payment-institution-license-from-monetary-authority-of-singapore-301895088.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">stating</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We are thrilled to receive this license that will allow Blockchain.com to bring our industry-leading products and services to Singapore, we commend the Monetary Authority of Singapore on its transparent regulatory process that prioritizes crypto industry oversight while allowing innovation to thrive.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Blockchain.com, which has issued over 99 million wallets and boasts more than 40 million users, is firmly committed to continuous growth and the expansion of its services. The company is presently registered and holds licenses in various regions, demonstrating its dedication to adhering to regulatory standards in diverse markets. Obtaining the Singapore payment provider license stands as a pivotal step toward realizing the company&#8217;s overarching goal.</p>
<h2>Singapore Seeks to Become the Hub of Web3 Innovation and Development</h2>
<p>Additionally, Ripple has received in-principle approval from the Monetary Authority of Singapore for an MPI license. Notably, after receiving in-principle approval, it took Circle seven months to obtain its MPI license. These developments show Singapore&#8217;s efforts to position itself as a center for cryptocurrency innovation and services.</p>
<p>The nation has shown its dedication to cryptocurrencies and web3 technologies in a number of ways, including by announcing plans to invest S$150 million in FinTech solutions over the next three years as part of its updated Financial Sector Technology and Innovation (FSTI) Scheme.</p>
<p>In order to develop innovative <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-fintech/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FinTech</a> solutions utilizing Web3 technologies, Singapore is also extending support to Web3 projects by offering funding and collaboration opportunities. The bank intends to work with significant industry players to achieve this.</p>
<p>In addition to promoting crypto solutions and services, Singapore introduced <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/singapore-financial-authority-crypto-trust/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">new regulations</a> in July to protect cryptocurrency users. These regulations include plans to prevent cryptocurrency providers from taking part in staking and lending activities for retail users, and they mandate that cryptocurrency services hold customer funds in statutory trust by year&#8217;s end.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-gptbot-web-crawling/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/singapore-blockchain-com-license/">Singapore Grants Blockchain.com Major Payment Institution License</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/singapore-blockchain-com-license/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>OpenAI Rolls Out GPTBot for Enhanced Web Crawling</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-gptbot-web-crawling/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-gptbot-web-crawling/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 11:14:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chatgpt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[openai]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266116</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-gptbot-web-crawling/">OpenAI Rolls Out GPTBot for Enhanced Web Crawling</a></p>
<p>The launch of GPTBot comes a few weeks after OpenAI filed a trademark application for "GPT-5".</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-gptbot-web-crawling/">OpenAI Rolls Out GPTBot for Enhanced Web Crawling</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-gptbot-web-crawling/">OpenAI Rolls Out GPTBot for Enhanced Web Crawling</a></p>
<p>OpenAI, a US-based <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/technology/artificial-intelligence-news/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">artificial intelligence</a> (AI) company, has introduced GPTBot, a groundbreaking web crawling tool designed to enhance future AI models like <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/everything-you-need-to-know-about-chatgpt-ai-chatbot/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ChatGPT</a>. According to the company&#8217;s blog post, the new AI tool serves as a web crawler, a digital explorer navigating the internet to index website content. Unlike traditional search engines like Google and Bing, the tool aims to leverage indexed data to improve the accuracy, versatility, and depth of upcoming AI models, promising a significant leap in user interactions.</p>
<p>GPTBOT&#8217;s primary mission is to gather publicly available data from various online sources across the globe. The company said it is committed to ethical data collection practices, equipping the new web crawlers with the ability to exclude sources that demand payment, collect personal information, or violate content guidelines to ensure responsible data usage.</p>
<h2>Website Owners Can Control the Use of GPTBot</h2>
<p>The company also <a href="https://platform.openai.com/docs/gptbot">said</a> in its announcement that it had built GPTBot to respect the autonomy of website owners. OpenAI introduced a series of security measures alongside GPTBot, which allows website administrators to control GPTBot&#8217;s interactions within their sites.</p>
<p>Website operators can choose to restrict the web crawlers from accessing their content by implementing a &#8220;disallow&#8221; command within a standard file on their servers. The move allows web owners to take control of their content.</p>
<p>As mentioned earlier, OpenAI&#8217;s new web crawlers were designed with a proactive feature that scans collected data, eliminating personally identifiable information (PII) and content violating its policies. However, according to Decrypt, some technology ethicists on Hacker News argued that the opt-out approach still raises concerns about consent and privacy protection.</p>
<p>The <a href="https://decrypt.co/151662/chatgpt-web-crawler-openai-data-scraper-gptbot-gpt-5">report</a> noted that certain users defended OpenAI&#8217;s decision by asserting that comprehensive data gathering is necessary for a capable future AI tool. One user emphasized the importance of current data to prevent GPT models from becoming stagnant in September 2021.</p>
<p>&#8220;They still need current data, or their GPT models will be stuck in September 2021 forever,&#8221; the user said.</p>
<p>Another tech enthusiast focused on privacy criticized OpenAI for not adequately citing sources, thereby obscuring its derivative work.</p>
<h2>OpenAI Files Patent Application for GPT-5 Model</h2>
<p>Meanwhile, the launch of GPTBot comes a few weeks after OpenAI filed a trademark application for &#8220;GPT-5&#8221;. The application, submitted to the US Patent and Trademark Office (USPTO) on July 18, suggests a potential successor to GPT-4.</p>
<p>While filing a trademark application does not guarantee an immediate product launch, in June, the company&#8217;s CEO Sam Altman said the firm was &#8220;nowhere close to beginning training on the GPT-5 model&#8221;. He further noted that multiple safety audits must be completed before implementing the model.</p>
<p>The company recently <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-launches-chatgpt-android-app/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">rolled out</a> an Android version of ChatGPT to increase users&#8217; adoption. The app was immediately made available to users in India, the US, Bangladesh, and Brazil, with plans to expand to other regions in the future.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cathie-wood-bitcoin-etf-sec/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-gptbot-web-crawling/">OpenAI Rolls Out GPTBot for Enhanced Web Crawling</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-gptbot-web-crawling/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cathie Wood Anticipates Multiple Bitcoin ETF Approvals by SEC</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/cathie-wood-bitcoin-etf-sec/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/cathie-wood-bitcoin-etf-sec/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 10:45:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funds & ETFs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blackrock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcetf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cathie Wood]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266117</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cathie-wood-bitcoin-etf-sec/">Cathie Wood Anticipates Multiple Bitcoin ETF Approvals by SEC</a></p>
<p>The approval of spot-Bitcoin ETF remains a hot issue of debate among investors, regulators, and financial institutions.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cathie-wood-bitcoin-etf-sec/">Cathie Wood Anticipates Multiple Bitcoin ETF Approvals by SEC</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cathie-wood-bitcoin-etf-sec/">Cathie Wood Anticipates Multiple Bitcoin ETF Approvals by SEC</a></p>
<p>Cathie Wood, the CEO of ARK Invest has expressed belief that the US Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) may approve multiple spot <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> Exchange-Traded Funds (ETFs) simultaneously.</p>
<h2>Cathie Wood Shifts Perspective on Bitcoin ETF</h2>
<p>Cathie Wood shared her updated <a href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/cathie-wood-says-sec-will-approve-multiple-bitcoin-etfs-at-once-1.1956073#:~:text=Cathie%20Wood%20Says%20SEC%20Will%20Approve%20Multiple%20Bitcoin%20ETFs%20at%20Once,-Emily%20Graffeo%20and&amp;text=(Bloomberg)%20--%20Cathie%20Wood%20said,for%20the%20long-awaited%20product" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">perspective</a> on spot Bitcoin ETF approvals during an interview with Bloomberg TV on Monday, where she stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>“I think the SEC if it&#8217;s going to approve a Bitcoin ETF, will approve more than one at once.”</p></blockquote>
<p>This shift in perception indicates a reversal in the crypto community, as her firm had previously claimed to be at the forefront of the approval process due to its early application submission with the SEC.</p>
<p>In June, ARK Invest made waves when it filed for a spot-Bitcoin ETF. The firm&#8217;s enthusiasm was boosted by its timely filing with the SEC. However, the environment has changed, with Wood speculating that the regulatory body may choose to approve many applications at the same time.</p>
<p>James Seyffart, an ETF analyst at Bloomberg Intelligence, has weighed in on Wood’s recent remarks about the potential approval of multiple spot-Bitcoin ETFs by the SEC. Seyffart believes that Wood’s observations align with the sentiments shared by many in the industry, including analysts like himself.</p>
<p>He points out that the SEC may find it easier to approve several spot Bitcoin funds simultaneously, given the current circumstances surrounding the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/grayscale/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Grayscale Investments</a> LLC lawsuit against the regulator.</p>
<p>Grayscale, a major player in the crypto asset management space, is currently embroiled in a legal battle with the SEC. The company took the SEC to court after the regulator rejected its plan to convert the Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC), which holds around $18 billion worth of Bitcoin, into an ETF.</p>
<p>Should the court rule in favor of Grayscale, it might signal to the SEC that there is a viable path for converting existing Bitcoin investment products into ETFs. As a result, the “path of least resistance” for the SEC, according to Seyffart, would be to approve multiple spot-Bitcoin funds concurrently, potentially following a successful resolution of Grayscale’s lawsuit.</p>
<h2>Spot Bitcoin ETFs: Intense Competition Ahead of Regulatory Approval</h2>
<p>The approval of spot-Bitcoin ETF remains a hot issue of debate among investors, regulators, and financial institutions. While the desire for a regulated Bitcoin ETF has progressively increased, the road to approval has been difficult.</p>
<p>The SEC has been hesitant to grant its blessing for such a product, citing concerns over market manipulation, liquidity, and custody. As a result, no spot Bitcoin ETF currently exists in the US.</p>
<p>However, this has not deterred several leading financial firms, including <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/blackrock/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BlackRock Inc</a> (NYSE: BLK), Fidelity Investment, WisdomTree, VanEck, and Invesco, from submitting their applications for approval, each offering products strikingly similar to the proposal put forth by ARK Invest.</p>
<p>Cathie Wood has noted that with multiple firms competing for approval with similar underlying assets, the success of each ETF will hinge on the issuer’s marketing acumen.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/softbank-loss-vision-fund-profit/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cathie-wood-bitcoin-etf-sec/">Cathie Wood Anticipates Multiple Bitcoin ETF Approvals by SEC</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/cathie-wood-bitcoin-etf-sec/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>SoftBank Announces Surprising Loss as Vision Fund Posts First Profit in Five Quarters</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/softbank-loss-vision-fund-profit/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/softbank-loss-vision-fund-profit/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 10:42:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[softbank]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[uber]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vision fund]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266102</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/softbank-loss-vision-fund-profit/">SoftBank Announces Surprising Loss as Vision Fund Posts First Profit in Five Quarters</a></p>
<p>The SoftBank loss surprised analysts who were expecting the company to report a gain, even though the company's investment arm is up.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/softbank-loss-vision-fund-profit/">SoftBank Announces Surprising Loss as Vision Fund Posts First Profit in Five Quarters</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/softbank-loss-vision-fund-profit/">SoftBank Announces Surprising Loss as Vision Fund Posts First Profit in Five Quarters</a></p>
<p><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/softbank/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">SoftBank Group Corp</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> reported a loss for the quarter ended June, surprising much of the market, which expected better. However, the company’s Vision Fund investment arm posted a gain even as indicators suggested a further loss for the fund.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">SoftBank group posted a net loss of 477.6 billion yen, about $3.3 billion. This is a far cry from the 75 billion Refinitiv analysts expected from the company. However, the figure is a significant improvement from the 3.16 trillion yen recorded in the same quarter last year.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">On the other hand, the SoftBank Vision Fund posted a profit even though analysts expected a loss. After five consecutive losing quarters, the Vision Fund gained 159.8 billion yen, about $1.1 billion, in the quarter ended June. Interestingly, SoftBank lost $32 billion during the last quarter, with significant losses from Indonesian e-commerce and ride-hailing company GoTo, as well as Chinese AI company SenseTime.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The SoftBank Vision Fund lost a cumulative ¥6.9 trillion, about $48 billion, over the last 2 years. It has recently suspended new investments and reduced its Alibaba stake. SoftBank also no longer has any stake in <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/uber/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Uber</a>. It initially invested in Uber in 2018 and then sold nearly a third of the stake. As of Monday, SoftBank </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/08/08/softbank-sells-entire-stake-in-uber-as-vision-fund-losses-mount.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">confirmed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> it offloaded all of its Uber holdings, likely to manage its financial health as losses continuously piled up.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">SoftBank in “Offense Mode” Despite Loss</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Speaking at a June shareholder meeting, SoftBank CEO Masayoshi Son said the company will now leave “defense mode” and enter “offense mode.” He explained that SoftBank now has the cash to be on the offensive:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">“In the past few years, we focused on being [on] ‘defense.’ Three years ago, we didn’t have a lot of cash on hand. But because we have been in defense mode, we have built our cash on hand to five trillion yen ($35.3 billion). We are ready to shift to offense mode. I am excited about that.”</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">SoftBank has faced its fair share of headwinds recently as the value of its investments has not spiked as expected. Last year, a top SoftBank exec Rajeev Misra stepped down from his roles as executive vice president and corporate officer. Misra was also the CEO of SoftBank Global Advisors, which controls Vision Fund 2, one of the funds under the SoftBank Vision Fund. Misra’s decision to step down came amid mounting pressure from the fund’s performance as stocks continued to crash and investments failed to pay off.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The market is now looking to SoftBank’s upcoming initial public offering (</span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-initial-public-offering-ipo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">IPO</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">) for its chip designer subsidiary, Arm Ltd. Arm recently </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/softbank-arm-us-only-listing/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">decided to shun the UK market</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> and opt for a US-only listing after talks with the British government did not yield favorable results. Now, the chip designer is looking at a $70 billion valuation, which would be the largest IPO in 2023.</span></p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitstamp-derivatives-trading-europe/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/softbank-loss-vision-fund-profit/">SoftBank Announces Surprising Loss as Vision Fund Posts First Profit in Five Quarters</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/softbank-loss-vision-fund-profit/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitstamp to Expand Derivatives Trading in Europe amid Fundraise</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitstamp-derivatives-trading-europe/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitstamp-derivatives-trading-europe/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 10:39:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitstamp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fca]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[galaxy digital]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gemini]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266111</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitstamp-derivatives-trading-europe/">Bitstamp to Expand Derivatives Trading in Europe amid Fundraise</a></p>
<p>Bitstamp is also looking to expand its operations in the UK after securing the FCA license earlier this year. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitstamp-derivatives-trading-europe/">Bitstamp to Expand Derivatives Trading in Europe amid Fundraise</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitstamp-derivatives-trading-europe/">Bitstamp to Expand Derivatives Trading in Europe amid Fundraise</a></p>
<p>One of the oldest cryptocurrency exchanges <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/bitstamp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitstamp</a> is looking to expand its footprint and service offerings amid the current talks of raising fresh funding. Jean-Baptiste Graftieaux, global chief executive officer of the exchange appraised the recent developments. As per the company spokesperson, Bitstamp started its fundraising efforts earlier this year in June 2023. Mike Novogratz&#8217;s Galaxy Digital is acting as an adviser in the entire process. Earlier, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/galaxy-digital/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Galaxy Digital</a> served as an adviser to Pantera, which later sold its minority stake in Bitstamp to Ripple in 2023. Bitstamp said that they would be using these funds to launch crypto derivatives trading in the European continent next year.</p>
<p>Additionally, they would also use these funds to expand the number of markets that it serves in Asia. The company spokesperson said that Bitstamp is also looking to expand its operations in the U.K. In a statement to Bloomberg, Graftieaux <a href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/crypto-exchange-bitstamp-in-talks-to-raise-funds-for-expansion-ceo-says-1.1956129" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Bitstamp is not for sale, and we are not actively looking to sell the company. Our current and exclusive priority is to raise money through strategic investors to accelerate Bitstamp’s growth by providing new products and services to retail and institutional crypto customers.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Earlier this year in June, Bitstamp also <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitstamp-fca-exchanges/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">secured</a> approval from UK’s Financial Conduct Authority (FCA) to function as a registered crypto firm in the region. After obtaining the license, Bitstamp stated its dedication to increasing its presence and investments in the UK market.</p>
<h2>Bitstamp&#8217;s Growth Over the Years</h2>
<p>As said, Bitstamp is one of the oldest crypto exchanges established in 2011 and based out of Luxembourg. Back then Bitstamp was among the major competitors to now-defunct Bitcoin exchange Mt. Gox. Now, it&#8217;s the seventh-largest exchange in the world. It had around $126 million worth of trading in a recent 24-hour period.</p>
<p>Bitstamp also has a part in the US entity called Bitstamp USA. The exchange also has a special license called BitLicense, essential to operate in New York state.</p>
<p>More platforms for cryptocurrencies are getting into the derivatives market. This market used to be mostly dominated by FTX and Binance. But after the FTX collapse, Bitstamp seems to be grabbing an opportunity here. Coinbase Global Inc and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/gemini/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Gemini</a>, two other big companies in the cryptocurrency world, started their own derivatives markets outside the US this year. Bitstamp was among the first exchanges to allow <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gemini-kraken-bitstamp-resume-xrp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">XRP trading</a> after the court ruling.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/scammers-pyusd-tokens/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitstamp-derivatives-trading-europe/">Bitstamp to Expand Derivatives Trading in Europe amid Fundraise</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitstamp-derivatives-trading-europe/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Scammers Release Multiple Copycat PYUSD Tokens</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/scammers-pyusd-tokens/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/scammers-pyusd-tokens/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 09:44:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[paypal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[paypal usd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pyusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266079</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/scammers-pyusd-tokens/">Scammers Release Multiple Copycat PYUSD Tokens</a></p>
<p>Scammers may continue to cash in on the PayPal stablecoin launch for as long as possible.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/scammers-pyusd-tokens/">Scammers Release Multiple Copycat PYUSD Tokens</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/scammers-pyusd-tokens/">Scammers Release Multiple Copycat PYUSD Tokens</a></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Bad actors have attempted to take advantage of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">PayPal</a>&#8216;s launch of its native stablecoin – PYUSD. The <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-paypal-usd-stablecoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">launch</a>, which took place barely 24 hours ago, now has competition from several fake tokens sporting the “PYUSD” ticker.</span></p>
<h2>A Wave of Fake Tokens Strikes, Here&#8217;s How to Know If Its Original</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to data from the decentralized exchange tracker DexScreener, there are about 30 new look-alike token pairs that have suddenly popped up in the hours following the launch.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">So far, these opportunists have minted the copycat tokens across different chains including <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a>, Binance Smart Chain, and even Coinbases’ newest layer 2 Base.</span></p>
<p>As of publication, the largest PYUSD token fraud appears to be one that was minted on Ethereum and has seen over $2.6 million in trading volume. The fake token launched just a few minutes after PayPal launched its own stablecoin.</p>
<p>Another token identifies as “PepeYieldUnibotSatoshiDoge,” and has surged over 3,000% in the last 4 hours.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, despite the abundance of fake PYUSD tokens, confirming its authenticity may be as simple as just verifying it at this contract <a href="https://etherscan.io/address/0x6c3ea9036406852006290770bedfcaba0e23a0e8" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">address</a>. Besides, PayPal has announced that PYUSD may only be transferred between PayPal and compatible external wallets. Therefore, it becomes nearly impossible that any of the tokens bearing a similar ticker on any decentralized exchange are the real deal.</p>
<h2>PYUSD Plummets Nearly 70%</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">PayPal USD displayed huge prospects in the early hours of its launch, surging over 30,000% in the first eight hours. But despite the impressive start, it has since retraced, losing about 70% of its earlier gains.</span></p>
<p>The sharp decline, however, appears to be linked to the several imposter tokens that are out there taking up its trading volume and activity without the investors knowing. And unless investors are capable of auditing smart contracts themselves, these scammers may continue to cash in on the PayPal stablecoin launch for as long as possible.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-iphone-15-mid-september-release/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/scammers-pyusd-tokens/">Scammers Release Multiple Copycat PYUSD Tokens</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/scammers-pyusd-tokens/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Apple’s iPhone 15 Set for Mid-September Release amid Smartphone Sale Slowdown</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-iphone-15-mid-september-release/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-iphone-15-mid-september-release/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mercy Tukiya Mutanya]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 09:39:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple iphone]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple iphone 15]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[iphone]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[iphone 15]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tim cook]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266078</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-iphone-15-mid-september-release/">Apple&#8217;s iPhone 15 Set for Mid-September Release amid Smartphone Sale Slowdown</a></p>
<p>Meanwhile, Chief Executive Officer Tim Cook pointed out that sales of Apple products in the United States were declining.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-iphone-15-mid-september-release/">Apple&#8217;s iPhone 15 Set for Mid-September Release amid Smartphone Sale Slowdown</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-iphone-15-mid-september-release/">Apple&#8217;s iPhone 15 Set for Mid-September Release amid Smartphone Sale Slowdown</a></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/apple-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Apple</a>’s iPhone 15 will reportedly go on sale around September 22, according to a <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2023-08-06/apple-iphone-15-comes-amid-us-sales-slowdown-tim-cook-q3-earnings-comments-lkzfs14u" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Bloomberg report</a> release on Monday, August 7, 2023. The launch is expected to follow an Apple event to be held on either September 12 or 13 during which consumers will get a peak into the new device’s features. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">During a <a href="https://www.apple.com/investor/earnings-call/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">post-earnings call</a> last week, Apple reported that “the smartphone market has been in a decline for the last couple of quarters in the United States,” sending the company’s stock sliding. The company’s fiscal third-quarter (ended July 1) earnings show that iPhone sales declined 2% to $39.67 billion. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">While iPhone sales are expected to improve this quarter, the company projects that revenue will remain in the same range as last quarter. In fact, Apple is headed for its fourth straight quarterly sales decrease, an event that has not occurred since 2001. This could be a challenge for the tech giant considering that the iPhone 15 is set to be the biggest update to the phone range in three years. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Previous major upgrades such as the iPhone 6 in 2014, iPhone X in 2017 and iPhone 12 in 2020 could depend on new features such as larger screens, 5G support and new designs, to sell the product. The iPhone 15 is expected to feature borders that are one-third thinner than the last model, a lighter titanium frame to replace the current stainless steel, better camera quality, a USB-C charging port, and a faster processor. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">For this upgrade, the company might have to look beyond the promise of new features to make sales. Apple, which rarely experiences sales declines, has faced major setbacks over the past years. These include a slowdown in sales in the Chinese market in early 2019, a launch delay due to the Covid-19 pandemic in 2020 and supply chain issues at Foxconn plants in China last year which negatively impacted holiday sales. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Chief Executive Officer Tim Cook pointed out that sales of Apple products in the United States were declining. The company noted an increase of 7.9% to $15.7 billion in revenue in the Chinese market – including the Hong Kong and Taiwan regions. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The device that is going on sale on September 22 will give the company about a week of iPhone 15 sales in the fourth quarter. It will be interesting to see how sales perform during the holiday quarter – October to December – which is Apple’s busiest time of the year. Barring any production or supply chain issues this year, the iPhone 15 has the potential to outperform the iPhone 14 Pro and Pro Max, making for better year-on-year figures.  </span></p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/zoom-terms-customer-data-ai/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-iphone-15-mid-september-release/">Apple&#8217;s iPhone 15 Set for Mid-September Release amid Smartphone Sale Slowdown</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-iphone-15-mid-september-release/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Zoom Updates Its Terms of Service, Promising Not to Use Customer Data to Train AI without Their Consent</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/zoom-terms-customer-data-ai/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/zoom-terms-customer-data-ai/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Darya Rudz]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 09:34:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[zoom]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[zoom ai]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[zoom artificial intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Zoom Communications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[zoom iq meeting summary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[zoom iq team chat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[zoom terms of service]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[zoom video communications]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266063</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/zoom-terms-customer-data-ai/">Zoom Updates Its Terms of Service, Promising Not to Use Customer Data to Train AI without Their Consent</a></p>
<p>In response to criticism of its updated Terms of Service, Zoom stated it does not train its AI tools "without customer consent."</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/zoom-terms-customer-data-ai/">Zoom Updates Its Terms of Service, Promising Not to Use Customer Data to Train AI without Their Consent</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/zoom-terms-customer-data-ai/">Zoom Updates Its Terms of Service, Promising Not to Use Customer Data to Train AI without Their Consent</a></p>
<p>Recently, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/zoom-video-communications/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Zoom Video Communications Inc</a> (NASDAQ: ZM) <a href="https://explore.zoom.us/en/terms/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">released</a> its updated terms of service. According to the new policy, Zoom might use its customers&#8217; data to train its artificial intelligence (AI) products. In a <a href="https://blog.zoom.us/zooms-term-service-ai/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">blog post</a> issued later, Zoom stated it does not train its artificial intelligence models on audio, video, or text chats from the app &#8220;without customer consent.&#8221;</p>
<p>The updated terms of use came into effect on July 27. The document reads that customers grant Zoom &#8220;perpetual, worldwide, non-exclusive, royalty-free, sublicensable, and transferable license and all other rights required or necessary&#8221; to their content for a number of purposes, which now include &#8220;machine learning&#8221; and &#8220;artificial intelligence.&#8221; Another section of the terms states that Zoom can use certain user data for &#8220;machine learning or artificial intelligence (including for the purposes of training and tuning of algorithms and models).&#8221;</p>
<p>The terms have been met with criticism, as they mark unethical employment of data and pose a risk of misuse of personal information.</p>
<p>In response to negative comments about using people&#8217;s data for training AI, Zoom Chief Product Officer Smita Hashim came up with a post that states the opposite.</p>
<p>&#8220;We recently introduced two powerful generative AI features – Zoom IQ Meeting Summary and Zoom IQ Team Chat Compose – on a free trial basis to enhance your Zoom experience. These features offer automated meeting summaries and AI-powered chat composition. Zoom account owners and administrators control whether to enable these AI features for their accounts,&#8221; wrote Smita Hashim.</p>
<p>Further, she explained that while enabling Zoom IQ Meeting Summary or Zoom IQ Team Chat Compose, users would be presented with a transparent consent process for training the AI models.</p>
<p>Smita Hashim added:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Your content is used solely to improve the performance and accuracy of these AI services. And even if you chose to share your data, it will not be used for training of any third-party models.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>To shed more light on the use of customer calls and video conferences, Zoom added the following to its Terms of Service:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Notwithstanding the above, Zoom will not use audio, video or chat Customer Content to train our artificial intelligence models without your consent.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Previously, there already were similar cases that led to legal action. An example is OpenAI which faced a federal lawsuit claiming the company trained its <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/everything-you-need-to-know-about-chatgpt-ai-chatbot/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ChatGPT</a> chatbot using data stolen from millions of people.</p>
<h2>Zoom AI Tools</h2>
<p>Earlier this year, Zoom rolled out two generative AI features: Zoom IQ Meeting Summary and Zoom IQ Team Chat Compose.</p>
<p>Zoom IQ Meeting Summary allows meeting hosts to initiate an AI-generated summary of their meeting powered by Zoom’s own large language models. When the host enables this feature in a meeting, participants will automatically receive a summary after the meeting ends.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Zoom IQ Team Chat Compose allows users to leverage OpenAI’s technology, to draft messages based on the context of a Team Chat thread in addition to changing message tone and length as well as rephrasing responses to customize text recommendations.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cypher-protocol-1m-exploit/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/zoom-terms-customer-data-ai/">Zoom Updates Its Terms of Service, Promising Not to Use Customer Data to Train AI without Their Consent</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/zoom-terms-customer-data-ai/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cypher Protocol Halts Smart Contract Following $1M Exploit</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/cypher-protocol-1m-exploit/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/cypher-protocol-1m-exploit/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 09:29:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cybersecurity News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cypher Protocol]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[defi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sol]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[solana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[usd coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[usdc]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266072</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cypher-protocol-1m-exploit/">Cypher Protocol Halts Smart Contract Following $1M Exploit</a></p>
<p>Following the attack, the Cypher Protocol team highlighted that an internal investigation had been launched to determine the root cause of the exploit.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cypher-protocol-1m-exploit/">Cypher Protocol Halts Smart Contract Following $1M Exploit</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cypher-protocol-1m-exploit/">Cypher Protocol Halts Smart Contract Following $1M Exploit</a></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Cypher Protocol, a </span><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/solana/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Solana</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">-based </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">decentralized futures exchange, faced a severe security breach on Monday, resulting in an estimated $1 million exploit. In response to the alarming incident, the platform swiftly halted its smart contract to prevent further damage.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Data </span><a href="https://solscan.io/account/HHm4wK91XvL3hhEC4hQHo544rtvkaKohQPc59TvZeC71#solTransfers" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">provided</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> by Solana blockchain explorer Solscan revealed that the attackers targeted vulnerabilities in Cypher’s smart contract to gain unauthorized access to user funds. The theft encompassed 38,530 Solana (SOL) tokens and $123,184 worth of USD Coin (USDC).</span></p>
<h2><b>Cypher Protocol Exploit: The Path to Recovery</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Following the attack, the Cypher Protocol team took to X (formerly Twitter) to </span><a href="https://twitter.com/cypher_protocol/status/1688641036476731393" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">report</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> the incident and highlighted that an internal investigation had been launched to determine the root cause of the exploit.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Notably, this investigation is crucial to identifying the flaws, and understanding how the attacker breached the smart contract in order to bolster the platform&#8217;s defenses and prevent future instances.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Additionally, the team has taken the bold step of reaching out to the hacker with the hope of negotiating the return of the stolen funds. Such attempts at resolution are complex and raise ethical and legal concerns within the crypto community.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Negotiating with hackers is a two-edged sword because it may result in the recovery of lost monies while also potentially inciting more attacks on the platform or other Decentralized Finance (</span><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-decentralized-finance-defi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">DeFi</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">) ventures. Nonetheless, Cypher’s readiness to engage in dialogue shows a dedication to its users’ interests as well as an effort to limit the consequences of the exploit.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Meanwhile, the stolen assets represent not just monetary value but also the trust and confidence users had placed in Cypher Protocol. The incident can potentially erode the faith of investors in DeFi platforms, leading to caution and reluctance in participating in such ventures in the future.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">For Cypher, the immediate challenge lies in ensuring that affected users are appropriately compensated and that security measures are bolstered to prevent future exploits. The platform’s response to this incident will be closely monitored by the broader blockchain community, as it could set a precedent for how other projects handle similar security breaches.</span></p>
<h2><b>Cypher Receives Community Support</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As soon as the exploit was discovered, the alleged hacker behind the heist moved to </span><a href="https://solscan.io/tx/4ZqYRfvPePGLpZCb6t1iq7gNMUwsrkcQoSAiDHq9gEYUve9t3b598Qf63uErtaoB1onScKf7VcmM3u8qVbAd3XK6"><span style="font-weight: 400;">send</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> 30,000 USDC worth of assets to Binance&#8217;s Solana address &#8220;kiing.sol.&#8221; The move was interpreted as an attempt to unload the illegally obtained assets, which sparked uproar in the blockchain community.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In an interesting turn of events, users leveraged </span><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Non-Fungible Tokens</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> (NFTs) to communicate directly with the attacker, imploring them to do the right thing and return the funds. These messages encapsulate the determination of the community to identify the perpetrator and reclaim the stolen assets.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The community’s collective actions not only demonstrate a spirit of solidarity but also highlight the growing importance of accountability within the DeFi ecosystem.</span></p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/elon-musk-brain-implant-neuralink-280m/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cypher-protocol-1m-exploit/">Cypher Protocol Halts Smart Contract Following $1M Exploit</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/cypher-protocol-1m-exploit/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Elon Musk’s Brain-Implant Company Neuralink Raises $280M in New Funding Round</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/elon-musk-brain-implant-neuralink-280m/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/elon-musk-brain-implant-neuralink-280m/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Darya Rudz]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 09:24:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investors News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon musk neuralink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[n1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[neuralink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[neuralink brain implants]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[neuralink funding round]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[neuralink trial]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266051</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/elon-musk-brain-implant-neuralink-280m/">Elon Musk’s Brain-Implant Company Neuralink Raises $280M in New Funding Round</a></p>
<p>The round follows approval for Neuralink's first human trials received by the startup from the US Food and Drugs Administration (FDA) in May. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/elon-musk-brain-implant-neuralink-280m/">Elon Musk’s Brain-Implant Company Neuralink Raises $280M in New Funding Round</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/elon-musk-brain-implant-neuralink-280m/">Elon Musk’s Brain-Implant Company Neuralink Raises $280M in New Funding Round</a></p>
<p>Neuralink Corp, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/elon-musk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Elon Musk</a>&#8216;s startup that focuses on brain-machine interfaces to provide solutions for those with paralysis, has closed a $280 million funding round. The funds raised will be used to further develop its N1 implants that &#8216;create a generalized brain interface to restore autonomy to those with unmet medical needs.&#8217;</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="474" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">We’re happy to announce our $280M Series D round led by <a href="https://twitter.com/foundersfund?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@foundersfund</a>. We’re extremely excited about this next chapter at Neuralink. </p>
<p>If you’d like to help make the first human experience incredible and work on engineering challenges to restore vision and mobility, come join!…</p>
<p>&mdash; Neuralink (@neuralink) <a href="https://twitter.com/neuralink/status/1688582504196739072?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 7, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The round was led by Founders Fund, a venture capital firm backed by billionaire Peter Thiel.</p>
<p>Scott Nolan, partner at Founders Fund, <a href="https://twitter.com/ScottNolan/status/1688585463676948480" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">commented</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Excited to support Neuralink’s next chapter of helping human patients in need. The team has been working for seven years to make this possible, pulling off technical breakthroughs that feel like science fiction.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>It has not been revealed at what valuation Neuralink started the funding round. Last month, &#8216;privately executed stock trades&#8217; estimated the value of Neuralink at $5 billion, which is more than double the worth of $2 billion back in 2020.</p>
<p>The round follows approval for Neuralink&#8217;s first human trials received by the startup from the US Food and Drugs Administration (FDA) in May.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="474" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">We are excited to share that we have received the FDA’s approval to launch our first-in-human clinical study!</p>
<p>This is the result of incredible work by the Neuralink team in close collaboration with the FDA and represents an important first step that will one day allow our…</p>
<p>&mdash; Neuralink (@neuralink) <a href="https://twitter.com/neuralink/status/1661857379460468736?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">May 25, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The N1 implants developed by Neuralink include multiple chips, a wireless battery and other electronics hermetically sealed within a device about the size of a large coin. Neural activity is recorded through 1024 electrodes distributed across 64 threads. These highly-flexible, ultra-thin threads are key to minimize damage during implantation and beyond. N1 is fully implantable, cosmetically invisible, and designed to let patients control a computer or mobile device anywhere they go. The battery is charged wirelessly from the outside via a compact, inductive charger that enables easy use from anywhere.</p>
<h2>Controversy around Elon Musk&#8217;s Neuralink</h2>
<p>Neuralink is not the first company to work on brain implants, but it has probably been one of the most discussed startups because of the controversial methods it employed for testing its technology.</p>
<p>In 2020, the company paid $1.4 million to the University of California, Davis, to use its facilities for conducting trials. In 2022, regulators raised concerns about tests run by Neuralink on animals. Between 2018 and 2022, the company reportedly experimented on and killed 1,500 animals, including pigs, rats, sheep and monkeys. The Physicians Committee for Responsible Medicine (PCRM), a group that campaigns for alternatives to animal testing, obtained public records detailing the experiments. It was found that one rhesus macaque monkey’s nausea was &#8220;so severe that the animal vomited and had open sores in her oesophagus before she was finally killed,&#8221; according to Ryan Merkley, PCRM’s director of research advocacy.</p>
<p>In late 2022, the US Department of Agriculture opened a probe into Neuralink over possible animal welfare violations. Meanwhile, Neuralink&#8217;s website was stating that &#8220;all novel medical devices and treatments must be tested in animals before they can be ethically trialed in humans.&#8221;</p>
<p>Earlier this year, the US Transportation Department began another investigation, alleging that the company did not follow proper procedure when shipping possibly hazardous materials.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-equity-indices-dow-400-points/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/elon-musk-brain-implant-neuralink-280m/">Elon Musk’s Brain-Implant Company Neuralink Raises $280M in New Funding Round</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/elon-musk-brain-implant-neuralink-280m/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4176 metric#misses=45 metric#hit-ratio=98.9 metric#bytes=1110272 metric#prefetches=214 metric#store-reads=22 metric#store-writes=2 metric#store-hits=220 metric#store-misses=6 metric#sql-queries=34 metric#ms-total=88.72 metric#ms-cache=5.16 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.2245 metric#ms-cache-ratio=5.8 -->