<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 20:56:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Fidelity may soon file for a spot bitcoin ETF</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/fidelity-may-soon-file-for-a-spot-bitcoin-etf/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wajeeh Khan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 20:56:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=144404</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Block says Fidelity is next in line to file for a spot bitcoin ETF. Oanda analyst Edward Moya shares his view on the Fidelity news. BlackRock also filed for such an exchange-traded fund last week. Fidelity is in focus on Tuesday following a report that the asset manager was next in line to file [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/fidelity-may-soon-file-for-a-spot-bitcoin-etf/">Fidelity may soon file for a spot bitcoin ETF</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>The Block says Fidelity is next in line to file for a spot bitcoin ETF.</li>
<li>Oanda analyst Edward Moya shares his view on the Fidelity news.</li>
<li>BlackRock also filed for such an exchange-traded fund last week.</li>
</ul>
<p>Fidelity is in focus on Tuesday following a report that the asset manager was next in line to file for a spot bitcoin ETF.</p>
<h2>Analyst reacts to the Fidelity news</h2>
<p>The news arrives only days after peer BlackRock filed with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission for such an exchange-traded fund (<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/should-exchanges-fear-a-blackrock-etf/">find out more</a>).</p>
<p>Fidelity refused to comment on <a href="https://www.theblock.co/post/236588/fidelity-preparing-to-submit-spot-bitcoin-etf-filing-source" target="_blank" rel="noopener">The Block&rsquo;s</a> report this morning. But a Senior Market Analyst at Oanda &ndash; Edward Moya said:</p>
<blockquote><p>There&rsquo;s a lot of optimism here that you&rsquo;re going to get a bitcoin ETF.</p></blockquote>
<p>Others that have recently filed for a spot bitcoin ETF include Invesco, WisdomTree, Bitwise, and VanEck. Such filings helped bitcoin hit $31,000 this week for the first time in more than a year.</p>
<h2>What a spot bitcoin ETF may mean for crypto</h2>
<p>It is noteworthy here that Fidelity had filed for a spot <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/bitcoin/">bitcoin</a> ETF in 2021 as well. At the time, it had faced rejection.</p>
<p>But this time could be different considering its peer BlackRock has filed for one as well and BlackRock has a reputation for making such a move only when it&rsquo;s convinced that it will receive approval, as per Oanda&rsquo;s Moya.</p>
<blockquote><p>If that does get done, it could open the door for much more institutional money and probably some high-net-worth retail traders to get back into crypto.</p></blockquote>
<p>Last week, Fidelity backed crypto exchange <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/new-crypto-exchange-edx-markets-goes-live/">EDX Markets</a> went live in the United States. On the downside, though, the U.S. regulator has recently filed lawsuits against both Binance and Coinbase Global Inc.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/fidelity-may-soon-file-for-a-spot-bitcoin-etf/">Fidelity may soon file for a spot bitcoin ETF</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitfinex launches P2P platform in Venezuela, Argentina and Colombia</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitfinex-launches-p2p-platform-in-venezuela-argentina-and-colombia/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitfinex-launches-p2p-platform-in-venezuela-argentina-and-colombia/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 18:49:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitfinex]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Latin america]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[P2P]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitfinex-launches-p2p-platform-in-venezuela-argentina-and-colombia/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitfinex P2P will support buying and selling of Bitcoin, Ethereum and Tether tokens USDt and EURt. The company is looking to bolster financial freedom and inclusion across Latin America. Bitfinex completed an investment in Chile-based crypto bank OrionX in May. Bitfinex, one of the leading digital asset trading platforms, is making further inroads in Latin [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitfinex-launches-p2p-platform-in-venezuela-argentina-and-colombia/">Bitfinex launches P2P platform in Venezuela, Argentina and Colombia</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Bitfinex P2P will support buying and selling of Bitcoin, Ethereum and Tether tokens USDt and EURt.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The company is looking to bolster financial freedom and inclusion across Latin America.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Bitfinex completed an investment in Chile-based crypto bank OrionX in May.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/bitfinex/">Bitfinex</a>, one of the leading digital asset trading platforms, is making further inroads in Latin America as it seeks to bring financial freedom and inclusion to the region.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In the latest <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/bitfinex/">Bitfinex news</a>, the company announced the launch of its peer-to-peer (P2P) platform for users in Venezuela, Colombia and Argentina.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitfinex P2P to support BTC, ETH and Tether</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Dubbed &lsquo;Bitfinex P2P,&rdquo; the platform will offer people in the three countries an avenue with which to directly buy and sell Bitcoin (BTC) and Ether (ETH). Users of Bitfinex P2P will also access Tether tokens (USDt and EURt) as well as Tether Gold (XAUt).</p>
<p dir="ltr">The platform will also allow customers to swap digital tokens, according to details in a <a href="https://blog.bitfinex.com/media-releases/bitfinex-launches-peer-to-peer-platform-bitfinex-p2p-in-venezuela-argentina-and-colombia/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">press release</a> published on Tuesday.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Paolo Ardoino, CTO of Bitfinex said:</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>By offering a reliable and efficient platform for P2P token trading, we are empowering our customers to engage with the marketplace in a way that affords maximum convenience based on their needs and preferences. We believe in the transformative power of Bitcoin and other digital assets, as well as the importance of providing greater access to innovative financial technologies worldwide</em>.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitfinex&rsquo;s entry into the P2P market in the region is likely to be welcome news to crypto users after two of the leading P2P marketplaces in LocalBitcoins and Paxful shut down their operations. The expansion also comes after Bitfinex <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitfinex-and-chiles-orionx-partner-to-accelerate-crypto-adoption-in-latin-america/">invested</a> in Chilean &ldquo;crypto bank&rdquo; OrionX, a deal completed in May.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitfinex-launches-p2p-platform-in-venezuela-argentina-and-colombia/">Bitfinex launches P2P platform in Venezuela, Argentina and Colombia</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitfinex-launches-p2p-platform-in-venezuela-argentina-and-colombia/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chromia (CHR) hits milestone as My Neighbor Alice Alpha Season 3 goes live</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/chromia-chr-hits-milestone-as-my-neighbor-alice-alpha-season-3-goes-live/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/chromia-chr-hits-milestone-as-my-neighbor-alice-alpha-season-3-goes-live/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 17:12:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/chromia-chr-hits-milestone-as-my-neighbor-alice-alpha-season-3-goes-live/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Chromia Appnet welcomes first ever decentralised token bridge with My Neighbor Alice collaboration. ALICE tokens can now be bridged from the Binance Smart Chain (BSC). Chromia token (CHR) was slightly lower on Tuesday afternoon, but was 12% higher in the past week. Chromia, a standalone public blockchain developed by Swedish company Chromaway AB, has hit [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chromia-chr-hits-milestone-as-my-neighbor-alice-alpha-season-3-goes-live/">Chromia (CHR) hits milestone as My Neighbor Alice Alpha Season 3 goes live</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Chromia Appnet welcomes first ever decentralised token bridge with My Neighbor Alice collaboration.</li>
<li dir="ltr">ALICE tokens can now be bridged from the Binance Smart Chain (BSC).</li>
<li dir="ltr">Chromia token (CHR) was slightly lower on Tuesday afternoon, but was 12% higher in the past week.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Chromia, a standalone public blockchain developed by Swedish company Chromaway AB, has hit a new milestone after blockchain-based game <a href="https://coinjournal.net/my-neighbor-alice/">My Neighbor Alice</a> Alpha Season 3 went live on the Appnet.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Decentralised token bridge on Chromia</h2>
<p dir="ltr">My Neighbor Alice Alpha Season 3 launched on the first ever Chromia Appnet, a collaboration that is set to see the public have access to MNA&rsquo;s unique multiplayer game. There is a &lsquo;free trial&rsquo; where players can tap into the benefits of land ownership as well as use the native MNA token ALICE.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Another milestone is the bridging of ALICE from Binance Smart Chain, the first bridged asset use on the Chromia Appnet.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">&#127800; My Neighbor Alice Alpha Season 3 is now LIVE!</p>
<p>Join us and explore an array of exciting new features, like: </p>
<p>&#128736; Crafting System<br>&#127379; FREE TRIAL for non-landowners <br>&#128444; Plot-sharing by landowners through FREE-RENTING <br>&#128087; ELLE branded Quests and <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/NFTs?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#NFTs</a> <br>&#129689; <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24ALICE&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$ALICE</a> token utilization&hellip; <a href="https://t.co/rmTNLs5rHP">pic.twitter.com/rmTNLs5rHP</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Alice (@MyNeighborAlice) <a href="https://twitter.com/MyNeighborAlice/status/1673650229420097537?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 27, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">Alpha Season 3 comes with all the popular game features, including fishing, farming and land decoration. However, there are also new exciting experiences such as sharing of land plots, staking ALICE and customising in-game avatars.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;T<em>oday, with the release of My Neighbor Alice Alpha Season 3, is a big milestone for both us and Chromia. We are the first app on Chromia appnet and the first project to utilise the decentralised token bridge in order to give in-game utility for $ALICE</em>,&rdquo; Viktor Plane, Technical Director at My Neighbor Alice<a href="https://twitter.com/snieking/status/1673566262843023361">&nbsp;<u>said</u></a> when commenting on the development.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Chromia&rsquo;s open source blockchain offers EVM compatibility for Ethereum and the Binance Smart Chain. It provides for the development of next-generation decentralised applications through enhanced scalability, data and storage capabilities and customizable fees.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The applications include DeFi options trading protocol Hedget that <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chromia-launches-defi-protocol-for-options-trading/">launched</a> in 2020 and the increasingly popular MNA. Chromia also enables supply chains, with Chromia&rsquo;s technology used to trace product origins and integration of NFTs.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Chromia (CHR) price</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The Chroma token (CHR), the native token of the Layer-1 blockchain network, hovered above $0.13, about 2.8% down in the past 24 hours at the time of writing. CHR however traded nearly 12% higher over the past week.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">ALICE price hovered at $1.06, just in the green over the past 24 hours and more than 20% up in the past seven days.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chromia-chr-hits-milestone-as-my-neighbor-alice-alpha-season-3-goes-live/">Chromia (CHR) hits milestone as My Neighbor Alice Alpha Season 3 goes live</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/chromia-chr-hits-milestone-as-my-neighbor-alice-alpha-season-3-goes-live/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Court denies Binance motion alleging SEC misconduct</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/court-denies-binance-motion-alleging-sec-misconduct/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/court-denies-binance-motion-alleging-sec-misconduct/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 15:48:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Policy and Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/court-denies-binance-motion-alleging-sec-misconduct/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A US judge has said the court cannot wordsmith the SEC and Binance&#8217;s press releases. But in denying the crypto exchange&#8217;s motion, Judge Amy Berman Jackson said either party has to &#8220;adhere to their ethical obligations at all times.&#8221; SEC sued Binance in early June and published a press release alleging commingling of user funds. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/court-denies-binance-motion-alleging-sec-misconduct/">Court denies Binance motion alleging SEC misconduct</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">A US judge has said the court cannot wordsmith the SEC and Binance&rsquo;s press releases.</li>
<li dir="ltr">But in denying the crypto exchange&rsquo;s motion, Judge Amy Berman Jackson said either party has to &ldquo;adhere to their ethical obligations at all times.&rdquo;</li>
<li dir="ltr">SEC sued Binance in early June and published a press release alleging commingling of user funds.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Judge Amy Berman Jackson on Monday June 26 denied a motion filed by crypto exchange Binance that sought to stop the SEC from making public statements on the SEC/Binance case.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/binance/">Binance</a> had alleged that the SEC had published misleading statements that could impact the case and taint the jury pool.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Three days on from the filing, the court pronounced itself on the motion, with Judge Jackson noting that the court cannot &ldquo;wordsmith&rdquo; either party&rsquo;s press releases. Her <a href="https://www.courtlistener.com/docket/67474542/securities-and-exchange-commission-v-binance-holdings-limited/?order_by=desc#minute-entry-347478862" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">order</a> read:</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>While all of the lawyers in this case should adhere to their ethical obligations at all times, it is not apparent that Court intervention to reiterate that point is needed at this time, or that it is necessary or appropriate for the Court to get involved in wordsmithing the parties&rsquo; press releases. Nor is it clear that the agency&rsquo;s public relations efforts to date will materially affect proceedings in this case</em>.&rdquo;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Binance questioned SEC&rsquo;s statements</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Binance&rsquo;s motion followed SEC&rsquo;s press release on June 21 in which the securities regulator had reiterated its allegations of commingling of user funds by the exchange&rsquo;s leadership.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The statements came after the two parties reached an agreement on the handling of assets of Binance.US. The agency had <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-sec-is-seeking-court-order-to-freeze-binance-uss-assets/">filed for a freeze on the exchange&rsquo;s assets</a> suggesting the need to protect US customers.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In its response to the SEC&rsquo;s press release, Binance said the regulator had published misleading facts about Binance and CEO Changpeng Zhao mishandling Binance.US customer funds.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The motion sought orders against the regulator &ndash; specifically the motion wanted Judge Jackson to order counsel to comply with ethical obligations and not to make &ldquo;<em>misleading extrajudicial statements that may materially impact court proceedings</em>.&rdquo;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">&ldquo;Not a great result for Binance&rdquo;</h2>
<p dir="ltr">John Reed Stark, Former Chief, SEC office of Internet Enforcement, <a href="https://twitter.com/JohnReedStark/status/1673400620944859149" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">commented</a> on the court&rsquo;s decision, suggesting that Binance&rsquo;s filing may not have been worth it.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>It seemed so frivolous on its face and more akin to marketing theater than legal argument</em>,&rdquo; he noted.</p>
<p dir="ltr">James &ldquo;MetaLawMan&rdquo; Murphy, a securities lawyer, said the judge&rsquo;s order isn&rsquo;t a great one for Binance &ndash; even if it doesn&rsquo;t impact the merits of its case.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Judge Jackson has issued a brief order denying the <a href="https://twitter.com/binance?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@Binance</a> motion before the SEC filed its response.<br>The judge wrote that it was not necessary to reiterate both side's obligations to comply with ethics rules, and she will not get involved in "wordsmithing the parties' press&hellip;</p>
<p>&mdash; MetaLawMan (@MetaLawMan) <a href="https://twitter.com/MetaLawMan/status/1673433720068657153?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 26, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">Separately, the court set forth a timeline for the early proceedings. Binance will plead its case on September 21, 2023 before the plaintiff presents their legal arguments on 7 November 7, 2023. The court will listen to replies starting December 12.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/court-denies-binance-motion-alleging-sec-misconduct/">Court denies Binance motion alleging SEC misconduct</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/court-denies-binance-motion-alleging-sec-misconduct/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin price action records decoupling from gold and silver</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-price-action-records-decoupling-from-gold-and-silver/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 13:43:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gold]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-price-action-records-decoupling-from-gold-and-silver/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s 30-day correlation with gold is at cycle lows after BTC price action in 2023. BTC has outperformed the precious metal even as its correlation with stocks also fell. Gold traded near $1,928 per ounce while silver price was at $22.94 per ounce on Tuesday morning. Gold continues to hover above $1,900 after its recent [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-price-action-records-decoupling-from-gold-and-silver/">Bitcoin price action records decoupling from gold and silver</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Bitcoin&rsquo;s 30-day correlation with gold is at cycle lows after BTC price action in 2023.</li>
<li dir="ltr">BTC has outperformed the precious metal even as its correlation with stocks also fell.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Gold traded near $1,928 per ounce while silver price was at $22.94 per ounce on Tuesday morning.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/gold/">Gold</a> continues to hover above $1,900 after its recent breakdown from year-to-date highs above $2,052 per ounce threatened a retreat to February lows. But at $1,928 per ounce, gold is negative in the past 30 days and just over 6% higher in the past six months.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Silver prices are also just slightly up at $22.94 per ounce as of writing. However, Silver is down 1.6% in the past 30 days and 3.3% in the red over the past six months.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitcoin decoupling from gold, silver</h2>
<p dir="ltr">On-chain data platform Glassnode has<a href="https://twitter.com/glassnode/status/1673648546103402496" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">&nbsp;<u>shared</u></a> fresh details showing <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">Bitcoin price</a> action has continued to decouple from the metals. In 2023, BTC has reached highs of $31,500 and is 14% up in the past 30 days and +85% YTD.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The correlation with gold and silver has reached near cycle lows for XAU/USD and new cycle low for XAG/USD.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>Local Bitcoin price action has recorded a decoupling from both Gold and Silver, with the 30 day correlation to gold residing near cycle lows of -0.78, whilst the correlation to Silver has reached a cycle low of -0.9 respectively</em>.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Local <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Bitcoin</a> price action has recorded a decoupling from both <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Gold?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Gold</a> and <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Silver?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Silver</a>, with the 30 day correlation to Gold residing near cycle lows of -0.78, whilst the correlation to Silver has reached a cycle low of -0.9 respectively. <a href="https://t.co/066EGsFWNI">pic.twitter.com/066EGsFWNI</a></p>
<p>&mdash; glassnode (@glassnode) <a href="https://twitter.com/glassnode/status/1673648546103402496?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 27, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">Although commodities are likely to see a boost with the upcoming US CB Consumer Confidence report on Tuesday, gold and silver remain largely constrained. The main hurdles are at $1,930 and $23.04 for XAU/USD and XAG/USD respectively.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Meanwhile, BTC is showing resilience above $30k and could rip upwards amid the recent spot ETF related news.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The probability that BTC/USD rises further is highlighted in the chart below by Santiment analysts. They say that following crypto markets&rsquo;s jump to local tops last Friday, expectation among traders has been for a retracement for buy the dip opportunities in the $27k-$29k region.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">&#128552; After <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/crypto?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#crypto</a> markets topped out last Friday, traders came into the start of the week with expecting that prices would continue to retrace &amp; provide opportunities to buy in the $27k-$29k level. High <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/bearish?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#bearish</a> sentiment increases further rise probability. <a href="https://t.co/bEkYCdNqVH">https://t.co/bEkYCdNqVH</a> <a href="https://t.co/PxJQBTN1Us">pic.twitter.com/PxJQBTN1Us</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Santiment (@santimentfeed) <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1673511851165122560?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 27, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">It&rsquo;s a scenario for increased bearish sentiment, which the analysts suggest could be an ingredient for new upward action.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">As CoinJournal <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoins-correlation-with-nasdaq-100-down-to-3-year-low/">reported</a> on Monday, latest data also shows Bitcoin&rsquo;s correlation with the Nasdaq 100 is at a three-year low.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-price-action-records-decoupling-from-gold-and-silver/">Bitcoin price action records decoupling from gold and silver</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chibi Finance allegedly executes $1M rug pull on Arbitrum, CHIBI plummets 98%</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/chibi-finance-allegedly-executes-1m-rug-pull-on-arbitrum-chib-plummets-98/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 12:30:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/chibi-finance-allegedly-executes-1m-rug-pull-on-arbitrum-chib-plummets-98/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Chibi Finance has allegedly executed a $1M rug pull on Layer 2 blockchain Arbitrum. The team has vanished and their social media accounts are inaccessible. Security platform Peckshield says the team channeled the funds via Tornado Cash. Arbitrum-based DeFi project Chibi Finance has disappeared into thin air with $1 million in what is reported to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chibi-finance-allegedly-executes-1m-rug-pull-on-arbitrum-chib-plummets-98/">Chibi Finance allegedly executes $1M rug pull on Arbitrum, CHIBI plummets 98%</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Chibi Finance has allegedly executed a $1M rug pull on Layer 2 blockchain Arbitrum.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The team has vanished and their social media accounts are inaccessible.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Security platform Peckshield says the team channeled the funds via Tornado Cash.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Arbitrum-based <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/defi/">DeFi</a> project Chibi Finance has disappeared into thin air with $1 million in what is reported to be a potential rug pull.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Chibi Finance, which went live only recently on Arbitrum&rsquo;s Layer 2 network, is said to have drained its liquidity pool, vanishing with 555 ether (ETH). At current market prices, that&rsquo;s about $1 million worth of user deposits.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Chibi Finance latest in rug pulls</h2>
<p dir="ltr">According to an <a href="https://twitter.com/PeckShieldAlert/status/1673615238758006786" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">alert</a> by blockchain security and data analystic firm PeckShield, the Chibi Finance team withdrew staked tokens by converting them to ETH and then funneling them to the Ethereum network via the crypto mixing service Tornado Cash.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/PeckShieldAlert?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#PeckShieldAlert</a> Seems like <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Chibifinance?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Chibifinance</a> rugged. ~$1M worth of cryptocurrencies were drained.<br>The stolen funds, which have been swapped for ~555 <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24ETH&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$ETH</a>, were bridged from <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Arbitrum?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Arbitrum</a> to Ethereum. <br>They have already been transferred into Tornado Cash<a href="https://t.co/HmVeZmWJS4">https://t.co/HmVeZmWJS4</a> <a href="https://t.co/1wM8j86fS4">pic.twitter.com/1wM8j86fS4</a></p>
<p>&mdash; PeckShieldAlert (@PeckShieldAlert) <a href="https://twitter.com/PeckShieldAlert/status/1673615238758006786?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 27, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">The Chibi Finance team has allegedly also &ldquo;disappeared&rdquo; with the DeFi projects social media accounts on <a href="https://twitter.com/Chibi_Fi" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Twitter</a> and Telegram deleted. The platform&rsquo;s website is also offline.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Chibi Finance&rsquo;s apparent rug pull adds to the recent spate of bad actors in the Arbitrum and Ethereum ecosystems. In April, zkSync project Merlin allegedly siphoned off $2 million from its users. Meanwhile, Arbitrum-based Swaprun vanished in May, with close to $3 million of user funds in another rug pull.</p>
<p dir="ltr">CHIBI, the native Chibi Finance token, has plummeted following the news. After trading above $1.62 on Monday, CHIB price fell sharply on Tuesday morning to almost zero. Data from CoinGecko shows the crypto token has lost 98.7% of its value in the past 24 hours and currently hovers near $0.017.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chibi-finance-allegedly-executes-1m-rug-pull-on-arbitrum-chib-plummets-98/">Chibi Finance allegedly executes $1M rug pull on Arbitrum, CHIBI plummets 98%</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>SwissOne launches ecosystem fund for IOTA and Shimmer</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/swissone-launches-ecosystem-fund-for-iota-and-shimmer/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 12:25:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[IOTA News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/swissone-launches-ecosystem-fund-for-iota-and-shimmer/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SwissOne Capital launched a major ecosystem fund for IOTA and Shimmer. The fund will invest in the most promising projects in the ecosystem. IOTA and Shimmer received a boost on Tuesday when SwissOne Capital unveiled the first ecosystem fund to support developers. The fund, which is dedicated to IOTA and Shimmer will invest financial resources [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/swissone-launches-ecosystem-fund-for-iota-and-shimmer/">SwissOne launches ecosystem fund for IOTA and Shimmer</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">SwissOne Capital launched a major ecosystem fund for IOTA and Shimmer.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The fund will invest in the most promising projects in the ecosystem.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/iota/"><u>IOTA</u></a> and Shimmer received a boost on Tuesday when SwissOne Capital unveiled the first ecosystem fund to support developers. The fund, which is dedicated to IOTA and Shimmer will invest financial resources to developers working on the ecosystem.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The minimum investment the fund will offer will be 10,000 euros or the equivalent in $MIOTA and $SMR. In a statement, Steffen Bassler, the CEO of SwissOne Capital said:</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;We are excited to launch this fund and offer our clients early access to projects building within the Shimmer and IOTA ecosystem. With ShimmerEVM rolling out, we believe this is the perfect time to launch a dedicated fund. We are committed to working with the Tangle Ecosystem Association to ensure that the fund is managed in the best interests of our clients.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">IOTA is one of the pioneers in distributed ledger technology (DLT). It pioneered a technology known as tangle, which is an open, feeless and scalable ledger, which is designed to support frictionless data and value transfer.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Shimmer, on the other hand, is a layer 1 network that provides staging and validation for the IOTA DLT. Like Polkadot&rsquo;s Kusama, Shimmer makes it possible for developers to build <a href="https://coinjournal.net/glossary/decentralized-applications-dapps/">dApps</a> and then test them before moving them to IOTA&rsquo;s ecosystem. SMR, its native token has over $71 million in market cap and over 249,150 total active addresses.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Shimmer is currently testing its EVM capabilities, as we wrote&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/iotas-defi-ecosystem-inches-closer-with-the-launch-of-the-shimmerevm-test-chain/"><u>here</u></a>. Ethereum Virtual Machine is a piece of software that is able to handle Ethereum smart contracts. It is one of the most popular approaches of improving a network&rsquo;s interoperability. In a note, the founder of IOTA said:</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;With the introduction of EVM-compatible smart contracts, Shimmer and IOTA kick off a new era of growth fueled by crypto-native use cases, primarily in DeFi, NFTs, gaming, and more. We are thrilled to see SwissOne Capital&rsquo;s commitment to investing in projects across the ecosystem and to see SISO grow alongside the community.&rdquo;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy IOTA</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/swissone-launches-ecosystem-fund-for-iota-and-shimmer/">SwissOne launches ecosystem fund for IOTA and Shimmer</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Polygon, Cardano price outlook as major crypto trading platform delists tokens</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/polygon-cardano-price-outlook-as-major-crypto-trading-platform-delists-tokens/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/polygon-cardano-price-outlook-as-major-crypto-trading-platform-delists-tokens/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 11:35:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robinhood]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/polygon-cardano-price-outlook-as-major-crypto-trading-platform-delists-tokens/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Polygon (MATIC) traded around $0.66 on Tuesday and Cardano (ADA) hovered above $0.28. Both tokens are to be delisted from Robinhood app after the SEC labelled them securities. MATIC and ADA fell sharply when Robinhood initially announced it would be ending trading support for the tokens. Robinhood will end its support for a number of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/polygon-cardano-price-outlook-as-major-crypto-trading-platform-delists-tokens/">Polygon, Cardano price outlook as major crypto trading platform delists tokens</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr"><span style="background-color: transparent">Polygon (MATIC) traded around $0.66 on Tuesday and Cardano (ADA) hovered above $0.28.</span></li>
<li>
<div>Both tokens are to be delisted from Robinhood app after the SEC labelled them securities.</div>

</li>
<li dir="ltr">MATIC and ADA fell sharply when Robinhood initially announced it would be ending trading support for the tokens.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Robinhood will end its support for a number of crypto tokens today, June 27 following an announcement made earlier this month. Among the tokens to be delisted are <a href="https://coinjournal.net/polygon/">Polygon (MATIC)</a> and <a href="https://coinjournal.net/cardano/">Cardano (ADA)</a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The prices of both tokens dipped after the crypto trading platform&rsquo;s initial announcement added to the overall negativity triggered by the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC)&rsquo;s lawsuits against crypto exchanges Binance and Coinbase.</p>
<p dir="ltr">What&rsquo;s the price outlook for the two tokens even as Bitcoin (BTC) bids to hold above the psychological $30k level?</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Polygon price outlook</h2>
<p dir="ltr">MATIC price fell 35% over two days when <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/robinhood/">Robinhood</a> announced its delisting on June 9, tanking from near $0.79 to $0.50. While bulls face pressure around $0.66, it&rsquo;s likely a bounce to the $0.75 area could materialise and galvanise buyers.</p>
<p dir="ltr">One of the factors in favour of Polygon bulls is the increased exchange outflows for MATIC. Data shows that more holders have moved tokens to self-custody wallets, the potential impact of which is further reduction in selling pressure.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to crypto analyst Michael van de Poppe, the dip to $0.50 resulted in &ldquo;a chain reaction of liquidations on the long side.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">He<a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoMichNL/status/1673009406542495745" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">&nbsp;<u>notes</u></a> that all these have since been taken up and a breakout is likely. However, MATIC/USD needs to flip $0.75 into support to provide a base for new upside momentum.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><div class="fr-img-space-wrap"><span class="fr-img-caption  fr-fic fr-dib fr-draggable" style="width: 615px"><span class="fr-img-wrap"><a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoMichNL/status/1673009406542495745/photo/1" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/05/27/1687865091580-c0ac42c2-1be2-4774-98b9-dac7b9a1849a.png" style="width: 700px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="700" height="306"><span class="fr-inner">Chart showing key price levels for MATIC/USD. Source:</span></a><a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoMichNL/status/1673009406542495745/photo/1">&nbsp;<u>Michael van de Poppe on Twitter</u></a></span></span>
<h2 class="fr-img-space-wrap2">Cardano price outlook</h2>
</div>
<p dir="ltr">Cardano, like Polygon, fell sharply as the SEC labelled ADA a security earlier this month. ADA lost over 42% of its value in the week between June 5 and June 10, falling from highs of $0.37 to $0.22.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">That was before the recent bounce across cryptocurrencies helped bulls push to $0.30.</p>
<div class="fr-img-space-wrap">
<div class="fr-img-space-wrap"><span class="fr-img-caption fr-fic fr-dib" style="width: 700px"><span class="fr-img-wrap"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/05/27/1687865452053-9587b9ef-2e29-405b-8571-db530210aeba.png" style="width: 700px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="700" height="242"><span class="fr-inner">
<p dir="ltr">Cardano price chart. Source:&nbsp;<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/YLWBDjAv/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">TradingView</a></p>
<p></p></span></span></span>
<p class="fr-img-space-wrap2">But while ADA/USD is up nearly 10% this past week, the losses over the past 30 days amount to 24% at current prices of $0.28. The areas around $0.25 and $0.22 are key should bears strengthen in the short term.</p>
</div>
</div>
<p dir="ltr">Meanwhile, the flipside would have breaking above $0.30 again highlight $0.40 as the next major hurdle.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/polygon-cardano-price-outlook-as-major-crypto-trading-platform-delists-tokens/">Polygon, Cardano price outlook as major crypto trading platform delists tokens</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/polygon-cardano-price-outlook-as-major-crypto-trading-platform-delists-tokens/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chancer set to benefit most from the fast-growing betting industry</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-set-to-benefit-most-from-the-fast-growing-betting-industry/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-set-to-benefit-most-from-the-fast-growing-betting-industry/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 09:07:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNB]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-set-to-benefit-most-from-the-fast-growing-betting-industry/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Chancer betting platform will allow people to set their own odds. People can also bet on anything on Chancer including betting on a friend completing a certain task. Chancer seeks to compete against traditional bookmakers who bet against participants. Since the US Supreme Court struck down the federal ban on sports betting in 2018, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-set-to-benefit-most-from-the-fast-growing-betting-industry/">Chancer set to benefit most from the fast-growing betting industry</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>The Chancer betting platform will allow people to set their own odds.</li>
<li>People can also bet on anything on Chancer including betting on a friend completing a certain task.</li>
<li>Chancer seeks to compete against traditional bookmakers who bet against participants.</li>
</ul>
<p>Since the US Supreme Court struck down the federal ban on sports betting in 2018, more than 30 states and the District of Columbia have legalized sports betting in one way or the other and 10 other states are expected to do so in the near future.</p>
<p>It is not only the United States that has seen an exponential growth in sports betting but a majority of other countries including countries like Kenya in Africa have also witnessed a market boom over the past few years. In 2022, the sports betting market was valued at $83.65 billion and it is projected to surge to 178.68 billion by 2030 according to Polaris Market Research.</p>
<p>However, most sports betting platforms operate as bookmakers and set odds against participants. A new entrant, <a href="https://chancer.com/">Chancer</a>, is seeking to change that by introducing a decentralized social predictive market-making platform allowing people to place bets on any prediction or event and have complete control over their bets.</p>
<p>Chancer, which is leveraging the power of Blockchain technology for decentralization, is currently in development and has already launched the presale of its native cryptocurrency CHANCER. At press time, 36,763,989 CHANCER tokens had been sold in the first stage.</p>
<p>Interested investors can purchase their tokens <a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=media&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal">here</a> using BNB or BUSD (BEP20) tokens.</p>
<h2>Chancer presale timelines</h2>
<p>Before delving into how CHANCER token holders will benefit from the first decentralized predictive market-making platform token, it is important to point out that the CHANCER presale is distributed over 12 stages.</p>
<p>At the time the presale is coming to an end, the price of the token is expected to be $0.021 according to Chancer&rsquo;s presale schedule.</p>
<h2>How CHANCER token holders will benefit</h2>
<p>Token holders will start seeing their benefits immediately after the presale concludes since the token is expected to go live on&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/uniswap/what-is-uniswap/">Uniswap</a>, and a number of centralized <a href="https://coinjournal.net/compare/best-cryptocurrency-exchanges/">crypto exchanges</a>. Holders will therefore be able to trade their tokens or even use them for other DeFi activities including staking to earn a passive income while waiting for the Chancer Mainnet launch scheduled for Q1, 2024.</p>
<p>Once functional, Chancer will allow users to participate in market making, virtual betting, WebRTC-Live Streaming, Share2Earn program, staking, and deployment of Full Validator Nodes; all of which are to be tested before the mainnet launch.</p>
<p>Additionally, those who participate in market making and participate in betting will get fee discounts, which is an incentive to make the platform affordable for those who its frequent users.</p>
<p>The node validators will be able to earn a passive income while bet winners will be rewarded in CHANCER tokens.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-set-to-benefit-most-from-the-fast-growing-betting-industry/">Chancer set to benefit most from the fast-growing betting industry</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-set-to-benefit-most-from-the-fast-growing-betting-industry/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
