<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 19:55:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>JPMorgan CEO Jamie Dimon Reiterates Bearish Stance on Bitcoin and Other Virtual Assets </title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-jamie-dimon-bitcoin/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-jamie-dimon-bitcoin/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 16:19:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jamie dimon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jpm coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jpmorgan]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=232019</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-jamie-dimon-bitcoin/">JPMorgan CEO Jamie Dimon Reiterates Bearish Stance on Bitcoin and Other Virtual Assets </a></p>
<p>Although Jamie Dimon remains a Bitcoin critic, JPMorgan continued to make waves in the blockchain industry.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-jamie-dimon-bitcoin/">JPMorgan CEO Jamie Dimon Reiterates Bearish Stance on Bitcoin and Other Virtual Assets </a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-jamie-dimon-bitcoin/">JPMorgan CEO Jamie Dimon Reiterates Bearish Stance on Bitcoin and Other Virtual Assets </a></p>
<p>While there are many <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> believers confident in the existence of the cryptocurrency, there are also unrepentant BTC critics like <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/jpmorgan-chase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">JPMorgan</a> (NYSE: JPM) CEO <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/jamie-dimon/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Jamie Dimon</a>. The CEO has made several bearish comments on crypto and continues to be vocal about his stance against all virtual currencies. One of his famous criticisms against Bitcoin was in 2017 when he called the top crypto asset a “fraud.” To further his opposition to the digital asset, he added that any JPMorgan trader caught trading BTC would be fired immediately.</p>
<p>Over time, Jamie Dimon has eased his posture about crypto assets but remains oppositional to Bitcoin. Some time ago, he revealed his belief in blockchain technology, noting that emerging technology has value. JPMorgan has also been exploring the blockchain despite the CEO’s stance on cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>Jamie Dimon is particularly against Bitcoin and all it stands for. He reiterated his opinion about Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies while speaking at the company’s 41st annual Healthcare Conference. He referred to digital currency as a speculative “asset” that can never replace real money or become an efficient payment system. JPMorgan’s boss added that crypt had become a standard tool among criminals for illicit activities. As a matter of fact, Dimon said virtual assets are used more for illegal activities than legal ones. The businessman further explained that crypto volatility is why some people invest in them other than acquiring tangible products and investing in services.</p>
<p>In a <a href="https://twitter.com/RasuShrestha/status/1612560300603248640" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">tweet</a>, the Chief Innovation and Commercialization Officer for Atrium Health, Rasu Shreshtha, wrote that Dimon called crypto a “Decentralized Ponzi scheme.” This is the umpteenth time Jamie Dimon will be attacking Bitcoin and other altcoins. The CEO referred to Bitcoin last year as “dirty” and “expensive.” He slammed crypto during the Institute of International Finance meeting held in Wasghton in October 2021. The billionaire stated that he would “never” buy cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>Although Jamie Dimon remains a Bitcoin critic, JPMorgan continued to make waves in the blockchain industry. The company already allows tokenized US dollar deposits with JPM Coin. Coinspeakr also <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpm-tokenize-euro-deposits-nft/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a> in October that the financial services company is creating a payment opportunity for Non-Fungible Tokens. The company <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-visa-blockchain-payment/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">partnered</a> with Visa to unveil a joint blockchain payment gateway. Reports showed that the duo was planning to roll out the payment gateway in multiple countries.</p>
<p>There were also talks on music <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NFT</a> media at JPMorgan.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/2022-crypto-startup-funding/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-jamie-dimon-bitcoin/">JPMorgan CEO Jamie Dimon Reiterates Bearish Stance on Bitcoin and Other Virtual Assets </a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-jamie-dimon-bitcoin/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Startup Funding Down 40% in 2022 to Its Lowest</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/2022-crypto-startup-funding/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/2022-crypto-startup-funding/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 13:34:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investors News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Startups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[a16z]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[celcius network]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[three arrows capital]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=231962</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/2022-crypto-startup-funding/">Crypto Startup Funding Down 40% in 2022 to Its Lowest</a></p>
<p>Although 2022 witnessed a major crash in crypto fundraises, it was still higher in comparison to 2018, 2019, and 2020. Market analysts expect VC investments in crypto to resume by the summer of 2023. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/2022-crypto-startup-funding/">Crypto Startup Funding Down 40% in 2022 to Its Lowest</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/2022-crypto-startup-funding/">Crypto Startup Funding Down 40% in 2022 to Its Lowest</a></p>
<p>The last year of 2022 was full of major collapses and bankruptcies in the crypto space which deeply impacted investor sentiment in the market. As per the latest development, crypto startup projects secured 42.5% less funding in 2022 in comparison to the previous year 2021.</p>
<h2>Crypto Startup Funding</h2>
<p>The year 2021 witnessed one of the biggest bull runs in the history of crypto. Furthermore, there was significant liquidity in the market due to the quantitative easing measures of the central bank.</p>
<p>But the last year of 2022 witnessed one of the major pullbacks in the crypto space leading to a major outflow of investor interest. Several companies had to halt their expansion plans with a few of them shutting down operations entirely.</p>
<p>As per the study by CoinGecko, crypto companies raised $21.26 billion last year, and almost half of it was secured during Q1 2022 when the sector was still in better shape. However, the market sentiment hit a new low in the second half triggered by the collapse of the Terra LUNA ecosystem. This incident alone wiped out $40 billion of investors&#8217; money from the market. The collapse of the Terra ecosystem led to major bankruptcies of giant firms like Three Arrows Capital (3AC) and Celsius Network.</p>
<p>During the third quarter of 2022, the total funds raised stood at just $3.61 billion. In the last quarter, the collapse of the crypto exchange FTX was another major blow to the entire crypto industry. As a result, the crypto firms could collectively raise less than $3 billion. In comparison, the total funds raised during the 2021 crypto bull run were more than $37 billion.</p>
<h2>Why 2022 Was Relatively Still Better</h2>
<p>Despite the major downturn in 2022, the last year was still better than some of the previous years like 2018, 2019, and 2020. Explaining the probable reason behind it, CoinGecko <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/research/publications/crypto-funding-over-time" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">explained</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“The relatively better funding performance in 2022 points to the cryptocurrency industry’s growth over the last five years, supported by more projects securing financial backing and increasing interest from institutional investors.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Top names such as VC giant Andreessen Horowitz (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/a16z/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">a16z</a>) raised secured one of the largest financing in crypto last year at $4.5 billion. A16z announced that they would distribute the capital across blockchain and crypto startups and would also invest in digital assets during the broader bear market.</p>
<p>Other significant investments during the last year include Immutable&#8217;s $500 million developer and venture investment fund, Fireblock&#8217;s $550 million in financing, and Consensys&#8217; $450 million funding round.</p>
<p>David Pakman, managing partner at crypto VC firm CoinFund said that VC firms are still interested in crypto. Just that they are taking more time to do due diligence. VC firms are now demanding stronger investor protection rules. Pakman said that the valuations in the crypto space are also becoming more realistic.</p>
<p>Robert Le, a crypto analyst at the research firm PitchBook expects VC investments to pick up during the summer of 2023. This is because crypto funds now have the obligation to deploy the massive capital they raised during the bull market of 2021. “It’s not going to remain low forever,” he said.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gala-nft-rally/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/2022-crypto-startup-funding/">Crypto Startup Funding Down 40% in 2022 to Its Lowest</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/2022-crypto-startup-funding/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>GALA Surges 140% amid Week-Long NFT Rally</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/gala-nft-rally/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/gala-nft-rally/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 13:30:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ape]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[decentraland]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gala]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sand]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[The Sandbox]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=231997</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gala-nft-rally/">GALA Surges 140% amid Week-Long NFT Rally</a></p>
<p>GALA was the top-gainer among the NFT rally that began last week and was last seen changing hands at $0.042.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gala-nft-rally/">GALA Surges 140% amid Week-Long NFT Rally</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gala-nft-rally/">GALA Surges 140% amid Week-Long NFT Rally</a></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Following a rousing start to the year, there were double-digit <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/gala/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">gains</a> over the past week among gaming and non-fungible token (</span><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">NFT</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">)-linked digital currencies. Notable tokens to experience an early 2023 rally include Gala (GALA), Apecoin (APE), Decentraland (MANA), and The Sandbox (SAND). </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to data from CoinGecko, the general crypto market capitalization is up 6.7% to $884 billion since the turn of the year. So far, this momentum shows no signs of slowing down anytime soon. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As it stands, NFT trading volume has seen a considerable upswing over the past week, increasing 31.56% to $207.358 million.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">GALA is the current rally leader among the top 100 digital currencies by market cap, with a 140% surge since last week. As of press time, the native token powering Gala&#8217;s crypto gaming ecosystem was changing hands at $0.042. This development also represents a 13% increase in value over the last 24 hours. As it stands, GALA is the 98th-largest digital currency by market capitalization. However, despite the crypto&#8217;s commendable weekly gains, it is still down 94.8% from its record high of $0.8248 in November last year. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Coinglass reports that GALA futures positions, which amount to $31.82 million, have been liquidated over the past week. Furthermore, approximately a quarter of those liquidations were long positions, with blown-out short trades constituting the rest. </span></p>
<h2><b>Beyond GALA, BAYC, Other Popular NFT Collections Also Record Week-Long Rally</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Bored Ape Yacht Club (BAYC) underpinning token APE and its upcoming metaverse initiative Otherside also climbed 23.5% over the past week. For example, as of press time, Apecoin is changing hands at $4.87, representing a 4.2% rise over the last 24 hours. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Meanwhile, Bored Ape NFT trading volume soared 32.38% over the past seven days to crest at $18.061 million. This spike in value was enough to cement BAYC&#8217;s position at the summit of the most-traded NFTs over the past week. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On the heels of the recent BAYC rally is another Apecoin-related NFT collection, Mutant Ape Yacht Club. This NFT collection surged 60.75% in trading volume across the past week to $13.310 million. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Beyond GALA and APE&#8217;s week-long nuclear ascent in value, numerous other gaming-adjacent crypto projects also saw serious gains within the same period. For instance, the Decentraland-underpinning token MANA rose 29% to $0.40 over the last seven days. This bullish development also reversed MANA&#8217;s monthly losses, although the coin is still down 89% on a yearly basis. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Sandbox&#8217;s native SAND token gained 26.5% over the same period but as of press time, was trading down 0.5% on the day. The current price of SAND is around $0.51. </span></p>
<h2><b>NFT Trading Volume Increase Set to Continue?</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The recent positive development in the trading of NFTs should come as a welcome relief to investors and observers. Furthermore, many of these market participants&#8217; confidence should be riding high in hopes of a sustained rally. Throughout much of last year, the crypto market wallowed in the pits as contagion crippled most bullish run attempts. However, as the 2023 market continues, the crypto market proves that while it might be down, it is not out.</span></p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/chip-tsmc-record-sales/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gala-nft-rally/">GALA Surges 140% amid Week-Long NFT Rally</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/gala-nft-rally/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chip Manufacturing Giant TSMC Reports Record Sales but Misses Estimates</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/chip-tsmc-record-sales/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/chip-tsmc-record-sales/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 13:16:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[semiconductors]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tsmc]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=231991</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/chip-tsmc-record-sales/">Chip Manufacturing Giant TSMC Reports Record Sales but Misses Estimates</a></p>
<p>As the world’s largest chip manufacturer, TSMC was positioned to bear the brunt of the slowing demands in general.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/chip-tsmc-record-sales/">Chip Manufacturing Giant TSMC Reports Record Sales but Misses Estimates</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/chip-tsmc-record-sales/">Chip Manufacturing Giant TSMC Reports Record Sales but Misses Estimates</a></p>
<p>Taiwanese multinational chip manufacturing giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/tsmc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Taiwan Semiconductor Mfg. Co. Ltd</a> (NYSE: TSM) has reported an impressive sales record for the 2022 financial year. According to the recent <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/world-biggest-chipmaker-tsmc-misses-061454788.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">release</a> by the company, its consolidated sales for the past year came in at  NT$2.26 trillion (US$75.23 billion), up 42.6% from the year-ago period.</p>
<p>Per the results shared, the annual growth was fueled by its performance in the fourth quarter which rose by 2% from the previous quarter. The chipmaker’s fourth quarter revenue was pegged at NT$625.5 billion ($20.6 billion), up 43%, however, this impressive figure came in behind the NT$636 billion projection from analysts.</p>
<p>Per the recently shared report, the company said its December sales soared 24% to NT$192.6 billion. The missed estimate comes as the first for the firm in 2 years, a situation that shows the company is not entirely immune to the current realities of the global economy.</p>
<p>Last year saw record inflationary growth across various economies and a corresponding hike in interest rates from Central Banks further aggravated the financial strain for most firms. With the trend, the purchasing powers of consumers were greatly hampered and this translated to a slowdown in the demand for high-end electronic devices.</p>
<p>As the world’s largest chip manufacturer, TSMC was positioned to bear the brunt of the slowing demands in general. Besides the economy, concerns surrounding China’s zero-COVID-19 policies at a point last year also lend a hand to the company’s revenue estimate miss.</p>
<p>As the sole supplier of the chip <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/apple-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Apple Inc</a> (NASDAQ: AAPL) uses for its iPhones and Mac, the riot from the American giant’s factory over lockdown discrepancies might have also had its undertone in hampering TSMC’s operations.</p>
<h2>TSMC and the Quest to Expand Its Chip Manufacturing Plants</h2>
<p>Over the years, TSMC has maintained a relatively limited number of its manufacturing plants, a move that has continued to threaten its future sustainability agenda. In a bid to change this narrative, the company is looking to diversify its plants’ geographical spread to the United States and Japan.</p>
<p>As <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tsmc-stock-down-3-in-pre-market-company-to-build-12b-chip-factory-in-u-s/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a> earlier by Coinspeaker, the company plans to build a $12 billion chip factory in the United States. The factory, when completed is billed to create as many as 1,600 jobs and it will further reduce the supply chain disruptions that may engulf the global economy as we have seen in the past 3 years.</p>
<p>While the current inflation outlook is still not looking favorable, TSMC may build on its momentum to cut its capital expenditure again this year as it did when it slashed it by 10% to $36 billion last year.</p>
<p>The company’s shares are up by 2.87% to $80.31, paring off the more than 27% loss it accrued last year.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/xiaomi-hesai-us-ipo/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/chip-tsmc-record-sales/">Chip Manufacturing Giant TSMC Reports Record Sales but Misses Estimates</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/chip-tsmc-record-sales/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Xiaomi-Backed Lidar Startup Hesai Planning to File for US IPO</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/xiaomi-hesai-us-ipo/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/xiaomi-hesai-us-ipo/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Darya Rudz]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 13:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[IPO News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[china IPO us]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hesai]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hesai ipo]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hesai technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hesai technology ipo]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=231961</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/xiaomi-hesai-us-ipo/">Xiaomi-Backed Lidar Startup Hesai Planning to File for US IPO</a></p>
<p>The details of the IPO have not been disclosed, but if Hesai proceeds with all the steps on time, it might be the first Chinese company to launch an IPO in the US this year. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/xiaomi-hesai-us-ipo/">Xiaomi-Backed Lidar Startup Hesai Planning to File for US IPO</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/xiaomi-hesai-us-ipo/">Xiaomi-Backed Lidar Startup Hesai Planning to File for US IPO</a></p>
<p>Hesai Technology, the Chinese leader in lidar technology for autonomous driving and ADAS, is planning to file for a US <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-initial-public-offering-ipo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">initial public offering</a> (IPO) as early as next week. According to those familiar with the matter, the startup could raise about $150 million through the IPO.</p>
<p>As reported by <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-01-10/xiaomi-backed-china-lidar-firm-hesai-nearing-us-ipo-filing-sources-say" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Bloomberg</a>, such investment banks and financial services companies as <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/credit-suisse/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Credit Suisse Group AG</a> (SWX: CSGN), <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/goldman-sachs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Goldman Sachs Group Inc</a> (NYSE: GS), and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/morgan-stanley/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Morgan Stanley</a> (NYSE: MS) are currently working with Hesai on its first-time shares offering. The details of the IPO have not been disclosed, but if Hesai proceeds with all the steps on time, it might be the first Chinese company to launch an IPO in the US this year.</p>
<p>Founded in 2014, Hesai Technology is a global leader in lidar technology for autonomous driving and ADAS. It empowers robotics and elevates lives through high-performance, reliable, and low-cost 3D sensors. According to Hesai, it has its customer base spread across more than 90 cities in 40 countries, including leading autonomous driving developers, OEMs, Tier 1 suppliers, and robotics companies. To date, Hesai has raised over $500 million from Xiaomi, Meituan, Bosch, Baidu, Lightspeed, Hillhouse, CPE, Qiming, and other global investors.</p>
<p>Notably, in 2022, Hesai became the first automotive lidar company in the world to exceed 10,000 units in monthly delivery, which is a great milestone for the industry. The company is leading the market, being the first in L4 autonomous driving lidar market share.</p>
<h2>IPOs in 2023: Brighter Year Ahead</h2>
<p>Back in the summer of 2021, both China and the US imposed new rules on Chinese companies seeking to trade on US exchanges, which compromised the valuations of the IPOs. The US securities regulators did not allow Chinese companies to raise money in the United States unless they provided a full explanation of their legal structures and disclosed the risk of Beijing interfering in their businesses. In addition, any Chinese company looking to conduct an IPO on a US stock exchange should have three years of audited financial statements ready in addition to the other disclosure materials required by the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). Meanwhile, Chinese authorities were proposing new rules that would ban companies with large amounts of sensitive consumer data from going public in the US.</p>
<p>As a result, global IPOs fell 44% year-over-year in the first three quarters of 2022. Besides, Chinese companies raised 96% lesser than last year from listings in the US. However, due to the ease of some obstacles, this year might be a bit brighter. Investors are now optimistic, believing that Chinese regulators will go easy on tech firms this year and also introduce measures to boost growth in the industry.</p>
<p>According to China&#8217;s Capital Market Services Group (CMSG), Chinese IPOs will grow steadily, with proceeds rising. The growth will be supported by the optimization of pandemic control measures on the Mainland and various economic measures on stabilizing economic growth and progress.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-10b-investment-chatgpt-creator/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/xiaomi-hesai-us-ipo/">Xiaomi-Backed Lidar Startup Hesai Planning to File for US IPO</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/xiaomi-hesai-us-ipo/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Microsoft in Talks Regarding $10B Investment in ChatGPT Creator</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-10b-investment-chatgpt-creator/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-10b-investment-chatgpt-creator/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 11:49:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Deals News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alphabet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chatgpt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[microsoft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[openai]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=231976</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-10b-investment-chatgpt-creator/">Microsoft in Talks Regarding $10B Investment in ChatGPT Creator</a></p>
<p>Computer software behemoth Microsoft plans to invest a substantial sum in OpenAI – the creator of ChatGPT.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-10b-investment-chatgpt-creator/">Microsoft in Talks Regarding $10B Investment in ChatGPT Creator</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-10b-investment-chatgpt-creator/">Microsoft in Talks Regarding $10B Investment in ChatGPT Creator</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/microsoft-corporation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Microsoft</a> (NASDAQ: MSFT) is <a href="https://www.semafor.com/article/01/09/2023/microsoft-eyes-10-billion-bet-on-chatgpt" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reportedly</a> lining up $10 billion to invest in ChatGPT owner and creator OpenAI. According to people familiar with the matter, the multinational tech corporation is talking with OpenAI regarding this investment. Should the deal scale through, Microsoft could own up to 49% of OpenAI. Semafor reports that the deal incorporates funding from other venture firms, which will value OpenAI at $29 billion, including the new investment. In addition, other investors could collectively own another 49% of OpenAI, with the platform’s non-profit parent receiving the remaining 2%.</p>
<p>Reports also state that a profit cap varies for each set of investors, which is unusual for venture deals. However, the terms and the investment amount could change, and the deal could fall apart.</p>
<p>Documents pertinent to the deal were sent to prospective investors in recent weeks. However, whether the deal materialized at its originally targeted time scale for the end of last year remains to be determined.</p>
<h2>Current Terms of Proposed Microsoft Deal with ChatGPT Owner</h2>
<p>The funding terms of the Microsoft-OpenAI deal would see the tech giant earn 75% of the ChatGPT creator’s profits for a while. This proceeds realization structure would only end after Microsoft has recouped its initial investment once OpenAI starts making money on ChatGPT. Furthermore, the artificial intelligence research laboratory could also figure out how to monetize other products, including the image creation tool Dall-E.</p>
<p>The deal does not specify whether any money spent by OpenAI on Microsoft’s cloud-computing arm would count towards offsetting its account.</p>
<p>Previous reports stated that OpenAI plans to facilitate the sale of shares by employees and early investors at a $29 billion valuation. Furthermore, at the time, venture capital firms, including Thrive Capital and Founders Fund, were purchasing shares from existing shareholders.</p>
<p>According to <a href="https://www.theinformation.com/articles/openai-valued-at-nearly-20-billion-in-advanced-talks-with-microsoft-for-more-funding" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">The Information</a>, last October, Microsoft was in talks with OpenAI to increase its stake in the platform. At the time, the computer software giant already had a $1 billion cash and cloud credits outlay in OpenAI since 2019.</p>
<p>Microsoft also intends to integrate its office suite services, such as Word, Outlook, and PowerPoint with ChatGPT’s functionalities.</p>
<h2>Other Ongoing Microsoft Exertions</h2>
<p><a href="https://www.theinformation.com/articles/microsoft-and-openai-working-on-chatgpt-powered-bing-in-challenge-to-google" target="_blank" rel="noopener">The Information</a> also reported last week that Microsoft plans to launch a version of its Bing search engine using ChatGPT’s AI. The prominent personal computers and software company could launch the new feature before the end of March. Furthermore, with this launch, Microsoft intends to challenge Google, a wildly popular search engine owned by <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/alphabet-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Alphabet</a> (NASDAQ: GOOGL).</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Microsoft still <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-official-hopes-metaverse/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">harbors high hopes</a> for the metaverse as the company angles to be among its leading pioneers. Microsoft chief strategy officer Henry Bzeih recently predicted that metaverse adoption would quicken in the years to come. According to Bzeih, the world would gravitate towards a more profound virtual arena. He also said that a hybrid prototype would hold much appeal for customers and corporate relationships.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/virgin-orbit-shares-failed-space-mission/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-10b-investment-chatgpt-creator/">Microsoft in Talks Regarding $10B Investment in ChatGPT Creator</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-10b-investment-chatgpt-creator/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Virgin Orbit Shares Slump 27% in Pre-Market after Its Failed Space Mission</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/virgin-orbit-shares-failed-space-mission/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/virgin-orbit-shares-failed-space-mission/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 11:45:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wall Street]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[spacex]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[virgin galactic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[virgin orbit]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=231921</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/virgin-orbit-shares-failed-space-mission/">Virgin Orbit Shares Slump 27% in Pre-Market after Its Failed Space Mission</a></p>
<p>The news of the mission’s failure did not augur well with the firm’s investors as reflected in its stock performance.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/virgin-orbit-shares-failed-space-mission/">Virgin Orbit Shares Slump 27% in Pre-Market after Its Failed Space Mission</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/virgin-orbit-shares-failed-space-mission/">Virgin Orbit Shares Slump 27% in Pre-Market after Its Failed Space Mission</a></p>
<p>Small satellites launcher Virgin Orbit Holdings Inc (NASDAQ: VORB) has recorded a massive slump in its share price following its failed space mission from the United Kingdom. As <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/01/09/virgin-orbit-stock-plummets-after-uk-launch-failure.html">reported</a> by CNBC, the company’s rocket which was meant to launch from Newquay, England would have delivered nine satellites to earth’s orbit had the space flight been successful.</p>
<h2>Virgin Orbit&#8217;s Space Mission</h2>
<p>Virgin Orbit’s Webcast revealed the LauncherOne rocket was actually released and fired its engine, a move that made it tweet after the launch saying the rocket “successfully reached Earth orbit.”</p>
<p>Virgin Orbit makes use of modified 747 jets to deliver its satellites to space. It releases its attached rockets mid-air, a unique way of launching these space crafts into space. Less than an hour when it made the tweet, the company shared that the rockets had an anomaly and could not reach earth’s orbit as planned.</p>
<p>The company also revealed it had deleted the first tweet and that it is investigating the flight data in a bid to fully understand what went wrong the company promised to share more details when it finally uncovers them. As a relief to the public, the company said the 747 jet and its crew safely returned to Spaceport Cornwall in southwest England.</p>
<p>Virgin Orbit was founded in 2021 and is not in any way new to failed missions. Since its inception, the company has conducted a total of 6 missions and this latest represents its second failed attempt in all. The company notably soft-pedaled on its space program in 2022 and launched only 2 missions, a far cry from the 4 to 6 it promised to launch at the beginning of the year.</p>
<p>The news of the mission’s failure did not augur well with the firm’s investors as reflected in its stock performance. The shares closed Monday’s session at $1.93, down by 8.53%. In today’s Pre-Market, the shares have plunged by an additional 27.98%.</p>
<h2>Virgin Orbit to Glean Insights from Virgin Galactic</h2>
<p>The business of space crafts remains a very complicated venture that it is only undertaken by a handful of companies around the world. Of those making buzz in recent times including <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/elon-musk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Elon Musk</a>’s <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/spacex/">SpaceX</a> and Jeff Bezos’ Blue Origin, Sir <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/richard-branson/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Richard Branson</a>’s <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/virgin-galactic/">Virgin Galactic Holdings Inc</a> (NYSE: SPCE) also ranks as a dominant player.</p>
<p>Virgin Orbit is a spin-off of the British Virgin Group as much as Virgin Galactic is, and in terms of development, the latter is making significant headways in its technology that the former can glean insights from.</p>
<p>While these companies remain under the same umbrella, they typically work autonomously, however, with Virgin Group the ranking largest shareholder, solidified with its latest <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/11/07/virgin-orbit-q3-results-25-million-raise-revised-outlook.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">$71 million funding</a> for the firm, the two rocket-building entities can share insights to prevent the prevalence of related mishaps in the coming future.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nepal-anti-crypto-policy/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/virgin-orbit-shares-failed-space-mission/">Virgin Orbit Shares Slump 27% in Pre-Market after Its Failed Space Mission</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/virgin-orbit-shares-failed-space-mission/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nepal Issues Yet Another Anti-Crypto Policy</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nepal-anti-crypto-policy/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nepal-anti-crypto-policy/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 11:42:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[china]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto adoption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto ban]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nepal]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=231904</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nepal-anti-crypto-policy/">Nepal Issues Yet Another Anti-Crypto Policy</a></p>
<p>Nepal has asked ISPs and email providers to expressly shut down everything that could propagate crypto in any way.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nepal-anti-crypto-policy/">Nepal Issues Yet Another Anti-Crypto Policy</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nepal-anti-crypto-policy/">Nepal Issues Yet Another Anti-Crypto Policy</a></p>
<p>Nepal has taken another major step to ensure that crypto and blockchain technology does not see the light of day within its jurisdiction. To this end, Nepal&#8217;s Telecommunications Authority has ordered that internet service providers (ISPs) must immediately clamp down on all crypto-related activities on the internet.</p>
<p>Per the <a href="https://nta.gov.np/en/notice-20230108/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">instruction</a>, the regulator asked the ISPs to expressly shut down everything that could propagate crypto in any way. That includes every crypto-based app, website, and even online network.</p>
<h2>Nepal Keen on Shutting Down Crypto Permanently</h2>
<p>It is worth mentioning that the latest move is only further proof of the country&#8217;s not-so-friendly stance on crypto.</p>
<p>Recall that in September 2021, the apex bank of the country banned all crypto-based activities including mining and trading. And to ensure that the ban is effective enough, Nepal began asking the public for information about anyone still carrying out illegalities by April 2022. For what it&#8217;s worth, cryptocurrency became one such &#8220;illegal activity&#8221; after its earlier ban.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the latest instruction also threatens legal actions against any ISPs or email service providers found wanting in the area of compliance. Therefore, all such platforms that are involved are expected to ensure that no crypto-related activities take place on their platforms.</p>
<h2>Threat to Crypto Adoption?</h2>
<p>Without a doubt, Nepal stands among the top 10 countries that are known to be very skeptical of crypto. These countries, including <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-backs-national-digital-yuan/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">China</a>, Algeria, Morocco, and others placed an outright ban on all things crypto. However, the ban appears not to be as effective as expected thus far. Especially in Nepal.</p>
<p>Despite Nepal&#8217;s best efforts to curb crypto-related activities, it seems they are actually on the rise. According to Chainalysis&#8217; Global Crypto Adoption Index for 2022, Nepal came up 16th, ahead of the UK, and Indonesia.</p>
<p>In the recent instruction issued to ISPs, Nepal also attested to this, claiming that virtual currency transactions have been &#8220;increasing in recent days.&#8221;</p>
<p>Without a doubt, Nepal gives a point of argument to those that will say that there is no stopping the global adoption of crypto. At least, for now. However, it remains to be seen whether or not, the new policy will significantly impact adoption in the country.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sanctions-inflow-tornado-cash/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nepal-anti-crypto-policy/">Nepal Issues Yet Another Anti-Crypto Policy</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nepal-anti-crypto-policy/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sanctions Reduce Total Inflow of Tornado Cash by 68%</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sanctions-inflow-tornado-cash/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sanctions-inflow-tornado-cash/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sanaa Sharma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 11:28:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ofac]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tornado.cash]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=231901</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sanctions-inflow-tornado-cash/">Sanctions Reduce Total Inflow of Tornado Cash by 68%</a></p>
<p>In the most recent report, Chainalysis research suggested that the illegal use of Tornado Cash was essentially associated with crypto hacks and scams, with an approximate average of thirty-four percent of all inflows.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sanctions-inflow-tornado-cash/">Sanctions Reduce Total Inflow of Tornado Cash by 68%</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sanctions-inflow-tornado-cash/">Sanctions Reduce Total Inflow of Tornado Cash by 68%</a></p>
<p>Tornado Cash, an open-source, decentralized cryptocurrency tumbler, which was recently in news for its conjectured role in the laundering of criminal proceeds, has been crippled after the levying of sanctions. The decentralized mixer, was, however, not completely put out of usage by the regulatory conduct.</p>
<p>The crypto mixer&#8217;s alleged malpractice was disclosed on August 8th last year by the Office of Foreign Assets Control (OFAC). In a report on January 9th, it was explained that while the sanctions have been able to reduce the inflow of Tornado Cash by sixty-eight percent in the past month, it is still operating and in use.</p>
<p>Since the firm is a smart-contract-based decentralized platform, no one person or institution can force the company to shut down the operations conveniently. The <a href="https://blog.chainalysis.com/reports/how-2022-crypto-sanction-designations-affected-crypto-crime/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a>, published by Chainalysis, also provided an example of darknet marketplace Hydra, which on the other hand, witnessed its cryptocurrency inflows dive to zero after German Police froze its servers as a result of the rulings. Even though the sanction was implemented on Tornado Cash with its front-end website taken down, the smart contracts can function indefinitely, which means anyone will be able to utilize it at any point in time. This eventually leads to another conclusion that decentralized services seem to be more of a tool that disincentivizes the service&#8217;s utility instead of completely pulling the plug on its usage.</p>
<p>OFAC, however, reprimanded Tornado Cash in August last year for issues regarding people allegedly using the mixer to launder billions worth of crypto since 2019, which also comprised the $455 million stolen by the North Korea-affiliated Lazarus Group.</p>
<p>The agency modified the sanctions in November as it paused the platform for allowing hostile cyber activities, which also backed the North Korean weapons of mass destruction program.</p>
<p>In the most recent report, Chainalysis research suggested that the illegal use of Tornado Cash was essentially associated with crypto hacks and scams, with an approximate average of thirty-four percent of all inflows. Even though the mixer wasn&#8217;t put out of business completely, the sanctions have scared people out of using the company platform.</p>
<p>This very week, another distinct report from blockchain security company SlowMist also described the kind of money that made rounds in a company like Tornado Cash. According to the company&#8217;s research, Ether worth $1.62 Billion was submitted within the platform during the previous year, with <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ether</a> worth $1.7 billion taken out.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-businesses-ledgerx-buyers/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sanctions-inflow-tornado-cash/">Sanctions Reduce Total Inflow of Tornado Cash by 68%</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sanctions-inflow-tornado-cash/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>FTX Businesses Like LedgerX Draw Interest from More than 100 Potential Buyers</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-businesses-ledgerx-buyers/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-businesses-ledgerx-buyers/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 11:01:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx.us]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[kroll]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ledgerx]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=231878</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-businesses-ledgerx-buyers/">FTX Businesses Like LedgerX Draw Interest from More than 100 Potential Buyers</a></p>
<p>FTX debtors have prioritized selling four businesses owned by the company, however, the US bankruptcy trustee in FTX’s case has argued that FTX has provided very little information on what's actually being sold. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-businesses-ledgerx-buyers/">FTX Businesses Like LedgerX Draw Interest from More than 100 Potential Buyers</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-businesses-ledgerx-buyers/">FTX Businesses Like LedgerX Draw Interest from More than 100 Potential Buyers</a></p>
<p>In the new legal filing of FTX&#8217;s bankruptcy case, more than 117 buyers have shown interest in purchasing the assets and businesses of the crypto exchange <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a>. It&#8217;s almost two months since crypto exchange FTX <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-bankruptcy-case-kroll-claims/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">filed</a> for bankruptcy in November 2022.</p>
<p>The crypto exchange&#8217;s bankruptcy filing includes more than 100 entities. As per the previous reports, FTX owes a total of $3.1 billion to its top 50 creditors. In this bankruptcy process, lawyers who are representing the FTX debtors have prioritized selling four businesses which include LedgerX, Embed, FTX Japan, and FTX Europe.</p>
<p>In a legal filing on Sunday, January 8, attorney Kevin Cofsky noted that all these four entities are relatively independent of FTX and their value could decrease during the bankruptcy case if not sold. Cofsky is currently a partner at investment bank Perella Weinberg Partner, which represents FTX US and other affiliate firms that have filed for bankruptcy protection.</p>
<p>Although 117 entities have shown interest, none of them have put in a firm offer to date. The debtors, however, have entered into a confidentiality agreement with 59 of these entities. As per the latest situation, 50 parties have shown interest in Embed, other 56 parties have shown interest in LedgerX, 41 have shown interest in FTX Japan, and 40 have shown interest in FTX Europe.</p>
<p>The initial hearing for the sales shall happen on Wednesday, January 11, However, the number of interested parties and other moving parts could affect the timing of the bankruptcy proceedings.</p>
<h2>Why Selling These FTX Businesses Is an Uphill Task</h2>
<p>In the filing over the last weekend, Andrew Vara, the US bankruptcy trustee in FTX’s case, argued that the crypto exchange has provided very little information on what is being sold. For each of the four entities, Vara said that crypto exchange FTX hasn&#8217;t outlined the financial affairs including assets and liabilities.</p>
<p>Vara <a href="https://restructuring.ra.kroll.com/FTX/Home-DownloadPDF" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Without these filings, there is no information regarding the nature or value assets of the Debtors whose businesses the Debtors seek to sell&#8221;.</p></blockquote>
<p>He further called for an independent investigation into the businesses before selling them. Vara said that “there is a serious concern” about these entities being involved in FTX&#8217;s bankruptcy and holding-related information. He added:</p>
<blockquote><p>“The sale of potentially valuable causes of action against the Debtors’ directors, officers and employees, or any other person or entity, should not be permitted when there has been serious allegations of wrongdoing, and no investigation yet into the scope of such wrongdoing, or the persons and entities that may have been involved”.</p></blockquote>
<p>Read other business news <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/business/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/morgan-stanley-bitcoin-market-gbtc/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-businesses-ledgerx-buyers/">FTX Businesses Like LedgerX Draw Interest from More than 100 Potential Buyers</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-businesses-ledgerx-buyers/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>