<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 18:14:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Aave V3 launches on Ethereum layer-2 network Metis</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/aave-v3-launches-on-ethereum-layer-2-network-metis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 18:14:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Aave News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/aave-v3-launches-on-ethereum-layer-2-network-metis/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Aave V3&#8217;s launch on Metis follows a community vote that went live earlier this month. According to the Metis team, there are various ways in which the Aave V3 integration will benefit ecosystem users. The DeFi protocol&#8217;s V3 is also live on Avalanche, Polygon, Optimism and Arbitrum. Aave, a decentralized liquidity protocol, has deployed on [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/aave-v3-launches-on-ethereum-layer-2-network-metis/">Aave V3 launches on Ethereum layer-2 network Metis</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Aave V3&rsquo;s launch on Metis follows a community vote that went live earlier this month.</li>
<li dir="ltr">According to the Metis team, there are various ways in which the Aave V3 integration will benefit ecosystem users.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The DeFi protocol&rsquo;s V3 is also live on Avalanche, Polygon, Optimism and Arbitrum.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/aave/">Aave</a>, a decentralized liquidity protocol, has deployed on the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/ethereum/">Ethereum</a> layer-2 scaling platform Metis, offering a range of decentralized finance (DeFi) features and products to its ecosystem.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The launch on the Metis Layer-2 comes after a community proposal for the zero-knowledge (zk) proof EVM, which enables Aave governance to activate the Aave V3 Metis pool by completing the initial setup and listing WETH, USDC, USDT, DAI, and METIS.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>The integration of Aave Protocol V3 brings enhanced capital efficiency with valuable new security and risk mitigation features</em>,&rdquo; Metis co-founder Kevin Liu <a href="https://metisdao.medium.com/aave-v3-now-available-on-metis-6e403e74b104" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">said</a>.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Capital efficiency for users</h2>
<p dir="ltr">V3 integration offers numerous benefits to ecosystem users, with network speed and security enhanced. Users will also take advantage of features such as lending and borrowing of assets with less collateral.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">This deployment will enable efficient capital markets in Metis, a key component for building and sustaining a Web3 Economy.</p>
<p>Users and builders will be able to enjoy DeFi composability, fostering a more diverse, complete and collaborative ecosystem&#128154;</p>
<p>&mdash; Metis &#127807; (@MetisDAO) <a href="https://twitter.com/MetisDAO/status/1655617476074393601?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">May 8, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">The launch of Aave V3 on Metis also means DeFi users can now generate yield easily via various supported assets even as they tap into enhanced risk management tools and reduced transaction fees through gas optimization. Overall, the integration brings more capital efficiency for Metis users and developers, the latter also accessing key tools for innovating decentralised applications.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Aave is a widely used DeFi protocol, boasting over $5.24 billion in total value locked (TVL), according to data from <a href="https://defillama.com/protocol/aave" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">DeFiLlama</a>.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The protocol&rsquo;s V3 version deployed on the Ethereum mainnet in January 2023 after successful launches on various Ethereum layer-2 protocols, including Polygon, Avalanche, Arbitrum, and Optimism.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/aave-v3-launches-on-ethereum-layer-2-network-metis/">Aave V3 launches on Ethereum layer-2 network Metis</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase is ‘not’ leaving the U.S. after all</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-is-not-leaving-the-u-s-after-all/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wajeeh Khan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 16:21:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Interview]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=138837</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>CEO Brian Armstrong says Coinbase won&#8217;t relocate overseas. The crypto exchange is interested in investing more in the UAE. Coinbase stock is up close to 70% for the year at writing. Coinbase Global Inc is in focus this morning after CEO Brian Armstrong confirmed that the crypto company was not considering leaving the United States. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-is-not-leaving-the-u-s-after-all/">Coinbase is ‘not’ leaving the U.S. after all</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>CEO Brian Armstrong says Coinbase won&rsquo;t relocate overseas.</li>
<li>The crypto exchange is interested in investing more in the UAE.</li>
<li>Coinbase stock is up close to 70% for the year at writing.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/coinbase/">Coinbase Global Inc</a> is in focus this morning after CEO Brian Armstrong confirmed that the crypto company was not considering leaving the United States.</p>
<blockquote><p>Coinbase is not going to relocate overseas. We&rsquo;re always going to have a U.S. presence.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Armstrong condemns SEC for being anti-crypto</h2>
<p>Armstrong continued to criticise the Securities and Exchange Commission, though, for regulatory uncertainty that&rsquo;s leaving the U.S. behind in the crypto space.</p>
<blockquote><p>The SEC is a bit of an outlier here. There&rsquo;s kind of a lone crusade, if you will, with Gary Gensler, the chair there, and he has taken a more anti-crypto view for some reason.</p></blockquote>
<p>The crypto market news arrives only days after Coinbase Global <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2023/05/04/coinbase-earnings-q1-2023-expectations/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a> its financial results for the first quarter that handily topped Street estimates.</p>
<p>Coinbase stock is up nearly 70% for the year at writing.</p>
<h2>Coinbase Global Inc to invest more in the UAE</h2>
<p>The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission is yet to officially respond to his comments on Monday.</p>
<p>CEO Armstrong had first <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/04/18/coinbase-could-move-away-from-us-if-no-regulatory-clarity-ceo-brian-armstrong/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">signalled</a> the possibility of relocating last month, weeks after the crypto exchange received a &ldquo;Wells Notice&rdquo; from the SEC. On CNBC&rsquo;s &ldquo;<a href="https://www.cnbc.com/video/2023/05/08/uae-putting-out-clear-rulebook-on-crypto-regulation-coinbase-ceo.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Capital Connection</a>&rdquo;, he said today:</p>
<blockquote><p>I don&rsquo;t think [Gary Gensler] is trying to regulate the industry as much as curtail it. He&rsquo;s created some lawsuits, and I think it&rsquo;s quite unhelpful for the industry in the U.S. writ large.</p></blockquote>
<p>The chief executive also confirmed that Coinbase was interested in investing more in the United Arab Emirates. He lauded European Union and the United Kingdom for welcoming legislations around cryptocurrencies as well.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-is-not-leaving-the-u-s-after-all/">Coinbase is ‘not’ leaving the U.S. after all</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Should you trade Metacade in May, even as Binance comes under pressure?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/should-you-trade-metacade-in-may-even-as-binance-comes-under-pressure/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/should-you-trade-metacade-in-may-even-as-binance-comes-under-pressure/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Motiur Rahman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 15:39:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technical Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/should-you-trade-metacade-in-may-even-as-binance-comes-under-pressure/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Metacade is correcting after claiming a high above $0.045 The token could benefit from increased listings and market events facing Binance MCADE is a potential buy as a support zone develops around $0.026 Metacade is now entering an exciting phase that could make a significant difference. That is becoming available to a large number of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/should-you-trade-metacade-in-may-even-as-binance-comes-under-pressure/">Should you trade Metacade in May, even as Binance comes under pressure?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Metacade is correcting after claiming a high above $0.045</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The token could benefit from increased listings and market events facing Binance</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">MCADE is a potential buy as a support zone develops around $0.026</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=invezz&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=price_prediction" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade</u></a> is now entering an exciting phase that could make a significant difference. That is becoming available to a large number of investors after major listings on Uniswap, BitMart, and MEXC.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">But even after listing on these exchanges, the token of the arcade platform has slowed down. As of press time, it exchanged hands at $0.0269, compared to its highest price of $0.045 at the start of the month. Is this a good opportunity to buy, or should investors stay away?</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Binance on US probe for averting sanctions to Russia</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Crypto markets could once again be staring at a red light. The world&rsquo;s largest crypto exchange Binance is under probe by the US Justice Department for possible subversions of sanctions placed against Russia.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Reports indicate that the US regulators want to know if Binance helped Russian customers move money and overcome sanctions.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Binance investigation could be monumental to crypto should US officials find the exchange guilty of the wrongdoing. As the leading exchange, increased scrutiny could spark market fears and potentially trigger fund withdrawals, as it has happened in the past.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Another potential impact is client shifts to decentralized exchanges like Uniswap. This happened when FTX collapsed in November 2022, which saw huge inflows into DEXs. Whether these two possibilities are bound to happen is highly speculative. But one thing is for sure should it occur. Tokens that are listed on DEXs like Metacade will benefit from the investor shift.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>What is Metacade, and what uniqueness is it offering?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade is a Web 3.0 community hub allowing gamers, developers, and crypto fans to collaborate. The platform wants to become the biggest gameFi arcade that is community governed. Investors earn through different methods &ndash; Create2Earn, Compete2Earn, and Work2Earn. They can also stake the native token to grow their bottom lines.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Since its launch and during the presale, Metacade has witnessed strong investor interest. Thanks to its robust earnings mechanics, Metacade promises to be a leader in the Web 3.0 space that is growing exponentially. The platform aims for a thriving ecosystem for its community. As such, it has committed to initiatives like Metagrants that will support new projects and applications. A platform launchpad, game testing, and advertisements are also expected to make Metacade a self-sustaining ecosystem.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Metacade more than doubles in price after exchange listings</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">The uniqueness of Metacade has helped the token&rsquo;s presale to sell out quickly. Now, the token is at the stage of exchange listings and has successfully debuted on Uniswap, BitMart, and MEXC Global.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As analysts had projected, the price of MCADE increased exponentially on the listing. At the beginning of May, the price rose above $0.045. The token&rsquo;s price during the final presale phase was $0.0.020, meaning it has more than doubled in value.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The price has now cooled, allowing investors to buy before more exchange listings follow. Let&rsquo;s look at how the price could behave at the current level.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>MCADE &ndash; a potential opportunity in May?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">As previously pointed out, MCADE is in a correction phase. This is a normal occurrence for every token or financial instrument after a prolonged uptrend. However, investors know corrections offer a chance to buy an asset at a lower price and ride the uptrend with a lower risk-return ratio.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade has been making these corrections. Each time, it has claimed a higher high and higher low. That means the token is still on an uptrend, and the correction could be an opportunity to buy.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">For instance, if we look at the current price, MCADE has held to the level for the past 3 days. It means potential support is developing around $0.026. If this level holds, it could be the perfect zone to buy MCADE in May. Considering the token is already available for trading on three exchanges, trading volumes could build up, and MCADE could claim a new high.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/should-you-trade-metacade-in-may-even-as-binance-comes-under-pressure/">Should you trade Metacade in May, even as Binance comes under pressure?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/should-you-trade-metacade-in-may-even-as-binance-comes-under-pressure/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>OKX plans to open an office in Turkey</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/okx-plans-to-open-an-office-in-turkey/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/okx-plans-to-open-an-office-in-turkey/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 15:33:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/okx-plans-to-open-an-office-in-turkey/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>OKX President Hong Fang said in a press release that the expansion is a big step towards empowering users. The exchange expects the new office in place over coming months. OKX was founded in 2017 and offers spot, margin and derivatives trading for its customers across the world. OKX, one of the largest crypto exchange [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/okx-plans-to-open-an-office-in-turkey/">OKX plans to open an office in Turkey</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">OKX President Hong Fang said in a press release that the expansion is a big step towards empowering users.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The exchange expects the new office in place over coming months.</li>
<li dir="ltr">OKX was founded in 2017 and offers spot, margin and derivatives trading for its customers across the world.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">OKX, one of the largest crypto exchange platforms and a leading Web3 company, plans to expand its global presence with a new office in Turkey.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Seychelles-based crypto platform was founded in 2017 and has grown to become one of the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/compare/best-cryptocurrency-exchanges/">best crypto exchanges</a> in the world. The firm has millions of customers and offers access to spot, margin and derivatives markets for hundreds of crypto tokens. The company also offers DeFi, gaming dApps and an NFT marketplace.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In the <a href="https://www.okx.com/learn/okx-to-expand-global-presence-with-tuerkiye-office" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">press release</a> published on Monday, OKX said it plans to have the office in operation in coming months.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>Opening an office in T&uuml;rkiye will be a crucial step for OKX as we move from a trust-based system to one that is trustless and empowers users to take control of their financial future. T&uuml;rkiye is an important market for us, and we&rsquo;re excited to build strong relationships with our users and contribute to the development of its crypto ecosystem</em>,&rdquo; OKX President Hong Fang said in a statement.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">OKX execs to speak at Blockchain Economy Istanbul Summit 2023</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The OKX team revealed the plans ahead of the Blockchain Economy Istanbul Summit 2023, with the exchange being a Title Sponsor and Premium Partner. The company&rsquo;s President Hong Fang, Chief Innovation Officer Jason Lau and Chief Marketing Officer Haider Rafique are set to be keynote speakers and panelists at the summit expected to run from 8-11 May, 2023.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The summit is Eurasia&rsquo;s largest blockchain event and the 8th&nbsp;edition in Istanbul will feature various crypto industry players, including investors, entrepreneurs and developers. Key topics will include Web3 and blockchain innovation.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Crypto ownership in Turkey has increased in the last few years, with the country currently home to over 13.6 million crypto owners. According to estimates, that&rsquo;s 16% of Turkey&rsquo;s population &ndash; making the country one of those with the largest number of people owning cryptocurrencies.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/okx-plans-to-open-an-office-in-turkey/">OKX plans to open an office in Turkey</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/okx-plans-to-open-an-office-in-turkey/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>AltSignals (ASI) token could surge as meme coin trading volume reaches a two-year high</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-asi-token-could-surge-as-meme-coin-trading-volume-surges-to-a-two-year-high/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 14:58:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-asi-token-could-surge-as-meme-coin-trading-volume-surges-to-a-two-year-high/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways Meme coin trading volume reached a two-year high last week. The milestones come as investors poured funds into PEPE, POOH, and other meme tokens. AltSignals&#8217; ASI token could be a big winner thanks to its utility in the trading ecosystem. The past few weeks have truly been the meme coin season. Meme coins, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-asi-token-could-surge-as-meme-coin-trading-volume-surges-to-a-two-year-high/">AltSignals (ASI) token could surge as meme coin trading volume reaches a two-year high</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Meme coin trading volume reached a two-year high last week.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The milestones come as investors poured funds into PEPE, POOH, and other meme tokens.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals&rsquo; ASI token could be a big winner thanks to its utility in the trading ecosystem.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">The past few weeks have truly been the meme coin season. Meme coins, especially those on the Ethereum network, have witnessed massive adoption over the past few weeks.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Pepe, POOH, and&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/pawswap-price-plunge-as-trillions-of-paw-are-staked/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Pawswap</u></a> are some of the most popular meme coins that launched in recent weeks and recorded massive profits. With the meme coin mania rising again, more traders could be looking to trade the coins and other cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals could play an important role in the ecosystem thanks to the various trading products and solutions it offers to traders.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">A surge in meme coin trading volume</h2>
<p dir="ltr">According to recent research by&nbsp;<a href="https://dune.com/j1002/meme-narrative-craze" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Dune Analytics</u></a>, the trading volume of meme coins is now at a two-year high.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The report revealed that the cryptocurrency market recorded a $2.3 billion in meme coin trading volume last week. This represents a six-fold rise from the preceding week&rsquo;s $387 million. It is also the highest meme coin trading volume recorded since May 2021.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Top of the pile is Pepecoin (PEPE), a g-themed token launched last month. With a total supply of 420 trillion, Pepecoin surpassed $1 billion in market cap last week and eventually reached its all-time high of $1.82 billion.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">In addition to PEPE, other low-cap meme tokens, including, DINO, WSB, CHAD and 4TOKEN, rose by hundreds of percentages over the past two weeks.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The rising interest in meme coins could lead to more interest in the cryptocurrency market over the next few months.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">An increase in the total cryptocurrency market cap</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The cryptocurrency market cap has increased since the start of the year and currently stands above $1.1 trillion. The increasing demand for meme coins could translate into the broader cryptocurrency market.</p>
<p dir="ltr">If that happens, the cryptocurrency market cap could record further growth over the next few weeks and months. The total cryptocurrency market cap is still down by more than 50% from the all-time high of $3 trillion recorded in November 2021.</p>
<p dir="ltr">With an increase in the total cryptocurrency market cap, we could see more traders enter the market and a surge in trading activities.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is AltSignals?</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://token.altsignals.io/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=invezz&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=investment_opportunity" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>AltSignals</u></a> is a trading platform designed to provide trading signals for cryptocurrencies and other asset classes, including stocks, forex, indices, and CFDs.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals is currently in a presale stage as the developers seek funds to improve their services. The development of ActualizeAI could improve AltSignals&rsquo; services and make it easier for traders in the market.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Actualize is fully automated and has a 24/7 trading function. ActualizeAI is designed to help traders to know when to enter trades, execute more accurate trades, and implement proper risk management strategies.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">ASI is the native token of the AltSignals ecosystem. Holders of the token will have access to various services offered by AltSignals. You can learn more about the&nbsp;<a href="https://token.altsignals.io/#how-to-buy" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>AltSignals pre-sale</u></a> by visiting their website.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How the surge affects AltSignals&nbsp;</h2>
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals could be one of the biggest beneficiaries of the current market trend changes. As more investors and traders enter the market, trading volume for various cryptocurrencies could increase.</p>
<p dir="ltr">More people will want to trade cryptocurrencies, and this is where AltSignals comes in. AltSignals could make it easier for users to trade meme coins and other cryptocurrencies.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Furthermore, AltSignals could make it easier to trade other asset classes like forex and stocks.</p>
<p dir="ltr">If that happens, its native ASI token could perform excellently. At the moment, ASI is still in its pre-sale stage, and the developers have raised more than $670k so far.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">One ASI is selling for about $0.015, and the price is expected to rise once the second stage of the token sale commences.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In the last bull cycle, the rallies recorded by the likes of Dogecoin and Shiba Inu showed that the Bull Run was in full flow. The rally by PEPE and other meme coins could indicate that another Bull Run could be on the cards.</p>
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals (ASI) is an even better token than PEPE and other meme coins since ASI has utility while most meme coins don&rsquo;t.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Are cryptocurrencies good investments?&nbsp;</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Historically, cryptocurrencies have been excellent investments. Cryptocurrencies have generated higher returns on investments (ROI) compared to stocks and commodities since Bitcoin launched in 2009.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin and Ether have given early investors thousands of percentages in ROI. Meme coins such as Dogecoin and Shiba Inu are not left out, while metaverse-focused tokens like MANA and SAND have also generated massive profits for early investors.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Is now a good time to buy AltSignals?</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://token.altsignals.io/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=invezz&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=investment_opportunity" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>AltSignals</u></a> is a highly promising project if the developers deliver on their promises. Cryptocurrency trading remains one of the hardest terrains to navigate, and having a tool that helps users to trade with ease could gain massive adoption.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The ActualizeAI solution could help boost AltSignals&rsquo; adoption rate, especially amongst crypto traders.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals is a project that holds a lot of promise if the development delivers on its products and features. The launch of ActualizeAI could see AltSignals&rsquo; adoption increase massively amongst crypto and forex traders.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">ASI could be a worthy coin to buy as its utility will increase once more people use AltSignals&rsquo; services.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-asi-token-could-surge-as-meme-coin-trading-volume-surges-to-a-two-year-high/">AltSignals (ASI) token could surge as meme coin trading volume reaches a two-year high</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>BRC-20 tokens have major flaws and issues, Mintlayer CEO says</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/brc-20-tokens-have-major-flaws-and-issues-mintlayer-ceo-says/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 13:56:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital token]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/brc-20-tokens-have-major-flaws-and-issues-mintlayer-ceo-says/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin BRC-20 tokens have skyrocketed over the past few days, with their combined market value rising to over $923 million as of 8 May, 2023. Mintlayer CEO Enrico Rubboli has highlighted some of the flaws and issues plaguing the BRC-20 token standard. Apart from not aligning with the &#8220;axioms of the core Bitcoin community,&#8221; flaws [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/brc-20-tokens-have-major-flaws-and-issues-mintlayer-ceo-says/">BRC-20 tokens have major flaws and issues, Mintlayer CEO says</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Bitcoin BRC-20 tokens have skyrocketed over the past few days, with their combined market value rising to over $923 million as of 8 May, 2023.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Mintlayer CEO Enrico Rubboli has highlighted some of the flaws and issues plaguing the BRC-20 token standard.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Apart from not aligning with the &ldquo;axioms of the core Bitcoin community,&rdquo; flaws and issues mean users are likely to be rug pulled.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/">Crypto news</a> this week indeed has the skyrocketing transactions of BRC-20 tokens as one of the reasons the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> network experienced massive congestion amid rising fees.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">As CoinJournal <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/why-is-the-crypto-market-down-today/">highlighted</a> on Monday morning, the crypto market was down as Binance halted BTC withdrawals amid the network congestion. Some of the trending BRC-20 tokens include ordi, pepe, meme, piza and domo.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Enrico Rubboli, the CEO of Bitcoin sidechain<a href="https://www.mintlayer.org/en/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">&nbsp;<u>Mintlayer</u></a>, says that while BRC-20 tokens continue to create a frenzy, there are flaws and other issues that plague the tokens and offshoot decentralised applications that try to connect with smart contracts.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What are BRC-20 tokens?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">BRC-20, or &ldquo;Bitcoin Request for Comment,&rdquo; is a token standard for Ordinals. The tokens allow for the issuance and transfer of fungible tokens on Bitcoin and hit the market soon after the mainnet launch of the Ordinals Protocol.</p>
<p dir="ltr">With BRC-20 tokens, one can etch digital art references into small Bitcoin transactions. The tokens are a creation of a pseudonymous crypto developer known as Domo.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to<a href="https://ordspace.org/brc20">&nbsp;<u>market data</u></a> for the token category, the combined value of all 11,705 BRC-20 tokens was $923 million as of Monday, 8 May 2023.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">BRC-20 tokens plagued by speed and transaction costs issues</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Among the insights Rubboli shared with CoinJournal on Monday is that while people pour BTC into minting BRC-20 tokens, there&rsquo;s a need to realise that the technology behind these assets is &ldquo;heavily flawed.&rdquo; He also notes that BRC-20 tokens aren&rsquo;t &ldquo;<em>in line with the axioms of the core Bitcoin community</em>.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Rubboli said that some of the issues currently plaguing the tokens and offshoot dApps within the ecosystem include speed, transaction costs and security.</p>
<p dir="ltr">On the issue of speed, he explains that transactions have to wait for Bitcoin block confirmation before settlement, which when combined with network congestion, has resulted in users waiting hours for transactions to clear.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Mintlayer CEO says BRC-20 tokens are potential rug pulls</h2>
<p dir="ltr">According to Rubboli, the use of token bridges and wrapped BTC could expose users to exploits, with DeFi bridges seeing more than<a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/08/10/hackers-have-stolen-1point4-billion-this-year-using-crypto-bridges.html" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">&nbsp;<u>$1.4 billion</u></a> lost to hackers that targeted crypto bridges in 2022. Rubboli believes the entire concept for BRC-20 was designed to confuse and mislead potential investors, with the creators leeching off the popular ERC-20 token standard.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Saying this could be an opportunity for scams, he added:</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>The entire ecosystem was set up to be confusing and misleading. BRC-20 was chosen not because it was the 20th proposed standard, but to leech off the popularity of Ethereum&rsquo;s ERC-20 token. The developers of the standard and the tools are not affiliated with Bitcoin, they are anonymous, and their software has not been thoroughly tested in this application</em>.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Besides, the hundreds of BRC-20 tokens might not just be totally worthless, but also minted specifically to rug pull later investors. BRC-20 token standard creator Domo has previously<a href="https://twitter.com/domodata/status/1633828036943704068" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">&nbsp;<u>warned</u></a> of the shortcomings of the software, including minting balances to intermediary wallets.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Regulatory issues also arise, with the minting of BRC-20 tokens likely to lead to regulatory concerns around commingling of user-generated tokens with BTC.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>If users mint unregulated securities, it could expose the Bitcoin blockchain to further regulatory scrutiny, which in turn exposes every BRC-20 to regulation due to 1 bad actor. A layer 2 solution fixes this problem as tokens are not commingled with Bitcoin</em>,&rdquo; he opined.</p>
<p dir="ltr">A layer 2 solution is a protocol that runs on top of a layer 1 blockchain, for instance Bitcoin or Ethereum. The key features that these protocols bring to the L1 include improved scalability and privacy among others.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">In blockchain, common layer 2 solutions include state channels, sidechains, and zero knowledge roll-ups.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/brc-20-tokens-have-major-flaws-and-issues-mintlayer-ceo-says/">BRC-20 tokens have major flaws and issues, Mintlayer CEO says</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Trillion dollar coin could be good news for Bitcoin, Cardano, Solana</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/trillion-dollar-coin-could-be-good-news-for-bitcoin-cardano-solana/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/trillion-dollar-coin-could-be-good-news-for-bitcoin-cardano-solana/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 12:59:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/trillion-dollar-coin-could-be-good-news-for-bitcoin-cardano-solana/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The US government could be forced to print a $1 trillion coin soon. Democrats and Republicans are yet to reach an agreement on a debt ceiling. Analysts expect that the two sides will ultimately reach an agreement. The US government is at a crossroads as divisions in Congress put the country at an elevated risk [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/trillion-dollar-coin-could-be-good-news-for-bitcoin-cardano-solana/">Trillion dollar coin could be good news for Bitcoin, Cardano, Solana</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The US government could be forced to print a $1 trillion coin soon.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Democrats and Republicans are yet to reach an agreement on a debt ceiling.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Analysts expect that the two sides will ultimately reach an agreement.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">The US government is at a crossroads as divisions in Congress put the country at an elevated risk of a default. In a recent statement, Janet Yellen, the Treasury Secretary warned that the American government could default in June if Democrats and Republicans fail to reach a deal. This is one of the top reasons why gold price has now soared to an all-time high.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">The trillion-dollar coin</h2>
<p dir="ltr">It is still unclear whether the US will default on its obligations if Congress fails to raise the debt ceiling. I believe that the situation will not get to that point because of its impact to the American economy.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Analysts believe that a default will lead to higher unemployment and possibly the collapse of the economy as we know it.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, the two sides will likely reach an agreement in the coming days. Signs of potential compromises will happen when Biden will meet Kevin McCarthy on Monday.</p>
<p dir="ltr">There are several options if the two sides fail to raise the debt limit. A likely solution will be to print a trillion dollar coin. The concept of that coin was mooted in 2011 when the US faced another debt ceiling issue.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">It would allow the Mint to come up with one platinum coin&nbsp;<a href="https://www.businessinsider.com/debt-ceiling-solution-mint-a-trillion-dollar-platinum-coin-2023-5?r=US&amp;IR=T"><u>valued</u></a> at $1 trillion. These funds would then be distributed to the Federal Reserve, which would then deposit it to the National Treasury. By doing that, the Treasury would then elimiate part of the national debt and postpone the need for raising the debt ceiling. A professor at Willamette University&nbsp;<a href="https://www.businessinsider.com/debt-ceiling-solution-mint-a-trillion-dollar-platinum-coin-2023-5?r=US&amp;IR=T" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>said</u></a>:</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;At this point, if any of the other solutions, the so-called more serious solutions would work, then they would&rsquo;ve been used by now. But they keep not actually being strong enough. The coin&rsquo;s the only one that&rsquo;s strong enough.&rdquo;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bullish for Bitcoin, Solana, Cardano</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Such a move would be positive for&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/"><u>Bitcoin</u></a>, which is seen as a digital version of gold. Unlike fiat currencies, Bitcoin cannot be printed because its supply of 21 million coins cannot be adjusted. If Bitcoin rises, we could now see altcoins like Solana, Cardano, and Tron rise because of the close correlation that exists.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The reality is that the American government is at risk of major changes going forward. For one, the total public debt has been in a strong upward trend in the past few years. It has jumped from just $320 million in 1970 to over $31.4 trillion today.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">And the situation will continue worsening because of the large budget deficits. By 2030, analysts expect that debt will rise to over $44 billion. The CBO&nbsp;<a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-budget-idUSKBN0OW1RY20150616"><u>believes</u></a> that the budget deficit will hit 5.9% of GDP by 2040.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy Bitcoin</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>

    <p>eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=MTM4ODEx&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy BTC with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    Public</h3>

    <p>Public is an investing platform that allows you to invest stocks, ETFs, crypto, and alternative assets like fine art and collectibles&mdash;all in one place.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/public-crypto?guid=MTM4ODEx&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy BTC with Public today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptocurrency execution and custody services are provided by Apex Crypto LLC (NMLS ID 1828849) through a software licensing agreement between Apex Crypto LLC and Public Crypto LLC. Crypto trading on Public platforms is served by Public Crypto LLC and offered through APEX Crypto. Please ensure that you fully understand the risks involved before trading." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/trillion-dollar-coin-could-be-good-news-for-bitcoin-cardano-solana/">Trillion dollar coin could be good news for Bitcoin, Cardano, Solana</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/trillion-dollar-coin-could-be-good-news-for-bitcoin-cardano-solana/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why is the crypto market down today?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/why-is-the-crypto-market-down-today/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 10:19:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/why-is-the-crypto-market-down-today/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The crypto market cap was down 3.2% in the past 24 hours to $1.2 trillion as Binance halted BTC withdrawals. The exchange&#8217;s action followed massive network congestion for Bitcoin amid increase in fees as tokens with inscriptions and ordinals pumped. Meanwhile, Bitcoin (BTC) saw its market cap drop to $540 billion for a 45% market [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/why-is-the-crypto-market-down-today/">Why is the crypto market down today?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>The crypto market cap was down 3.2% in the past 24 hours to $1.2 trillion as Binance halted BTC withdrawals.</li>
<li>The exchange&rsquo;s action followed massive network congestion for Bitcoin amid increase in fees as tokens with inscriptions and ordinals pumped.</li>
<li>Meanwhile, Bitcoin (BTC) saw its market cap drop to $540 billion for a 45% market dominance.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">The total cryptocurrency market cap is down 3.2% to $1.2 trillion in the past 24 hours as of writing. The top two digital assets by market capitalization <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">Bitcoin (BTC)</a> and Ethereum (ETH) are both down more than 3% in the same period and -5.4% and -2.2% respectively over the past seven days.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As a result, BTC price is below $28,000 while Ether is trading near $1,850 amid broader selling pressure for crypto.</p>
<p dir="ltr">While most big cap tokens are down about 3 to 6%, Pepe (PEPE) and Sui (SUI) are the biggest losers in the top 100 coins with about -12% performance in the past 24 hours.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Why crypto market is down today &ndash; look at Bitcoin</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The traditional markets continue to see some negativity as traders place new bets on regional banks plummeting again following last week&rsquo;s bounce. The outlook isn&rsquo;t the same for crypto and Bitcoin indeed rallied as multiple US bank <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/stocks/">stocks</a> dumped.</p>
<p dir="ltr">But why is the crypto market cap down? Notably, crypto remains volatile and BTC is finding it difficult to break higher following the rejections near $30,000. However, panic selling could be behind this latest down leg, particularly with such data as the one showing enormous BTC outflows from the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/binance/">Binance</a> exchange.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">BREAKING: <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Binance?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Binance</a> outflow data confirms largest withdrawal in it's history, over 162,000 <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24BTC&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$BTC</a> has left the exchange, valued at over $4.6 Billion.</p>
<p>Are Whales/Insiders jumping ship? &#128064; <a href="https://t.co/QSXYAEvHkt">pic.twitter.com/QSXYAEvHkt</a></p>
<p>&mdash; WhaleWire (@WhaleWire) <a href="https://twitter.com/WhaleWire/status/1655339441416724482?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">May 7, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">Binance <a href="https://twitter.com/binance/status/1655430207023747074" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">addressed</a> the &ldquo;outflows&rdquo; funds movement between its hot and cold wallets amid the adjustments in BTC address. This comes after the exchange suspending Bitcoin transactions as the flagship network experienced massive congestion. It&rsquo;s a scenario that saw transaction fees spike significantly.</p>
<p dir="ltr">For instance, on Sunday, transaction fees in BTC block 788695 was 6.7 BTC, higher than the block subsidy of 6.25 BTC. On-chain data shows Bitcoin experienced a spike in blockspace demand, pushing transactions fees higher.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to on-chain analytics platform Glassnode, the high demand for blockspace is being driven by BRC-20 tokens. The tokens that use inscriptions and ordinals have been up as shown by the 9% gains for <a href="https://coinjournal.net/stacks/">Stacks (STX)</a> amid BTC price decline.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Bitcoin</a> is experiencing extremely high demand for blockspace, driven by BRC-20 tokens, utilizing text based inscriptions, and ordinals</p>
<p>This is a revenue boost for Miners, as the average fee paid per block has reached 2.905 <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24BTC&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$BTC</a>, near past bull peaks</p>
<p>&#128202;<a href="https://t.co/DyVjODagG9">https://t.co/DyVjODagG9</a> <a href="https://t.co/8ZV0i4DNzm">pic.twitter.com/8ZV0i4DNzm</a></p>
<p>&mdash; glassnode (@glassnode) <a href="https://twitter.com/glassnode/status/1655405102960869377?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">May 8, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">As such, the Bitcoin market cap is down to $540 billion today, representing about 45% of market dominance. <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/ethereum/">Ethereum</a>&lsquo;s market dominance currently stands around 18.6%</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitcoin price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The announcement that Binance had suspended BTC withdrawals &ndash; on two occasions &ndash; looks to have spooked a few traders into action. But the crypto market cap could recoup some of the losses ahead of a crucial week with economic news. Binance is also reportedly eyeing Bitcoin Lightning Network transactions.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Crypto analyst Michael van de Poppe highlights Bitcoin price levels at $27.4k or even $26.8k could provide the bounce area.</p>
<p>&ldquo;<em>Mentioned before that $29.2K was the key level to break for #Bitcoin. We did have a bounce towards it, but no break. Additionally some FUD regarding #Binance doesn&rsquo;t help. Looking at $27.4K or $26.8K for potential longs towards the CME gap at $29.6K</em>,&rdquo; the analyst<a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoMichNL/status/1655494168016306176" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">&nbsp;<u>tweeted</u></a> on Monday morning.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/why-is-the-crypto-market-down-today/">Why is the crypto market down today?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>PEPE price dives after Whale transfers trillions of tokens to Binance</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/pepe-price-dives-after-whale-transfers-trillions-of-tokens-to-binance/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 07:49:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/pepe-price-dives-after-whale-transfers-trillions-of-tokens-to-binance/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>At press time, PEPE was trading at $0.000002328. The token price has declined by 10.93% in the last 24 hours. PEPE hit an all-time high of $0.000004354 on May 5, 2023. Three days after hitting its all-time high, PEPE, a meme token that has seen its popularity go through the roof recently, is now on [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/pepe-price-dives-after-whale-transfers-trillions-of-tokens-to-binance/">PEPE price dives after Whale transfers trillions of tokens to Binance</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul class="decimal_type">
<li>At press time, PEPE was trading at $0.000002328.</li>
<li>The token price has declined by 10.93% in the last 24 hours.</li>
<li>PEPE hit an all-time high of $0.000004354 on May 5, 2023.</li>
</ul>
<p>Three days after hitting its all-time high, PEPE, a meme token that has seen its popularity go through the roof recently, is now on the decline. &nbsp;</p>
<p>The price of PEPE has dropped by 46.53% in just three from its all-time high of $0.000004354, which it hit after the meme token got listed on several major exchanges including <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/okx-review-a-one-stop-platform-for-crypto-defi-dapps-nfts-and-gamefi/">OKX&nbsp;</a>and <a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/binance/">Binance</a>.</p>
<div class="fr-img-space-wrap"><span class="fr-img-caption fr-fic fr-dib fr-draggable" style="width: 591px"><span class="fr-img-wrap">
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/04/08/1683531662085-e221187b-384e-4e7e-bc3d-6a7347abf8a6.jpg" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="591" height="368"><span class="fr-inner">PEPE price</span></p>
<p></p></span></span>
<p class="fr-img-space-wrap2">&nbsp;</p>
</div>
<h2>About 4.23 trillion PEPE tokens sent to Binance</h2>
<p>According to a <a href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1654546602449862656?s=20">tweet</a> by blockchain data provider Lookonchian, a giant whale bought 4.23 trillion PEPE tokens using 422 $ETH and 200K $USDC. The whale then deposited all the purchased PEPE to Binance.</p>
<p>The above transactions were made on May 5, the same day <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/support/announcement/binance-will-list-floki-floki-and-pepe-pepe-in-the-innovation-zone-f68a3bc6eb014ed9bacf1d6c71dc1134?ref=AZTKZ9XS&amp;utm_source=BinanceTwitter&amp;utm_medium=GlobalSocial&amp;utm_campaign=GlobalSocial">Binance announced PEPE&rsquo;s listing</a>. Immediately after purchasing the trillion of PEPE tokens, the price of PEPE skyrocketed making the whale accrue a profit of about $14.5 million at the time he was depositing the token in Binance.</p>
<p>There is fear in the market that the move by the whale to send the meme coins to Binance could be in preparation to sell the tokens in order to recoup profits before the token dumps. These fears have exerted pressure on the market resulting in the current price drop.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/pepe-price-dives-after-whale-transfers-trillions-of-tokens-to-binance/">PEPE price dives after Whale transfers trillions of tokens to Binance</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
