<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 21:29:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Block reports a 34% increase in its second-quarter Bitcoin revenue</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/block-q2-bitcoin-revenue-increase/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wajeeh Khan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 21:29:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Square]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=148653</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Block reports market-beating results for its fiscal second quarter. It attributed nearly half of its quarterly revenue to Bitcoin sales. Shares of the fintech still ended nearly 15% down on Friday. Block Inc ended nearly 15% down on Friday even though it reported market-beating results for its second financial quarter. Bitcoin made up half of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/block-q2-bitcoin-revenue-increase/">Block reports a 34% increase in its second-quarter Bitcoin revenue</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Block reports market-beating results for its fiscal second quarter.</li>
<li>It attributed nearly half of its quarterly revenue to Bitcoin sales.</li>
<li>Shares of the fintech still ended nearly 15% down on Friday.</li>
</ul>
<p>Block Inc ended nearly 15% down on Friday even though it reported market-beating results for its second financial quarter.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin made up half of Block&rsquo;s Q2 revenue</h2>
<p>The financial technology company saw continued interest in digital assets in Q2.</p>
<p>Its Bitcoin revenue went up 34% on a year-over-year basis to $2.40 billion and made up nearly half of its total quarterly revenue. Block also revealed in a <a href="https://investors.block.xyz/overview/default.aspx" target="_blank" rel="noopener">letter to shareholders</a> today:</p>
<blockquote><p>As of June 30<sup>th</sup>, fair value of our investment in BTC was $245 million based on observable market prices, which was $142 million greater than carrying value after cumulative impairment charges.</p></blockquote>
<p>The multinational attributed $44 million worth of gross profit in its recently concluded quarter to <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> sales &ndash; up 7.0% versus a year ago. Block shares are now down nearly 30% versus their year-to-date high.</p>
<h2>Notable figures in Block&rsquo;s Q2 earnings print</h2>
<ul>
<li>Lost $123 million versus the year-ago $208 million</li>
<li>Per-share loss narrowed from 36 cents to 20 cents</li>
<li>Adjusted EPS printed at 39 cents as per the press release</li>
<li>Sales went up 26% year-on-year to $5.53 billion</li>
<li>Consensus was 36 cents a share on $5.1 billion in revenue</li>
<li>Square and Cash App gross profits climbed 18% and 37%</li>
<li>Gross payment volume increased 12% to $59.01 billion</li>
</ul>
<p>Block now forecasts $1.5 billion in full-year adjusted EBITDA. Its previous guidance was for $1.36 billion. The conglomerate also said in its <a href="https://investors.block.xyz/overview/default.aspx" target="_blank" rel="noopener">letter to shareholders</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>In early 2023, we incorporated Gen AI as a strategic priority because we believe the tech can create new features and efficiencies for our customers.</p></blockquote>
<p>Wall Street currently has a consensus &ldquo;<a href="https://www.wsj.com/market-data/quotes/SQ/research-ratings" target="_blank" rel="noopener">overweight</a>&rdquo; rating on Block stock.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/block-q2-bitcoin-revenue-increase/">Block reports a 34% increase in its second-quarter Bitcoin revenue</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Curve hacker returns part of the stolen assets</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/curve-hacker-returns-part-of-the-stolen-assets/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/curve-hacker-returns-part-of-the-stolen-assets/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 19:31:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Curve Dao Token News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/curve-hacker-returns-part-of-the-stolen-assets/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The hack that took place on July 30, resulted in Curve Finance losing $61 million in crypto assets. The hacker also targeted Alchemix&#8217;s alETH pools and Metronome&#8217;s msETH stealing assets worth $22.6 million and $3.4 million respectively. The hacker has returned at least $10 million worth of crypto assets to Alchemix&#8217;s multi-signature wallet. In an [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/curve-hacker-returns-part-of-the-stolen-assets/">Curve hacker returns part of the stolen assets</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul class="decimal_type">
<li>The hack that took place on July 30, resulted in Curve Finance losing $61 million in crypto assets.</li>
<li>The hacker also targeted Alchemix&rsquo;s alETH pools and Metronome&rsquo;s msETH stealing assets worth $22.6 million and $3.4 million respectively.</li>
<li>The hacker has returned at least $10 million worth of crypto assets to Alchemix&rsquo;s multi-signature wallet.</li>
</ul>
<p>In an attempt to facilitate the return of the assets during the $61 million Curve Finance hack, the perpetrator on Friday contacted Alchemix, one of the victims, using an <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/what-is-ethereum/">Ethereum</a> blockchain transaction.</p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/AlchemixFi/status/1687469467196928000">Data on Etherscan</a> shows that they then made multiple transfers totalling about $10 million worth of ether (ETH) and alETH to Alchemix&rsquo;s multi-signature wallet.</p>
<p>It is worth noting that the governance token of Curve Finance, <a href="https://coinjournal.net/curve-dao/">Curve DAO Token (CRV)</a>, saw a significant increase following the return of the stolen assets. The CRV token hit a daily high of $0.6288 following the news, which has given victims hope of recovering the stolen assets.</p>
<p>The news comes a few days after Huobi&rsquo;s co-founder <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/huobi-co-founder-buys-10-million-curve-dao-tokens-from-curve-founder/">purchased 10 million CRV tokens</a> from Curve Finance founder, who is seeking to reduce the stablecoins loans he had taken using CRV as collateral.</p>
<h2>Hacker offered a bounty to return funds</h2>
<p>A bounty to recover the money taken in the recent attack was announced by Curve Finance, Metronome, and Alchemix on August 3. The three projects declared that they are open to talking with anyone who was involved in the most recent Curve exploits.</p>
<p>The three companies have suggested offering the attacker(s) a 10% bounty of the stolen money in exchange for returning the other 90%.</p>
<p>As an inducement, the projects have promised that they won&rsquo;t pursue further action or involve law enforcement if the attacker(s) voluntarily return the stolen funds.</p>
<p>But if the attacker(s) don&rsquo;t return the remaining assets, the 10% bounty will be paid to whoever can locate and offer proof that will result in the guilty parties&rsquo; being found guilty in a court of law. The three <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/defi/">DeFi</a> platforms promise to pursue the attacker(s) to the fullest extent permitted by law and through all legal avenues.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/curve-hacker-returns-part-of-the-stolen-assets/">Curve hacker returns part of the stolen assets</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/curve-hacker-returns-part-of-the-stolen-assets/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Miami mayor to accept presidential campaign donations in BTC</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/miami-mayor-to-accept-presidential-campaign-donations-in-btc/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/miami-mayor-to-accept-presidential-campaign-donations-in-btc/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 18:14:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/miami-mayor-to-accept-presidential-campaign-donations-in-btc/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Miami Mayor Francis Suarez, a Republican, announced his candidacy for the 2024 presidential election in June. Miami has currently been trending for all the right reasons from Lionel Messi mania to the mayor accepting BTC donations. The mayor has also said that he would ban a central bank digital currency (CBDC). Bitcoin-friendly Miami Mayor Francis [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/miami-mayor-to-accept-presidential-campaign-donations-in-btc/">Miami mayor to accept presidential campaign donations in BTC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Miami Mayor Francis Suarez, a Republican, announced his candidacy for the 2024 presidential election in June.</li>
<li>Miami has currently been trending for all the right reasons from Lionel Messi mania to the mayor accepting BTC donations.</li>
<li>The mayor has also said that he would ban a central bank digital currency (CBDC).</li>
</ul>
<p>Bitcoin-friendly Miami Mayor Francis Suarez has said that he will accept <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/what-is-bitcoin/">Bitcoin (BTC)</a> donations for his presidential campaign.</p>
<p>Speaking on a popular media TV outlet, Suarez said:</p>
<p><em>&ldquo;Officially, my campaign is accepting bitcoin,&rdquo; Suarez explained. &ldquo;This is a process of developing technologies that will create democratising opportunities for wealth creation and will not be manipulated by a human being&rsquo;s ulterior motives, political goals, and so on.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p>According to Suarez, supporters can now donate as little as 0.00034BTC, or the equivalent of $1, at his campaign website.</p>
<h2>Suarez&rsquo;s view on CBDCs</h2>
<p>Suarez, who is known to advocate for Bitcoin, has said that he would ban a central bank digital currency (CBDC). &nbsp;He said that people do not want the federal government to know where they have their money and how much money they have.</p>
<p>Suarez launched the MiamiCoin (MIA) in 2021, which he hoped would be used to <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/miami-city-to-dole-out-yield-from-staking-miamicoin-says-mayor/">pay a recurring Bitcoin stimulus</a> (similar to dividends) to Miami citizens.</p>
<p>The mayor has criticized the current US administration led by Joe Biden. Castigating the government, Suarez said:</p>
<p><em>&ldquo;The biggest mistake that this administration has made is they don&rsquo;t understand crypto so they have gone to a regulated-by-enforcement mechanism as opposed to set the ground rules. You have to be able to classify certain digital products, you have to be able to have certain guidelines and rules that are clear with respect to the custody of assets.&rdquo;</em></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/miami-mayor-to-accept-presidential-campaign-donations-in-btc/">Miami mayor to accept presidential campaign donations in BTC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/miami-mayor-to-accept-presidential-campaign-donations-in-btc/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>$1.6M raised one month into Shiba Memu presale, BitMart listing announced</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/1-6m-raised-one-month-into-shiba-memu-presale-bitmart-listing-announced/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/1-6m-raised-one-month-into-shiba-memu-presale-bitmart-listing-announced/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 17:08:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[exchanges]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/1-6m-raised-one-month-into-shiba-memu-presale-bitmart-listing-announced/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>At press time, 53,351,246 SHMU tokens had been sold raising over $1,612,597. SHMU price which rises every few hours had just risen from 0.017875 USDT to 0.018100 USDT. Shiba Memu has today announced the listing of its SHMU token on the BitMart crypto exchange. Shiba Memu, a bustling new AI-powered cryptocurrency meme coin, has announced [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/1-6m-raised-one-month-into-shiba-memu-presale-bitmart-listing-announced/">$1.6M raised one month into Shiba Memu presale, BitMart listing announced</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul class="decimal_type">
<li>At press time, 53,351,246 SHMU tokens had been sold raising over $1,612,597.</li>
<li>SHMU price which rises every few hours had just risen from 0.017875 USDT to 0.018100 USDT.</li>
<li>Shiba Memu has today announced the listing of its SHMU token on the BitMart crypto exchange.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news">Shiba Memu</a>, a bustling new AI-powered cryptocurrency meme coin, has announced the listing of its native token SHMU on BirtMart. The project is currently conducting a presale of the SHMU token which has already surpassed $1.6 million one month after the presale started.</p>
<p>The meme coin project has attracted quite a sensation among crypto investors as it rides the artificial intelligence (AI) and meme coin hype.</p>
<h2>SHMU listing on BitMart</h2>
<p>BitMart has been a significant player in the cryptocurrency industry since 2017. It provides over 1500 cryptocurrency trading pairs.</p>
<p>The choice of BitMart as its first centralized cryptocurrency exchange where SHMU will be listed has certainly caused a sensation among SHMU holders who will now be able to trade the new meme coin after purchasing it in the presale. In addition, more investors will certainly flock to the Shiba Memu presale for fear of being left out when the presale comes to an end.</p>
<p>The realistic idea and endearing Shiba Memu mascot have sparked a wave of interest from investors and cryptocurrency enthusiasts who understand the project&rsquo;s long-term potential.</p>
<p>In addition, the team behind the project expertly developed a smart contract that ensures that the scheduled SHMU price increase every 24 hours. This alluring mechanism is especially alluring to fans of presales because it ensures that the token purchase price will always be less than the final listing price on the exchange. Better still, investors are optimistic that the token price will see a considerable price surge once it list on the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/compare/best-cryptocurrency-exchanges/">crypto exchange</a>.</p>
<h2>Should you invest in Shiba Memu today?</h2>
<p>While making an investment move is a preserve of an investor, <a href="https://coinjournal.net/cryptocurrencies/invest/">investing in a cryptocurrency</a> project carries significant risks owing to the volatile nature of the cryptocurrency market. Nevertheless, many people have reaped big from new crypto projects, especially meme coin projects which are known to go viral immediately after they are launched.</p>
<p>That said, Shiba Memu is a unique meme coin project that leverages the power of AI and blockchain technology to create an unstoppable, entirely self-sufficient marketing powerhouse. The project sets itself apart from the like of <a href="https://coinjournal.net/shiba-inu/what-is-shiba-inu/">Shiba Inu</a>, PEPE, <a href="https://coinjournal.net/dogecoin/what-is-dogecoin/">Dogecoin</a>, and KEKE, which became popular purely because of their community engagements without any real-world use case apart from acceptance as payment options in several retail outlets.</p>
<p>The listing on BitMart is also quite a good proposition seeing that it adds to the credibility of the project which is barely a month old since its presale went live. If interested in the Shiba Memu project, you can purchase the SHMU tokens <a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news">here</a>.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/1-6m-raised-one-month-into-shiba-memu-presale-bitmart-listing-announced/">$1.6M raised one month into Shiba Memu presale, BitMart listing announced</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/1-6m-raised-one-month-into-shiba-memu-presale-bitmart-listing-announced/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Price Predictions: GMX, Trader Joe (JOE), Casper (CSPR)</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-predictions-gmx-trader-joe-joe-casper-cspr/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-predictions-gmx-trader-joe-joe-casper-cspr/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 14:57:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-predictions-gmx-trader-joe-joe-casper-cspr/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrencies remained in a consolidation phase this week. Trader Joe, GMX, and Casper Network were among the top movers on Friday. Cryptocurrencies reacted mildly to the latest US jobs numbers published on Friday.&#160;Bitcoin is still loitering at the $20,000 level while the volume traded in exchanges has dropped. This article will look at some of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-predictions-gmx-trader-joe-joe-casper-cspr/">Crypto Price Predictions: GMX, Trader Joe (JOE), Casper (CSPR)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Cryptocurrencies remained in a consolidation phase this week.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Trader Joe, GMX, and Casper Network were among the top movers on Friday.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Cryptocurrencies reacted mildly to the latest US jobs numbers published on Friday.&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/"><u>Bitcoin</u></a> is still loitering at the $20,000 level while the volume traded in exchanges has dropped. This article will look at some of the top cryptocurrencies that made some strong moves on Friday, including GMX, Trader Joe, and Casper.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Trader Joe price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Trader Joe is a leading&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/glossary/decentralized-exchange-dex/"><u>decentralized exchange</u></a> that was started operations in&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/avalanche"><u>Avalanche</u></a>, one of the top chains in the world. The token rose slightly on Friday after the network launched on Ethereum, the biggest player in the industry. This means that the platform is also in Arbitrum and BNB Chain.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Trader Joe&rsquo;s JOE token has been in a strong bearish trend in the past few weeks. In this period, it has dropped by more than 29% from the highest point in June. The token has remained below the 25-period and 50-period moving averages (MA). It has formed a falling wedge pattern, which is usually a bullish sign.</p>
<p dir="ltr">JOE price will likely remain in this range during the weekend since the integration of Ethereum will not have an impact on the network. As such, it will remain between the support and resistance levels at $0.30 and $0.32.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/07/04/1691160947934-408e12fc-a138-409b-97ba-58933664b951.png" style="width: 599px;height: 291.513px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="599" height="291.513"></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">GMX price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/gmx/"><u>GMX</u></a> is a leading decentralized exchange (DEX) that provides perpetual futures products. It is the biggest DEX in Arbitrum, the biggest layer-2 network in the world. The GMX token rose after the developers launched its V2 on Thursday. This new version will introduce more coins like Dogecoin at lower fees.</p>
<p dir="ltr">GMX token has made a strong bullish comeback in the past few days. This recovery started after the token settled at $49.03, the lowest level since June 19th. It has moved above the 25-day moving average.</p>
<p dir="ltr">At the same time, it has formed an inverted cup and handle pattern, which is usually a bearish sign. Therefore, the token will likely resume the bearish trend and retest the support at $49.03.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/07/04/1691160948038-435c0bfa-4076-4a4d-ab7b-fc8d79d74e6a.png" style="width: 600px;height: 292px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="600" height="292"></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy GMX token</h2>
<p dir="ltr">
        </p><div class="relative">

            
        </div>


<h2 dir="ltr">Casper price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Casper price has made a strong comeback in the past few days. On the four-hour chart, the pair has risen in the past four straight hours. It has moved above the important resistance level at $0.040, the highest level on July 28th. &nbsp;It then moved to the key resistance point at June 22nd.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Casper token has jumped above the 50-day and 25-day moving averages. The outlook for Casper&rsquo;s CSPR is bullish, with the next level to watch being at $0.043. This view will be confirmed if the token jumps above the key resistance at $0.041</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/07/04/1691160948073-63b170d9-5d73-441e-9698-8eb3c9d08c37.png" style="width: 678px;height: 329.96px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="678" height="329.96"></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy Casper</h2>
<p dir="ltr">
        </p><div class="relative">

            <div class="mb-3  pb-6  px-6  bg-slate-50  rounded-xl  ps-shadow-inner">

    <h3 class="inline-block">
        BKEX    </h3>

            <p class="text-sm">BKEX is a centralized cryptocurrency exchange located in British Virgin Islands. There are 254 coins and 415 trading pairs on the exchange.</p>
    
    <div class="w-full  flex  flex-wrap  items-start  flex-col  gap-2">

        
<a href="/visit/bkex-crypto?guid=MTQ4NjIw&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="nofollow sponsored noopener" target="_self" class="inline-block  text-indigo-600  underline  hover:text-indigo-200  ease-in-out  duration-300  transition-all" title="Buy CSPR with BKEX today">Buy CSPR with BKEX today</a>

    </div>

</div><div class="  pb-6  px-6  bg-slate-50  rounded-xl  ps-shadow-inner">

    <h3 class="inline-block">
        Huobi    </h3>

            <p class="text-sm">Start Your Cryptocurrency Journey Today. Huobi Global has a variety of features that make it an ideal place to buy and sell digital asset.</p>
    
    <div class="w-full  flex  flex-wrap  items-start  flex-col  gap-2">

        
<a href="/visit/huobi-crypto?guid=MTQ4NjIw&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="nofollow sponsored noopener" target="_self" class="inline-block  text-indigo-600  underline  hover:text-indigo-200  ease-in-out  duration-300  transition-all" title="Buy CSPR with Huobi today">Buy CSPR with Huobi today</a>

    </div>

</div>
        </div>



<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-predictions-gmx-trader-joe-joe-casper-cspr/">Crypto Price Predictions: GMX, Trader Joe (JOE), Casper (CSPR)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-predictions-gmx-trader-joe-joe-casper-cspr/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Revolut to terminate US crypto services due to regulatory challenges</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/revolut-to-terminate-us-crypto-services-due-to-regulatory-challenges/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/revolut-to-terminate-us-crypto-services-due-to-regulatory-challenges/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 14:45:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Policy and Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Revolut]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/revolut-to-terminate-us-crypto-services-due-to-regulatory-challenges/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways Fintech firm Revolut is set to terminate its cryptocurrency services to users in the United States. The firm cited the current regulatory environment as the reason behind its exit. Revolut to halt crypto services in the US UK fintech firm Revolut has revealed that it would no longer provide cryptocurrency services to its [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/revolut-to-terminate-us-crypto-services-due-to-regulatory-challenges/">Revolut to terminate US crypto services due to regulatory challenges</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Fintech firm Revolut is set to terminate its cryptocurrency services to users in the United States.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The firm cited the current regulatory environment as the reason behind its exit.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr">Revolut to halt crypto services in the US</h2>
<p dir="ltr">UK fintech firm Revolut has revealed that it would no longer provide cryptocurrency services to its users in the United States.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The firm said it made this decision due to the regulatory environment in the US. starting September 2nd, Revolut&rsquo;s customers in the US will no longer be able to purchase cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The company informed its US users via email a few hours ago. However, its users will still be able to sell their crypto assets until October 2nd. Starting from October 3rd, users will no longer be able to buy, sell, or hold crypto assets on Revolut.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">While commenting on this&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>latest cryptocurrency news</u></a>, a Revolut spokesperson said;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;As a result of the evolving regulatory environment and the uncertainties around the crypto market in the U.S., we&rsquo;ve taken the difficult decision, together with our U.S. banking partner, to suspend access to cryptocurrencies through Revolut in the U.S.&rdquo;&nbsp;</em></p>
<p dir="ltr">Metropolitan Commercial Bank is Revolut&rsquo;s banking partner in the United States.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Non-US customers will continue to enjoy crypto services</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Revolut said the decision doesn&rsquo;t affect its users outside the United States. Its users in other parts of the world can register and use Revolut&rsquo;s cryptocurrency services.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">This latest development comes roughly a month after&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/revolut-to-delist-polygon-solana-and-cardano/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Revolut delisted</u></a> Polygon (MATIC), Solana (SOL) and Cardano (ADA) in the United States. These tokens are regarded as unregistered securities by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).</p>
<p dir="ltr">US users that fail to sell their crypto holdings before October 2nd will see their assets get liquidated on October 3rd. Users will receive the same market price for each token at that time, the company confirmed.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/revolut-to-terminate-us-crypto-services-due-to-regulatory-challenges/">Revolut to terminate US crypto services due to regulatory challenges</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/revolut-to-terminate-us-crypto-services-due-to-regulatory-challenges/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chancer seizes the moment as meme trading volume dips</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-seizes-the-moment-as-meme-trading-volume-dips/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 11:38:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOGE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-seizes-the-moment-as-meme-trading-volume-dips/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Currently, one CHNACER toke is going for $0.011. The price is expected to rise to $0.012 in the next presale stage. The trading volume of the top meme coins on August 4 dropped by about 8%. The new decentralized predictive market-making platform is seizing the moment with its CHANCER presale while a majority of popular [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-seizes-the-moment-as-meme-trading-volume-dips/">Chancer seizes the moment as meme trading volume dips</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul class="decimal_type">
<li>Currently, one CHNACER toke is going for $0.011.</li>
<li>The price is expected to rise to $0.012 in the next presale stage.</li>
<li>The trading volume of the top meme coins on August 4 dropped by about 8%.</li>
</ul>
<p>The new decentralized predictive market-making platform is seizing the moment with its CHANCER presale while a majority of popular meme coins struggle to gain traction. At the time of writing, the presale had raised $1,129,584 confirming the excitement that the new betting platform is causing among bettors and crypto investors.</p>
<p>Betting fans are rushing to own the CHANCER tokens for fear of being left out when the platform launched in Q1, 2024 allowing token holders to create, participate in and profit from their very own predictive markets based on their interests, expertise and social opportunities. If interested, you can visit <a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news">Chancer&rsquo;s official website</a> to purchase CHANCER tokens.</p>
<h2>Meme coins price performance&nbsp;</h2>
<p>A majority of popular meme coins like <a href="https://coinjournal.net/dogecoin/what-is-dogecoin/">Dogecoin (DOGE)</a>, PEPE, <a href="https://coinjournal.net/floki/">FLOKI</a>, and others have been struggling to turn bullish. The once very popular PEPE, for example, has lost 10% in value in the past week while Dogecoin has dropped by 3% in the same timeframe.</p>
<p>Apart from <a href="https://coinjournal.net/shiba-inu/what-is-shiba-inu/">Shiba Inu (SHIB)</a> and its sister token <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bone/">Bone ShibaSwap (BONE)</a> which have registered considerable gains among the old meme coin projects, a majority of the best-performing meme coins are the newly launched coins like Bald 2.0 (BALD2), 4-Chain (4CHAIN), and Turbo (TURBO) which have gained by 28%, 31%, and 17% respectively according to data on Coinmarketcap.</p>
<p>The rise and rise of new meme coins is a positive proposition for Chancer which is seeking to revolutionize the betting industry by using <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/blockchain/">blockchain technology</a> to give bettors the freedom of being their own wager market makers. And while some may argue the meme mania only lasts for a short period after a new project launches and then fades off, Chancer&rsquo;s case could be different seeing that it is leveraging the multibillion betting industry.</p>
<h2>Is Chancer a good investment opportunity?</h2>
<p>The choice of investing in any new project is purely a discretion of an investor especially when it comes to cryptocurrency projects, which carry quite significant risks due to the volatile nature of the cryptocurrency market.</p>
<p>That said, new meme crypto projects have been stealing the show within the crypto sphere with the explosion of the value of their tokens. A good example is PEPE and KEKE which briefly surpassed the two leading meme coins, SHIB and DOGE, in popularity when they were launched. Interestingly, once a meme coin becomes popular, it remains a favourite among crypto traders and investors even after the popularity fades.</p>
<p>Chancer is riding on the meme coins frenzy and the rising betting industry and it is already stealing the show with its presale which has sold 21,660,036 CHANCER tokens so far. Besides offering holder opportunities in the Chancer platform once it launches, holders are excited about the price which has been constantly rising throughout the presale.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-seizes-the-moment-as-meme-trading-volume-dips/">Chancer seizes the moment as meme trading volume dips</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu and IOTA become collateral assets on Binance</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-and-iota-become-collateral-assets-on-binance/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-and-iota-become-collateral-assets-on-binance/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 11:18:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[IOTA News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-and-iota-become-collateral-assets-on-binance/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways Crypto exchange Binance has added SHIB, IOTA and other cryptocurrencies as collateral assets on its platform. Binance also included 22 new cryptocurrencies as loanable assets.&#160; Binance Approves SHIB as a collateral asset Binance, the world&#8217;s leading cryptocurrency exchange, announced on Friday, August 4th that it has approved SHIB, Shiba Inu&#8217;s native token, as [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-and-iota-become-collateral-assets-on-binance/">Shiba Inu and IOTA become collateral assets on Binance</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Crypto exchange Binance has added SHIB, IOTA and other cryptocurrencies as collateral assets on its platform.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Binance also included 22 new cryptocurrencies as loanable assets.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr">Binance Approves SHIB as a collateral asset</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Binance, the world&rsquo;s leading cryptocurrency exchange, announced on Friday, August 4th that it has approved SHIB, Shiba Inu&rsquo;s native token, as a collateral asset on its lending platform.</p>
<p dir="ltr">While announcing this&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>latest cryptocurrency news</u></a>, Binance said it had added new loanable and collateral assets for its users.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In its&nbsp;<a href="https://www.binance.com/en/support/announcement/new-loanable-assets-and-collateral-assets-available-on-flexible-loan-vip-loan-2023-08-04-9c8303191b1a4a6bbd7458b3e4ff668d" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>blog post</u></a> earlier today, Binance said that SHIB, COMP, IOTA, RLC, HOT, ENJ, THETA, and IOST are now collateral assets on its platform. This means users can borrow funds on the Binance lending platform and use these cryptocurrencies as collateral.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Furthermore, users can borrow new assets, including AUCTION, PYR, ILV, KNC, YGG, GAS, CELO, and IRIS, using the flexible loan option. Meanwhile, NKN, FARM, DIA, YGG, OGN, and ACA have been added to the VIP loan options.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Binance explained that its Flexible Loan is an isolated, over-collateralised, and open-term loan service that allows users to complete loan orders while collateralising cryptocurrencies in existing Simple Earn Flexible Products subscriptions.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Meanwhile, the VIP Loan is designed as a large personal and institutional over-collateralised loan featuring competitive rates, terms, and services.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Binance could list the BONE token&nbsp;</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The cryptocurrency is also considering listing the BONE token on its platform. BONE is the governance token of ShibaSwap, Shiba Inu&rsquo;s decentralised exchange. The token allows the Shiba Inu community to vote on upcoming proposals, submit proposals and access future NFTs.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The BONE token could also be an integral part of the upcoming Shibarium mainnet launch. The project&rsquo;s lead developer, Shytoshi Kusama, has previously stated that the Shibarium mainnet launch could happen this month.</p>
<p>However, there is no specific launch date. SHIB, the native token of the Shiba Inu ecosystem, is currently up by more than 4% in the last 24 hours. At press time, the&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/shiba-inu/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>price of SHIB</u></a> stands at $0.00000861.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-and-iota-become-collateral-assets-on-binance/">Shiba Inu and IOTA become collateral assets on Binance</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-and-iota-become-collateral-assets-on-binance/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Should you buy or sell Bitcoin ahead of the July NFP report?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/should-you-buy-or-sell-bitcoin-ahead-of-the-july-nfp-report/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/should-you-buy-or-sell-bitcoin-ahead-of-the-july-nfp-report/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mircea Vasiu]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 09:30:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/should-you-buy-or-sell-bitcoin-ahead-of-the-july-nfp-report/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The July NFP report is due today, and the US dollar&#8217;s volatility is set to increase Bitcoin holds close to its yearly highs The bias for Bitcoin remains bullish while the market holds above the rising trendline&#160; The Non-Farm Payrolls (NFP) report is released on the first Friday of each month. It shows the change [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/should-you-buy-or-sell-bitcoin-ahead-of-the-july-nfp-report/">Should you buy or sell Bitcoin ahead of the July NFP report?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>The July NFP report is due today, and the US dollar&rsquo;s volatility is set to increase</li>
<li>Bitcoin holds close to its yearly highs</li>
<li>The bias for Bitcoin remains bullish while the market holds above the rising trendline&nbsp;</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p>The Non-Farm Payrolls (NFP) report is released on the first Friday of each month. It shows the change in the number of workers in the US economy &ndash; the largest economy in the world.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Because of that, the economic report directly impacts financial markets. The dollar fluctuates widely on the NFP report&rsquo;s release, and even the cryptocurrency market participants are interested in trading the report.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Bitcoin&rsquo;s correlation with the dollar&rsquo;s strength or weakness increased since more institutional investors included Bitcoin in their portfolios. This year, the dollar declined, as reflected by the EUR/USD exchange rate that reached a new high for the year less than two weeks ago.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Therefore, it is unsurprising that Bitcoin holds close to its yearly highs ahead of the July NFP report. Also, the bias remains bias as Bitcoin holds above the upward trendline that marks the 2023 bullish trend.&nbsp;</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/07/04/1691140914149-c53a59cf-1961-4cf1-a3d4-2060705b25aa.jpg" style="width: 1800px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="1800" height="439"></p>
<p><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/?exchange=CRYPTO" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Bitcoin chart by TradingView</a></p>
<h2>The bias remains bullish while Bitcoin holds above the rising trendline</h2>
<p>The technical picture favors more upside for Bitcoin for at least three reasons.&nbsp;</p>
<p>First, since the 2022 lows, Bitcoin formed a series of higher highs and higher lows. Such formation is typical in bullish trends, and while in place, the bias remains bullish.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Second, one can properly identify the bullish trend by connecting the lower highs. Bulls will keep buying the dips as long as the price action holds above it.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Third, a possible bullish flag, marked in blue on the chart above, has a target of $35k for Bitcoin, as indicated by its measured move.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Therefore, today&rsquo;s NFP report can be the one to make or break the trend. On a better-than-expected report, Bitcoin might test the trendline as the dollar should strengthen. On the other hand, if the US economy added fewer jobs in July than the market expects, Bitcoin might go for the bullish flag&rsquo;s measured move in the days to come.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/should-you-buy-or-sell-bitcoin-ahead-of-the-july-nfp-report/">Should you buy or sell Bitcoin ahead of the July NFP report?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/should-you-buy-or-sell-bitcoin-ahead-of-the-july-nfp-report/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
