<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 19:02:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Pancake Protectors to Bring Play-to-Earn to Gaming PancakeSwap Users</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/pancake-protectors-play-to-earn-pancakeswap/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/pancake-protectors-play-to-earn-pancakeswap/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[staff writer]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 19:02:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gaming News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[axie infinity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cake]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pancakeswap]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=256948</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/pancake-protectors-play-to-earn-pancakeswap/">Pancake Protectors to Bring Play-to-Earn to Gaming PancakeSwap Users</a></p>
<p>PancakeSwap launched the play-to-earn game "Pancake Protectors", integrating their native token CAKE and offering rewards up to 10,000 CAKE for top-ranked players.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/pancake-protectors-play-to-earn-pancakeswap/">Pancake Protectors to Bring Play-to-Earn to Gaming PancakeSwap Users</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/pancake-protectors-play-to-earn-pancakeswap/">Pancake Protectors to Bring Play-to-Earn to Gaming PancakeSwap Users</a></p>
<p>On May 29th, PancakeSwap, the decentralized exchange (DEX) operating under the automated market maker (AMM) model, announced the launch of the play-to-earn (P2E) game &#8220;Pancake Protectors&#8221;, powered by GameFi Mobos&#8217; PvP protocol.</p>
<p>Pancake Protectors is based on the subgenre of strategy games known as Tower Defense (TD), where players&#8217; main objective is to protect territories or possessions by strategically placing defensive structures on the assigned map.</p>
<h2>Pancake Protectors Promises to Be a Different P2E Game</h2>
<p>According to PancakeSwap&#8217;s <a href="https://blog.pancakeswap.finance/articles/pancake-protectors-is-here-discover-the-power-of-cake-and-perks-for-pancake-squads-and-bunnies" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announcement</a>, the exchange&#8217;s native token <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/pancake/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CAKE</a> has already been integrated into the game, allowing players to use them to acquire NFT characters with additional benefits such as increased tradability and superior attributes, as well as enhancing their heroes&#8217; abilities and other multiple functions.</p>
<p>Additionally, users will be able to unlock numerous levels, Battle Pass, and Privilege Card by using CAKE, as well as purchase in-game currency and gift packages. Similarly, they will be able to stake CAKE to obtain additional resources.</p>
<p>Regarding rewards, Pancake Protectors will offer exclusive prizes of up to 10,000 CAKE during the first season. The rewards will be distributed through a ranking system among the top 1,000 players, with the first-place winner receiving 1,000 CAKE and those ranked between positions 801 and 1,000 receiving 0.1 CAKE.</p>
<p>Therefore, the higher your ranking position, the more opportunities you have to win up to $1,700 per season, assuming the price of CAKE remains at $1.7.</p>
<h2>CAKE Price Increased by 16% Following the Announcement of Pancake Protectors Launch</h2>
<p>After the news of Pancake Protectors&#8217; launch, CAKE rose by more than 18%, going from $1.54 to $1.82. However, the price experienced a slight pullback and is currently trading at $1,715.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s worth mentioning that CAKE has been one of the most affected tokens during the crypto winter, as it has <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/pancakeswap-cake-plunging/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">fallen</a> by more than 96% from its all-time high of $44.2 reached in April 2021.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="alignnone" src="https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/pancake-protectors-play-to-earn-pancakeswap-1.png" alt="Pancake Protectors to Bring Play-to-Earn to Gaming PancakeSwap Users" width="1024" height="614" /></p>
<p>Although Pancake Protectors offers players the opportunity to earn rewards while playing, it is impossible to say whether it will become the next Axie Infinity or Plant vs. Undead, two of the most famous crypto games in the ecosystem that managed to attract <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/axie-infinity-multi-records-gaming/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">millions of players</a> to the crypto market.</p>
<p>However, for Tower Defense enthusiasts, the play-to-earn option offered by Pancake Protectors can be very appealing. After all, who wouldn&#8217;t want to receive money while having fun?</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-japan-semiconductor-chip-export/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/pancake-protectors-play-to-earn-pancakeswap/">Pancake Protectors to Bring Play-to-Earn to Gaming PancakeSwap Users</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/pancake-protectors-play-to-earn-pancakeswap/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>China Persuades Japan to Lift Restrictions on Semiconductor Chip Export to Harmonize International Trade</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-japan-semiconductor-chip-export/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-japan-semiconductor-chip-export/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 16:58:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[g7]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nvidia]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=256936</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-japan-semiconductor-chip-export/">China Persuades Japan to Lift Restrictions on Semiconductor Chip Export to Harmonize International Trade</a></p>
<p>China has agreed to work with Japan to promote practical cooperation in key economic and trade areas including advancements in the semiconductor industry.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-japan-semiconductor-chip-export/">China Persuades Japan to Lift Restrictions on Semiconductor Chip Export to Harmonize International Trade</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-japan-semiconductor-chip-export/">China Persuades Japan to Lift Restrictions on Semiconductor Chip Export to Harmonize International Trade</a></p>
<p>The global geopolitical crisis has significantly impacted the overall development of technology. The ongoing war between Ukraine and Russia, which is estimated to take several years to resolve, has significantly increased the rift between global military superpowers. Moreover, the United States has significantly influenced other nations with high-tech capabilities in Europe and Asia to sideline Russia and China in regard to semiconductor cup developments.</p>
<h2>China Fights Back through Japan</h2>
<p>The People&#8217;s Republic of China has been at loggerheads with the United States over the control of global semiconductors for several years. Before the Covid-19 pandemic, the Trump administration had initiated several measures to prevent Chinese tech companies from accessing United States-made semiconductor chips among other technologies. As a result, Chinese-based tech companies including Huawei Technologies Co. have not been able to access key technologies from the United States and its allies.</p>
<p>In its defense, the United States government has cited security reasons, blaming the Chinese counterparts for using their technologies to advance nuclear weapons advancements. With China being accused of helping Russia evade sanctions put in place by Western countries, United States allies have played along the White House card.</p>
<p>In the latest developments, Chinese Commerce Minister Wang Wentao has asked the Japanese official to lift the restrictions on semiconductor chip export control. Notably, Wentao described the Japanese semiconductor export control measure as a wrongdoing that seriously violated international economic and trade rules.</p>
<p>The statements from Wentao to the Japanese Trade Minister Yasutoshi Nishimura were made on May 26 at the Asia-Pacific Economic Cooperation (APEC) conference in Detroit. Already, Japan and Netherlands have played along the United States rules to sideline the Chinese demands on semiconductor chips.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, the G7 nations led by the United States agreed to de-risk but not to decouple from China.</p>
<p>As a result, the Chinese commerce ministry&#8217;s statement on Monday <a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/china-urges-japan-correct-its-wrongdoing-imposing-chip-export-controls-2023-05-29/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">expressed</a> that China &#8220;is willing to work with Japan to promote practical cooperation in key economic and trade areas&#8221;.</p>
<h2>A.I Development as the Bigger Picture</h2>
<p>The huge demand for artificial intelligence (AI) and supercomputers has spiked the need for advanced semiconductor chips. The high chip demand is evident from the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/nvidia/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Nvidia Corporation</a> (NASDAQ: NVDA) stock market which has rallied more than 166 percent YTD to a valuation of about $961.97 billion. In its latest quarterly revenue update, Jensen Huang, founder, and CEO of Nvidia, noted thaat the company is on the move to ramp up chip production to meet the high demand in the artificial intelligence market.</p>
<p>The Chinese government also wants to remain highly competitive in the technology industry including the smartphone sector, 5G network development, digital economy, and artificial intelligence capabilities.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-debt-ceiling-crypto-tax-bill/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-japan-semiconductor-chip-export/">China Persuades Japan to Lift Restrictions on Semiconductor Chip Export to Harmonize International Trade</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-japan-semiconductor-chip-export/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Latest US Debt Ceiling Proposal Strikes Out Unpopular Crypto Tax Bill</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-debt-ceiling-crypto-tax-bill/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-debt-ceiling-crypto-tax-bill/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 16:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[joe biden]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=256920</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-debt-ceiling-crypto-tax-bill/">Latest US Debt Ceiling Proposal Strikes Out Unpopular Crypto Tax Bill</a></p>
<p>The recent US debt ceiling deal has struck out the previous crypto tax bill proposed by the Biden administration. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-debt-ceiling-crypto-tax-bill/">Latest US Debt Ceiling Proposal Strikes Out Unpopular Crypto Tax Bill</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-debt-ceiling-crypto-tax-bill/">Latest US Debt Ceiling Proposal Strikes Out Unpopular Crypto Tax Bill</a></p>
<p>Congressman Warren Davidson has confirmed that the recent <a href="https://docs.house.gov/billsthisweek/20230529/BILLS-118hrPIH-fiscalresponsibility.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener">US debt ceiling deal</a> blocks a potentially pivotal crypto tax bill proposed by the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/joe-biden/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Biden</a> administration. Davidson&#8217;s confirmation came as a <a href="https://twitter.com/WarrenDavidson/status/1663001207651155970?s=20" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">response to a tweet</a> by Bitcoin advocate and Riot Platforms research executive Pierre Rochard asking for clarity.</p>
<p>Following Sunday&#8217;s debt ceiling agreement between US President Joe Biden and House Speaker Kevin McCarthy, Rochard <a href="https://twitter.com/BitcoinPierre/status/1662998382774820864" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">noted</a> the absence of BTC mining in the proposed document. As a result, the VP of Research at Riot Platforms wanted to know whether Biden&#8217;s previously proposed Digital Asset Mining Energy (DAME) excise tax was off the table.</p>
<p>The crypto mining tax bill sought to impose a 30% tax on mining firms. This was to make up for the environmental and societal damage caused by their activities. However, according to Davidson, that proposed crypto tax bill was struck off in Sunday&#8217;s US debt ceiling agreement.</p>
<p>In response to Davidson&#8217;s affirmation, Rochard touched on the implications of the debt ceiling deal, <a href="https://twitter.com/BitcoinPierre/status/1663002157799317504" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">pointing out</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Well, as for the deal as a whole, I think divided government entails negotiation and compromise; elections have consequences. There&#8217;s a big one next year!&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The crypto enthusiast also <a href="https://twitter.com/BitcoinPierre/status/1663004622422679557" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">thanked</a> Davidson for providing clarity and described the Congressman as being receptive to Bitcoin matters.</p>
<h2>Digital Asset Mining Energy (DAME) Tax</h2>
<p>In March, the Biden administration proposed the Digital Asset Mining Energy tax, applicable to two digital asset mining classes. According to DAME, miners operating on Proof-of-Work (PoW) and Proof-of-Stake (PoS) protocols should be held accountable.</p>
<p>The proposed crypto mining tax bill called for all digital miners to disclose information &#8211; including electricity consumption levels &#8211; regardless of inherent consumption differences. The framework also called for disclosing the electricity source and its corresponding value. The Biden administration previously stressed that imposing financial constraints on miners is in America&#8217;s best interest.</p>
<p>However, critics of the so-called crypto mining reform question the perceived double standard of the tax bill. For instance, crypto advocate Robert F. Kennedy Jr <a href="https://twitter.com/RobertKennedyJr/status/1653808852972740608?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1653808852972740608%7Ctwgr%5E79a8f7910486ad745ba13d0258e8ba2ac7a6bd33%7Ctwcon%5Es1_&amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fdecrypt.co%2F142711%2Fus-debt-ceiling-deal-blocks-30-bitcoin-mining-tax-congressman" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">previously argued</a> that Bitcoin mining used roughly the same energy as video games, yet the latter does not face a ban. Earlier this month, Kennedy Jr also <a href="https://twitter.com/RobertKennedyJr/status/1653808786577010697?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1653808852972740608%7Ctwgr%5E79a8f7910486ad745ba13d0258e8ba2ac7a6bd33%7Ctwcon%5Es2_&amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fdecrypt.co%2F142711%2Fus-debt-ceiling-deal-blocks-30-bitcoin-mining-tax-congressman" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">described</a> crypto as a &#8220;major innovation engine&#8221; and called the mining tax a &#8220;bad idea&#8221;.</p>
<h2>US Debt Ceiling Bill Faces Intense Lawmaker Scrutiny Despite Knocking Off Controversial Crypto Tax Proposal</h2>
<p>Despite blocking the mining tax bill, the debt ceiling document still faces intense scrutiny from Congress. Furthermore, the bill, dubbed the &#8220;Fiscal Responsibility 5 Act of 2023,&#8221; has to secure approval from both legislative chamber members before it becomes law. Democratic and Republican lawmakers have to vote on the bill&#8217;s implementation before a June 5th deadline. The US president previously urged both party members to come together to pass the bill swiftly. As Biden said on Sunday, &#8220;The only way forward [is] a bipartisan agreement.&#8221;</p>
<p>Biden&#8217;s proposed debt ceiling bill seeks to suspend the US debt limit until 2025, averting a federal default. Furthermore, the &#8220;Fiscal Responsibility 5 Act of 2023&#8221;, decided upon late Sunday, proposes cutting back on government spending.</p>
<p>Observers believe some of the debt ceiling bill&#8217;s proposed dictates could prove unpopular with Congress and alienate lawmakers. However, Biden remains optimistic that the document would secure the necessary votes for implementation. House Speaker McCarthy also expressed optimism at the voting process outcome, saying, &#8220;People can look together to be able to pass this.&#8221;</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/mediatek-nvidia-ai-automobiles/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-debt-ceiling-crypto-tax-bill/">Latest US Debt Ceiling Proposal Strikes Out Unpopular Crypto Tax Bill</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-debt-ceiling-crypto-tax-bill/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>MediaTek &amp; Nvidia Partner to Enhance User In-Cabin AI Experience in Affordable &amp; Luxurious Automobiles</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/mediatek-nvidia-ai-automobiles/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/mediatek-nvidia-ai-automobiles/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 14:37:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Transportation News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mediatek]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[microsoft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nvidia]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=256889</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/mediatek-nvidia-ai-automobiles/">MediaTek &#038; Nvidia Partner to Enhance User In-Cabin AI Experience in Affordable &#038; Luxurious Automobiles</a></p>
<p>Leading chipmakers MediaTek and Nvidia recently combined resources to “offer a truly unique” in-cabin AI experience in automobiles. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/mediatek-nvidia-ai-automobiles/">MediaTek &#038; Nvidia Partner to Enhance User In-Cabin AI Experience in Affordable &#038; Luxurious Automobiles</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/mediatek-nvidia-ai-automobiles/">MediaTek &#038; Nvidia Partner to Enhance User In-Cabin AI Experience in Affordable &#038; Luxurious Automobiles</a></p>
<p>Taiwan’s MediaTek Inc has <a href="https://blogs.nvidia.com/blog/2023/05/28/mediatek-intelligent-cabin-solutions/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">partnered</a> with US chip-manufacturing giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/nvidia/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NVIDIA</a> (NASDAQ: NVDA) to bring enhanced AI tech to automobiles. The partnership seeks to revamp in-car experiences with software-defined, smart cabin solutions using Nvidia’s GPU chiplets. The joint artificial and accelerated computing offerings would be available in a broad vehicle class range, from entry-level to premium automobiles.</p>
<h2>Executives Comment on MediaTek-Nvidia AI Infotainment Experience for Automobiles</h2>
<p>MediaTek CEO Rick Tsai and NVIDIA founder and CEO Jensen Huang announced the AI-inspired partnership for automobiles at a recent <a href="https://www.nvidia.com/en-us/events/computex/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Computex</a> press conference. Tsai enthused about the collaboration’s prospects and hailed Nvidia’s industry-leading antecedents, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>“NVIDIA is a world-renowned pioneer and industry leader in AI and computing. With this partnership, our collaborative vision is to provide a global one-stop shop for the automotive industry, designing the next generation of intelligent, always-connected vehicles. Through this special collaboration with NVIDIA, we will together be able to offer a truly unique platform for the compute-intensive, software-defined vehicle of the future.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Meanwhile, Huang was equally as upbeat about combining forces with Taiwanese rival MediaTek for the betterment of the automobile industry. The Nvidia chief executive explained that AI and accelerated computing can transform the auto industry. With MediaTek and Nvidia collaborating, car owners will be able to enjoy enhanced safety, improved user experiences, and connected services.</p>
<h2>Details Revealed So Far on Automotive AI Initiative</h2>
<p>By combining Nvidia’s GPUs and AI technology with MediaTek’s chipsets, Huang suggested that the end feature would raise the bar in automobile in-car user experience.</p>
<p>Nvidia develops GPUs for several personal-oriented user devices, including laptops, desktops, workstations, and servers. Additionally, the leading US software and the fabless company also offers systems-on-chips (SoCs) for automotive and robotics applications. MediaTek plans to integrate these sophisticated GPU chiplets into its own automotive SoCs for enhanced automobile AI tech.</p>
<p>The Taiwanese fabless semiconductor company’s specially developed automotive SoCs would feature Nvidia AI and graphics intellectual property in its design architecture. The Nvidia chiplets would also be connected by an ultra-fast chiplet interconnect technology.</p>
<p>Other details regarding the upcoming combined chipset model, including its name or specifications, remain unknown. However, information suggests the automotive AI offering would belong to the MediaTek Dimensity Auto range. Additional information also reveals that a new operating system would power the upcoming infotainment system. According to reports, MediaTek would integrate the Nvidia Drive OS, Drive IX, CUDA, and TensorRT software tech with the new operating system. Alternatively, the blended infotainment development makes more in-vehicle options available to Nvidia Drive platform automakers.</p>
<h2>Nvidia in Blazing Form Could Soon Join Amazon, Apple, in Trillion-Dollar Market Cap Club</h2>
<p>The MediaTek automobile AI development comes on the heels of Nvidia’s <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-trillion-dollar-market-cap/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">rousing run</a> to a trillion-dollar market cap. The Santa Clara-based chip manufacturer has experienced explosive growth in value and is not far from a $1 trillion valuation. Nvidia’s market surge is due to an <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-earnings-ai-rally/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">increased quarterly earnings outlook</a> and better-than-expected sales forecast. The chip maker has boosted production to meet soaring demand due to the fast-growing popularity of accelerated computing and generative AI.</p>
<p>Nvidia’s lofty operational outlook also recently sparked a rally in other tech-exposed companies such as <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/microsoft-corporation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Microsoft</a> (NASDAQ: MSFT) and C3.ai Inc (NYSE: AI).</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gemini-genesis-motion-sec-earn/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/mediatek-nvidia-ai-automobiles/">MediaTek &#038; Nvidia Partner to Enhance User In-Cabin AI Experience in Affordable &#038; Luxurious Automobiles</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/mediatek-nvidia-ai-automobiles/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gemini and Genesis File Motion to Dismiss SEC’s Lawsuit against Earn Program</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/gemini-genesis-motion-sec-earn/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/gemini-genesis-motion-sec-earn/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 13:51:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[earn program]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gemini]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gemini Earn]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[genesis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=256900</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gemini-genesis-motion-sec-earn/">Gemini and Genesis File Motion to Dismiss SEC’s Lawsuit against Earn Program</a></p>
<p>The outcome of the SEC's lawsuit against Gemini and Genesis is expected to have significant implications for the crypto industry and its evolving regulatory landscape.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gemini-genesis-motion-sec-earn/">Gemini and Genesis File Motion to Dismiss SEC’s Lawsuit against Earn Program</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gemini-genesis-motion-sec-earn/">Gemini and Genesis File Motion to Dismiss SEC’s Lawsuit against Earn Program</a></p>
<p>Gemini crypto exchange, and Genesis, an insolvent crypto lender, have jointly <a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.nysd.592343/gov.uscourts.nysd.592343.30.0.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">filed</a> a motion in US federal court, seeking the dismissal of the complaint filed by the United States <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Securities and Exchange Commission</a> (SEC) complaint against the Earn Program.</p>
<p>The SEC alleges that the Earn Program, operated by both firms, violates Federal Securities laws by offering unregistered securities to investors. According to a lawsuit <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-genesis-gemini-securities/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">filed</a> in January, the SEC claims Gemini through its Earn Program raised billions of dollars worth of crypto assets from hundreds of thousands of investors.</p>
<p>Specifically, the SEC highlighted that Genesis held approximately $900 million in assets belonging to 340,000 investors when withdrawals were frozen from the platform in November, which coincided with Genesis filing for bankruptcy protection in the US.</p>
<h2>Gemini Earn: Speaking Up Against the SEC</h2>
<p>In response, both firms say that the SEC&#8217;s assertions are without substance and fail to establish a breach of securities laws. Gemini&#8217;s statement in its recent filings emphasizes its position that it does not require any lending or borrowing by any party participating in the Earn Program.</p>
<p>The firm added that it is only responsible for facilitating lending arrangements between lenders and borrowers and is not involved in the lending process. Furthermore, Gemini highlights two key arguments that the tri-party Master Digital Asset Loan Agreement (MDALA) does not meet the criteria for classification as a security under US securities regulations.</p>
<p>Gemini&#8217;s first argument revolves around the SEC&#8217;s failure to adequately argue that the MDALA meets the legal criteria for being classified as a security. On the other hand, Gemini&#8217;s second argument criticizes the SEC for failing to establish non-conclusive claims of selling or offering the MDALA to any entity.</p>
<p>Gemini Earn is a lending program developed by Gemini that allows customers to lend their crypto to institutional borrowers while earning interest on their investments.</p>
<p>Before Gemini <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gemini-ends-earn-program-genesis/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ended</a> the Earn Program, both firms were collaborating on the operations of the product. Notably, it gained traction in the crypto ecosystem, attracting a large number of individuals looking to profit from their crypto holdings.</p>
<h2>Implications and Future Prospects</h2>
<p>The outcome of the SEC&#8217;s lawsuit against Gemini and Genesis is expected to have significant implications for the crypto industry and its evolving regulatory landscape. A favorable ruling for the companies could affirm the position that the Earn Program does not inherently constitute “security” and may provide clarity for other lending programs in the industry.</p>
<p>On the other hand, if the court upholds the SEC&#8217;s accusations, it might have ramifications for loan programs and exchanges that engage in similar activity. Increased regulatory scrutiny on lending initiatives is possible, which might result in increased compliance requirements and potential limitations on the services provided by crypto platforms.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-ai-supercomputer-computex-2023/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gemini-genesis-motion-sec-earn/">Gemini and Genesis File Motion to Dismiss SEC’s Lawsuit against Earn Program</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/gemini-genesis-motion-sec-earn/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nvidia Unveils DGX GH200 Next-Generation AI Supercomputer at Computex 2023</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-ai-supercomputer-computex-2023/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-ai-supercomputer-computex-2023/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[staff writer]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 13:45:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dgx gh200]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[google cloud]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Meta]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[microsift]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nvidia]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=256884</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-ai-supercomputer-computex-2023/">Nvidia Unveils DGX GH200 Next-Generation AI Supercomputer at Computex 2023</a></p>
<p>Nvidia has announced that the DGX GH200 supercomputer should be ready by the end of 2023.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-ai-supercomputer-computex-2023/">Nvidia Unveils DGX GH200 Next-Generation AI Supercomputer at Computex 2023</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-ai-supercomputer-computex-2023/">Nvidia Unveils DGX GH200 Next-Generation AI Supercomputer at Computex 2023</a></p>
<p>Jensen Huang, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/nvidia/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Nvidia</a> CEO, made some announcements about the company’s DGX GH200 supercomputer during his presentation at Computex, an annual computer expo held in Taiwan. He mentioned that the supercomputer is being created to assist companies in creating generative AI models.</p>
<p>There has been a noticeable shift toward AI-assisted solutions provided by established and emerging tech companies due to numerous businesses integrating AI into their services. Unsurprisingly, the DGX GH200 will be involved in creating generative AI models. These neural network-powered models examine past data to find patterns and produce original, creative content. The DGX GH200’s emphasis on helping businesses in this area fits with the wider industry trend toward using AI for improved results.</p>
<p>Jesen Huang indicated that the company is working full force to produce the supercomputer before the end of the year. He also mentioned that the Nvidia Grace Superchips are being worked on, and the Grace platform is growing in its supercomputer achievements. These developments are important to other key announcements he made during his speech at Comptex 2023.</p>
<h2>The Features of the NVIDIA DGX GH200 AI Supercomputer</h2>
<p>The emerging Nvidia supercomputer has some features that make it stand out. It is made up of an NVLink Switch System. That allows the system to permit 256 GH200 Grace Hopper Superhips to work together as a single graphics processing unit. The chips also have powerful properties that help them deliver 1 exaflop performance and 144 terabytes of shared memory. This is nearly 500 times more powerful than a single DGX A100 system.</p>
<p>There is a significant difference between this supercomputer and other similar ones when one looks at the <a href="https://www.top500.org/news/frontier-remains-sole-exaflop-machine-and-retains-top-spot-improving-upon-its-previous-hpl-score/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">list of the top 500 recently released</a>. According to the ranking, Frontier is the only one capable of exaflop-level performance, reaching 1.2 exaflops after an improvement from its initial 1.194 exaflops per second. The Fugaku system in Japan is ranked second on the list, but it lags far behind Frontier in terms of capacity, with a score of 0.442 exaflops per second. Finland’s LUMI system takes third place with a score of 0.3091 exaflops per second.</p>
<p>Given this, one can appreciate Nvidia’s supercomputer’s potential strength, which could rank closely behind Frontier as the second exaflop machine with only a small difference between them.</p>
<p>The DGX GH200 supercomputer has the interest of well-known technology companies like <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/meta/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Meta</a>, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/microsoft/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Microsoft</a>, and Google Cloud. These businesses are anticipated to be among the solution’s early adopters, testing it to see how well it can handle tasks and heavy workloads.</p>
<p>One of Nvidia’s ongoing projects is the AI models for gaming applications, which aim to help game developers create unique character conversations and animation models. The idea is to give video game characters better conversational skills to interact in the gaming world in a more natural manner.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/reddit-collectible-avatars-10m-users/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-ai-supercomputer-computex-2023/">Nvidia Unveils DGX GH200 Next-Generation AI Supercomputer at Computex 2023</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-ai-supercomputer-computex-2023/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Reddit Collectible Avatars Has More Than 10M Users Now</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/reddit-collectible-avatars-10m-users/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/reddit-collectible-avatars-10m-users/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 12:50:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[reddit]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=256857</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/reddit-collectible-avatars-10m-users/">Reddit Collectible Avatars Has More Than 10M Users Now</a></p>
<p>There are currently a total of 9,909,465 million holders for the Reddit collectible avatars aka the Reddit NFTs. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/reddit-collectible-avatars-10m-users/">Reddit Collectible Avatars Has More Than 10M Users Now</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/reddit-collectible-avatars-10m-users/">Reddit Collectible Avatars Has More Than 10M Users Now</a></p>
<p>Just within 11 months since its launch in July 2022, Reddit Collectible Avatars have seen massive traction with more than 10 million holders of its collectible avatars.</p>
<p>As per the <a href="https://dune.com/polygon_analytics/reddit-collectible-avatars" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">data</a> from Dune Analytics, there are currently a total of 9,909,465 million holders for the Reddit collectible avatars aka the Reddit NFTs. Of them, 7.7 million holders have been identified as single collective avatar holders. These are the holders that do not have multiple wallets.</p>
<p>As said, last year in July 2022, Reddit launched a collectible avatar marketplace on <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a>&#8216;s Layer-2 scalability platform Polygon. All of the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NFTs</a> within the customizable collection have been designed by independent artists as well as Reddit content creators.</p>
<p>Reddit has successfully introduced its Polygon-based NFTs called Collectible Avatars. It allows users to showcase diverse avatars on social media platforms, marking a significant achievement in bringing NFTs to its mainstream audience.</p>
<p>Following the launch of the Reddit NFTs, avatar holders surged fast. However, soon by November 2022, the total avatar holders reached a plateau of 3 million. Also, this year in 2023, there&#8217;s a massive growth spurt with the total number of wallets tripling in just the last six months.</p>
<h2>The Surge in Reddit NFT Holders</h2>
<p>Since the beginning of 2023, the total number of Reddit NFT holders has surged by 80%. Currently, the collection has a total of 13.7 million NFT avatars, and the total market cap of Reddit Collectible Avatars has surged to $38.4 million.</p>
<p>Furthermore, data shows that the total sale of Reddit NFTs has been 303,033 of which the cumulative sales volume has reached $32.6 million. On Sunday, May 28, popular Redditor “ContextMelodic4212” congratulated the platform on the achievement but also added that the bot activity could be responsible partly for the growth. The Redditor <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/13uate7/well_done_reddit_you_onboarded_almost_10m_users/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">added</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Actually there are some issues here and there with Avatars getting scooped or botted by some, it’s far from being perfect. However, I can’t think of a better use case for this technology!”</p></blockquote>
<p>Last week, the social media platform Reddit also announced support for gaming giant Ubisoft’s Rabbids NFT collection. All the Redditors started claiming free Rabbids NFT avatars for their profiles on the platform.</p>
<blockquote>
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Who knew a plunger was just what your Avatar needed? 🪠 In partnership with Ubisoft, we’re bringing <a href="https://twitter.com/RabbidsOfficial?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@RabbidsOfficial</a> to Reddit! Get your Rabbids <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/RedditCollectibles?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#RedditCollectibles</a> now.<a href="https://t.co/e81Zn0Yr6S">https://t.co/e81Zn0Yr6S</a> <a href="https://t.co/1lKFUU0rrJ">pic.twitter.com/1lKFUU0rrJ</a></p>
<p>— Reddit (@Reddit) <a href="https://twitter.com/Reddit/status/1661821118917779457?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">May 25, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>In 2006, Rabbids emerged as a spin-off video game from the Rayman series. In December 2021, Ubisoft became the first major publisher to introduce in-game NFT items. The Rabbids NFT avatar collection was subsequently launched for The Sandbox metaverse game in February.</p>
<p>Last week, Polygon co-founder Sandeep Nainwal also said that he&#8217;s a big fan of Reddit NFTs. He added:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Reddit is perhaps the only well-known Big Tech company who has cracked the NFT code and they are able to drive a lot of engagement with Reddit NFTs.”</p></blockquote>
<p>He also made some suggestions stating that a secondary marketplace and an artist launchpad “could be some great additions to take Reddit NFTs to the next level”.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/wharton-jeremy-siegel-ai-bubble/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/reddit-collectible-avatars-10m-users/">Reddit Collectible Avatars Has More Than 10M Users Now</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/reddit-collectible-avatars-10m-users/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Wharton Professor Jeremy Siegel Says AI Surge Is Not Bubble Yet</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wharton-jeremy-siegel-ai-bubble/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wharton-jeremy-siegel-ai-bubble/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[staff writer]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 12:27:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[adobe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ai]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Amazon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[aws]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blizzard]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chatgpt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[openai]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=256877</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/wharton-jeremy-siegel-ai-bubble/">Wharton Professor Jeremy Siegel Says AI Surge Is Not Bubble Yet</a></p>
<p>The high demand for AI stocks has raised concerns about a possible bubble, as many investors are pumping funds into AI technologies. However, renowned economist Jeremy Siegel believes it's not yet time for a bubble.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/wharton-jeremy-siegel-ai-bubble/">Wharton Professor Jeremy Siegel Says AI Surge Is Not Bubble Yet</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/wharton-jeremy-siegel-ai-bubble/">Wharton Professor Jeremy Siegel Says AI Surge Is Not Bubble Yet</a></p>
<p>Investors are placing big bets on the potential for artificial intelligence (AI) as the technology continues to boom. While some have expressed concerns about a possible bubble forming in the AI market, Jeremy James Siegel, a renowned economist, and Russell E. Palmer, professor of finance at the Wharton University of Pennsylvania, remain optimistic, stating that it is not a bubble yet.</p>
<p>In an <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/29/its-not-a-bubble-yet-whartons-jeremy-siegel-predicts-big-tech-boom-fueled-by-ai.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">interview</a> with CNBC on Monday, Siegel disclosed that the current situation differs from the dot-com bubble of the late 1990s, referring to a period between 1995 and 2000 when investors bought stocks of internet-based startups hoping for high returns but were met with market failures instead.</p>
<p>The Wharton professor said that he has been getting questions about whether the increased interest in AI would lead to a repeat event of the dot-com bubble.</p>
<h2>Nvidia Reports Impressive Q1 Earnings Fueled by Interest in AI</h2>
<p>Siegel believes that the current excitement around AI is driven by two things: the interest in the technology and the success of companies like Nvidia, a leading provider of AI chips. Nvidia, an American-based multinational tech firm, recently <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvda-shares-ath-nvidia-q1-ai/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a> blowout earnings in the just-concluded quarter. This caused its shares to rally by 24% and reach an all-time high.</p>
<p>The demand for Nvidia&#8217;s chips in AI applications has been skyrocketing, driving the company&#8217;s market capitalization close to $1 trillion. During the earnings call, Nvidia&#8217;s CEO, Jensen Huang, confirmed the surging demand for their data center products. Year-to-date, Nvidia shares have surged by an impressive 166%.</p>
<p>While the Wharton professor acknowledges that Nvidia shares may be slightly overvalued in the long term, he emphasizes that momentum can carry stocks far higher than their fundamental value in the short term, noting that predicting how high these shares might go is difficult.</p>
<p>″[In the] long term I would say that [Nvidia shares] were probably slightly overvalued. But for the short term, we know momentum can carry stocks far higher than their fundamental value, and no one can predict how high they might go,” Siegel said.</p>
<h2>Is AI Changing the World? A Look at the Latest Trends</h2>
<p>Since the launch of ChatGPT, a generative AI chatbot designed by OpenAI in November last year, interest in such technologies has skyrocketed, causing panic that AI might replace humans.</p>
<p>Companies like Adobe and Activision Blizzard have recently joined the AI bandwagon to empower human creativity.</p>
<p>Earlier this month, Adobe <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/adobe-blizzard-generative-ai-tools/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">introduced</a> its &#8220;Generative Fill&#8221; AI to support graphic designers using Photoshop to create unique content. Like Adobe, Blizzard also plans to launch an image-generating system to assist humans.</p>
<p>In April, e-commerce giant Amazon <a href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/announcing-new-tools-for-building-with-generative-ai-on-aws/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announced</a> the launch of its &#8220;Amazon Bedrock&#8221;, which offers Amazon Web Service (AWS) users the opportunity to build their own generative AI technologies using its foundation models (FMs).</p>
<p>The company aims to make AI development more accessible by providing a secure online service that enables corporate entities to create their own applications.</p>
<p>Amazon claims that the new service can run AI software more effectively and affordably than other competitors, aiming to make AI technology available to a broader range of businesses.</p>
<p>In addition to Amazon Bedrock, the e-commerce giant has <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/amazon-artificial-intelligence/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">incorporated</a> AI into its platform to improve its delivery speed. The new tool will assist shoppers in locating the nearest warehouse with the products the customer needs.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fantom-gas-monetization-developers/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/wharton-jeremy-siegel-ai-bubble/">Wharton Professor Jeremy Siegel Says AI Surge Is Not Bubble Yet</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wharton-jeremy-siegel-ai-bubble/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fantom Launches Gas Monetization Feature with Incentives for Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fantom-gas-monetization-developers/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fantom-gas-monetization-developers/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 12:13:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fantom]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftm]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gas Fee]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Incentivization]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=256861</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fantom-gas-monetization-developers/">Fantom Launches Gas Monetization Feature with Incentives for Developers</a></p>
<p>The gas monetization functionality encourages a more inclusive and robust developer ecosystem on the Fantom platform.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fantom-gas-monetization-developers/">Fantom Launches Gas Monetization Feature with Incentives for Developers</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fantom-gas-monetization-developers/">Fantom Launches Gas Monetization Feature with Incentives for Developers</a></p>
<p>Blockchain protocol Fantom (FTM) <a href="https://twitter.com/AndreCronjeTech/status/1662762820155342848" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announced</a> on Twitter that it has released a gas monetization feature that will enable its developers to receive 15% of the gas commissions generated.</p>
<p>With this groundbreaking development, Fantom is set to revolutionize the landscape of decentralized application (dApp) development and incentivize developers to build innovative solutions on its blockchain platform.</p>
<p>Based on the data provided, Fantom’s current available funds for the program amount to 10,492 FTM. Out of the total available funds, 514 FTM has been distributed, while the total generated funds amount to 11,006 FTM. While Fantom did not give further details about the update, some Twitter users have asked a variety of questions such as whether the incentive will also be beneficial to investors as rewards.</p>
<p>Notably, gas fees have long been a source of concern among blockchain developers and users. These fees are essentially transaction charges incurred when executing operations on a blockchain network, and they are critical in ensuring the network&#8217;s security and integrity.</p>
<p>However, they can frequently constitute a barrier to entry for developers, particularly in times of high network congestion which causes soaring gas prices. Therefore, Fantom&#8217;s gas monetization functionality strives to address this issue by giving developers a unique opportunity to recoup a percentage of the gas revenues generated through their dApps.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Fantom is not the first platform to consider developers in terms of hefty gas fees. In the past, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/matic-network/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Polygon</a>, Ethereum&#8217;s Layer-2 scalability platform, agreed on a hardfork to handle gas spikes and chain reorganization problems.</p>
<h2>Advantages of Fantom’s Gas Monetization Feature</h2>
<p>The gas monetization functionality encourages a more inclusive and robust developer ecosystem on the Fantom platform. It will encourage developers to contribute their ideas and expertise, knowing that they will be rewarded for their work.</p>
<p>This incentive structure could attract a diverse variety of developers, resulting in more creativity and a wider selection of high-quality DApps on the Fantom network. This can create a stronger incentive for developers to hold onto their earned tokens, as their value is tied to the success and growth of the Fantom platform.</p>
<p>Increased token holding among developers can reduce sell pressure in the market, potentially stabilizing or positively influencing the token&#8217;s price. Recall that the Fantom token has witnessed a more severe drop in value in recent times, which has raised concerns for investors.</p>
<p>In addition to benefiting developers, this feature also offers advantages to the Fantom ecosystem as a whole. By encouraging more developers to join the platform and build on Fantom, the network stands to gain a richer assortment of applications and services.</p>
<p>This, in turn, can drive user adoption and increase overall network usage, further solidifying Fantom&#8217;s position as a leading blockchain platform. By introducing this innovative incentive model, Fantom is taking a proactive step to nurture its developer community and encourage the creation of cutting-edge decentralized applications.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-markets-higher-us-debt/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fantom-gas-monetization-developers/">Fantom Launches Gas Monetization Feature with Incentives for Developers</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fantom-gas-monetization-developers/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>European Markets Open Higher Following US Debt Ceiling Deal</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-markets-higher-us-debt/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-markets-higher-us-debt/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 11:14:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Indices]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cac40]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dax]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[joe biden]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nvidia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stoxx 600]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=256844</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-markets-higher-us-debt/">European Markets Open Higher Following US Debt Ceiling Deal</a></p>
<p>European stock markets were higher in pre-trade amid impending Congress vote on the proposed US debt ceiling bill.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-markets-higher-us-debt/">European Markets Open Higher Following US Debt Ceiling Deal</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-markets-higher-us-debt/">European Markets Open Higher Following US Debt Ceiling Deal</a></p>
<p>European markets <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/29/european-markets-live-updates-stocks-news-data-and-earnings.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">opened higher</a> on Monday following the US debt ceiling deal between President <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/joe-biden/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Joe Biden</a> and House Speaker Kevin McCarthy. Over the weekend, the two high-ranking politicians finally agreed to raise the US debt ceiling, thereby preventing a default. In light of the deal, Biden and McCarthy now seek to convince Congress to approve implementation in the coming week.</p>
<h2>European Markets Respond Positively to US Debt Ceiling Development Following Choppy Week</h2>
<p>The development of the US debt ceiling saw European stock markets, including Germany’s DAX and France’s CAC40, up 0.5% in pre-trade. All sectors were marginally higher, with autos and banks at the forefront of gains. The European market upswing also follows a turbulent week where the Stoxx 600 index slumped to an 8-week low before paring some losses Friday. The pan-European index closed 1.2% higher on May 26th after enduring three negative sessions that saw it fall to its lowest level since early April.</p>
<p>On Friday, all sectors closed in positive territory, with tech stocks leading the way following <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/nvidia/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Nvidia</a>’s (NASDAQ: NVDA) stellar operational outlook.</p>
<p>UK markets are closed today for a bank holiday, while US markets remain closed for Memorial Day.</p>
<h2>Takeaways from Debt Ceiling Development</h2>
<p>On Friday, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-treasury-yield-debt-ceiling/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">US Treasury yields fell</a> as investors awaited updates on debt ceiling negotiations and the release of critical inflation data. However, following successful debt ceiling negotiations between US political leaders, Republican and Democratic lawmakers must now vote to support the new bill. Biden and McCarthy’s proposed measure must secure enough bipartisan Congress support before the June 5th deadline to avoid a potential first-ever government default.</p>
<p>However, reports suggest that the US House of Representatives could vote by Wednesday, with the upper chamber following suit later this week. With debt-limit negotiators quickly drafting the bill’s wording, Biden expressed relief at the agreeable conclusion between himself and McCarthy. On Sunday evening at the White House, the Democratic US president described the outcome with the Republican speaker as “good news”. Furthermore, Biden added late yesterday:</p>
<blockquote><p>“The [debt-ceiling] agreement prevents the worst possible crisis, a default, for the first time in our nation’s history. Takes the threat of a catastrophic default off the table.”</p></blockquote>
<p>The US president also urged both parties in the legislature to come together to pass the bill swiftly. “The speaker and I made clear from the start that the only way forward was a bipartisan agreement,” Biden pointed out.</p>
<h2>A Lot at Stake with Impending US Debt Ceiling Bill Voting Session</h2>
<p>The debt-ceiling agreement proposes spending cuts but could alienate some lawmakers as they inspect the bill’s inherent concessions. However, Biden remains confident that the bill would secure the necessary votes to see implementation. McCarthy also expressed optimism at the outcome of the voting process, saying, “[ultimately] people can look together to be able to pass this”.</p>
<p>A US debt default could freeze the already compromised financial markets and trigger a global fiscal crisis. Should this occur, analysts predict widespread doom, including sky-high unemployment and borrowing rates, and a stock-market plunge. Furthermore, analysts also say a default could impact the Treasury debt market and erode household wealth.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/biden-debt-ceiling-japanese-market/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-markets-higher-us-debt/">European Markets Open Higher Following US Debt Ceiling Deal</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-markets-higher-us-debt/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4259 metric#misses=42 metric#hit-ratio=99.0 metric#bytes=1173975 metric#prefetches=193 metric#store-reads=20 metric#store-writes=2 metric#store-hits=199 metric#store-misses=3 metric#sql-queries=34 metric#ms-total=96.93 metric#ms-cache=5.18 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.2466 metric#ms-cache-ratio=5.3 -->