<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
>

<channel>
	<title>CoinCu News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://coincu.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coincu.com</link>
	<description>Coin and Crypto Infomation Update</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 04:05:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/cropped-Screen-Shot-2022-05-31-at-14.56.39-32x32.png</url>
	<title>CoinCu News</title>
	<link>https://coincu.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>ShapeShiftÂ Reviews: Your Multi-Chain Crypto Home Base?</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/199586-shapeshift-reviews-your-multi-chain-crypto/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Annie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 03:59:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange Reviews]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Multi-Chain Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ShapeShift]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=199586</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[ShapeShift is known for its simple and secure approach to cryptocurrency trading, offering users the ability to swap cryptocurrencies quickly and privately without the need for an account. What Is ShapeShift? ShapeShift is a popular cryptocurrency exchange platform that allows users to quickly and easily trade one cryptocurrency for another without the need for creating [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>ShapeShift is known for its simple and secure approach to cryptocurrency trading, offering users the ability to swap cryptocurrencies quickly and privately without the need for an account.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image is-style-default">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-96.png"><img decoding="async" width="1024" height="477" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-96-1024x477.png" alt="ShapeShiftÂ Reviews: Your Multi-Chain Crypto Home Base?" class="wp-image-199607" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-96-1024x477.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-96-300x140.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-96-768x357.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-96-1536x715.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-96-2048x953.png 2048w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-96-750x349.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-96-1140x531.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="ShapeShiftÂ Reviews: Your Multi-Chain Crypto Home Base? 1"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">What Is ShapeShift?</h2>


<div class="wp-block-image is-style-default">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-98.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="512" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-98-1024x512.png" alt="ShapeShiftÂ Reviews: Your Multi-Chain Crypto Home Base?" class="wp-image-199609" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-98-1024x512.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-98-300x150.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-98-768x384.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-98-360x180.png 360w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-98-750x375.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-98-1140x570.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-98.png 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="ShapeShiftÂ Reviews: Your Multi-Chain Crypto Home Base? 2"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>ShapeShift is a popular cryptocurrency exchange platform that allows users to quickly and easily trade one cryptocurrency for another without the need for creating an account or undergoing a lengthy registration process. It was founded in 2014 by Erik Voorhees and has gained recognition in the crypto community for its simplicity and privacy-focused approach.</p>



<p>ShapeShift is its ability to facilitate instant cryptocurrency swaps. Users can select the cryptocurrency they want to convert and the cryptocurrency they want to receive, and ShapeShift will execute the trade at the current exchange rate. ShapeShift supports a wide range of cryptocurrencies, making it convenient for users to exchange various digital assets.</p>



<p>ShapeShift is its non-custodial nature. Unlike traditional exchanges, ShapeShift does not hold user funds in its platform. Instead, it enables direct peer-to-peer transactions between users&#8217; wallets, allowing for increased security and control over their assets. This also means that ShapeShift does not require users to create an account or provide personal information, enhancing privacy and anonymity.</p>



<p>ShapeShift has evolved over time and introduced additional features to its platform. This includes the ShapeShift API, which allows developers to integrate ShapeShift functionality into their own applications, and ShapeShift Membership, a subscription-based program that offers benefits such as higher trading limits and rewards.</p>



<p>ShapeShift underwent a significant change in 2021, transitioning from its original model to a decentralized exchange (DEX) known as ShapeShift DAO. As a DEX, ShapeShift DAO operates on a blockchain network, enabling users to trade cryptocurrencies in a decentralized manner while maintaining control over their funds.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">How Does ShapeShift Work?</h2>


<div class="wp-block-image is-style-default">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-97.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="513" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-97-1024x513.png" alt="ShapeShiftÂ Reviews: Your Multi-Chain Crypto Home Base?" class="wp-image-199608" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-97-1024x513.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-97-300x150.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-97-768x385.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-97-1536x770.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-97-2048x1027.png 2048w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-97-360x180.png 360w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-97-750x376.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-97-1140x572.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="ShapeShiftÂ Reviews: Your Multi-Chain Crypto Home Base? 3"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>ShapeShift works as a cryptocurrency exchange platform that allows users to trade one cryptocurrency for another in a quick and straightforward manner. Here&#8217;s an overview of how SS typically operates:</p>



<ol>
<li>Selection of Cryptocurrencies: Users start by selecting the cryptocurrencies they want to exchange. SS supports a wide range of cryptocurrencies, including popular ones like Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH), Ripple (XRP), and many others.</li>



<li>Input of Receiving Address: Users provide the wallet address where they want to receive the converted cryptocurrency. This address must correspond to the selected cryptocurrency.</li>



<li>Confirmation of Transaction Details: SS displays the exchange rate and the amount of cryptocurrency that will be received based on the current market rate. Users review and confirm the transaction details before proceeding.</li>



<li>Sending the Initial Cryptocurrency: Users initiate the trade by sending the initial cryptocurrency they want to exchange to a unique deposit address provided by SS. This can be done by scanning a QR code or manually entering the address.</li>



<li>Verification of Transaction: SS monitors the blockchain network to confirm the receipt of the initial cryptocurrency. Once the transaction is verified, SS proceeds to the next step.</li>



<li>Sending the Converted Cryptocurrency: After the verification, SS sends the converted cryptocurrency to the receiving wallet address specified by the user. The transaction is executed at the current exchange rate provided at the beginning of the process.</li>



<li>Transaction Completion: Once the converted cryptocurrency is sent, the transaction is considered complete. Users can verify the transaction on the blockchain network by checking the receiving wallet address.</li>
</ol>



<p>ShapeShift operates as a non-custodial exchange, meaning it does not hold user funds or require user accounts. Users maintain control over their wallets and private keys throughout the exchange process, which enhances security and privacy. However, it also means that ShapeShift does not offer features like account balances or transaction history.</p>



<p>ShapeShift provides a user-friendly interface on its website and also offers an API for developers to integrate its functionality into their own applications. By simplifying the cryptocurrency exchange process and emphasizing user control and privacy, ShapeShift aims to provide a convenient solution for users seeking to swap cryptocurrencies efficiently.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Features of ShapeShift</h2>


<div class="wp-block-image is-style-default">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-99.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="600" height="240" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-99.png" alt="ShapeShiftÂ Reviews: Your Multi-Chain Crypto Home Base?" class="wp-image-199610" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-99.png 600w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-99-300x120.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" title="ShapeShiftÂ Reviews: Your Multi-Chain Crypto Home Base? 4"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>ShapeShift offers several features that make it a popular choice for users looking to exchange cryptocurrencies quickly and conveniently. Here are some key features of ShapeShift:</p>



<ol>
<li>Instant Cryptocurrency Exchange: SS enables instant cryptocurrency exchanges, allowing users to trade one cryptocurrency for another in a seamless manner. The exchange is executed at the current market rate, providing users with immediate access to the desired cryptocurrency.</li>



<li>Wide Range of Supported Cryptocurrencies: SS supports a vast selection of cryptocurrencies, including major coins like Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH), Litecoin (LTC), and many others. This extensive range of supported cryptocurrencies offers users flexibility and options for their trading needs.</li>



<li>Non-Custodial Nature: SS operates as a non-custodial exchange, which means it does not hold user funds or require users to create accounts. Users maintain control over their wallets and private keys throughout the exchange process, enhancing security and privacy.</li>



<li>Simple and User-Friendly Interface: SS is designed with simplicity in mind, providing a user-friendly interface that makes it easy for both beginners and experienced users to navigate and execute cryptocurrency exchanges. The platform focuses on streamlining the exchange process and removing unnecessary complexities.</li>



<li>Privacy and Anonymity: SS prioritizes user privacy by not requiring any personal information during the exchange process. Users can trade cryptocurrencies without the need for account creation or identity verification, enhancing anonymity.</li>



<li>ShapeShift API: SS offers an API (Application Programming Interface) that allows developers to integrate ShapeShift&#8217;s exchange functionality into their own applications or platforms. This enables developers to leverage ShapeShift&#8217;s infrastructure to offer cryptocurrency exchange services to their users.</li>



<li>ShapeShift DAO: SS has transitioned into a decentralized exchange (DEX) known as ShapeShift DAO. As a DEX, ShapeShift DAO operates on a blockchain network and provides users with decentralized trading capabilities.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Pros and Cons</h2>


<div class="wp-block-image is-style-default">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-100.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="508" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-100-1024x508.png" alt="ShapeShiftÂ Reviews: Your Multi-Chain Crypto Home Base?" class="wp-image-199611" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-100-1024x508.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-100-300x149.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-100-768x381.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-100-1536x762.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-100-2048x1017.png 2048w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-100-360x180.png 360w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-100-750x372.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-100-1140x566.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="ShapeShiftÂ Reviews: Your Multi-Chain Crypto Home Base? 5"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>Pros of ShapeShift:</p>



<ol>
<li>Instant Exchanges: SS facilitates instant cryptocurrency exchanges, allowing users to quickly swap one digital asset for another without delays or waiting for order matching.</li>



<li>Wide Range of Supported Cryptocurrencies: SS supports a vast selection of cryptocurrencies, giving users access to a diverse range of digital assets for trading.</li>



<li>Non-Custodial and Privacy-Focused: SS operates as a non-custodial exchange, meaning users retain control of their funds and private keys throughout the exchange process. It also prioritizes user privacy by not requiring user accounts or personal information.</li>



<li>User-Friendly Interface: SS provides a user-friendly interface that simplifies the exchange process, making it accessible to both novice and experienced cryptocurrency users.</li>



<li>ShapeShift DAO: SS&#8217;s transition into a decentralized exchange (ShapeShift DAO) allows users to trade cryptocurrencies in a decentralized manner, contributing to the principles of decentralization and blockchain technology.</li>
</ol>



<p>Cons of ShapeShift:</p>



<ol>
<li>Lack of Advanced Trading Features: SS focuses on simplicity and instant exchanges, which means it lacks advanced trading features commonly found on traditional exchanges, such as order books, limit orders, and advanced charting tools.</li>



<li>Lack of Account Features: As a non-custodial exchange, SS does not offer user accounts, balances, or transaction history. This may be a limitation for users who prefer a more comprehensive overview of their trading activities.</li>



<li>Limited Customer Support: SS&#8217;s customer support options are limited compared to traditional exchanges. As a decentralized platform, the support channels may not offer the same level of responsiveness or availability.</li>



<li>Transaction Fees: SS charges fees for cryptocurrency exchanges, and while they are typically included in the exchange rate, they can be higher compared to some traditional exchanges. Users should consider the fees associated with each transaction.</li>



<li>Market Volatility: The instantaneous nature of SS&#8217;s exchanges exposes users to market volatility. The exchange rate may fluctuate during the confirmation process, resulting in slightly different amounts of the converted cryptocurrency.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">How to Trade on ShapeShift?</h2>



<p>To trade on ShapeShift, follow these general steps:</p>



<ol>
<li>Select the Cryptocurrencies: Start by deciding which cryptocurrencies you want to trade. SS supports a wide range of cryptocurrencies, so you have various options to choose from.</li>



<li>Choose the Trading Method: SS offers different ways to trade, depending on your preferences and needs. You can trade directly on the ShapeShift website, use SS&#8217;s API to integrate trading functionality into your own application, or access SS through third-party wallets or platforms that have integrated SS.</li>



<li>Provide Receiving Address: Specify the wallet address where you want to receive the converted cryptocurrency. Make sure to input the correct address for the specific cryptocurrency you wish to receive.</li>



<li>Input Sending Address: Provide the wallet address from which you will send the initial cryptocurrency you want to exchange. Double-check the address to ensure accuracy.</li>



<li>Confirm Transaction Details: Review the exchange rate and the amount of the converted cryptocurrency you will receive. Ensure that the details are correct before proceeding.</li>



<li>Initiate the Trade: Send the initial cryptocurrency to the unique deposit address provided by SS. This can be done by scanning a QR code or manually entering the address. Make sure to send the exact amount required to complete the trade.</li>



<li>Monitor the Transaction: Track the progress of your transaction. SS will verify the transaction on the blockchain network and proceed with the exchange once the initial cryptocurrency is received.</li>



<li>Receive the Converted Cryptocurrency: Once the initial transaction is confirmed, SS will send the converted cryptocurrency to the specified receiving address. The cryptocurrency will be transferred to your wallet.</li>



<li>Verify the Transaction: Check your receiving wallet address to ensure that the converted cryptocurrency has been successfully deposited.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">ShapeShift Fees</h2>



<p>ShapeShift charges fees for its cryptocurrency exchange services. The fee structure of ShapeShift can vary depending on the cryptocurrencies being traded and other factors. Here are some key points to understand about ShapeShift fees:</p>



<ol>
<li>Trading Fees: SS&#8217;s trading fees are included in the exchange rate provided at the beginning of the transaction. The fees are typically calculated as a percentage of the transaction amount and can vary based on market conditions and the specific cryptocurrencies being exchanged.</li>



<li>Network Fees: In addition to trading fees, SS passes on the network fees associated with the blockchain networks used for cryptocurrency transactions. These network fees are required to process and validate transactions on the respective blockchain networks.</li>



<li>Fee Calculation: SS&#8217;s fees are integrated into the exchange rate to provide users with a transparent and simplified trading experience. This means that the exchange rate you see at the beginning of the transaction already includes the applicable fees, so you don&#8217;t need to calculate them separately.</li>



<li>Fee Disclosure: SS provides transparent fee disclosure during the transaction process. Before confirming the trade, you will see the exchange rate and the resulting amount of the converted cryptocurrency, which includes the fees.</li>



<li>Fee Estimation: SS&#8217;s website and API provide fee estimation tools that allow users to get an estimate of the trading fees for a particular transaction before initiating the trade. This can help users plan their trades and understand the cost implications.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">ShapeShift App</h2>


<div class="wp-block-image is-style-default">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-101.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="534" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-101-1024x534.png" alt="ShapeShiftÂ Reviews: Your Multi-Chain Crypto Home Base?" class="wp-image-199612" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-101-1024x534.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-101-300x156.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-101-768x401.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-101-1536x801.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-101-2048x1068.png 2048w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-101-750x391.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-101-1140x595.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="ShapeShiftÂ Reviews: Your Multi-Chain Crypto Home Base? 6"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>ShapeShift had a mobile app available for both iOS and Android devices. The ShapeShift app provided users with a convenient way to access and manage their cryptocurrency exchanges on the go. However, it&#8217;s important to note that the availability and features of the ShapeShift app may have evolved or changed since then, and I recommend checking the official ShapeShift website or app store for the most up-to-date information on the ShapeShift app.</p>



<ol>
<li>Cryptocurrency Trading: The SS app likely allows users to trade one cryptocurrency for another directly from their mobile devices. Users can select the cryptocurrencies they want to exchange, input the necessary addresses, and complete the transactions.</li>



<li>Wallet Integration: The app may integrate with users&#8217; cryptocurrency wallets, allowing them to securely store and manage their digital assets within the app. This integration simplifies the process of initiating trades and accessing funds for exchanges.</li>



<li>Account Management: The SS app might offer features for managing user accounts, such as viewing transaction history, checking balances, and monitoring the status of ongoing trades.</li>



<li>Price Tracking and Alerts: SS app users may have access to real-time cryptocurrency price tracking, enabling them to stay updated on market trends. Additionally, the app might provide price alerts to notify users of significant price movements or specific price targets.</li>



<li>Security Features: ShapeShift likely incorporates security measures in its app, such as encryption, two-factor authentication (2FA), and biometric authentication (e.g., fingerprint or face recognition) to ensure the safety of user accounts and transactions.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">ShapeShift Security</h2>



<p>ShapeShift places a strong emphasis on security to protect user funds and personal information. Here are some of the security measures and practices employed by ShapeShift:</p>



<ol>
<li>Non-Custodial Model: SS operates as a non-custodial exchange, which means that it does not hold user funds. Users retain control over their wallets and private keys throughout the exchange process. This reduces the risk of hacking or theft from centralized exchange wallets.</li>



<li>Two-Factor Authentication (2FA): SS offers optional two-factor authentication as an extra layer of security. Users can enable 2FA using authenticator apps, such as Google Authenticator or Authy, to provide an additional verification step during account access.</li>



<li>Secure Communication: ShapeShift employs encryption protocols, including HTTPS (Hypertext Transfer Protocol Secure), to ensure secure communication between users&#8217; devices and the ShapeShift platform. This helps protect sensitive data from unauthorized access.</li>



<li>Wallet Integration: SS allows users to use their own cryptocurrency wallets for trading. By utilizing existing wallets, users can leverage the security features of their preferred wallet providers, such as hardware wallets or secure software wallets.</li>



<li>Privacy-Focused: SS respects user privacy and does not require users to create accounts or provide personal information during the exchange process. This reduces the risk of data breaches and protects user anonymity.</li>



<li>Ongoing Security Audits: SS conducts regular security audits and assessments to identify and address potential vulnerabilities. This helps ensure that the platform maintains a robust security posture and stays up to date with the latest security best practices.</li>



<li>Bug Bounty Program: ShapeShift operates a bug bounty program, encouraging security researchers and the wider community to report any security vulnerabilities they discover. This allows ShapeShift to address potential issues promptly and reward those who contribute to the platform&#8217;s security.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Conclusion</h2>



<p>ShapeShift caters to users who prioritize simplicity, privacy, and instant exchanges. It is important for users to conduct their own research and understand the fees, risks, and features associated with ShapeShift before engaging in cryptocurrency trading.</p>



<p id="block-643c4ba8-b40b-4525-9a96-f280dbfbeb9d"><strong><em>DISCLAIMER:&nbsp;</em></strong><em>The Information on this&nbsp;website&nbsp;is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>



<p id="block-522ef498-a505-4d0b-9a0d-b2e5cca12111">Join us to keep track of news:&nbsp;<a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right" id="block-4fa7c042-0908-4ee5-9ff4-91607eb34413"><strong>Annie</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right" id="block-84ea04e6-519a-4165-8e39-faa42e0200e5"><strong>Coincu</strong>&nbsp;<strong>New</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ShapeShift-Reviews-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>AzukiDAO&#8217;s Lawsuit With Founder Zagabond To Recover 20,000 ETH Get Support</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/199572-azukidaos-lawsuit-zagabond-founder/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Foxy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 03:49:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[NFTs News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[# Cryptocurrencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[#Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Azuki]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Azuki Elementals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AzukiDAO]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[rug pull]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sue]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Zagabond]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=199572</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Jeremy Cahen founder of NFT marketplace Not Larva Labs, said he would help the AzukiDAO take legal action against co-founder Azuki Zagabond.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>The founder of Not Larva Labs said he has evidence of the Zagabond scam created by Azuki, and he is willing to testify in court.</em></li>



<li><em>AzukiDAO proposes to hire a lawyer to recover 20,000 ETH from the founder of Zagabond and sue the project.</em></li>



<li><em>So far, the vote has exceeded the majority to pass it.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Jeremy Cahen (Twitter nickname PAULY), founder of NFT marketplace Not Larva Labs, said he would happily help the Azuki community take legal action against co-founder Azuki Zagabond.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-90.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="655" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-90-1024x655.png" alt="AzukiDAO&#039;s Lawsuit With Founder Zagabond To Recover 20,000 ETH Get Support" class="wp-image-199588" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-90-1024x655.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-90-300x192.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-90-768x491.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-90-1536x982.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-90-750x480.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-90-1140x729.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-90.png 1681w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="AzukiDAO&#039;s Lawsuit With Founder Zagabond To Recover 20,000 ETH Get Support 7"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>Jeremy Cahen also said that Zagabond and his team fraudulently appropriated more than $100,000,000 from the community. Jeremy would love to testify in court about all this, and I have full personal information about many of the team members involved in these scams.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">I will gladly aid the Azuki community in their legal actions against <a href="https://twitter.com/ZAGABOND?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener">@ZAGABOND</a>.<br><br>He is a pathological liar and serial criminal and I and my colleagues and I spent over a year tracking him down to recover $3,000,000 USDC worth of funds that he defrauded.<br><br>He and his team haveâ€¦ <a href="https://t.co/kqSA7jA6hy" target="_blank">https://t.co/kqSA7jA6hy</a></p>&mdash; PAULY (@Pauly0x) <a href="https://twitter.com/Pauly0x/status/1675583611561443329?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener">July 2, 2023</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>Not Larva Labs founder&#8217;s endorsement of AzukiDAO after the community proposed hiring an attorney to assist the community in recovering 20,000 ETH from Zagabond and suing it yesterday.</p>



<p>Specific content includes: hiring a lawyer to file a lawsuit against Zagabond, the founder of Azuki, accusing the organization of having many Rug projects; withdrawing 20,000 ETH issued by Elementals from the team and distributing it to the DAO to promote the growth of the entire Azuki community and provide rewards and incentives for artists, content creators, and builder. So far, the vote has exceeded the majority to pass it.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-92.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="818" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-92-1024x818.png" alt="AzukiDAO&#039;s Lawsuit With Founder Zagabond To Recover 20,000 ETH Get Support" class="wp-image-199593" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-92-1024x818.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-92-300x240.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-92-768x613.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-92-1536x1226.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-92-750x599.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-92-1140x910.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-92.png 1721w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="AzukiDAO&#039;s Lawsuit With Founder Zagabond To Recover 20,000 ETH Get Support 8"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>Azuki Dao provides financial support for 20000E Dao. Funds will be used to help us organize a Study Group for the Lawsuit. The proposed voting deadline is July 3. It is known that AzukiDAO and 20000E DAO were founded by members and former owners of the Azuki community, not the official Azuki group.</p>



<p>Ahead of the news on May 10, 2022, the founder of the Azuki team, ZAGABOND.ETH, <a href="https://mirror.xyz/0x1Cb8332607fba6A780DdE78584AD3BFD1eEB1E40/yG8rI1lpQGLPhZch0kjxYRjKTtA9rAL51zg-ZrURyAc" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">admitted</a> in a mirror post that the Azuki team has operated three projects CryptoPhunks, Tendies, and CryptoZunks, in the past year.</p>



<p>At the heart of the controversy is their supposed strategy of &#8216;pulling the rug&#8217;, used in the &#8220;Azuki Elementals&#8221; casting process. The move deeply upset the staunch holders of the project.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-91.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="576" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-91-1024x576.png" alt="AzukiDAO&#039;s Lawsuit With Founder Zagabond To Recover 20,000 ETH Get Support" class="wp-image-199591" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-91-1024x576.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-91-300x169.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-91-768x432.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-91-750x422.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-91-1140x641.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-91.png 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="AzukiDAO&#039;s Lawsuit With Founder Zagabond To Recover 20,000 ETH Get Support 9"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>Originating from the launch of Azuki&#8217;s new series, &#8220;Azuki Elementals&#8221;. The series sold out in less than 20 minutes for 2 ETH each, raising an impressive $38 million.</p>



<p>Many issues surfaced during the launch, from grievances about the short 10-minute time period for Mint being whitelisted to site overload leading to Mint errors and duplications &#8211; overduplication of features between the original Azuki and the new Azuki Elementals. Investors expressed concern about the potential dilution of the first-generation Azuki&#8217;s value. The controversy escalated when the project team reportedly moved 20,000 ETH shortly after the launch.</p>



<p>The event was marred with allegations of unfair behavior and the dizzying price drop of the original Azuki collection, which <a href="https://coincu.com/199468-azuki-nft-floor-price-dropped-54-last-7-days/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">plummeted</a> from over 17 ETH just a week ago to just 5.8 ETH.</p>



<p id="block-643c4ba8-b40b-4525-9a96-f280dbfbeb9d"><strong><em>DISCLAIMER:&nbsp;</em></strong><em>The Information on this&nbsp;website&nbsp;is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>



<p id="block-522ef498-a505-4d0b-9a0d-b2e5cca12111">Join us to keep track of news:&nbsp;<a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right" id="block-4fa7c042-0908-4ee5-9ff4-91607eb34413"><strong>Foxy</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right" id="block-84ea04e6-519a-4165-8e39-faa42e0200e5"><strong>Coincu</strong>&nbsp;<strong>News</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Thumb-2023-Foxy-47-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Market Overview Last Week From June 26th To July 2nd</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/199564-market-overview-from-june-26th-to-july-2nd/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[David]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 03:44:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[# Cryptocurrencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[#Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[#marketoverview]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[#Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=199564</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[This document provides a market overview for the week of June 26th to July 2nd. The content includes updates and analyses of market trends and movements during this period. Quick look market overview about big news! Binance&#8217;s L2 opBNB network is currently running on the testnet. There is a lot of information about this airdrop [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>This document provides a market overview for the week of June 26th to July 2nd. The content includes updates and analyses of market trends and movements during this period.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Quick look market overview about big news!</strong></h2>



<p>Binance&#8217;s L2 opBNB network is currently running on the testnet. There is a lot of information about this airdrop with the slogan that if you missed BNB in 2017, you should not miss this one, although Binance has announced that there is no airdrop. The way to do it is similar to other L2s, by going to the faucet token testnet and experiencing it.</p>



<p>Binance Labs announces the results of the 5th Incubation Program, consisting of 5 projects receiving investment out of 12 selected for review: Bracket Labs, DappOS, Kryptoskatt, Mind Network, and zkPass. More than 900 projects were registered for the 5th incubation round, but only 12 were selected for review. Finally, only 5 projects were invested in, showing the program&#8217;s strict requirements. Binance Labs also revealed that the 6th incubation round is about to open for registration. Interested projects should follow Binance&#8217;s Twitter for the latest updates.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-gallery has-nested-images columns-default is-cropped wp-block-gallery-1 is-layout-flex">
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-03_10-25-00.jpg"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="578" data-id="199579" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-03_10-25-00-1024x578.jpg" alt="Market Overview - Binance news
" class="wp-image-199579" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-03_10-25-00-1024x578.jpg 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-03_10-25-00-300x169.jpg 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-03_10-25-00-768x433.jpg 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-03_10-25-00-750x423.jpg 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-03_10-25-00-1140x643.jpg 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-03_10-25-00.jpg 1383w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Market Overview Last Week From June 26th To July 2nd 10"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">Market overview &#8211; Binance news</figcaption></figure>
</figure>



<p>MicroStrategy has just bought an additional 12,333 $BTC. The average estimated price of this amount of $BTC is $28,136, meaning that the fund currently has a profit of ~$27.6M.</p>



<p>The chairman of the Fed said that interest rates could be raised two more times. Some macroeconomic news from last week: The PCE inflation index decreased to 3.8%, much lower than the estimated 4.6%. Core PCE is at 4.6%, lower than the estimated 4.7%.</p>



<p>SEC said: &#8220;BTC ETF applications are not yet complete,&#8221; causing the price of BTC to drop to 29,500 in the middle of the week. Some updates on Bitcoin Spot ETF:</p>



<p>Fidelity, Wisdomtree, Invesco/Galaxy, and VanEck have all amended their proposals for Bitcoin Spot ETF and submitted new versions to the SEC.</p>



<p>ArkInvest also revised its proposal, but only the current version was modified. This means that the SEC did not return the proposal, so over time, if an ETF is approved, Cathie Wood ArkInvest will be the first company.</p>



<p>All proposals state that they: &#8220;expect to participate in a monitoring agreement with Coinbase, Inc.&#8221;</p>



<p>Bitwise also revised its proposal but did not include any sharing agreement language.</p>



<p>Companies are working very quickly.</p>



<p>BlackRock has not yet revised its text, and on the Nasdaq website, BlackRock&#8217;s proposal is still listed as &#8220;pending.&#8221;</p>



<p>It is important to note that the SEC has not made any official announcements, and all information we hear is from the Wall Street Journal.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Market overview &#8211;</strong> <strong>Celsius will begin liquidating its altcoins into BTC and ETH to repay its creditors!</strong></h2>



<figure class="wp-block-gallery has-nested-images columns-default is-cropped wp-block-gallery-3 is-layout-flex">
<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-03_10-25-05.jpg"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="631" height="513" data-id="199580" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-03_10-25-05.jpg" alt="photo 2023 07 03 10 25 05" class="wp-image-199580" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-03_10-25-05.jpg 631w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-03_10-25-05-300x244.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 631px) 100vw, 631px" title="Market Overview Last Week From June 26th To July 2nd 11"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">Market overview &#8211; Celsius</figcaption></figure>
</figure>



<p>The sale begins on July 1st, and some tokens include:</p>



<p>CEL &#8211; $100 million (CEL&#8217;s current market cap is $37 million) </p>



<p>MATIC &#8211; $58 million </p>



<p>ADA &#8211; $28 million </p>



<p>LINK &#8211; $20 million </p>



<p>LTC &#8211; $19 million </p>



<p>BCH &#8211; $15.7 million</p>



<p>So Celsius&#8217; debtors and customers will soon receive their compensation!</p>



<p>Polynetwork has been hacked again. Previously, it was involved in a nearly $600M incident. This time, $42 billion was minted, mostly on Chain Metis. Details:</p>



<p>99,999,184 BNB and 10 billion BUSD were issued on Metis, and 999.8127T SHIB was issued on Heco, 87,579,118 COW and 999,998,434 OOE, 636,643,868 STACK, 88,640,563 GM and 2,175,053 03 were issued on Polygon, and 378,028,371 STACK, 82,854,568 XTM, 11,026,341 SPAY, issued 89,383,712 GM on Avalanche, 8,882,911 METIS, 926,160,132 DOV, 978,102,855 SLD, and other assets were issued on BSC.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Market overview &#8211; Some significant unlocking periods in July.</strong></h2>



<figure class="wp-block-gallery has-nested-images columns-default is-cropped wp-block-gallery-5 is-layout-flex">
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-03_10-25-08.jpg"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="586" data-id="199581" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-03_10-25-08-1024x586.jpg" alt="photo 2023 07 03 10 25 08" class="wp-image-199581" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-03_10-25-08-1024x586.jpg 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-03_10-25-08-300x172.jpg 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-03_10-25-08-768x440.jpg 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-03_10-25-08-750x429.jpg 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-03_10-25-08-1140x653.jpg 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-03_10-25-08.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Market Overview Last Week From June 26th To July 2nd 12"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">Market overview &#8211; Tokens unlocked</figcaption></figure>
</figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Market overview &#8211;</strong> <strong>Update some macro events that may affect crypto in July.</strong></h2>



<p> <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f4cc.png" alt="ðŸ“Œ" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> 1:00 6/7: FOMC Meeting &#8211; High impact </p>



<p><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f4cc.png" alt="ðŸ“Œ" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> 19:15 6/7: ADP Non-farm &#8211; Medium impact</p>



<p> <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f4cc.png" alt="ðŸ“Œ" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> 19:30 6/7: US Unemployment Claims &#8211; Medium impact</p>



<p> <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f4cc.png" alt="ðŸ“Œ" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> 21:00 6/7: ISM Services PMI &#8211; Medium impact </p>



<p><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f4cc.png" alt="ðŸ“Œ" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> 19:30 7/7: Non-farm Payrolls &#8211; High impact </p>



<p><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f4cc.png" alt="ðŸ“Œ" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> 19:30 12/7: US CPI Release &#8211; High impact </p>



<p><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f4cc.png" alt="ðŸ“Œ" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> 19:30 13/7: US PPI Release &#8211; Fairly high impact </p>



<p><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f4cc.png" alt="ðŸ“Œ" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> 19:30 18/7: US Retail Sales &#8211; Fairly high impact </p>



<p><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f4cc.png" alt="ðŸ“Œ" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> 1:00 27/7: FED Interest Rate Decision &#8211; High impact </p>



<p><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f4cc.png" alt="ðŸ“Œ" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> 19:30 27/7: US GDP Release &#8211; High impact </p>



<p><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f4cc.png" alt="ðŸ“Œ" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> 19:30 28/7: US Core PCE &#8211; Fairly high impact.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Market overview &#8211; Trend analysis for this week!</strong></h2>



<p>The trend will likely be POW coins due to next year&#8217;s halving event. Market overview &#8211; Here are some Pow coins in the BTC ecosystem that are frequently mentioned:</p>



<p>$STX &#8211; BTC Layer 2, smart contracts; $BCH &#8211; BTC fork $RIF &#8211; identity &amp; storage $T &#8211; tBTC, a merger between $KEEP and $NU $HARD &#8211; lending &amp; borrowing BTC, KAVA eco $REN &#8211; defi BTC $BADGER &#8211; defi for BTC $PNT &#8211; ptokens for BTC $ALEX: Dex of $STX $SOV: Smartcontract, Lending, Borrowing $PCX: BTC Layer2 omniBTC $ORD: Dex $ML: BTC layer2 (high inflation) $LBTC: Lighting Bitcoin $BC: Old Bitcoin BRC20 $ORDI, $VMPX, $PEPEBRC, $MEMEBRC, $PIZABRC, $TRAC, $BIOP, $BSVBRC &#8230;</p>



<p>This year is the year of Cex fud, so let&#8217;s take a look at Dex</p>



<figure class="wp-block-gallery has-nested-images columns-default is-cropped wp-block-gallery-7 is-layout-flex">
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="661" data-id="199582" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-03_10-25-12-1024x661.jpg" alt="photo 2023 07 03 10 25 12" class="wp-image-199582" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-03_10-25-12-1024x661.jpg 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-03_10-25-12-300x194.jpg 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-03_10-25-12-768x496.jpg 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-03_10-25-12-750x484.jpg 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-03_10-25-12-1140x736.jpg 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-03_10-25-12.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Market Overview Last Week From June 26th To July 2nd 13"><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">Market overview &#8211; DEX trading volume</figcaption></figure>
</figure>



<p>DEX trading <a href="https://coincu.com/198147-may-the-ethereum-price-reach-2000-again/" data-type="URL" data-id="https://coincu.com/198147-may-the-ethereum-price-reach-2000-again/">volume on Ethereum </a>is currently the highest, followed by Arbitrum, BNB Chain, and Polygon.</p>



<p>Since Arbitrum launched its token, it has been relatively quiet, with much Fud about the foundation selling tokens. With this volume, there may be many gems in this ecosystem soon.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER:&nbsp;</em></strong><em>The information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>



<p>Join us to keep track of news:&nbsp;<a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong><em>David</em></strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong><em>Coincu News</em></strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/c7dec957c25c12024b4d-1024x731.jpg" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/jpeg" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>ShakepayÂ Reviews: TheÂ Easiest WayÂ For Canadians To Buy And Earn Bitcoin?</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/199561-shakepay-reviews-canadians-to-buy-earn-bitcoin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Annie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 03:35:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange Reviews]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buy And Earn Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shakepay]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ShakepayÂ Reviews]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=199561</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Shakepay is a Canadian-based cryptocurrency platform and mobile application that offers a user-friendly and convenient way for users to buy, sell, and manage cryptocurrencies. With its intuitive interface, Shakepay simplifies the process of entering the world of cryptocurrencies, particularly for Canadian users. Shakepay&#8217;s key features include the ability to buy and sell cryptocurrencies using Canadian [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Shakepay is a Canadian-based cryptocurrency platform and mobile application that offers a user-friendly and convenient way for users to buy, sell, and manage cryptocurrencies. </p>


<div class="wp-block-image is-style-default">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-86.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="616" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-86-1024x616.png" alt="image 86" class="wp-image-199573" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-86-1024x616.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-86-300x181.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-86-768x462.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-86-1536x924.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-86-2048x1232.png 2048w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-86-750x451.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-86-1140x686.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="ShakepayÂ Reviews: TheÂ Easiest WayÂ For Canadians To Buy And Earn Bitcoin? 14"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>With its intuitive interface, Shakepay simplifies the process of entering the world of cryptocurrencies, particularly for Canadian users.</p>



<p>Shakepay&#8217;s key features include the ability to buy and sell cryptocurrencies using Canadian dollars (CAD), instant transfers between Shakepay users, the SP Card for cryptocurrency spending, and a secure cryptocurrency wallet. The platform emphasizes security by implementing measures like encryption, two-factor authentication, and cold storage for funds.</p>



<p>While Shakepay has its strengths, such as its user-friendly interface and instant transfers, there are also some limitations to consider. Shakepay has a limited selection of cryptocurrencies available for trading, and it is currently only accessible to Canadian residents. The platform charges fees for transactions and services, which users should take into account when using the platform.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">What Is Shakepay?</h2>


<div class="wp-block-image is-style-default">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Shakepay.jpeg"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="535" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Shakepay-1024x535.jpeg" alt="Shakepay" class="wp-image-199574" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Shakepay-1024x535.jpeg 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Shakepay-300x157.jpeg 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Shakepay-768x401.jpeg 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Shakepay-750x392.jpeg 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Shakepay-1140x596.jpeg 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Shakepay.jpeg 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="ShakepayÂ Reviews: TheÂ Easiest WayÂ For Canadians To Buy And Earn Bitcoin? 15"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>Shakepay is a Canadian-based cryptocurrency platform and mobile application that allows users to buy, sell, and trade cryptocurrencies. It was founded in 2015 with the goal of making it easier for people to enter the world of cryptocurrencies. SP provides a user-friendly interface and a seamless experience for buying and selling cryptocurrencies, particularly Bitcoin and Ethereum.</p>



<p>One of the key features of Shakepay is its ability to simplify the process of purchasing cryptocurrencies using Canadian dollars (CAD). Users can link their bank accounts to the SP app and easily transfer funds to buy cryptocurrencies. SP also supports instant fund transfers between Shakepay users, making it convenient for friends or family members to send and receive cryptocurrencies.</p>



<p>Shakepay offers a cryptocurrency wallet where users can securely store their digital assets. The platform prioritizes security and implements various measures, such as multi-factor authentication and cold storage, to protect users&#8217; funds.</p>



<p>Shakepay also offers a Shakepay Card, which is a prepaid Visa card linked to users&#8217; Shakepay accounts. This card allows users to spend their cryptocurrencies at any merchant that accepts Visa, both online and offline. When making a purchase, the Shakepay Card automatically converts the selected cryptocurrency into the local currency, providing a seamless spending experience.</p>



<p>Shakepay aims to provide a user-friendly and accessible platform for Canadians to enter the world of cryptocurrencies, facilitating the buying, selling, and spending of digital assets.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">How Does Shakepay Work?</h2>


<div class="wp-block-image is-style-default">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-87.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="633" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-87-1024x633.png" alt="image 87" class="wp-image-199576" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-87-1024x633.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-87-300x185.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-87-768x475.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-87-1536x949.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-87-2048x1266.png 2048w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-87-750x464.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-87-1140x705.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="ShakepayÂ Reviews: TheÂ Easiest WayÂ For Canadians To Buy And Earn Bitcoin? 16"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>Shakepay works as a cryptocurrency platform and mobile application that simplifies the process of buying, selling, and spending cryptocurrencies. Here&#8217;s an overview of how Shakepay works:</p>



<ol>
<li>Account Creation: To get started with SP, users need to download the SP mobile app from the App Store or Google Play Store. After installing the app, users can create an account by providing their personal information and completing the verification process.</li>



<li>Funding the Account: Once the account is set up, users can link their bank accounts to the SP app. This allows them to transfer funds from their bank account to their SP account in Canadian dollars (CAD). The linked bank account is used to deposit and withdraw funds.</li>



<li>Buying and Selling Cryptocurrencies: With funds in their SP account, users can buy cryptocurrencies, primarily Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH). SP offers a simple interface where users can enter the amount of cryptocurrency they wish to purchase and confirm the transaction. The app will display the current exchange rate and any associated fees. Selling cryptocurrencies follows a similar process, where users can choose to sell their digital assets and receive the proceeds in CAD.</li>



<li>Cryptocurrency Wallet: SP provides a built-in cryptocurrency wallet where users can securely store their digital assets. The wallet supports multiple cryptocurrencies, allowing users to hold and manage different tokens in one place. SP implements security measures, such as two-factor authentication and cold storage, to safeguard users&#8217; funds.</li>



<li>Sending and Receiving Cryptocurrencies: SP allows users to send and receive cryptocurrencies to and from other SP users instantly. Users can simply enter the recipient&#8217;s Shakepay username or scan a QR code to initiate a transfer. This feature makes it convenient for friends or family members to send and receive cryptocurrencies within the SP ecosystem.</li>



<li>Shakepay Card: SP offers a prepaid Visa card known as the SP Card. This card is linked to users&#8217; SP accounts and allows them to spend their cryptocurrencies at any merchant that accepts Visa. When making a purchase, the selected cryptocurrency is automatically converted into the local currency at the current exchange rate, providing a seamless spending experience.</li>



<li>Security and Compliance: SP places a strong emphasis on security and compliance. It employs industry-standard security measures, including encryption, multi-factor authentication, and cold storage for cryptocurrency storage. SP is also regulated by the Financial Transactions and Reports Analysis Centre of Canada (FINTRAC) as a Money Services Business (MSB), ensuring compliance with applicable regulations and Know Your Customer (KYC) requirements.</li>
</ol>



<p>Shakepay simplifies the process of buying, selling, and spending cryptocurrencies by providing a user-friendly interface, instant fund transfers, a secure wallet, and the Shakepay Card for easy cryptocurrency spending.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Features of Shakepay</h2>


<div class="wp-block-image is-style-default">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-88.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="506" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-88-1024x506.png" alt="image 88" class="wp-image-199577" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-88-1024x506.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-88-300x148.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-88-768x380.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-88-1536x759.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-88-2048x1013.png 2048w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-88-750x371.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-88-1140x564.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="ShakepayÂ Reviews: TheÂ Easiest WayÂ For Canadians To Buy And Earn Bitcoin? 17"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>Shakepay offers several features that make it a popular choice for users looking to buy, sell, and manage cryptocurrencies:</p>



<ol>
<li>Buy and Sell Cryptocurrencies: SP allows users to easily buy and sell cryptocurrencies, including Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH), and others. Users can fund their SP accounts using Canadian dollars (CAD) via bank transfers and initiate transactions with competitive pricing.</li>



<li>Shakepay Card: Shakepay offers a prepaid Visa card called the SP Card, which is linked to users&#8217; SP accounts. The card allows users to spend their cryptocurrencies at any merchant that accepts Visa, both online and offline. When making a purchase, the selected cryptocurrency is automatically converted into the local currency, facilitating seamless spending.</li>



<li>Instant Fund Transfers: SP enables instant transfers of funds between Shakepay users. Users can send and receive cryptocurrencies instantly, making it convenient for peer-to-peer transactions or splitting bills among friends and family.</li>



<li>ShakeSats: ShakeSats is a unique feature of SP that allows users to buy and hold satoshis, which are smaller units of Bitcoin. ShakeSats enables users to accumulate small amounts of Bitcoin over time, contributing to the growing adoption and interest in cryptocurrencies.</li>



<li>Cryptocurrency Wallet: SP provides a secure and user-friendly cryptocurrency wallet for storing digital assets. The wallet supports various cryptocurrencies, offering users a convenient way to manage and hold their tokens. SP implements security measures, such as two-factor authentication and cold storage, to protect users&#8217; funds.</li>



<li>Auto-Buy: SP offers an Auto-Buy feature that allows users to set up recurring purchases of cryptocurrencies. Users can schedule automatic purchases at specified intervals, such as daily, weekly, or monthly, helping them to consistently invest in cryptocurrencies.</li>



<li>Shakepay Referral Program: SP has a referral program that rewards users for inviting others to join the platform. Users can earn referral bonuses in Bitcoin for each successful referral, contributing to their cryptocurrency holdings.</li>



<li>Security and Compliance: SP prioritizes the security of user funds and personal information. It employs robust security measures, including encryption, two-factor authentication, and cold storage. SP is also compliant with Canadian regulations as a registered Money Services Business (MSB) and follows Know Your Customer (KYC) procedures.</li>



<li>User Support: SP provides customer support to assist users with any questions or issues they may encounter. Users can reach out to the SP support team via email or in-app chat for prompt assistance.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Pros and Cons</h2>



<p>Pros of Shakepay:</p>



<ol>
<li>User-Friendly Interface: SP offers a user-friendly interface that makes it easy for beginners to navigate and use the platform for buying, selling, and managing cryptocurrencies.</li>



<li>Convenience: SP simplifies the process of buying and selling cryptocurrencies, particularly for Canadian users. It allows users to link their bank accounts, facilitating easy fund transfers and eliminating the need for complex deposit methods.</li>



<li>Instant Transfers: SP enables instant transfers of cryptocurrencies between Shakepay users, providing a convenient way to send and receive digital assets quickly.</li>



<li>Shakepay Card: The SP Card allows users to spend their cryptocurrencies at any merchant that accepts Visa, both online and offline. This feature provides flexibility and convenience for cryptocurrency holders to use their funds in everyday transactions.</li>



<li>Security Measures: SP implements robust security measures, including encryption, two-factor authentication, and cold storage, to protect users&#8217; funds and personal information. It is also regulated as a Money Services Business (MSB), ensuring compliance with relevant regulations.</li>



<li>Cryptocurrency Wallet: SP provides a built-in cryptocurrency wallet where users can securely store their digital assets. The wallet supports multiple cryptocurrencies, making it convenient for users to manage and hold their tokens in one place.</li>



<li>ShakeSats: SP&#8217;s ShakeSats feature allows users to accumulate small amounts of Bitcoin over time, making it accessible for users to participate in the world of cryptocurrencies.</li>
</ol>



<p>Cons of Shakepay:</p>



<ol>
<li>Limited Cryptocurrency Selection: SP primarily focuses on Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH) for buying and selling. While these are the most popular cryptocurrencies, users looking for a wider range of altcoins may find the selection limited.</li>



<li>Availability: SP is currently available only to Canadian residents. Users from other countries are unable to access and use the platform.</li>



<li>Limited Payment Options: SP primarily supports bank transfers as the funding method, which may be restrictive for users who prefer alternative payment methods like credit cards or PayPal.</li>



<li>Exchange Fees: SP charges fees for cryptocurrency transactions, including buying, selling, and converting cryptocurrencies. While the fees are competitive, they still represent an additional cost for users.</li>



<li>Customer Support: While SP offers customer support, some users have reported delays in response times or difficulties in getting their issues resolved promptly.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Shakepay Fees</h2>


<div class="wp-block-image is-style-default">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-89.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="565" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-89-1024x565.png" alt="image 89" class="wp-image-199578" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-89-1024x565.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-89-300x166.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-89-768x424.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-89-1536x847.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-89-2048x1130.png 2048w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-89-750x414.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-89-1140x629.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="ShakepayÂ Reviews: TheÂ Easiest WayÂ For Canadians To Buy And Earn Bitcoin? 18"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p><br>Shakepay charges fees for various transactions and services on its platform. Here is an overview of the main fees associated with Shakepay:</p>



<ol>
<li>Trading Fees: SP charges trading fees when buying or selling cryptocurrencies. The fee structure is based on a percentage of the transaction amount and varies depending on the type of transaction (buy or sell) and the cryptocurrency being traded. The exact fee percentages can be found on the Shakepay website or within the app.</li>



<li>Conversion Fees: Shakepay applies conversion fees when converting between different cryptocurrencies within the platform. The conversion fee is a percentage-based fee applied to the transaction amount</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Shakepay Customer Service</h2>



<p>Shakepay provides customer service to assist users with any inquiries or issues they may encounter. Here are some ways to access Shakepay&#8217;s customer service:</p>



<ol>
<li>In-App Chat: The primary method to reach Shakepay&#8217;s customer service is through the in-app chat feature. Users can access the chat by logging into their SP account on the mobile app and navigating to the &#8220;Support&#8221; section. From there, they can initiate a chat conversation with a SP representative.</li>



<li>Email Support: Users can also contact SP&#8217;s customer service via email. They can send an email to <a href="mailto:support@shakepay.com">support@shakepay.com</a> with their questions or concerns, and a SP representative will respond to their query.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Conclusion</h2>



<p>Shakepay is a reputable and reliable platform for individuals in Canada who want to engage with cryptocurrencies. It provides a seamless user experience, prioritizes security, and offers features like the Shakepay Card to enable cryptocurrency spending. Users should carefully consider their needs and preferences to determine if Shakepay aligns with their requirements for buying, selling, and managing cryptocurrencies.</p>



<p id="block-643c4ba8-b40b-4525-9a96-f280dbfbeb9d"><strong><em>DISCLAIMER:&nbsp;</em></strong><em>The Information on this&nbsp;website&nbsp;is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>



<p id="block-522ef498-a505-4d0b-9a0d-b2e5cca12111">Join us to keep track of news:&nbsp;<a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right" id="block-4fa7c042-0908-4ee5-9ff4-91607eb34413"><strong>Annie</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right" id="block-84ea04e6-519a-4165-8e39-faa42e0200e5"><strong>Coincu</strong>&nbsp;<strong>New</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Shakepay-Reviews-The-Easiest-Way-For--1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>PolyNetwork Hacked Possibly Due To Stealing 3/4 Of Admin&#8217;s Private Key: Report</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/199559-polynetwork-hacked-due-to-stealing-private-key/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Foxy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 03:11:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[# Cryptocurrencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[#Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Admin&#039;s Private Key]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dedaub]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[polynetwork]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stealing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=199559</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Research by security firm Dedaub said that the root cause of PolyNetwork attack could be the theft of three-quarters of the administrator's private key.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>Security firm Dedaub reckons that three-quarters of an administrator&#8217;s private key being stolen led to the carnage on PolyNetwork.</em></li>



<li><em>However, the cause could be Rug Pull or offline software running on three of the four admins was compromised.</em></li>



<li><em>The Poly team has paused their EthCrossChainManager smart contract on several chains, notably Metis, BSC, and Ethereum.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Research by security firm Dedaub said that the root cause of PolyNetwork attack could be the theft of three-quarters of the administrator&#8217;s private key.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-84.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="538" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-84-1024x538.png" alt="PolyNetwork Hacked Possibly Due To Stealing 3/4 Of Admin&#039;s Private Key: Report" class="wp-image-199568" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-84-1024x538.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-84-300x158.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-84-768x403.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-84-750x394.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-84-1140x599.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-84.png 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="PolyNetwork Hacked Possibly Due To Stealing 3/4 Of Admin&#039;s Private Key: Report 19"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>Security firm Dedaub stated in a blog post that the root cause of the attack on the PolyNetwork cross-chain interaction protocol was not a logic error in the smart contract but most likely 3/4 errors in smart contracts. Poly Administrator&#8217;s private key has been stolen or misused.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Poly chain hack technical postmortem explains how the signature scheme of the cross-chain bridge was used as intended in smart contract Merkle verifier.<br><br>It is presumed the keeper private keys were compromised (or misused).<a href="https://t.co/EXwSedk9cD" target="_blank">https://t.co/EXwSedk9cD</a></p>&mdash; Dedaub (@dedaub) <a href="https://twitter.com/dedaub/status/1675627338371874816?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener">July 2, 2023</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>Dedaub also mentioned that it took PolyNetwork seven hours to respond to the attack, while the attacker orchestrated several transactions across multiple chains to take advantage of this. So far, there is no clear evidence that the private keys were stolen. It could be Rug Pull, or maybe offline software running on three of the four admins was compromised.</p>



<p>Suppose Poly developers confirm that the attack is linked to a compromised signing key. In that case, it raises questions about the applicability of a centralized cross-chain bridge that controls a lot of money.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-85.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="512" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-85-1024x512.png" alt="PolyNetwork Hacked Possibly Due To Stealing 3/4 Of Admin&#039;s Private Key: Report" class="wp-image-199569" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-85-1024x512.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-85-300x150.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-85-768x384.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-85-1536x768.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-85-360x180.png 360w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-85-750x375.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-85-1140x570.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-85.png 2048w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="PolyNetwork Hacked Possibly Due To Stealing 3/4 Of Admin&#039;s Private Key: Report 20"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>The attack also showed less-than-perfect monitoring of the Poly group of the underlying bridge. If the protocol has been established with a rapid monitoring solution, this will significantly reduce the response time and potentially save some affected money.</p>



<p>It was reported yesterday that hackers had released over a dozen assets across several chains through Poly Network, worth $35 billion. The Poly team <a href="https://coincu.com/199536-polynetwork-57-assets-10-blockchains-affected/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">has paused</a> their EthCrossChainManager smart contract on several chains, most notably on Metis, BSC, and Ethereum.</p>



<p>There are reports that the attackers have transferred more than $5 million in cryptocurrencies on chains like Ethereum.</p>



<p>This is not the first time PolyNetwork has been hacked. Previously on August 10, 2021, caused more than $600 million in damage, but fortunately, the amount was refunded.</p>



<p id="block-643c4ba8-b40b-4525-9a96-f280dbfbeb9d"><strong><em>DISCLAIMER:&nbsp;</em></strong><em>The Information on this&nbsp;website&nbsp;is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>



<p id="block-522ef498-a505-4d0b-9a0d-b2e5cca12111">Join us to keep track of news:&nbsp;<a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right" id="block-4fa7c042-0908-4ee5-9ff4-91607eb34413"><strong>Foxy</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right" id="block-84ea04e6-519a-4165-8e39-faa42e0200e5"><strong>Coincu</strong>&nbsp;<strong>News</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Thumb-2023-Foxy-46-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Report SEC Chairman Gary Gensler Resigned Is It True?</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/199551-sec-chairman-gary-gensler-resigned-is-it-true/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Foxy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 02:35:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[# Cryptocurrencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[#Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gary Gensler]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Resigned]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rumor]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=199551</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A fake website recently started spreading rumors that SEC Chairman Gary Gensler has resigned, but that is not true.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>Recently a report has begun to spread rumors that SEC Chairman Gary Gensler has resigned.</em></li>



<li><em>However, SEC PR told FOX reporters that Gensler would not step down.</em></li>



<li><em>President Gary Gensler is on a full-blown assault on the crypto industry, most notably the recent lawsuit with Binance and Coinbase.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>A fake website recently started<a href="https://www.thecryptoalert.com/post/sec-sources-confirm-gary-gensler-resignation" target="_blank" rel="noopener"> spreading rumors </a>that SEC Chairman Gary Gensler has resigned, but that is not true.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-81.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="576" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-81-1024x576.png" alt="Report SEC Chairman Gary Gensler Resigned Is It True?" class="wp-image-199554" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-81-1024x576.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-81-300x169.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-81-768x432.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-81-750x422.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-81-1140x641.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-81.png 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Report SEC Chairman Gary Gensler Resigned Is It True? 21"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>The site publishes only a few articles. Some crypto bloggers are also spreading this rumor. In it, one of the sources reporting Gensler&#8217;s resignation is the CoinDesk website. CoinDesk cited an unnamed source as saying that Gensler resigned immediately. However, CoinDesk later updated its story to say that the source was mistaken and Gensler did not leave.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-80.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="900" height="182" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-80.png" alt="Report SEC Chairman Gary Gensler Resigned Is It True?" class="wp-image-199553" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-80.png 900w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-80-300x61.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-80-768x155.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-80-750x152.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 900px) 100vw, 900px" title="Report SEC Chairman Gary Gensler Resigned Is It True? 22"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">Fake reports are spread</figcaption></figure></div>


<p>After the rumor spread, FOX Business Network (FBN) reporter Charles Gasparino attempted to get an answer from SECGov, and as expected, its media department announced that Gary Gensler was not resigning.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Breaking: As expected <a href="https://twitter.com/SECGov?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener">@SECGov</a> PR says <a href="https://twitter.com/GaryGensler?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener">@GaryGensler</a> is not resigning</p>&mdash; Charles Gasparino (@CGasparino) <a href="https://twitter.com/CGasparino/status/1675650578657992704?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener">July 2, 2023</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>At the beginning of June, the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) launched two major legal actions against two leading cryptocurrency exchanges, Binance and Coinbase, accusing the exchanges of violating the US securities laws.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-82.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="788" height="443" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-82.png" alt="Report SEC Chairman Gary Gensler Resigned Is It True?" class="wp-image-199555" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-82.png 788w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-82-300x169.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-82-768x432.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-82-750x422.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 788px) 100vw, 788px" title="Report SEC Chairman Gary Gensler Resigned Is It True? 23"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>At the heart of this attack is Gary Gensler, who was appointed SEC chairman in February 2021. Gensler today looks like <a href="https://coincu.com/193410-sec-chair-gary-gensler-warns-crypto-frenzy/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">the crypto industry&#8217;s worst enemy</a>, putting out what sounds like a complete negation of the entire point of the existence of cryptocurrencies.</p>



<p>Having said that, since his first year as head of the SEC, Gensler has consistently believed that most cryptocurrencies fit the definition of securities and crypto exchanges. Cryptocurrency needs to be registered with the SEC, and stablecoins are &#8220;poker chips&#8221; to gamble on cryptocurrencies that pose systemic economic risks.</p>



<p>At the same time, Gensler said in testimony before Congress that the US government and Congress should develop more definitive rules for cryptocurrencies.</p>



<p>However, contrary to this argument, Coinbase has always made the point that the SEC has been deliberately dodging the requirement to make specific regulations for the crypto industry and many other companies in the industry for a long time. However, the crypto companies is still accused of non-compliance.</p>



<p id="block-643c4ba8-b40b-4525-9a96-f280dbfbeb9d"><strong><em>DISCLAIMER:&nbsp;</em></strong><em>The Information on this&nbsp;website&nbsp;is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>



<p id="block-522ef498-a505-4d0b-9a0d-b2e5cca12111">Join us to keep track of news:&nbsp;<a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right" id="block-4fa7c042-0908-4ee5-9ff4-91607eb34413"><strong>Foxy</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right" id="block-84ea04e6-519a-4165-8e39-faa42e0200e5"><strong>Coincu</strong>&nbsp;<strong>News</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Thumb-2023-Foxy-45-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Litecoin Halving Less Than 30 Days, LTC Up 31% In The Last Week</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/199544-litecoin-halving-less-than-30-days-ltc-up-31/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Foxy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 01:55:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[# Cryptocurrencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[#Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bulllish]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=199544</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[According to Litecoin halving data, 29 days, 20 hours and 45 minutes (1,7682 blocks) are still left before the Litecoin (LTC) block reward halving. ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>Litecoin halving just 29 days, 20 hours, and 45 minutes (17682 blocks) ahead of the Litecoin (LTC) block reward halving.</em></li>



<li><em>Litecoin (LTC) price has increased by almost 31% in the past seven days and is currently trading at $114.</em></li>



<li><em>Most investors expect the Litecoin price to increase after the halving event, as the number of rewards will decrease, thus increasing demand.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>According to Litecoin halving data, 29 days, 20 hours and 45 minutes (1,7682 blocks) are still left before the <a href="https://coincu.com/199062-litecoin-is-coming-back-strong/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Litecoin (LTC) </a>block reward halving. The halving is scheduled to take place on August 2, at which point the block reward will drop from 12.5 LTC to 6.25 LTC.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-79.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="611" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-79-1024x611.png" alt="Litecoin Halving Less Than 30 Days, LTC Up 31% In The Last Week" class="wp-image-199548" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-79-1024x611.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-79-300x179.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-79-768x458.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-79-750x447.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-79.png 1076w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Litecoin Halving Less Than 30 Days, LTC Up 31% In The Last Week 24"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>Litecoin has been trending on social media as the asset approaches its halving event. Litecoin has seen significant growth over the past 30 days. The price of LTC has increased by more than 27% since the one-month countdown to the Litecoin halving began. LTC has emerged as one of the best-performing tokens over the past week, with a gain of 30.4%. Currently, LTC is trading at $114.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-77.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="412" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-77-1024x412.png" alt="Litecoin Halving Less Than 30 Days, LTC Up 31% In The Last Week" class="wp-image-199546" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-77-1024x412.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-77-300x121.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-77-768x309.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-77-1536x618.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-77-2048x824.png 2048w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-77-750x302.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-77-1140x459.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Litecoin Halving Less Than 30 Days, LTC Up 31% In The Last Week 25"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">7 days LTC price chart. Source: CoinMarketCap</figcaption></figure></div>


<p>Most investors expect the Litecoin price to increase after the halving event, as the number of rewards will decrease, thus increasing demand. However, there are several other factors to consider.</p>



<p>A significant trend to watch is the influx of new miners. The long-term value of LTC is predicted to increase as supply decreases. As a result, many will want to participate in the possible bull run.</p>



<p>Each LTC price halving is usually very chaotic. This includes a significant price pump, a corresponding correction, a price low, and a local rally to the top. After the halving, the price of LTC was corrected from the high at that time. It will then form a new low followed by a sharp rise to a new all-time high. Therefore, we will likely see a post-halving price pump on August 2, 2023. And according to previous halvings, the price could correct before reaching a local top.</p>



<p>According to experts&#8217; analysis, the cryptocurrency shows a bullish bias and could be close to converting the $100 resistance level into support. This could lead to a major breakout and sustained rally that could lead the token to hit $130 in the near future.</p>



<p id="block-643c4ba8-b40b-4525-9a96-f280dbfbeb9d"><strong><em>DISCLAIMER:&nbsp;</em></strong><em>The Information on this&nbsp;website&nbsp;is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>



<p id="block-522ef498-a505-4d0b-9a0d-b2e5cca12111">Join us to keep track of news:&nbsp;<a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p id="block-4fa7c042-0908-4ee5-9ff4-91607eb34413"><strong>Foxy</strong></p>



<p id="block-84ea04e6-519a-4165-8e39-faa42e0200e5"><strong>Coincu</strong>&nbsp;<strong>News</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Thumb-2023-Foxy-44-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>PolyNetwork Down, 57 Assets In 10 Blockchains Affected By Attack</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/199536-polynetwork-57-assets-10-blockchains-affected/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Foxy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 01:30:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[# Cryptocurrencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[#Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[attack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[polynetwork]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=199536</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[PolyNetwork, a cross-chain interoperability protocol, tweeted that they will be suspending services while dealing with the attack. The cause of the attack has not yet been revealed.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>PolyNetwork announced the suspension of all platform activities to focus on remediation.</em></li>



<li><em>The attack left 57 assets affected across 10 blockchains, with an estimated $34 billion in damage.</em></li>



<li><em>The project contacted most of the project teams and urged them to withdraw liquidity from decentralized exchanges quickly.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>According to official sources, PolyNetwork, a cross-chain interoperability protocol, tweeted that they will be suspending services while dealing with the attack. The cause of the attack has not yet been revealed.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-75.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1000" height="600" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-75.png" alt="PolyNetwork Down, 57 Assets In 10 Blockchains Affected By Attack" class="wp-image-199538" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-75.png 1000w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-75-300x180.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-75-768x461.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-75-750x450.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" title="PolyNetwork Down, 57 Assets In 10 Blockchains Affected By Attack 26"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>The attack affected 57 assets across 10 blockchains. The team has begun communicating with centralized exchanges, cybersecurity experts, and individuals with relevant knowledge. Users with information are also encouraged to contact the platform. The network also expects attackers to cooperate and return users&#8217; assets to avoid any potential legal consequences.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">We kindly request the assistance of cybersecurity professionals and individuals with relevant knowledge. If you possess any information that could aid us in this endeavor, we encourage you to actively contact us. <br>ã€2/7ã€‘</p>&mdash; Poly Network (@PolyNetwork2) <a href="https://twitter.com/PolyNetwork2/status/1675591971501375489?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener">July 2, 2023</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>To further mitigate risk, PolyNetwork contacted most of the project teams and urged them to withdraw liquidity from decentralized exchanges quickly. It also advised users holding affected assets to withdraw liquidity and unlock LP tokens quickly.</p>



<p>According to Beosin Alert monitoring, hackers minted over $34 billion in assets across multiple chains, and some of the stolen funds (approximately $800,000) were moved to the Ethereum address: 0xe0Afadad1d93704761c8550F21A53DE3468Ba599.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-76.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="571" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-76-1024x571.png" alt="PolyNetwork Down, 57 Assets In 10 Blockchains Affected By Attack" class="wp-image-199540" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-76-1024x571.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-76-300x167.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-76-768x428.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-76-750x418.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-76-1140x635.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-76.png 1321w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="PolyNetwork Down, 57 Assets In 10 Blockchains Affected By Attack 27"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>On the morning of July 2, blockchain security unit Peckshield<a href="https://coincu.com/199488-polynetwork-suspected-hacking-released-assets/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"> reported</a> that PolyNetwork had encountered a certain vulnerability, allowing attackers to mint a large number of tokens on many different chains. Specifically, looking at the hacker&#8217;s address, it can be seen that he interacted with Poly Network and minted $42.1 billion worth of tokens.</p>



<p>In the past, PolyNetwork on August 10, 2021, was attacked by bad guys, siphoning up to $611 million. It was the most severe crypto hack in history up to that point, surpassed only by Axie Infinity&#8217;s Ronin bridge hack in March 2022, which caused $622 million in damage. Under pressure from the project and the crypto community, the hacker returned almost all the money taken from the attack a few days later.</p>



<p id="block-643c4ba8-b40b-4525-9a96-f280dbfbeb9d"><strong><em>DISCLAIMER:&nbsp;</em></strong><em>The Information on this&nbsp;website&nbsp;is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>



<p id="block-522ef498-a505-4d0b-9a0d-b2e5cca12111">Join us to keep track of news:&nbsp;<a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right" id="block-4fa7c042-0908-4ee5-9ff4-91607eb34413"><strong>Foxy</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right" id="block-84ea04e6-519a-4165-8e39-faa42e0200e5"><strong>Coincu</strong>&nbsp;<strong>News</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Thumb-2023-Foxy-43-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Frax Finance Review: Project To Eliminate Weaknesses of Algorithmic Stablecoins</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/199523-frax-finance-review/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Harold]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 16:25:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Reviews]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AAVE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AMO]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Curve]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FRAX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Frax Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Frax Protocol]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FraxLend]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FraxSwap]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FXS]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uniswap]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=199523</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[By integrating the functionalities of Curve, UniSwap, and AAVE into a single platform, Frax Finance could provide users with a comprehensive DeFi experience.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Frax Finance sounds like an interesting concept! By integrating the functionalities of Curve, UniSwap, and AAVE into a single platform, it could provide users with a comprehensive DeFi experience.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-72.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="512" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-72-1024x512.png" alt="image 72" class="wp-image-199531" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-72-1024x512.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-72-300x150.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-72-768x384.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-72-1536x768.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-72-360x180.png 360w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-72-750x375.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-72-1140x570.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-72.png 1800w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Frax Finance Review: Project To Eliminate Weaknesses of Algorithmic Stablecoins 28"></a></figure></div>


<p>Curve is known for being a liquidity destination, UniSwap is a leading decentralized exchange, and AAVE is a popular lending protocol. Frax Finance aims to combine these functions into a unified platform.</p>



<p>With Frax Finance, users could enjoy the benefits of liquidity provision, decentralized trading, and lending/borrowing within a single app. This integration would streamline the user experience and eliminate the need to switch between different platforms for various DeFi activities.</p>



<p>So what is Frax Finance? Let&#8217;s find out more about this project with Coincu.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">What is Frax Finance?</h2>



<p>Frax Finance is the name of a DeFi initiative that offers a number of multi-chain goods. Frax Finance refers to a complete ecosystem of Defi goods and services, including Frax Protocol (or Frax Finance Protocol), Fraxlend, Fraxswap, stablecoin FRAX, and so on.</p>



<p>The project is the pioneering initiative in the paradigm of partly reserved algorithmic stablecoins (Fractional Algorithmic). The purpose of Frax Finance is to develop a decentralized, stable, scalable, and capital-efficient stablecoin. The Frax Finance network&#8217;s mechanism is made up of two tokens:</p>



<ul>
<li>FRAX: Frax Finance is an algorithmic stablecoin that is partially collateral-backed and partly algorithmically stable.</li>



<li>Frax Shares (FXS): The Frax Finance network&#8217;s governance and utility token. FXS is accumulated with the value from the unsecured FRAX rate, fees, and protocol revenue.</li>
</ul>



<p>Prior to the introduction of the Frax Protocol, stablecoins were classified into three types:</p>



<ul>
<li>Collateral stablecoin using fiat, real-world assets issued by a non-traditional company/consortium: USDT from Tether, USDC from Circle, or BUSD from Paxos.</li>



<li>Crypto-collateral: There include CDP systems such as Maker DAO, that issue DAI, Venus, that issue VAI; and Parrot, that issue PAI.</li>



<li>There is no need for collateral since the system is entirely algorithmic.</li>
</ul>



<p>Frax Finance introduces a fourth form of stablecoin: a fractional-algorithmic stablecoin, whose exchange rate stability mechanism is partly dependent on algorithms and partially backed by other assets.</p>



<p>Frax is now being implemented on Ethereum and 12 other blockchains, along with two stablecoins, FRAX (anchor to USD rate) and FPI (anchor to US CPI, not yet launched). The Frax protocol&#8217;s ultimate purpose is to create a highly scalable, decentralized cryptocurrency in substitute of digital assets with a fixed supply, such as BTC.</p>



<p>Frax Finance&#8217;s approach to developing Web-Apps, or what Frax Finance hopes to provide to consumers, is to give Defi services on an All-in-One platform that exists on several chains with strategic items such as:</p>



<ul>
<li>FRAX &#8211; Stablecoins</li>



<li>FraxSwap &#8211; AMM DEX</li>



<li>FraxLend &#8211; Lending protocol</li>
</ul>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-74.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1000" height="563" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-74.png" alt="image 74" class="wp-image-199533" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-74.png 1000w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-74-300x169.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-74-768x432.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-74-750x422.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" title="Frax Finance Review: Project To Eliminate Weaknesses of Algorithmic Stablecoins 29"></a></figure></div>


<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">How does it work?</h2>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Mechanism for mortgages</strong></h3>



<p>USDC is originally completely collateralized FRAX. Later, as stablecoin demand grew and mortgage rates fell, FRAX was partly collateralized with FXS and USDC. FXS, which works similarly to the LUNA/UST method, supports the algorithm component of FRAX.</p>



<p>Frax Mining Process: The user inputs $0.88 USDC and xFXS has a value of 0.12$ to the protocol, resulting in a total valuation of $1. The user is then given one FRAX unit. Since the fraction of FXS delivered into the protocol will be burnt, each FRAX held by the user is only backed by $0.88 USDC.</p>



<p>Mortgage Withdrawal Procedure: The user returns FRAX to the protocol for burning. The protocol generates an appropriately valued quantity of yFXS equal to $0.12 (y may vary, maybe equal to x owing to variable FXS pricing) plus $0.88 collateralized USDC, which is returned to the customer.</p>



<ul>
<li>Where F is the minted FRAX unit.</li>



<li>Y is the unit of USDC loaded into the system. Py is the USDC/USD rate.</li>



<li>Z is the FXS unit loaded into the system. Pz is the FXS/USD rate.</li>



<li>Cr is the USDC Mortgage Rate.</li>
</ul>



<p>The collateral method described above serves as the foundation for the exchange rate stabilization mechanism described below.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Exchange rate stabilization mechanism</strong></h3>



<p>FRAX supply is changed to fit market supply and demand by focusing on market players&#8217; interests.</p>



<p>Considering the secondary market price of FRAX is larger than $1 for any reason, it is comprehensible that the demand for FRAX exceeds the supply. Assuming that FRAX always respects the mortgage rule, anybody may mint FRAX for $1 and sell it on the secondary market for more than $1 to benefit from the exchange rate difference. At this moment, the supply of FRAX has been increased.</p>



<p>When the price of FRAX on the secondary market is less than $1, anybody may acquire it and use the Frax Protocol to withdraw $1 in USDC and FXS. The supply of FRAX is presently diminishing, while demand in secondary markets is increasing, causing FRAX to revert to the peg price of $1.</p>



<p>FRAX&#8217;s price volatility is therefore transferred to the FXS. Depending on the circumstances, this might be beneficial or detrimental. If the supply of FRAX continues to rise, more FXS will be burnt, deflating the supply of FXS.</p>



<p>The protocol uses Algorithmic Market Operations (AMO) to achieve stability in the first version &#8211; Frax v1. Every one hour, if FRAX is greater than $1, Cr (USDC collateral rate) decreases by 0.25%, if FRAX is less than $1, Cr increases by 0.25% to increase the collateral structure in USDC, and Cr stays the same when Frax price = 1.</p>



<p>Frax v2 expands on the AMO concept introduced in v1 by aiming to operate as many AMOs as possible in order to enhance protocol, boost privacy and capital efficiency, and empower FXS holders more. This allows the protocol to mint extra FRAX when the price is more than $1 in order to return the price to $1.</p>



<p>AMOs may be openly suggested and formed by the community, but they must be approved by a governance vote before they can be implemented. Today, four AMOs have been deployed, with two more in the works.</p>



<p>The Frax system receives FRAX and FXS collateral pricing data through Oracle Chainlink and Uniswap.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading has-black-color has-text-color"><strong>FRAX</strong></h3>



<p>FRAX is an algorithmic stablecoin with price stability achieved by asset collateralization. Mortgage rates are adjusted hourly to the value of FRAX by 0.25%.</p>



<p>To develop stability for the protocol before permitting collateral with many other assets, the assets used as collateral to produce FRAX are currently only stablecoins such as USDT and USDC.</p>



<p>FRAX is always created/redeemed with a value of one dollar. As FRAX exceeds $1, a reward is created that motivates users to mint additional FRAX. When FRAX is less than $1, however, there is an advantage to redeeming FRAX.</p>



<p>The overall value of FRAX created (mine) is guaranteed to be equal to the sum of the collateral value at the collateral rate and the FXS value (the number of FXS to be burned). When FRAX is redeemed, the user receives the collateral as well as FXS at the same value (this FXS is generated).</p>



<p>Moreover, following the release of Frax V2, Frax used Curve&#8217;s governance architecture, which is Vote Escrowed (ve). You will need to lock FXS in order to obtain veFXS for administration and prizes.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-70.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="394" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-70-1024x394.png" alt="image 70" class="wp-image-199527" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-70-1024x394.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-70-300x115.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-70-768x295.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-70-1536x590.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-70-750x288.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-70-1140x438.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-70.png 1600w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Frax Finance Review: Project To Eliminate Weaknesses of Algorithmic Stablecoins 30"></a></figure></div>


<h3 class="wp-block-heading has-black-color has-text-color"><strong>Fraxswap</strong></h3>



<p>Fraxswap is Frax Finance&#8217;s AMM, and it is based on Uniswap V2.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading has-black-color has-text-color"><strong>Fraxlend</strong></h3>



<p>Frax Finance cannot construct a comprehensive DeFi ecosystem without a lending platform &#8211; a decentralized capital market. Fraxlend is a freshly released loan platform by Frax Finance.</p>



<p>Anybody may generate liquidity between two ERC-20 tokens using Fraxlend, and everyone can develop and participate in lending and borrowing operations.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-69.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="619" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-69-1024x619.png" alt="image 69" class="wp-image-199526" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-69-1024x619.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-69-300x181.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-69-768x464.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-69-750x453.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-69-1140x689.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-69.png 1536w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Frax Finance Review: Project To Eliminate Weaknesses of Algorithmic Stablecoins 31"></a></figure></div>


<p>The following people are involved in the loan process on Fraxlend, according to the diagram above:</p>



<ul>
<li>FraxLend Pair: This is similar to a loan contract in that the contract will record the collateral and the lending assets are ERC20 tokens. Fraxlend Pair Deployer, the makers of this asset pair, implemented it.</li>



<li>Lenders: Lenders that deposit Token Asset into the Fraxlend Pair will get interest in fTokens. Lending tokens may be traded for fTokens.</li>



<li>Borrowers: Borrowers deposit tokens as collateral into Fraxlend Pair in order to borrow Token Asset.</li>



<li>Rate Calculator is in charge of calculating interest rates.</li>



<li>The market pricing for both the Asset Token and the Collateral Token is determined by one (or two) ChainLink Oracles in each contract.</li>
</ul>



<p>In the liquidation procedure, this approach remains identical to previous loan arrangements. Each borrower&#8217;s position is governed by an LTV, which is the ratio of the value of the borrowed asset to the value of the collateral placed. As the exchange rate between Token Asset and Collateral Token changes, LTV changes. When a borrower&#8217;s LTV (Loan to value) exceeds the limit LTV, he or she might add collateral or repay the loan to put the LTV back into a safe range. Instead, anybody may return all or part of the loan on the borrower&#8217;s behalf and earn the collateral&#8217;s value plus a liquidation fee.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">FXS token</h2>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading" id="section-3"><strong>Key Metrics</strong></h3>



<ul>
<li>Token Name: Frax Share</li>



<li>Ticker: FXS</li>



<li>Blockchain: Ethereum</li>



<li>Token Standard: ERC-20, Bep-20, PRC-20, SPL</li>



<li>Contract:
<ul>
<li>ERC-20:&nbsp;0x3432b6a60d23ca0dfca7761b7ab56459d9c964d0</li>



<li>BEP-20:&nbsp;0xe48a3d7d0bc88d552f730b62c006bc925eadb9ee</li>



<li>PRC-20:&nbsp;0x1a3acf6d19267e2d3e7f898f42803e90c9219062</li>



<li>SPL:&nbsp;6LX8BhMQ4Sy2otmAWj7Y5sKd9YTVVUgfMsBzT6B9W7ct</li>
</ul>
</li>



<li>Token type: Utility, Governance.</li>



<li>Total Supply: 99,707,753 FXS</li>



<li>Circulating Supply: 72,740,215 FXS</li>
</ul>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Token Allocation</strong></h3>



<ul>
<li>Liquidity Mining: 60%</li>



<li>Team:20%</li>



<li>Token Sale: 12%</li>



<li>Treasury: 5%</li>



<li>Advisors: 3%</li>
</ul>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Use Cases</strong></h3>



<p>The FXS token serves the following purposes:</p>



<ul>
<li>It is a token for project management</li>



<li>FRAX is created by combining it with collateral.</li>
</ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Team</h2>



<p>Frax Finance&#8217;s team is primarily made up of people from previous initiatives, such as Everipedia, a Wikipedia Blockchain, and DecentralBank.</p>



<ul>
<li>Sam Kazemian &#8211; CEO &amp; Founder: An Iranian-American programmer and Internet entrepreneur. He founded everipedia as well.</li>



<li>Jason Yu Huan &#8211; Co-Founder: An American computer scientist and University of California, Los Angeles graduate.</li>



<li>Travis Moore &#8211; CTO &amp; Co-Founder: A UCLA graduate with degrees in Molecular Biology, Biochemistry, and Neuroscience, Travis Moore is a computer programmer, angel investor, and entrepreneur.</li>



<li>Kedar Iyer &#8211; Advisor: A blockchain programmer, entrepreneur, and book author. Kedar formerly worked as the CTO of DecentralBank and the software director of Everipedia.</li>
</ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Investors and Backers</h2>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-71.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="864" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-71-1024x864.png" alt="image 71" class="wp-image-199528" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-71-1024x864.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-71-300x253.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-71-768x648.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-71-750x633.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-71-1140x962.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-71.png 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Frax Finance Review: Project To Eliminate Weaknesses of Algorithmic Stablecoins 32"></a></figure></div>


<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Conclusion</h2>



<p>Frax Finance is a well-known stablecoin initiative in the cryptocurrency industry that has weathered multiple market storms while maintaining its peg.</p>



<p>It is a truly decentralized system with on-chain governance, and it will be the first and only stablecoin to use a hybrid fractional-algorithm architecture when it launches in November 2020. While not yet fully developed, Frax Finance always has highly promising directions and promises to establish an extraordinarily robust ecosystem. Nonetheless, Frax Finance&#8217;s market penetration in the cryptocurrency sector remains minimal.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER: </em></strong><em>The information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>



<p>Join us to<a href="https://coincu.com" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"> keep track of news</a>:&nbsp;<a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Harold</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Coincu</strong> <strong>News</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-73-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Convex Finance Review: DeFi Platform During The Explode Of Curve Wars</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/199515-convex-finance-review/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Harold]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 09:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Reviews]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Convex Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CRV]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Curve Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Curve Wars]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CVX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Frax Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FXS]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[veCRV]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=199515</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Convex Finance presents an interesting approach for users to earn benefits and get increased CRV payouts without locking up their CRV tokens.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Decentralized income is at the heart of the blockchain, cryptocurrency, and decentralized finance (DeFi) ecosystem. In with this agreement, Convex Finance presents an interesting approach for users to earn benefits and get increased CRV payouts without locking up their CRV tokens.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-65.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="559" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-65-1024x559.png" alt="Convex Finance Review: DeFi Platform During The Explode Of Curve Wars" class="wp-image-199517" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-65-1024x559.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-65-300x164.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-65-768x419.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-65-1536x838.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-65-750x409.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-65-1140x622.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-65.png 2017w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Convex Finance Review: DeFi Platform During The Explode Of Curve Wars 33"></a></figure></div>


<p>So what is Convex Finance? Let&#8217;s find out more about this project with Coincu.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">What is Convex Finance?</h2>



<p>Convex Finance is a one-of-a-kind platform that allows Curve.fi LPs to earn trading fees as a return. These LPs may also claim increased CRV benefits without locking up CRV tokens. Dividing trading costs between users and LPs increases capital efficiency. It also maintains a healthy balance between liquidity providers (LPs) and CRV token holders.</p>



<p>Convex is also noted for its low cost. The platform charges no costs for withdrawals and keeps performance fees to a bare minimum. CVX stakeholders often get performance fees, sometimes known as gas fees. Surprisingly, on Convex, both LPs and CRV stakeholders earn CVX as a mining return. CVX is also the Convex Finance ecosystem&#8217;s native coin. The tokens also act as governance tokens, with holders responsible for allocating veCRV tokens.</p>



<p>Convex Finance was founded in Curve Wars with the ability to increase earnings for Curve Finance and Frax Finance token holders, CRV and FXS, respectively. Moreover, Convex maximizes earnings for LPs on Curve and Frax. Convex has been quite successful despite having a significantly different operating paradigm than other platforms at the same time.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">How does it work?</h2>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Convex Finance and Curve Finance</strong></h3>



<p>Convex has an interaction with two items on Curve Finance, including CRV holders and liquidity providers. And now we&#8217;ll look at how Convex works with each of the items listed above.</p>



<p><strong>CRV holders</strong></p>



<p>Convex enables consumers to lock CRV on their platform for a bigger payout than Curve Finance offers. And the following is Convex&#8217;s method of action for CRV holders:</p>



<ul>
<li>Step 1: Users will permanently register their CRV with Convex Finance.</li>



<li>Step 2: Convex Finance returns it to the user cvxCRV. This cvxCRV reflects the CRV supplied by the user to the platform.</li>



<li>Step 3: Convex owning veCRV permits the platform to get a portion of Curve Finance&#8217;s income, which Convex re-shares with cvxCRV holders.</li>



<li>Step 4: In addition to income sharing from Curve, the Convex platform will reward cvxCRV holders in CVX (this is more of Convex when comparing Curve Finance directly).</li>



<li>Step 5: Customers may exit cvxCRV&#8217;s position on Curve Finance by trading in the cvxCRV &#8211; CRV liquidity pair.</li>
</ul>



<p><strong>Curve Finance liquidity providers</strong></p>



<p>Convex interacts with liquidity providers on Curve Finance in addition to CRV holders. And the operating method on Curve Finance between Convex Finance and liquidity sources is as follows:</p>



<ul>
<li>Step 1: LPs will get LP Tokens reflecting their liquidity on Curve Finance after supplying liquidity on Curve Finance. After that, the user transfers and bets the LP Token on the Convex Finance platform.</li>



<li>Step 2: Convex Finance will provide a reward as part of the money generated by the Curve Finance protocol, as well as certain incentive tokens such as LDO, SNX, and so on. Moreover, the token is the incentive that LPs get. CVX. Particularly appealing are the $0 deposit and withdrawal fees.</li>



<li>Step 3: At any moment, users may unlock their LP Token.</li>
</ul>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-66-1024x540.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="540" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-66-1024x540.png" alt="Convex Finance Review: DeFi Platform During The Explode Of Curve Wars" class="wp-image-199518" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-66-1024x540.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-66-300x158.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-66-768x405.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-66-1536x810.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-66-750x396.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-66-1140x601.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-66.png 1600w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Convex Finance Review: DeFi Platform During The Explode Of Curve Wars 34"></a></figure></div>


<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Frax Finance and Convex Finance</strong></h3>



<p>Convex, like Frax Finance, features two products for FXS holders and also provides liquidity on Frax Finance.</p>



<p><strong>FXS holders</strong></p>



<p>When users lock FXS on the Convex platform, a number of events occur, including:</p>



<ul>
<li>Step 1: The user deposits FXS into the Convex platform, and Convex locks permanently on the Frax Finance platform to receive veFXS.</li>



<li>Step 2: The customer will get a 1 &#8211; 1 ratio cvxFXS with the FXS put into the platform.</li>



<li>Step 3: The user is rewarded with the platform&#8217;s CVX; moreover, if the user&#8217;s cvxFXS is introduced to create liquidity on Curve for the cvsFXS &#8211; FXS pair, they will be rewarded when they directly stake FXS on Frax Finance as FXS.</li>



<li>Step 4: Users may exit their cvsFXS position by trading the cvsFXS &#8211; FXS pair on Curve Finance.</li>
</ul>



<p><strong>Frax Finance liquidity providers</strong></p>



<p>This method is analogous to how Convex interacts with LPs on Curve Finance. This mechanism works as follows:</p>



<ul>
<li>Step 1: You must take this quantity of LP Token if you are staking your LP Token on Frax Finance.</li>



<li>Step 2: Make a deposit of your LP Token with Convex Finance.</li>
</ul>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-67.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="538" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-67-1024x538.png" alt="Convex Finance Review: DeFi Platform During The Explode Of Curve Wars" class="wp-image-199519" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-67-1024x538.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-67-300x158.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-67-768x403.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-67-750x394.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-67-1140x599.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-67.png 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Convex Finance Review: DeFi Platform During The Explode Of Curve Wars 35"></a></figure></div>


<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Highlights</h2>



<p>Convex enables Curve.fi LPs to earn transaction fees and claim higher CRV without locking up the CRV. With little effort, LPs may increase their CRV and liquidity mining returns.</p>



<p>Convex enables users to gain transaction fees as well as a portion of the CRV increase obtained by LPs if they desire to stake CRV. This results in a better balance between LPs and CRV stakeholders, as well as improved capital efficiency.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Liquidity Providers (LPs)</strong></h3>



<p>The Convex ecosystem is supported by LPs and stakers. On Convex, LPs will receive trading fees as well as increased CRV. As previously indicated, LPs are not required to lock up any CRV tokens in order to get these benefits. On Convex, LPs will:</p>



<ul>
<li>Staking for higher rewards is automatically triggered when Curve LP tokens are deposited into Convex Finance.</li>



<li>Get CRV as well as other tokens as prizes (SNX, PNT, BOR, LDO,â€¦).</li>



<li>Prizes are obtained from the Curve gauge on a regular basis and transferred to the Synthetix-inspired Reward contract, with rewards given after seven days.</li>



<li>Add and remove liquidity quickly and conveniently, with no extra deposit or withdrawal fees.</li>



<li>Get a CVX &#8211; Convex token based on the CRV received by the user.</li>
</ul>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CRV Stakers</strong></h3>



<ul>
<li>Submitting CRV to Convex will result in it being locked indefinitely and returned to cvxCRV.</li>



<li>cvxCRV should be deposited into the Reward contract (can be withdrawn at any time).</li>



<li>Take advantage of the CRV incentive.</li>



<li>Get the same transaction fees as if you owned a veCRV.</li>



<li>Although permanently closed, users may trade at Pool cvxCRV/CRV if they desire to return to CRV.</li>



<li>Get a CVX &#8211; Convex token based on the CRV received by the user.</li>
</ul>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CVX Stakers</strong></h3>



<p>Stake CVX to get platform transaction fees in the form of cvxCRV. Despite the fact that it was just recently introduced, Convex&#8217;s TVL has developed significantly. Convex&#8217;s TVL is now $3.27B, ranking 7th on DefiLlama, indicating that Curve&#8217;s user base is quite huge and they require a location to enhance revenues.</p>



<p>Moreover, 16% of the farm reward from CRV will be removed and distributed in the form of CRV as follows:</p>



<ul>
<li>10% off on cvxCRV.</li>



<li>CVX Stakers get a 5% discount.</li>



<li>1% gas cost reimbursement for collecting and delivering prizes under Reward contracts.</li>
</ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Liquidity Pools on Convex</h2>



<p>Convex Finance&#8217;s pools will be determined by a user&#8217;s unique objectives, risk tolerance, and other choices. Nonetheless, certain pools have regularly supplied consumers with large reward chances without incurring small impermanent losses. These are a few of Convex&#8217;s most popular and successful pools:</p>



<ul>
<li>Tricrypto pool (USDT+BTC+ETH): This pool enables users to stake three highly liquid assets: USDT, BTC, and ETH, and earn trading fees, CRV, and CVX in exchange for trading fees, CRV, and CVX. This pool gives players equal exposure to USDT, Bitcoin, and ETH while paying a 13.5% APR.</li>



<li>stETH pool (ETH/STETH): Users may stake stETH, a wrapped version of ETH that can be used to generate yield on the Lido staking platform. At 5.4% APR, the stETH pool has delivered the greatest dividends for ETH investors.</li>



<li>4pool (DAI/USDC/USDT/SUSD): This pool enables users to stake DAI, USDC, USDT, and SUSD, four extremely liquid stablecoins. This pool has delivered its participants with a 3.8% APR return with no impermanent loss.</li>
</ul>



<p>It&#8217;s important to note that the returns of these pools might fluctuate over time, and consumers should always do their own research and assess the risks before investing in any pool. While selecting a pool, consumers should also consider liquidity, token price stability, and the project&#8217;s overall long-term viability.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">CVX token</h2>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading" id="key-metrics"><strong>Key Metrics</strong></h3>



<ul>
<li>Ticker: CVX.</li>



<li>Blockchain: Ethereum.</li>



<li>Contract: 0x4e3fbd56cd56c3e72c1403e103b45db9da5b9d2b.</li>



<li>Token Standard: ERC-20.</li>



<li>Token Type: Utility, Governance.</li>



<li>Total Supply: 100,000,000 CVX.</li>



<li>Circulating Supply: 78,493,982 CVX.</li>
</ul>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading" id="token-allocation"><strong>Token Allocation</strong></h3>



<ul>
<li>Curve LP rewards: 50%.</li>



<li>Liquidity mining: 25%.</li>



<li>Treasury: 9.7%.</li>



<li>veCRV holders: 1%.</li>



<li>veCRV voters: 1%.</li>



<li>Investors: 3.3%.</li>



<li>Convex Team: 10%.</li>
</ul>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-64.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="911" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-64-1024x911.png" alt="Convex Finance Review: DeFi Platform During The Explode Of Curve Wars" class="wp-image-199516" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-64-1024x911.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-64-300x267.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-64-768x683.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-64-750x667.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-64-1140x1014.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-64.png 1400w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Convex Finance Review: DeFi Platform During The Explode Of Curve Wars 36"></a></figure></div>


<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>&#x200d;Release Schedule</strong></h3>



<ul>
<li>25% for Liquidity Mining will be distributed gradually over 4 years</li>



<li>9.7% for Treasury distributed in the first 1 year</li>



<li>1% for veCRV Voters and veCRV Holders are distributed at the time of TGE</li>



<li>3.3% for Investors distributed gradually over 1 year</li>



<li>10% for Convex Team is distributed gradually over 1 year.</li>
</ul>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Use Cases</strong></h3>



<p>CVX may be staked on Convex Finance in exchange for CRV and FXS from Curve and Frax LP. CVX may also be locked for extra Curve and Frax LP awards.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Team</h2>



<p>Convex Finance&#8217;s team is not publicly known, and the project is regarded to be an anonymous team. The team&#8217;s anonymity is widespread in the DeFi field, and it is thought to be done to avoid regulatory scrutiny and possible legal difficulties. Having said that, it is usually assumed that the development community behind Curve Finance is the entity responsible for implementing and maintaining the protocol.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Conclusion</h2>



<p>Convex is a platform that was formed when Curve Wars burst, and it is still growing today because to the vigor of Curve Finance. After then, the project continues to expand on Frax Finance. Finally, Convex Finance is a well-known DeFi protocol that focuses on maximizing yield production for Curve.fi liquidity providers and CRV stakeholders, with over $4 billion in total value locked. The platform allows users to optimize their profits with minimum effort and great capital efficiency by offering tokenized deposits, increased CRV incentives, and its native CVX token.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER: </em></strong><em>The information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>



<p>Join us to keep track of news:&nbsp;<a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Harold</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Coincu</strong> <strong>News</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-68-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
