<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 20:59:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Kin price soars after proposal to burn 7 trillion KIN passes</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/kin-price-soars-after-proposal-to-burn-7-trillion-kin-passes/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/kin-price-soars-after-proposal-to-burn-7-trillion-kin-passes/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 20:59:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/kin-price-soars-after-proposal-to-burn-7-trillion-kin-passes/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Kin community adopts proposal to burn 7 trillion of supply. The total supply of Kin is 10 trillion KIN tokens. The price of native token KIN jumps more than 20% as traders react to news. Kin Foundation has announced that a proposal seeking to burn trillions of KIN tokens has passed. According to an update [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/kin-price-soars-after-proposal-to-burn-7-trillion-kin-passes/">Kin price soars after proposal to burn 7 trillion KIN passes</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Kin community adopts proposal to burn 7 trillion of supply.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The total supply of Kin is 10 trillion KIN tokens.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The price of native token KIN jumps more than 20% as traders react to news.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Kin Foundation has <a href="https://twitter.com/Kin_Ecosystem/status/1684614013223567378" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">announced</a> that a proposal seeking to burn trillions of KIN tokens has passed. According to an update from the organisation, the community&rsquo;s vote on the proposal to burn Kin Reserves will see over 7 trillion KIN tokens destroyed.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Update: The proposal to burn the Kin Reserves has passed after a token weighted vote by the Kin community. </p>
<p>You can read the official results of the vote and next steps here: <a href="https://t.co/0qVaJsYnKE">https://t.co/0qVaJsYnKE</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Kin Ecosystem &#11042; (@Kin_Ecosystem) <a href="https://twitter.com/Kin_Ecosystem/status/1684614013223567378?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 27, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Kin&rsquo;s path to decentralisation</h2>
<p dir="ltr">About 4.96 trillion KIN held by the foundation and 2.1 trillion KIN planned for burning by Kik should be destroyed by end of day Friday, July 28. That would see roughly 71% of the total KIN supply burned.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;As a next step, the 4.96T Kin Reserves will be sent to a new Solana address and burned. After this the 2.10T Kin that Kik has agreed to burn will follow the same process. Once these burns are complete I will publish a new post that shows the on chain proof of these burns. I am hopeful this will happen by the end of day tomorrow,&rdquo; the <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/kin/comments/15b7iwc/kin_burn_vote_passes/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">update</a> read.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Ted Livingston, founder and CEO of Code, says the burn will make Kin a fully decentralised cryptocurrency. There will be no inflation, foundation or website.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>The vote to burn the Kin Reserves has passed, with the vast majority of votes in support. Kin is about to become one of the only fully decentralised cryptocurrencies out there, with no inflation, no foundation, and no website. More details to come once the burn is complete</em>,&rdquo; he <a href="https://twitter.com/ted_livingston/status/1684579497386065923" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">noted</a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to data from CoinGecko, the cryptocurrency&rsquo;s current circulating supply is 2,207,205,857,149. The maximum supply is 10 trillion.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">KIN price surges</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The <a href="https://coinjournal.net/price/">price of KIN</a> soared after the vote closed, with the token&rsquo;s value having reached an intraday high of $0.000022. KIN was up 22% in the past 24 hours and more than 68% in the past week after its price jumped to highs near $0.000030 following the proposal.</p>
<p dir="ltr">KIN&rsquo;s all-time high of $0.00122572 was reached on January 7, 2018.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/kin-price-soars-after-proposal-to-burn-7-trillion-kin-passes/">Kin price soars after proposal to burn 7 trillion KIN passes</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/kin-price-soars-after-proposal-to-burn-7-trillion-kin-passes/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin-focused MicroStrategy stock has 22% upside – analyst says</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/microstrategy-stock-has-22-upside-td-cowen-analyst/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wajeeh Khan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 18:50:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MicroStrategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=147824</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TD Cowen analyst sees upside in MicroStrategy to $520. Lance Vitanza explained his bullish view in a research note. MicroStrategy stock has already tripled since the start of 2023. MicroStrategy Inc has already tripled since the start of this year but a TD Cowen analyst continues to see further upside in this stock. MicroStrategy stock [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/microstrategy-stock-has-22-upside-td-cowen-analyst/">Bitcoin-focused MicroStrategy stock has 22% upside – analyst says</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>TD Cowen analyst sees upside in MicroStrategy to $520.</li>
<li>Lance Vitanza explained his bullish view in a research note.</li>
<li>MicroStrategy stock has already tripled since the start of 2023.</li>
</ul>
<p>MicroStrategy Inc has already tripled since the start of this year but a TD Cowen analyst continues to see further upside in this stock.</p>
<h2>MicroStrategy stock could climb to $520</h2>
<p>Lance Vitanza assumed coverage of the software company today with an &ldquo;outperform&rdquo; rating and said its shares could climb to $520 &ndash; up another 22% from here.</p>
<p>For institutional investors, he said in his research note, MicroStrategy stock is the best way to gain exposure to <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a>.</p>
<blockquote><p>MSTR uses all its retained earnings and then some to buy and hold BTC [that] reflects a belief that Bitcoin will prove a superior store of value relative to metals and fiat currencies.</p></blockquote>
<p>The Nasdaq-listed firm is set to report its Q2 earnings next week. <a href="https://www.nasdaq.com/market-activity/stocks/mstr/earnings" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Consensus</a> is for it to lose 71 cents a share versus an alarming $92.81 per share a year ago.</p>
<h2>MSTR trumps BTC or a Bitcoin ETF</h2>
<p>The Virginia-based company currently owns more than 150,000 Bitcoin in total.</p>
<p>Vitanza recommends MicroStrategy stock also because it&rsquo;s free from some of the fees related to investing directly in Bitcoin or a Bitcoin ETF. He&rsquo;s convinced that its underlying business serves as downside protection as well.</p>
<blockquote><p>We see MicroStrategy as an attractive vehicle for investors looking to gain Bitcoin exposure.</p></blockquote>
<p>MicroStrategy is lobbying for a change in accounting rules related to BTC which may also boost its financials. Bitcoin-specific catalysts, including &ldquo;<a href="https://decrypt.co/149829/bitcoin-halving-is-less-than-40000-blocks-away-heres-what-that-means/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">halving</a>&rdquo; and approval of a <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/united-states-sec-officially-accepts-valkyrie-spot-bitcoin-etf-application/">spot bitcoin exchange-traded fund</a> will also benefit MSTR, the TD Cowen analyst concluded.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/microstrategy-stock-has-22-upside-td-cowen-analyst/">Bitcoin-focused MicroStrategy stock has 22% upside – analyst says</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Decentralized exchange PancakeSwap taps zkSync Era blockchain</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/decentralized-exchange-pancakeswap-taps-zksync-era-blockchain/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/decentralized-exchange-pancakeswap-taps-zksync-era-blockchain/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 17:25:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/decentralized-exchange-pancakeswap-taps-zksync-era-blockchain/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>PancakeSwap initially launched on BNB Chain but is now available on five blockchains. The zkSync Era blockchain is the most recent blockchain that the DEX will be available on. The move is aimed at expanding PancakeSwap&#8217;s user base and increasing protocol revenue. The decentralized exchange PancakeSwap (CAKE) is now available on the zkSync Era blockchain [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/decentralized-exchange-pancakeswap-taps-zksync-era-blockchain/">Decentralized exchange PancakeSwap taps zkSync Era blockchain</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>PancakeSwap initially launched on BNB Chain but is now available on five blockchains.</li>
<li>The zkSync Era blockchain is the most recent blockchain that the DEX will be available on.</li>
<li>The move is aimed at expanding PancakeSwap&rsquo;s user base and increasing protocol revenue.</li>
</ul>
<p>The decentralized exchange PancakeSwap (CAKE) is now available on the zkSync Era blockchain according to a statement made by the DEX&rsquo;s creator &ldquo;Chef Cocoa&rdquo; on Thursday. While this is a major milestone for the DEX, the news has not caused a significant price movement on the native token <a href="https://coinjournal.net/pancakeswap/">CAKE</a>, seeing it has only gained about 1.40% today.</p>
<p>The move is consistent with PancakeSwap&rsquo;s goals to grow its user base and boost the protocol&rsquo;s income.</p>
<h2>Available Pancakeswap features on Era blockchain</h2>
<p>To start with, PancakeSwap&rsquo;s token swap and liquidity provisioning features will be available with transactional fees of 0.01% of the trading value.</p>
<p>In the coming weeks, the farms feature that allows users to stake their liquidity pool (LP) tokens to earn CAKE while keeping the LP tokens will go live.</p>
<p>As a decentralized exchange, PancakeSwap uses smart contracts instead of middlemen to process trades, lending and lottery services for users. Besides zkSync Era, PancakeSwap is currently available on the BNB Chain, <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/ethereum/">Ethereum</a>, Polygon zkEVM, and Aptos. As of Wednesday, the DEX held more than $1/57 billion worth of tokens according to data from DefiLlama.</p>
<p>On the other hand, zkSync Era, which was launched by Developer Matter Labs as an <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/what-is-ethereum/">Ethereum</a> layer 2 blockchain compatible with the Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM) allows developers to deploy applications between zkSync Era and the Ethereum mainnet using the same code.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/decentralized-exchange-pancakeswap-taps-zksync-era-blockchain/">Decentralized exchange PancakeSwap taps zkSync Era blockchain</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/decentralized-exchange-pancakeswap-taps-zksync-era-blockchain/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Optimism and Arbitrum metrics diverge as OP token outperforms</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/optimism-and-arbitrum-metrics-diverge-as-op-token-outperforms/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/optimism-and-arbitrum-metrics-diverge-as-op-token-outperforms/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 16:32:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/optimism-and-arbitrum-metrics-diverge-as-op-token-outperforms/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Optimism and Arbitrum are some of the best-known layer-2 networks. The two network&#8217;s metrics have diverged in the past few days. These metrics include the number of users and open interest. Optimism and Arbitrum ecosystems have diverged in the past few weeks. Arbitrum&#8217;s number of active addresses has dropped from an all-time high of 191,612 [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/optimism-and-arbitrum-metrics-diverge-as-op-token-outperforms/">Optimism and Arbitrum metrics diverge as OP token outperforms</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Optimism and Arbitrum are some of the best-known layer-2 networks.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The two network&rsquo;s metrics have diverged in the past few days.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">These metrics include the number of users and open interest.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Optimism and Arbitrum ecosystems have diverged in the past few weeks. Arbitrum&rsquo;s number of active addresses has dropped from an all-time high of 191,612 in March this year to over 148k. Most recently, Optimism&rsquo;s users has been in an upward trend and reached a high of 132,893.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The same trend is happening in their the performance of their decentralized finance (DeFi) industry. Data compiled by DeFi Llama shows that Optimism&rsquo;s total value locked (TVL) in its ecosystem stands at over $1.27 billion while Arbitrum&rsquo;s&nbsp;<a href="https://defillama.com/chain/Arbitrum"><u>stands</u></a> at over $3 billion.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The two ecosystems have been relatively stable in the past few weeks. However, while Arbitrum&rsquo;s TVL has dropped by 0.40% in the past 30 days, Optimism&rsquo;s TVl has risen by over 13% in the past 30 days. This makes it second only to Solana whose TVL has jumped by more than 30%.</p>
<p dir="ltr">TVL is an important metric in the crypto industry in that it shows the amount of money locked in a network. Ideally, a network with a higher TVL is seen as being more active. In this regard, the most active ecosystems are&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/"><u>Ethereum</u></a>,&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/tron"><u>Tron</u></a>, and BNB Chain.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Additional data shows that the open interest of Optimism and Arbitrum&rsquo;s tokens has diverged. The open interest of Arbitrum futures stands at $160 million, where it has been in the past few months. Optimism&rsquo;s open interest, on the other hand, has been in an upward trend as you can see below. It rose to over $171 million this month and has now stabilised at $143 million.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/27/1690475473373-a9b95461-462a-467f-ade9-a1e196289086.jpg" style="width: 628px;height: 177.951px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="628" height="177.951"></p>
<p dir="ltr">A likely reason for this divergence is Worldcoin, the recently launched cryptocurrency. The WLD token has done well mostly because of the underlying technology and the fact that its creator is the founder of OpenAi, the company that introduced ChatGPT. Worldcoin is built on top of &nbsp;Optimism.</p>
<p dir="ltr">At the same time, the OP token has outperformed Arbitrum&rsquo;s token. OP has risen by more than 20% this year while ARB token has risen by 4% in the past 30 days.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/27/1690475473039-1e535975-8d13-4f3d-b28f-6359512697e6.png" style="width: 640px;height: 311.018px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="640" height="311.018"></p>
<p dir="ltr">Looking ahead, the next catalyst for Optimism token will be the upcoming token unlock that will happen on Sunday. The event will see the number of outstanding tokens jump according to the vesting schedule.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy Optimism</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/optimism-and-arbitrum-metrics-diverge-as-op-token-outperforms/">Optimism and Arbitrum metrics diverge as OP token outperforms</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/optimism-and-arbitrum-metrics-diverge-as-op-token-outperforms/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin inverse relationship with dollar weakening</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-inverse-relationship-with-dollar-weakening/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-inverse-relationship-with-dollar-weakening/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dan Ashmore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 15:23:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-inverse-relationship-with-dollar-weakening/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The US dollar is the global reserve currency, meaning it is a key influence on all risk assets Bitcoin has seen its negative correlation with the dollar pick up since the transition to a tight monetary regime, meaning it tends to strengthen when the dollar falls This inverse relationship has softened in recent weeks, as [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-inverse-relationship-with-dollar-weakening/">Bitcoin inverse relationship with dollar weakening</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>The US dollar is the global reserve currency, meaning it is a key influence on all risk assets</li>
<li dir="ltr">Bitcoin has seen its negative correlation with the dollar pick up since the transition to a tight monetary regime, meaning it tends to strengthen when the dollar falls</li>
<li dir="ltr">This inverse relationship has softened in recent weeks, as Bitcoin has failed to capitalise on dollar weakness arising from lower inflation in the US</li>
<li dir="ltr">If history is to be followed and the correlation returns, Bitcoin could be in a place to advance</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The status of the US dollar as the world&rsquo;s reserve currency means it exhibits an enormous influence on risk assets not only in the US, but across the financial world.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin is no exception. We have seen an inverse relationship between the two assets play out over the last few years, meaning that as the dollar weakens, Bitcoin tends to strengthen, and vice-versa.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">This is for a couple of reasons. Firstly, Bitcoin is commonly quoted in USD due to, as mentioned above, the dollar being the global reserve currency. Therefore, it is simple math that when the denominator weakens (dollar), the ratio goes up, all else equal.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, the effects run deeper. Across international trade, debt and non-bank borrowing, the dollar reigns supreme. Firms issuing debt in foreign currency do so via the dollar an estimated 70% of the time (the euro is next with approximately 20%). Again, this is due to its status as the global reserve currency (we see the same in sovereign debt markets). As the dollar weakens, the cost of servicing this debt falls, greasing the wheels of global liquidity. Hence, risk assets tend to appreciate as the dollar falls, albeit a generalisation.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">For Bitcoin, we saw this in effect in 2022, as the dollar surged to a twenty-year high while Bitcoin was ravaged in line with risk assets across the market. Yet in the last month, the correlation has been fading and heading towards zero (i.e. no relationship at all).&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14541360">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">The above chart shows that this has happened a few times before in the last six months, only for the correlation to soon return (i.e. dip back down towards -1). The first major deviation came in March, when the regional bank crisis was triggered amid the sudden collapse of Silicon Valley Bank, sparking mass volatility in the market, with Bitcoin gaining nicely in the aftermath. More recently, the deviation seem to have been caused by the crypto-specific episodes featuring the SEC&rsquo;s lawsuits against Binance and Coinbase, and the spot ETF applications from a slew of large asset managers.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">In the last week, the dollar has weakened further, continuing its steep downward trend. Its fall of nearly 2.5% is its worst drop since November, when softer-than-expectation inflation readings landed, fuelling speculation that the Federal Reserve would pare back on interest rate rises sooner than previously anticipated. Higher interest rates propel dollar strength, as capital is attracted to the dollar to exploit the higher yield on offer.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Ten days ago, inflation landed at 3%, again softer than expected and causing a repeat of November&rsquo;s episode: yet more dollar decline as the market positions itself for a potential end to the rate hiking regime. There is also the case of the dollar strengthening during times of macro uncertainty because, as the reserve currency, it is the safest asset on record. With correlations going to one in a crisis, there tends to be a significant strengthening of the dollar when fear increases.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">This is part of the reason for the dollar&rsquo;s relentless advance in the first three quarters of last year, while the subsequent easing this year has seen the opposite. The below chart shows this relationship over the last half-century, with periods of recession (grey on the chart) typically resulting in gains for the greenback. &nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14541146">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">Looking forward, one can imagine a scenario where the dollar continues to head lower. Inflation in the US is far lower than most other countries; eurozone inflation is at 5.5%, while the UK is at 7.9%, to name a couple. The Fed should have a greater ability to ease off the rate hikes if that divergence is maintained and inflation in the US continues to fall.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">For Bitcoin, should its inverse relationship with the dollar return, this could mean it may in a position to take advantage. It should be noted, however, that crypto-specific risk is high, which can overshadow any dollar effects easily. Not to mention the macro climate remains uncertain, even if things are brightening up. But history tells us that a weakening dollar is a boon for Bitcoin, and the past nine months have been no exception to this rule.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-inverse-relationship-with-dollar-weakening/">Bitcoin inverse relationship with dollar weakening</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-inverse-relationship-with-dollar-weakening/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A temperature check on crypto as market eyes end of rate hiking cycle</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/a-temperature-check-on-crypto-as-market-eyes-end-of-rate-hiking-cycle/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dan Ashmore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 15:17:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/a-temperature-check-on-crypto-as-market-eyes-end-of-rate-hiking-cycle/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key Takeaways The Federal Reserve increased interest rates 0.25% Wednesday, but the market is anticipating the hiking cycle is coming to a close Optimism is flowing in crypto markets, which saw crushing losses in 2022 as rates rose swiftly While the Fed has said it no longer forecasts a recession, this could be a double-edged [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/a-temperature-check-on-crypto-as-market-eyes-end-of-rate-hiking-cycle/">A temperature check on crypto as market eyes end of rate hiking cycle</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2 dir="ltr">Key Takeaways</h2>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">The Federal Reserve increased interest rates 0.25% Wednesday, but the market is anticipating the hiking cycle is coming to a close</li>
<li dir="ltr">Optimism is flowing in crypto markets, which saw crushing losses in 2022 as rates rose swiftly</li>
<li dir="ltr">While the Fed has said it no longer forecasts a recession, this could be a double-edged sword for crypto</li>
<li dir="ltr">Fed may be reluctant to cut rates, instead electing to for the <em>higher for longer&nbsp;</em>approach, something which could restrain crypto</li>
<li dir="ltr">Employment is at half-century lows, wage pressure remains and core inflation has been stickier than the headline number</li>
<li dir="ltr">Overall, macro environment is far brighter than nine months ago, but caution may be prudent for crypto investors despite market-wide sentiment spiking rapidly</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p dir="ltr">Following the latest 25 bps increase to the federal funds rate Wednesday, which was widely anticipated ahead of time by the market, the most important interest rate in the economy is now a remarkable 525 bps above where it was prior to March 2022, when the Fed first hiked rates.</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14565862">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">Finally, after a relentless liquidity squeeze, the market is anticipating that the end of the road may be nigh. For Bitcoin investors, this is music to their ears. Or at least that is what many in the sector are currently proclaiming. The only thing is, the true story may be a bit more convoluted.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitcoin has moved with yield expectations</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Firstly, it is unquestioned that the transition to a higher yield environment has been a death wish for crypto. As inflation became rampant last year and we transitioned to a new paradigm of tight monetary policy after a decade of essentially-free money, digital assets were crushed. Liquidity was sucked out of the entire system, hurting assets which reside on the long end of the risk spectrum the most. And that is certainly where crypto has set up shop in its brief existence thus far.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The below chart shows this as well as any. Plotting the two-year treasury yield, which moves with rate expectations, on an inverted axis against the Bitcoin price shows how much the latter has dipped in line with the rise in yields. And we know that where Bitcoin goes, crypto tends to follow.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14565739">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">The optimism being spouted about now is centred on the hope that much-coveted rate cuts are imminent. Yet there is reason to believe that this may still be premature, for a number of reasons. The bulk of Powell&rsquo;s comments from Wednesday&rsquo;s meeting can be dismissed as diplomatic answers structured to leave the Fed with as much optionality as possible going forward, but one admission was notable: the revelation that the Fed is no longer forecasting a recession. &nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;So the staff now has a noticeable slowdown in growth starting later this year in the forecast, but given the resilience of the economy recently, they are no longer forecasting a recession,&rdquo; Powell said.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">While this may sound like good news &ndash; and it is! &ndash; this also means that, perhaps counter-intuitively, Bitcoin may not have quite the boost behind it that it may have otherwise hoped for. The reason is that, if we go back to Economics 101, the Fed utilises rate cuts to stimulate a sluggish economy. If a recession is no longer anticipated, it is less likely these cuts will come.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Federal Reserve has been extremely reluctant to cut rates in the last few decades unless explicitly forced to, such as when the economy went into a tailspin as the COVID pandemic suddenly emerged in March 2020. If we view the below chart, showing the fed rate all the way back to 1990, we see that without a recession, the administration has been cautious for the most part. And with inflation remaining higher than its 2% target, it feels ambitious to assume it will change that approach anytime soon.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14566272">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">While rate <em>hikes&nbsp;</em>may be coming to an end, rate <em>cuts&nbsp;</em>don&rsquo;t feel like they will transpire anytime soon.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">This thought is reinforced when digging into the numbers underlying this unique current macro situation. While the headline figure of 3% inflation is drawing all the attention, the core number is perhaps the better gauge; this strips out the volatile effects of food and energy and can be more relevant for the Fed&rsquo;s policy decisions. Looking at this core number, it has dropped only 110 bps in the last year and remains at a stout 4.8%. This contrasts with a fall of 690 bps in the headline figure over the same period.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14566155">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">Not to mention that with the way the CPI is structured as a YoY number, we are into the stage of the year where inflation was always going to fall. This is because there were such hot readings landing at this time last year, when energy prices were sky-high and inflation came within 10 bps of hitting double digits. These readings dropping out of the index creates a more dramatic reduction in the YoY number.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">While 3% may sound close to 2%, this difference also remains a chasm, should the Fed remain determined to get back to its original target. Jim Bianco, speaking to the On the Margin podcast this week, had a good way of explaining why this matters.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;The Fed would tell us that the neutral funds rate is half a percent above inflation&hellip;so if the long-run (inflation) rate is 3% (as opposed to 2%), the neutral rate is 3.5%, so they are 200 bps above that (at the current fed rate). When the yield curve normalises out again, it should be positive 150 bps &ndash; that is historically where it has been.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">With a 150bps spread on the yield curve, he concludes that the 10-year yield must be at 5% to be neutral. Currently, the 10-year yield is at 3.9%, meaning via Bianco&rsquo;s summation, rates would need to come <em>up&nbsp;</em>110 bps to hit the Fed&rsquo;s notion of neutrality under a 3% inflation target regime. This illustrates how the journey to 2% remains important, should that still be the Fed&rsquo;s target (which Powell has adamantly repeated it is).&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Lagged effects of monetary policy&nbsp;</h2>
<p dir="ltr">In addition to the inflation number, there is no getting around the fact that wage pressure remains high and unemployment is at 3.6%, hanging around the lowest mark in half a century. This, again, is great news for the overall economy, but will also spell concern in the Fed that inflationary pressure remains and the fight is not yet over. Cutting into this environment feels like a risk that Powell and co. are not in a position to take, and perhaps won&rsquo;t be for longer than some anticipate.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">With monetary policy operating with such a notorious lag, and the fact this hiking cycle has been among the swiftest in modern history, it needs to be caveated that, while the Fed is determined to keep all options open, there genuinely is a lot of uncertainty.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">For crypto, this bears consideration amid the tangible excitement that has begun flowing through certain circles. Undoubtedly, this has been a tremendous run and the industry would have snapped your hand off if you offered them this position nine months ago, when FTX circled the drain and threatened to pull a chunk of the entire asset class down with it. But the battle has not quite been won yet, even if the tide has begun to turn.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/a-temperature-check-on-crypto-as-market-eyes-end-of-rate-hiking-cycle/">A temperature check on crypto as market eyes end of rate hiking cycle</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>SEC approves new AI-related rules for brokers: Is this the game-changer for AltSignals?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/sec-approves-new-ai-related-rules-for-brokers-is-this-the-game-changer-for-altsignals/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/sec-approves-new-ai-related-rules-for-brokers-is-this-the-game-changer-for-altsignals/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 12:08:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brokers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/sec-approves-new-ai-related-rules-for-brokers-is-this-the-game-changer-for-altsignals/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SEC approved new AI-related rules targeting brokers on July 26. This comes amid growing adoption of AI across all areas of the global economy. What does this mean for AltSignals, the trading firm behind the upcoming ActualizeAI. Regulation remains a huge factor in the overall growth and adoption of cryptocurrency, and the US Securities and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sec-approves-new-ai-related-rules-for-brokers-is-this-the-game-changer-for-altsignals/">SEC approves new AI-related rules for brokers: Is this the game-changer for AltSignals?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">SEC approved new AI-related rules targeting brokers on July 26.</li>
<li dir="ltr">This comes amid growing adoption of AI across all areas of the global economy.</li>
<li dir="ltr">What does this mean for AltSignals, the trading firm behind the upcoming ActualizeAI.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/regulation/">Regulation</a> remains a huge factor in the overall growth and adoption of cryptocurrency, and the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC)&rsquo;s recent onslaught on crypto exchanges reveals just as much.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Also, days after it suffered a blow in its case against Ripple over XRP, the SEC has moved to approve new rules with regard to likely <a href="https://www.sec.gov/tm/iabd-staff-bulletin-conflicts-interest" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>conflict of interest</u></a> as broker platforms increasingly integrate artificial intelligence. What does this mean and does it impact <a href="https://token.altsignals.io/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>AltSignals</u></a>?</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What the SEC&rsquo;s new rules on AI application by brokers says</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/compare/best-cryptocurrency-brokers/">Brokers</a>, basically platforms that facilitate the exchange of crypto for crypto or fiat, use optimization technology. The SEC is looking to adopt new rules around these &ldquo;optimization functions&rdquo;, with changes prohibiting brokers from leveraging AI or data analytics tools to their own advantage.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to details in a <a href="https://www.sec.gov/files/34-97990-fact-sheet.pdf" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>fact sheet</u></a> the agency published on July 26, the use of these technologies, including algorithms and models, creates potential conflict of interest. In particular, when broker firms tap into the highlighted technology to foster investor interaction, possible conflict of interest arises when the firms use these to lure the same investors.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The changes to AI use applies to crypto transactions involving broker-dealers registered with the securities regulator and will go to a final vote after the end of a 60-day period for public feedback. Meanwhile, the SEC has acknowledged that at the moment, no crypto entity is duly registered as a national securities exchange.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Good news for AI-powered crypto trading platforms like Fetch.ai and AltSignals? It&rsquo;s still early days in terms of regulation of AI and we cannot forestall what might come down the road. However, clarity for both the crypto industry and the artificial intelligence space could be what sparks the next adoption wave for the likes of AltSignals.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The European Union&rsquo;s recently adopted EU AI Act and similar efforts in the US has seen many AI behemoths, including Google&rsquo;s Alphabet Inc., Microsoft and Meta pursue safeguards that will align the sector to regulatory measures aimed at protecting consumers.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is AltSignals?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals is a trading platform that offers access to market signals for traders. After seeing increased adoption since its debut in 2017, and with users cutting across all market segments, the company is in the process of bolstering its proprietary trading algorithm with integration of blockchain technology and an artificial intelligence-powered layer.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The new platform, ActualizeAI, will be powered by a crypto token called ASI. Currently, AltSignals is offering the native token to early backers of its AI layer, with the presale in the second stage and having raised more than $1.21 million.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Opportunities for investors using ActualizeAI and ASI</h2>
<p dir="ltr">While AltSignals&rsquo; AltAlgo algorithm offers trading signals with win rates of 64% or so, the upcoming AI-infused layer ActualizeAI could push this to staggering levels.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The whitepaper outlines machine learning, natural language processing and other features as additions that could see AltSignals&rsquo; accuracy levels jump to an average of 80% across its buy and sell signals. A platform that allows for real-time access and automation, the future of ActualizeAI could be transformative for traders across the industry.</p>
<p dir="ltr">ASI will give holders exclusive access to the AltSignals AI platform when it goes live. Token holders could also tap into their holdings to earn more tokens via staking or through participating in product development programs to earn rewards.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Savvy investors can unlock more passive income potential by holding 50,000 tokens. According to details on the AltSignals <a href="https://token.altsignals.io/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>website</u></a>, not only does this offer unlimited access to ActualizeAI, but also allows one to mint the &ldquo;Access AI Pass.&rdquo; &nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">With this, members have the opportunity to activate a passive income generation stream via a revenue-sharing model linked to all products released in the ActualizeAI ecosystem.</p>
<p>Do you want to learn more about AltSignals or join the presale? Go to AltSignals.io <a href="https://token.altsignals.io/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>here</u></a>.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sec-approves-new-ai-related-rules-for-brokers-is-this-the-game-changer-for-altsignals/">SEC approves new AI-related rules for brokers: Is this the game-changer for AltSignals?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/sec-approves-new-ai-related-rules-for-brokers-is-this-the-game-changer-for-altsignals/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>BarnBridge (BOND) token takes to the sky weeks after SEC probe scare</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/barnbridge-bond-token-takes-to-the-sky-weeks-after-sec-probe-scare/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/barnbridge-bond-token-takes-to-the-sky-weeks-after-sec-probe-scare/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 11:20:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DAO]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/barnbridge-bond-token-takes-to-the-sky-weeks-after-sec-probe-scare/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The BarnBridge token has hit a daily high of $3.82, after a 30% surge earlier today. At press time, the token was trading at $3.69, up 24.94% in 24 hours. On July 7, there were reports of the US SEC investigating the BarnBridge and members associated with the DAO. The BarnBridge (BOND) token started the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/barnbridge-bond-token-takes-to-the-sky-weeks-after-sec-probe-scare/">BarnBridge (BOND) token takes to the sky weeks after SEC probe scare</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul class="decimal_type">
<li>The BarnBridge token has hit a daily high of $3.82, after a 30% surge earlier today.</li>
<li>At press time, the token was trading at $3.69, up 24.94% in 24 hours.</li>
<li>On July 7, there were reports of the US SEC investigating the BarnBridge and members associated with the DAO.</li>
</ul>
<p>The BarnBridge (BOND) token started the day with a major jump, reclaiming all the losses it made since June 24. Although the token has since slightly pulled back from today&rsquo;s high of $3.82, the token is still way above where it was trading when revelations of the US Security and Exchanges Commission (SEC) probe were made.</p>
<div class="fr-img-space-wrap"><span class="fr-img-caption fr-fic fr-dib fr-draggable" style="width: 615px"><span class="fr-img-wrap">
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/27/1690456324514-429d4d1d-7a1e-45dc-80f2-4e2a9672ff84.jpg" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="615" height="448"><span class="fr-inner" style="background: transparent;position: relative">BarnBridge price chart. Source: Coinmarketcap</span></p>
<p></p></span></span>
<p class="fr-img-space-wrap2">&nbsp;</p>
</div>
<p>While the sudden price surge is welcome news for the crypto community, there are questions as to what is behind the move. In this article, we shall shed some light on what is happening behind the scenes.</p>
<h2>Why is the BarnBridge token price rising?</h2>
<p>On July 6 2023, Douglas Park, the elected legal counsel of the BarnBridge DAO took to social media platforms including X (formerly Twitter) to <a href="https://twitter.com/Barn_Bridge/status/1677110787780018176?s=20">state</a> that the US SEC had started investigating the BarnBridge DAO. Soon after, BarnBridge co-founder Tyler Ward, who commonly referred to as &ldquo;Lord Tyler&rdquo; on Discord, confirmed Park&rsquo;s message was accurate.</p>
<p>Following Park&rsquo;s revelation, the BOND token dipped by 10% sending shockwaves among the community.</p>
<p>At the time, Park suggested that &ldquo;all work&rdquo; on BarnBridge-related products should stop, including the closing of liquidity pools, in order to &ldquo;reduce potential further legal liability,&rdquo; and that people shouldn&rsquo;t be paid for work resulting from the DAO&rsquo;s investment efforts.</p>
<p>The details of the investigations were, however, never disclosed, probably due to what Park called &ldquo;ongoing&rdquo; investigations.</p>
<p>Some DAO members raised suspicions over the Park&rsquo;s announcement with one member on Discord asking for supporting evidence of the SEC&rsquo;s investigation implying that BarnBridge&rsquo;s founders could be using it as an excuse to facilitate an &ldquo;exit strategy&rdquo; to possibly defraud investors. Tyler Ward however rebutted the allegation, stating it would be the &ldquo;worst thought-out rug attempt in history.&rdquo;</p>
<p>From the time the SEC investigation allegations were made to date, nothing much has surfaced about the investigations and the BarnBridge community is likely starting to blush off the effects of the allegations seeing that the BarnBridge (BONB) token has witnessed a tremendous increase in trading activity in the last two days. At the time of writing, the trading volume was up 1852.83% over the last 24 hours.</p>
<p>It is also important to note that a similar BOND price surge was witnessed last year at a similar time as <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/barnbridges-bond-crypto-price-could-jump-by-at-least-46/">previously covered</a> by Coinjounal.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/barnbridge-bond-token-takes-to-the-sky-weeks-after-sec-probe-scare/">BarnBridge (BOND) token takes to the sky weeks after SEC probe scare</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/barnbridge-bond-token-takes-to-the-sky-weeks-after-sec-probe-scare/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fireblocks, Astar Network partner to bring crypto and DeFi to over 650 banks</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/fireblocks-astar-network-partner-to-bring-crypto-and-defi-to-over-650-banks/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/fireblocks-astar-network-partner-to-bring-crypto-and-defi-to-over-650-banks/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 10:10:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Japan]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/fireblocks-astar-network-partner-to-bring-crypto-and-defi-to-over-650-banks/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Fireblocks&#8217; integration with Astar Network could bring crypto and DeFi to over 650 banks. Institutional investors across banks, exchanges, OTCs and hedge funds will leverage Fireblocks&#8217; technology to easily and securely access crypto on Astar. An event to celebrate the integration attracted over 200 guests, including executives at VCs and Web3 founders. Fireblocks, an enterprise-grade [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/fireblocks-astar-network-partner-to-bring-crypto-and-defi-to-over-650-banks/">Fireblocks, Astar Network partner to bring crypto and DeFi to over 650 banks</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Fireblocks&rsquo; integration with Astar Network could bring crypto and DeFi to over 650 banks.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Institutional investors across banks, exchanges, OTCs and hedge funds will leverage Fireblocks&rsquo; technology to easily and securely access crypto on Astar.</li>
<li dir="ltr">An event to celebrate the integration attracted over 200 guests, including executives at VCs and Web3 founders.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="http://www.fireblocks.com/" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Fireblocks</a>, an enterprise-grade platform for institutional adoption of digital assets, has integrated with Astar Network, an EVM and WebAssembly (Wasm) compatible smart contracts platform.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The collaboration could see more than 650 banks and institutional investors use Fireblocks&rsquo; technology to access and manage their digital assets, boosting institutional adoption of <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/defi/">DeFi</a> on Astar, the two platforms said in a press release.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Banks, OTCs, <a href="https://coinjournal.net/compare/best-cryptocurrency-exchanges/">exchanges</a> and hedge funds also have an opportunity to leverage Fireblock&rsquo;s MPC-based wallet infrastructure to access Astar&rsquo;s assets, including on leading Astar-based DeFi protocol ArthSwap.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>We are excited to add Astar to the Fireblocks Network and support the growth of Japan&rsquo;s leading smart contract platform</em>,&rdquo; said Stephen Richardson, Managing Director, Financial Markets and Head of APAC at Fireblocks.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Multichain access to dApps</h2>
<p dir="ltr">With Astar offering a multichain, interoperable environment, the integration with Fireblocks allows users to tap into decentralized applications (dApps) on Ethereum and Polkadot ecosystems. Banks and institutional investors looking to diversify with digital assets will also access functionality such as trading, swaps and lending of digital assets on the Astar platform.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>Fireblocks is a leading platform catering to institutional investors. We&rsquo;re looking forward to leveraging this integration to enhance adoption while giving institutions looking to build on Astar a secure and robust way to safeguard their digital assets</em>,&rdquo; Maarten Henskens, CEO of Astar Foundation, said in a statement.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Astar, Fireblocks and bitbank celebrated the integration during the WebX event in Tokyo, with more than 200 guests attending. &nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The event attracted executives of global enterprises, VCs and Web3 founders, with discussions around blockchain-powered decentralized protocols.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/fireblocks-astar-network-partner-to-bring-crypto-and-defi-to-over-650-banks/">Fireblocks, Astar Network partner to bring crypto and DeFi to over 650 banks</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/fireblocks-astar-network-partner-to-bring-crypto-and-defi-to-over-650-banks/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
