<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 13:54:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Hong Kong crypto platform HKVAX receives approval-in-principle from SFC</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/hong-kong-crypto-platform-hkvax-receives-approval-in-principle-from-sfc/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 13:54:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Policy and Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[exchanges]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/hong-kong-crypto-platform-hkvax-receives-approval-in-principle-from-sfc/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>HKVAX has moved closer to becoming only the third platform to receive a VATP licence in Hong Kong. This is after it obtained an approval-in-principle from the Hong Kong Securities and Futures Commission (SFC) The SFC website lists OSL and Hashkey as only two VATP licensed companies. Hong Kong Virtual Asset Exchange (HKVAX) has received [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/hong-kong-crypto-platform-hkvax-receives-approval-in-principle-from-sfc/">Hong Kong crypto platform HKVAX receives approval-in-principle from SFC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">HKVAX has moved closer to becoming only the third platform to receive a VATP licence in Hong Kong.</li>
<li dir="ltr">This is after it obtained an approval-in-principle from the Hong Kong Securities and Futures Commission (SFC)</li>
<li dir="ltr">The SFC website lists OSL and Hashkey as only two VATP licensed companies.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Hong Kong Virtual Asset Exchange (HKVAX) has received a notice of approval-in-principle from the Hong Kong Securities and Futures Commission (SFC).</p>
<p dir="ltr">A <a href="https://www.hkvax.com/news/detail?diffId=1673250247927656448" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">press release</a> from HKVAX noted that the approval will see the platform become only the third virtual asset trading platform (VATP) to be licensed by the SFC.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>We are delighted to have received approval-in-principle from the SFC and look forward to creating a safe and trusted environment for investors in one of the world&rsquo;s largest and most dynamic financial centres</em>,&rdquo; said Dr. Anthony Ng, co-founder and CEO of HKVAX.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to HKVAX, a final approval from the regulator will allow the company to provide regulated activities identified as Type 1 (securities offerings) and Type 7 (automated trading services) to customers. HKVAX will offer three core products to users once the regulatory process is done &ndash; an OTC brokerage, an institutional-grade exchange platform, and custody solution.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">HKVAX to join OSL and Hashkey as third VATP licence</h2>
<p dir="ltr">&nbsp;HKVAX&rsquo;s approval-in-principle could see it join OSL and Hashkey as the third licensed VATP in Hong Kong. Details on the SFC <a href="https://www.sfc.hk/en/Welcome-to-the-Fintech-Contact-Point/Virtual-assets/Virtual-asset-trading-platforms-operators/Lists-of-virtual-asset-trading-platforms" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">website</a> show that OSL received the first digital assets broker licence in December 2020, while Hashkey was licensed in November 2022.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The path to approval for HKVAX comes on the back of the Hong Kong government&rsquo;s push to bring into operation <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/hong-kong-to-release-crypto-framework-next-month-bloomberg/"><u>a new crypto framework</u></a> for the virtual asset industry.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Among the changes has been the requirement that registered institutions and banks extend services to SFC-licensed crypto platforms. Firms seeking to offer virtual assets are also obligated to apply for appropriate licences before providing these services.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Sam Fok, co-founder and COO at HKVAX said they welcome the new changes meant to provide regulatory clarity for the industry in Hong Kong. He added:</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>Over the last two years, we have worked very closely with the government and other stakeholders to strengthen regulations. We welcome the changes proposed recently by the SFC that open up virtual assets to a wider community while providing investors of all types with the transparency, reliability and protection they expect. The changes also signal Hong Kong&rsquo;s intent to become a global virtual asset hub</em>.&rdquo;</p>
<p>On August 7, the SFC <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/hong-kong-warns-crypto-exchanges-about-improper-practices/"><u>published a warning to VATPs</u></a> that are yet to get properly licensed not to mislead users, particularly through statements published in relation to &ldquo;their intention to apply for licences.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>
<p>According to the regulator, such announcements are likely to &ldquo;give the public a false sense of assurance&rdquo; that the VATP is compliant with SFC regulations.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/hong-kong-crypto-platform-hkvax-receives-approval-in-principle-from-sfc/">Hong Kong crypto platform HKVAX receives approval-in-principle from SFC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Barcelona to host this year’s record-breaking European Blockchain Convention</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/barcelona-to-host-this-years-record-breaking-european-blockchain-convention/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/barcelona-to-host-this-years-record-breaking-european-blockchain-convention/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 12:56:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/barcelona-to-host-this-years-record-breaking-european-blockchain-convention/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways The city of Barcelona will host this year&#8217;s EBC9, the largest European blockchain convention so far. The event will last for three days, starting from October 24th. Coinjournal is a proud media partner of the convention. Barcelona to host EBC9 Barcelona, the Catalan capital, will host this year&#8217;s European Blockchain Convention 9 (EBC9). [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/barcelona-to-host-this-years-record-breaking-european-blockchain-convention/">Barcelona to host this year’s record-breaking European Blockchain Convention</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The city of Barcelona will host this year&rsquo;s EBC9, the largest European blockchain convention so far.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The event will last for three days, starting from October 24th.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Coinjournal is a proud media partner of the convention.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr">Barcelona to host EBC9</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Barcelona, the Catalan capital, will host this year&rsquo;s European Blockchain Convention 9 (EBC9). This will be the largest European blockchain event so far and will take place from October 24-27.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to the organisers, EBC9 will be the largest event of its kind for the second half of the year. The event will have in attendance roughly 5,000 delegates, making it the largest EBC event so far.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The event coincides with the El Cl&aacute;sico clash between Barcelona and Real Madrid, perhaps the most significant football rivalry in the world.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The organisers revealed that 300 founders, CEOs, and industry experts will be in attendance to speak at the event. Some of the speakers include C-level execs from Nansen, Fidelity, Fabric Ventures, and Animoca Brands.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Furthermore, there would be speakers from traditional companies, including Banco Santander and Volkswagen. Senior personnel from Binance Labs and Galaxy Digital will also be in attendance.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Coinjournal is a proud media partner of the European Blockchain Convention.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">While commenting on this&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>latest cryptocurrency news</u></a>, Victoria Gago, co-founder of the European Blockchain Convention, stated that;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;We have seen a significant increase in registrations and interest from exhibitors and sponsors alike after the overwhelmingly positive feedback we got from our previous edition. Building on that momentum, we are moving EBC9 to Fira Barcelona, a much larger venue. As the largest convention centre in Spain, it offers ample space for exhibitors, a greater variety of content, and more engaging experiences.&rdquo;</em></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">EBC speakers to touch on diverse topics</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The Co-founder, Daniel Salmeron, said they are excited to bring together the worlds of TradFi, digital assets and web3. He said;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;The participation of so many traditional banks and financial institutions demonstrates their commitment and optimism about the future of crypto and digital assets.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p dir="ltr">EBC9 will see speakers touch on a wide range of topics, including regulatory challenges, CBDCs, privacy, the institutionalization of crypto, DeFi, sustainability, tokenization, and the ascent of AI.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The event won&rsquo;t solely be around panel discussions and workshops. The organisers have put in place a 3,000 sqm exhibition area for sponsors and exhibitors. There will also be AMA sessions with speakers, a 1-to-1 meeting area, and five themed networking lounges.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Other events for attendees to enjoy include an investor meetup, an art gallery, and the second edition of the EBC Start-up Awards.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Finally, there will be a Hackathon where 200+ hackers, 30+ mentors and 20 teams are expected to participate in a 48 hours hackathon.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">You can learn more about the European Blockchain Convention, including sponsorship, ticketing details and the full list of speakers, via their official website,&nbsp;<a href="http://www.eblockchainconvention.com" rel="nofollow"><u>www.eblockchainconvention.com</u></a></p>
<p dir="ltr">Launched in 2018, European Blockchain Convention is the most influential blockchain event in Europe, connecting industry professionals, startups, and technology leaders. The event provides a platform for sharing insights, fostering collaborations, and exploring the vast potential of blockchain, crypto, and digital assets.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/barcelona-to-host-this-years-record-breaking-european-blockchain-convention/">Barcelona to host this year’s record-breaking European Blockchain Convention</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/barcelona-to-host-this-years-record-breaking-european-blockchain-convention/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is Cardano a ghost chain? No. Just extremely overvalued</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/is-cardano-a-ghost-chain-no-just-extremely-overvalued/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/is-cardano-a-ghost-chain-no-just-extremely-overvalued/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 12:44:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/is-cardano-a-ghost-chain-no-just-extremely-overvalued/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Cardano has been criticized as one of the biggest ghost chains in the industry. But its metrics shows that its network activity is doing well. Cardano, one of the most popular blockchains, is also a highly controversial one as concerns about its ecosystem growth remain. Some crypto watchers believe that it is a highly overvalued [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/is-cardano-a-ghost-chain-no-just-extremely-overvalued/">Is Cardano a ghost chain? No. Just extremely overvalued</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Cardano has been criticized as one of the biggest ghost chains in the industry.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">But its metrics shows that its network activity is doing well.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/cardano/"><u>Cardano</u></a>, one of the most popular blockchains, is also a highly controversial one as concerns about its ecosystem growth remain. Some crypto watchers believe that it is a highly overvalued project while others argue it is a ghost chain.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Is Cardano a ghost chain?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">A ghost chain is defined as a crypto project that has nothing going on in its ecosystem. And there are so many such chains in the crypto industry. Some of the top ghost chains are Kadena, Velas, and XDS Network among others.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Cardano, on the other hand, cannot be defined as a ghost chain because its ecosystem is growing. For example, its&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/learn/what-is-defi/"><u>DeFi</u></a> ecosystem is thriving even as the crypto winter continues. Data compiled by DeFi Llama shows that Cardano&rsquo;s TVL has jumped to $227 million, making it the 14th biggest chain in the world.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In ADA terms, Cardano&rsquo;s TVL has jumped to an all-time high of over 750 million ADA coins. This growth has been driven by the rising number of DeFi protocols in Cardano and the performance of platforms like MuesliSwap, MinSwap, SundaeSwap, and Indigo.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Further, Cardano also has many users. As shown below, the network is <a href="https://defillama.com/chain/Cardano?currency=ADA&amp;users=true&amp;tvl=false"><u>averaging</u></a> over 30k daily users. Most ghost chains rarely have any users.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/07/11/1691757737443-9c96b1e4-be0d-46bd-811b-9e41809aed49.jpg" style="width: 657px;height: 313.656px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="657" height="313.656"></p>
<p dir="ltr">Cardano is also active in the NFT industry. Data by CryptoSlam shows that the total sales of Cardano NFTs in the past 24 hours totaled $277k, making it the eighth biggest player in the industry after Ethereum, Polygon, Mythos, Immutable X, BNB Chain, and Bitcoin.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Cardano&rsquo;s valuation is stretched</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, we can conclude without a doubt that Cardano is not a ghost chain. Instead, I believe that Cardano is just highly overvalued. According to CoinMarketCap, Cardano is valued at over $10 billion. At its peak, it was valued at over $90 billion.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Despite the drawdown, it is hard to explain this valuation since $10 billion is a lot of money. Its valuation means that Cardano is valued higher than American Airlines, Lazard, and Moelis.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The biggest challenge is that the ecosystem is getting highly competitive. Most of this competition is coming from layer-2 networks like Arbitrum, Polygon, Base, and Optimism among others.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Cardano has also failed to attract the biggest players in industries like tokenization, stablecoins, and DeFi. Instead, big players like AAVE, Uniswap, and PancakeSwap have moved to L2 networks.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy Cardano</h2>
<p dir="ltr">
        </p><div class="relative">

            
        </div>



<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/is-cardano-a-ghost-chain-no-just-extremely-overvalued/">Is Cardano a ghost chain? No. Just extremely overvalued</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/is-cardano-a-ghost-chain-no-just-extremely-overvalued/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How rising Bitcoin dominance invalidates many crypto assumptions</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/how-rising-bitcoin-dominance-invalidates-many-crypto-assumptions/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/how-rising-bitcoin-dominance-invalidates-many-crypto-assumptions/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dan Ashmore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 11:50:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Opinion]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/how-rising-bitcoin-dominance-invalidates-many-crypto-assumptions/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key Takeaways Bitcoin dominance has risen above 50%, having started the year at 42% Traditionally, dominance falls while market prices are rising in the sector, marking the year 2023 out as unusual&#160; This hammers home how Bitcoin is still finding its feet, and why prudence needs to be taken when extrapolating past performance to the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/how-rising-bitcoin-dominance-invalidates-many-crypto-assumptions/">How rising Bitcoin dominance invalidates many crypto assumptions</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2 dir="ltr">Key Takeaways</h2>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Bitcoin dominance has risen above 50%, having started the year at 42%</li>
<li dir="ltr">Traditionally, dominance falls while market prices are rising in the sector, marking the year 2023 out as unusual&nbsp;</li>
<li dir="ltr">This hammers home how Bitcoin is still finding its feet, and why prudence needs to be taken when extrapolating past performance to the future</li>
<li dir="ltr">Bitcoin was only launched in 2009 and had minimal liquidity for the first few years, meaning our sample space of data is too short to make assumptions solely based on the past </li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin dominance, which measures the ratio of the Bitcoin market cap to the entire cryptocurrency market cap, has clambered back above 50%. With the period of relative serenity in the crypto markets recently, it has been rangebound for the last two months, although dipped to 49% last week.</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, the dominance of the world&rsquo;s biggest crypto has surged since the start of this year, having been in the low 40&rsquo;s as the book was closed on the year 2022.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/07/10/1691667088491-ef3d0717-e9d9-41dc-8a09-cd1b9dd9aaf8.png" style="width: 600px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="600" height="286"></p>
<p dir="ltr">The increase is the biggest prolonged expansion in Bitcoin dominance since 2019, when it rose from 53% to 72% in a five-month period beginning that April.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/07/10/1691667112490-9ac68aa5-4deb-47cb-a13c-c61ff2592cfc.png" style="width: 600px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="600" height="286">Notably, the rise of Bitcoin&rsquo;s dominance this time around contrasts with what we have seen in the past regard the timing of cycles. Despite its extreme volatility when comparing to other major asset classes, Bitcoin can generally be viewed as the lowest-beta option within digital assets. </p>
<p dir="ltr">In previous cycles, the dominance has hence tended to fall in bull markets as altcoins outpace Bitcoin&rsquo;s gains. The pattern has tended to be as follows:</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Bear market</li>
<li dir="ltr">Bitcoin rises, dominance jumps&nbsp;</li>
<li dir="ltr">Altcoins rise more, dominance falls</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"></p>
<p dir="ltr">This time around, the altcoins have not fulfilled their end of the bargain.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Crypto market is changing fundamentally</h2>
<p dir="ltr">There are a few theories which spring to mind to explain these occurences. The first is that Bitcoin is separating itself from the rest of the crypto market. Regulation is one factor here &ndash; Bitcoin has proven to be more immune than many other coins in the space, many of whom have been weighed down by the crackdown in the US around securities laws.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The SEC explicitly named many tokens as securities, including SOL (Solana), MATIC (Polygon) and ADA (Cardano). While Ripple won a landmark case (at least partially) against the SEC last month, providing hope for the future legal path of these proceedings, the intense hostility shown by lawmakers in the US has undoubtedly served to dampen token prices. Bitcoin, however, seems to be in its own genre, targeting &ldquo;commodity&rdquo; status rather than a security.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Then there is the elephant in the room: all the sordid activity that has taken place in the crypto industry over the past eighteen months. From the Terra death spiral to the Celsius scandal to the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ftx-insolvent-what-next-for-crypto/"><u>FTX &ldquo;deceit&rdquo;</u></a>, crypto has taken a beating. This has undoubtedly affected Bitcoin too (as its price chart will so obviously indicate), but it is fair to say that the part of the crypto space that lies further out on the risk curve may find it harder to regain trust from institutions and trad-fi actors (or to win it to begin with, if it never had it in the first place).&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Many have always argued that Bitcoin is separate from the rest of crypto, so much so that the faction who advertise this aggressively have been labelled with the moniker &ldquo;Bitcoin maximalists&rdquo;. As least as far as regulation goes, it seems lawmakers may be coming around towards also separating out the asset from the rest of the crowd.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin has suffered immensely in the last year, however less so price-wise than other coins, while its network has remained online, always, without a hitch. There are many other cryptos who can argue the same, but whether fair or unfair, they may be getting caught up in the reputational crossfire a little more than Bitcoin is.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Beyond these speculative theories, perhaps the greatest lesson of all is to be aware of how fickle many of the trends within the crypto are. Are we really surprised that Bitcoin dominance has risen and altcoins have not caught up as the positive sentiment continues? Why? Because of history?</p>
<p dir="ltr">Let us remind ourselves that &ldquo;history&rdquo; pertains to barely a minute here. Bitcoin was launched in 2009, and didn&rsquo;t trade with any sort of genuine liquidity until perhaps 2015 (if even). Altcoins were even later. The sample size which we have to work with here is far too small to make any sort of concrete conclusions. Compare this to the stock market, or bonds, where we can make all sorts of return and risk assumptions to fit nicely into our Black-Litterman models or so forth.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Not only is the sample size small, but the timing is important, too. Bitcoin was borne out of the embers of one of the greatest crashes in economic history, launched two months before the stock market bottomed in March 2009. Following those tumultuous years, we embarked upon one of the longest bull markets in history. Risk assets went parabolic as generationally-low interest rates fuelled dizzying gains.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, until last year, Bitcoin &ndash; and crypto &ndash; had only ever experienced a low-interest rate, free money economy of up-only risk assets. I have spent a lot of time having fun with Bitcoin models, and my number one takeaway is that, quite simply, <em>we don&rsquo;t know.&nbsp;</em></p>
<p dir="ltr">The world is still figuring out what cryptocurrency is. One day, we will know exactly how to model this thing, just like pension funds know exactly how to apply Markowitz theory to stock/bond portfolios. There will come a day when an efficient frontier portfolio has magic Internet money in it.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">But we aren&rsquo;t there yet. Hence, we can certainly lean on the past few years for guidance, but putting too much weight into this incredibly short and bespoke period (which also included a once-in-a-lifetime pandemic that saw the global economy abruptly lock down) would be misguided.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Perspective is needed. And we don&rsquo;t have a good enough viewpoint yet to get that perspective.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/how-rising-bitcoin-dominance-invalidates-many-crypto-assumptions/">How rising Bitcoin dominance invalidates many crypto assumptions</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/how-rising-bitcoin-dominance-invalidates-many-crypto-assumptions/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu price prediction amid intensifying Shiba Memu competition</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-price-prediction-amid-intensifying-shiba-memu-competition/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-price-prediction-amid-intensifying-shiba-memu-competition/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 10:32:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-price-prediction-amid-intensifying-shiba-memu-competition/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Shiba Inu is expected to rise higher if it breaks above $0.00001. Shiba Inu is facing stiff competition from new Shiba-themed meme coins like Shiba Memu. Shiba Memu has raised over $1.7 million in its ongoing token presale. The value of Shiba Inu (SHIB) has surged by 32% over the past 30 days, offering meme [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-price-prediction-amid-intensifying-shiba-memu-competition/">Shiba Inu price prediction amid intensifying Shiba Memu competition</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul class="decimal_type">
<li>Shiba Inu is expected to rise higher if it breaks above $0.00001.</li>
<li>Shiba Inu is facing stiff competition from new Shiba-themed meme coins like Shiba Memu.</li>
<li>Shiba Memu has raised over $1.7 million in its ongoing token presale.</li>
</ul>
<p>The value of <a href="https://coinjournal.net/shiba-inu/what-is-shiba-inu/">Shiba Inu (SHIB)</a> has surged by 32% over the past 30 days, offering meme coins traders and investors a reason to smile. This upward momentum is not solely due to prevailing positive sentiment in the crypto market. There are a number of other factors main among them being the upcoming Shibarium, an innovative layer-2 scaling solution that distinguishes itself with unique attributes.</p>
<p>Besides its arch-rival, <a href="https://coinjournal.net/dogecoin/what-is-dogecoin/">Dogecoin (DOGE)</a>, Shiba Inu has also been facing steep competition from newcomer meme coins like PEPE and <a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news">Shiba Memu (SHMU)</a>, which is currently in the presale phase. So let&rsquo;s delve into what the future holds for SHIB amid this competition.</p>
<h2>Shiba Inu facing a major resistance at $0.00001</h2>
<p>At press time, SHIB&rsquo;s trading price, according to information from CoinGecko, was $0.00000998. SHIB has demonstrated a rising trend of 19 % in the last seven days. The token has today continued with the bull trend gaining 1% at the time of writing.</p>
<p>Prior to today&rsquo;s price surge, SHIB on Wednesday, experienced a huge rise of 5.75%, reaching $0.00001005.This upward trend fits with a recovery pattern that started two days ago after hitting a low of $0.0000947.</p>
<h2>SHIB price prediction</h2>
<p>SHIB&rsquo;s price has remained well above the 50-day and 200-day Moving Average lines, reflecting the market&rsquo;s active buyer activity. The bullish pressure on the market is further increased by the MACD line crossing above the signal line, although the RSI is moving closer to the overbought zone.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/07/11/1691749705314-69c0f5db-a19f-4085-8750-c5e6c1ba382f.jpg" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="615" height="276"></p>
<p>Nevertheless, for Shiba Inu to make good its bullish potential, it has to beat the resistance at $0.00001 which is further supported by the 200-day MA, creating a strong counterforce to the upward trend of SHIB.</p>
<p>While SHIB might have some trouble breaking through the $0.00001 level and could drop much lower to the area around the 50-day MA, any significant surge above this price level might push SHIB to new highs in the near future.</p>
<h2>Shiba Inu vs Shiba Memu</h2>
<p>While the hype around Shiba Inu has increased in the recent past as the community awaits the launch of Shibarium, a new artificial intelligence (AI) powered meme coin by the name of Shiba Memu is giving Shiba Inu some steep competition.</p>
<p>Shiba Memu combines meme coins&rsquo; concept of building a strong and passionate community around a common idea with artificial intelligence. Shiba Memu incorporates cutting-edge artificial intelligence (AI) technology, promoting itself not just as a crypto-token for entertainment but also as an innovator offering practical utility in the digital sphere and luring Shiba Inu whales.</p>
<p>The Shiba Memu community is expanding, and the coin is swiftly rising to the top of the meme tokens market. Besides its growing community, its innovative approach to meme coins is grabbing people&rsquo;s interest and luring in investors from all over the world as evident in the amount it has managed to rise in its token presale in about a month.</p>
<p>In addition to all the good features, SHMU&rsquo;s price continues to rise throughout the presale. At the time of writing, one SHMU token was going for 0.019450 USDT with the next price rise expected to take place in 6 hours&rsquo; time. Those interested in participating in the Shiba Memu presale can purchase SHMU tokens <a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news">here</a>.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-price-prediction-amid-intensifying-shiba-memu-competition/">Shiba Inu price prediction amid intensifying Shiba Memu competition</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-price-prediction-amid-intensifying-shiba-memu-competition/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin price outlook as Shiba Memu’s presale hits $1.5M</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-price-outlook-as-shiba-memus-presale-hits-1-5m/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 09:59:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-price-outlook-as-shiba-memus-presale-hits-1-5m/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways Bitcoin is still trading around $29k per coin and could dip lower in the near term. Shiba Memu&#8217;s presale has hit $1.5 million after selling more than 52 million SHMU tokens.&#160; Bitcoin has been underperforming in recent weeks, down from the $31k level it achieved last month. The world&#8217;s leading cryptocurrency by market [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-price-outlook-as-shiba-memus-presale-hits-1-5m/">Bitcoin price outlook as Shiba Memu’s presale hits $1.5M</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin is still trading around $29k per coin and could dip lower in the near term.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu&rsquo;s presale has hit $1.5 million after selling more than 52 million SHMU tokens.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin has been underperforming in recent weeks, down from the $31k level it achieved last month. The world&rsquo;s leading cryptocurrency by market cap is struggling around the $29k region, and market experts believe it could dip lower in the near term.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu has continued to set new records with its presale despite the bearish market conditions.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">BItcoin Stays Around $29k</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The cryptocurrency market has been bearish since the start of the month. The prices of most cryptocurrencies are trading in the red zone despite the positive performance recorded earlier this week.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin has lost more than 1% of its value so far this week and is now trading at $29,119 per coin. Ether, Dogecoin, Solana, XRP, and other leading cryptocurrencies are all down by more than 2% so far this week.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Despite the bearish trend,&nbsp;<a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Shiba Memu&rsquo;s</u></a> presale continues to set new records. The team has raised more than $1.5 million so far, with more than 52 million tokens sold.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Shiba Memu?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu is an exciting project in the cryptocurrency space that seeks to combine the powers of blockchain technology and artificial intelligence. With the rise of AI, their applications have become vast globally.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Shiba Memu</u></a> is a project that wants to leverage AI and blockchain to make it easier for people and organisations to create content and roll out marketing campaigns.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">In their whitepaper, the team explained that Shiba Memu could handle the task of numerous marketing agencies. As an AI tool, Shiba Memu is always active and will work 24/7 to find the best work going on in creative advertising, consuming it and generating better content marketing.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The idea to launch as a meme token has to do with the recent popularity of meme projects in the cryptocurrency space. Within the space of two years, the market cap of meme coins grew from practically $0 to $20 billion in 2022.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, what makes Shiba Memu different from other meme token projects is that it has an excellent use case. Shiba Memu can be regarded as a self-sufficient marketing tool powered by AI technology.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu can be able to create marketing strategies, roll out PR schedules, and promote campaigns on relevant forums and social media platforms. At the moment, Shiba Memu is available on the Ethereum and BNBChain blockchains.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Shiba Memu&rsquo;s presale hits $1.5M</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu&rsquo;s presale has been going on excellently despite the bearish trend in the market. The presale has been around for roughly a month now, and the team has raised $1.5 million so far.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Shiba Memu project has sold over 52 million SHMU tokens to raise $1.5 million. The team intends to use the funds to develop some of its products and services.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to their whitepaper, most of the funds generated in the presale would be directed towards developing the Shiba Memu AI technology. By leveraging AI technology, Shiba Memu can provide exciting marketing services to its users.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Shiba Memu platform would also have a robotastic dashboard, allowing users to interact with the AI, provide feedback, make suggestions, and ask questions.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Click here</u></a> to find out more about Shiba Memu&rsquo;s presale event.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Shiba Memu price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Predicting Shiba Memu&rsquo;s price would be impossible at the moment since the SHMU token is still in its presale stage. At the moment, 1 SHMU = 0.017650 USDT.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to the team, SHMU&rsquo;s price increases every day at 6 pm GMT. In a few hours, the token will go for 0.017875 USDT.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">SHMU began trading at $0.011125 when the presale began and will trade at $0.0244 when the presale ends. The SHMU token can be purchased using Ethereum, USDT, BNB and BUSD</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Should you buy Shiba Memu today?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu could be an excellent project for investors to get into. The fact that it is still in its early stage means that it could generate impressive ROI for investors in the medium to long term.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">As a project,&nbsp;<a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Shiba Memu</u></a> is combining AI and blockchain technology, making it an interesting meme token. With the right level of adoption, SHMU&rsquo;s price could rally over the next few months and years.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">In addition to that, a Bull Run by the broader crypto market could see SHMU&rsquo;s price also rally higher. So far, Bitcoin and other major cryptocurrencies are up by over 40% year-to-date.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">A combination of excellent adoption and a Bull Run by the broader crypto market could make SHMU one of the best performers in the market over the coming months.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-price-outlook-as-shiba-memus-presale-hits-1-5m/">Bitcoin price outlook as Shiba Memu’s presale hits $1.5M</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bittrex agrees to settle $24M in SEC lawsuit, doesn&#8217;t accept or decline allegations</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bittrex-agrees-to-settle-24m-in-sec-lawsuit-doesnt-accept-or-decline-allegations/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/bittrex-agrees-to-settle-24m-in-sec-lawsuit-doesnt-accept-or-decline-allegations/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 08:50:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bittrex]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bittrex-agrees-to-settle-24m-in-sec-lawsuit-doesnt-accept-or-decline-allegations/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bittrex was charged in April by the SEC for selling unregistered securities. Besides Bittrex, Coinbase and Binance are also facing similar charges. Although Bittrex agreed to pay the $24 million, it has not mentioned anything to do with accepting or denying the SEC allegations. The US-based cryptocurrency exchange Bittrex&#160;has agreed to settle $24 million with [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bittrex-agrees-to-settle-24m-in-sec-lawsuit-doesnt-accept-or-decline-allegations/">Bittrex agrees to settle $24M in SEC lawsuit, doesn&#8217;t accept or decline allegations</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bittrex was charged in April by the SEC for selling unregistered securities.</li>
<li>Besides Bittrex, Coinbase and Binance are also facing similar charges.</li>
<li>Although Bittrex agreed to pay the $24 million, it has not mentioned anything to do with accepting or denying the SEC allegations.</li>
</ul>
<p>The US-based cryptocurrency exchange <a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/bittrex/">Bittrex&nbsp;</a>has agreed to settle $24 million with the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) in the lawsuit where the SEC accused the exchange of offering unregistered securities to US investors. The SEC has today confirmed the payment in a tweet.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Today we announced that crypto asset trading platform Bittrex Inc. and its co-founder and former CEO, William Shihara, agreed to settle charges that they operated an unregistered national securities exchange, broker, and clearing agency.</p>
<p>&mdash; U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (@SECGov) <a href="https://twitter.com/SECGov/status/1689741781481504768?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 10, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The exchange, however, has not agreed to nor rejected the SEC allegations of offering unregistered securities.</p>
<h2>SEC&rsquo;s allegations against Bittrex</h2>
<p>The US SEC had filed a <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sec-sues-crypto-exchange-bittrex-and-its-ex-ceo/">lawsuit against Bittrex and its former CEO</a>, William Shihara, in April for selling unregistered securities. The SEC also claimed that the exchange&rsquo;s foreign subsidiary, Bittrex Global GmbH, has failed to register as a national securities exchange.</p>
<p>Bittrex is not the only cryptocurrency under siege by the SEC. Binance and Coinbase are also facing similar charges. However, both <a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/binance/">Binance</a> and <a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/coinbase/">Coinbase</a> have vowed to fight till the end. Coinbase, which is a listed public company says that the SEC is contradicted since it knew about the exchanges dealing when the company applied to be listed as a public company.</p>
<p>However, the court is yet to approve the settlement and a Bitterx spokesperson said that they would comment more about the settlement once the court approves the agreement</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bittrex-agrees-to-settle-24m-in-sec-lawsuit-doesnt-accept-or-decline-allegations/">Bittrex agrees to settle $24M in SEC lawsuit, doesn&#8217;t accept or decline allegations</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/bittrex-agrees-to-settle-24m-in-sec-lawsuit-doesnt-accept-or-decline-allegations/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rocket Pool soars after Coinbase’s purchase of RPL tokens</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/rocket-pool-soars-after-coinbases-purchase-of-rpl-tokens/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 19:14:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/rocket-pool-soars-after-coinbases-purchase-of-rpl-tokens/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Rocket Pool price soared nearly 10% after Coinbase Ventures&#8217;s purchase of RPL tokens. The Coinbase venture arm announced the strategic investment on Thursday. RPL rose to highs of $29.25, with over $15 million traded in 24 hours as volume spiked 75% Rocket Pool (RPL) price soared nearly 10% on Thursday to trade at intraday highs [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/rocket-pool-soars-after-coinbases-purchase-of-rpl-tokens/">Rocket Pool soars after Coinbase’s purchase of RPL tokens</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Rocket Pool price soared nearly 10% after Coinbase Ventures&rsquo;s purchase of RPL tokens.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The Coinbase venture arm announced the strategic investment on Thursday.</li>
<li dir="ltr">RPL rose to highs of $29.25, with over $15 million traded in 24 hours as volume spiked 75%</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Rocket Pool (RPL) price soared nearly 10% on Thursday to trade at intraday highs of $29.25 on the crypto exchange <a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/coinbase/">Coinbase</a>. The token&rsquo;s 24-hour trading volume rose 75% to over $15 million.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The price of the decentralised <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/">Ethereum</a> staking protocol was around $28.45 at the time of writing, still up roughly 7% after a slight drawdown following broader crypto reaction to the US inflation data release.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Why did Rocket Pool price go up today?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Rocket Pool is a liquid staking protocol on Ethereum that has increasingly become popular across the ecosystem. Its <a href="https://rocketpool.net/#stake-run-node" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">website</a> shows the protocol has over 779,800 ETH staked and more than 3,110 node operators. According to data from DeFiLlama, only Lido and Coinbase have more TVL than Rocket Pool among liquid staking platforms.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The native RPL tokens are used for incentivizing ecosystem users and for governance purposes. The RPL price surge today came after a major announcement related to the token.</p>
<p dir="ltr">On Thursday, Coinbase Ventures &ndash; the investment arm of US-based crypto exchange Coinbase, announced it had made a strategic investment in Rocket Pool. This was done via a purchase of RPL from the Rocket Pool team, Coinbase Ventures wrote on X (formerly Twitter).</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Exciting news to share: Coinbase Ventures recently made a strategic investment into <a href="https://twitter.com/Rocket_Pool?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@Rocket_Pool</a> by purchasing RPL tokens from the Rocket Pool team.</p>
<p>&mdash; Coinbase Ventures &#128737;&#65039; (@cbventures) <a href="https://twitter.com/cbventures/status/1689639108837249024?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 10, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">The investment follows the Coinbase unit&rsquo;s move to join Rocket Pool&rsquo;s Oracle DAO and the unveiling of Base, the crypto exchange&rsquo;s layer-2 platform. Highlighting the collaboration with Rocket Pool, the Coinbase team said the investment is part of the push to scale Ethereum&rsquo;s infrastructure and bring the next billion users to the ecosystem.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>We know the Rocket Pool team shares this belief and we&rsquo;re delighted to support them via active participation in their Oracle DAO and using ETH from our corporate balance sheet to operate several hundred nodes on the Rocket Pool network</em>,&rdquo; they wrote on X.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/rocket-pool-soars-after-coinbases-purchase-of-rpl-tokens/">Rocket Pool soars after Coinbase’s purchase of RPL tokens</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gemini lists XRP, opens token deposits</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/gemini-lists-xrp-opens-token-deposits/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/gemini-lists-xrp-opens-token-deposits/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 16:41:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gemini]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/gemini-lists-xrp-opens-token-deposits/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>At press time XRP token was trading at $0.6294, down 3.97% in 24 hours. Only XRP deposits were possible at the time of writing. The exchange has promised to open XRP trading soon. Gemini, a cryptocurrency exchange, has announced that it will support the XRP Ledger (XRP) blockchain, adding it to a growing list of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/gemini-lists-xrp-opens-token-deposits/">Gemini lists XRP, opens token deposits</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>At press time XRP token was trading at $0.6294, down 3.97% in 24 hours.</li>
<li>Only XRP deposits were possible at the time of writing.</li>
<li>The exchange has promised to open XRP trading soon.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/gemini/">Gemini</a>, a cryptocurrency exchange, has announced that it will support the XRP Ledger (XRP) blockchain, adding it to a growing list of supported networks. The exchange has opened token deposits with trading expected to start soon be possible.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">We have xciting news!</p>
<p>XRP is now available for deposits on Gemini. Trading support will follow xtra soon. &#129309; <a href="https://t.co/f2EjxewRm0">pic.twitter.com/f2EjxewRm0</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Gemini (@Gemini) <a href="https://twitter.com/Gemini/status/1689634981738401793?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 10, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The news has however done little to stop the bearish trend that has seen the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ripple/">XRP token price</a> drop by over 6% in the past seven days.</p>
<h2>Why Gemini listing is a great plus for XRP</h2>
<p>The XRP token was delisted by all cryptocurrency exchanges when the United States Securities and Exchanges Commission (SEC) filed a lawsuit against Ripple Labs for what it stated as selling a security without the required registration. However, exchanges have been lining up to relist XRP after <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ripple-wins-sec-case-xrp-not-a-security/">Ripple won the case</a>.</p>
<p>Gemini is known for having strict listing requirements, and many cryptocurrencies have struggled to meet them. Therefore, this news is encouraging for the XRP community after the recently won battle against the US SEC although there are speculations that the case could be appealed.</p>
<p>With <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ripple/what-is-ripple/">Ripple (XRP) </a>now available on Gemini Exchange, it is poised to reach a wider audience of investors and traders leading to increased liquidity and trading volume for the cryptocurrency. Besides its widespread acceptance across the crypto space, Ripple has also been working extremely hard to gain acceptance in the traditional financial world.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/gemini-lists-xrp-opens-token-deposits/">Gemini lists XRP, opens token deposits</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/gemini-lists-xrp-opens-token-deposits/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
