<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>CoinGape</title>
	<atom:link href="https://coingape.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coingape.com/</link>
	<description>CoinGape - 24*7 Crypto Updates</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 08:50:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/14183030/cropped-CoinGape_logo-32x32.png</url>
	<title>CoinGape</title>
	<link>https://coingape.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>LUNC News: Terra Classic Validator ClassyCrypto Burns 13 Million LUNC</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/lunc-news-terra-classic-validator-classycrypto-burns-13-million-lunc/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Varinder Singh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 08:36:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terra]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terra Classic]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=132438</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Terra Classic validator Classy&#8217;s Crypto Sphere has burned nearly 13 million LUNC tokens in a single transaction on Wednesday. The total number of LUNC tokens burned by the community has now reached over 36.277 billion. The validator is associated with Terra Classic influencer ClassyCrypto. ClassyCrypto Contributes Terra Classic (LUNC) Burn Effort Terra Classic influencer ClassyCrypto <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/lunc-news-terra-classic-validator-classycrypto-burns-13-million-lunc/" title="LUNC News: Terra Classic Validator ClassyCrypto Burns 13 Million LUNC"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/lunc-news-terra-classic-validator-classycrypto-burns-13-million-lunc/">LUNC News: Terra Classic Validator ClassyCrypto Burns 13 Million LUNC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="667" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/28144248/lunc-terra-classic-chart-background-260nw-2163031359-e1662619569544.webp" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="LUNC News: Terra Classic Validator ClassyCrypto Burns 13 Million LUNC" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p>Terra Classic validator Classy&#8217;s Crypto Sphere has burned nearly 13 million LUNC tokens in a single transaction on Wednesday. The total number of LUNC tokens burned by the community has now reached over 36.277 billion<span id="total" class="badge bg-dark text-end lh-1">. The validator is associated with Terra Classic influencer ClassyCrypto.</span></p>
<h2>ClassyCrypto Contributes Terra Classic (LUNC) Burn Effort</h2>
<p>Terra Classic influencer ClassyCrypto in a <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/ClassyCrypto_/status/1605291349351321623" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">tweet</a> on December 21 announced officially burning 100% of its LUNC validator commission. The burn included Classy&#8217;s Crypto Sphere validator commission of nearly 8 million LUNC tokens, <span class="css-901oao css-16my406 r-poiln3 r-bcqeeo r-qvutc0">ad revenue from </span><span class="r-18u37iz">LUNC</span><span class="css-901oao css-16my406 r-poiln3 r-bcqeeo r-qvutc0"> videos on YouTube, </span>and others.</p>
<p>ClassyCrypto said they have burned almost 13 million LUNC tokens after a 0.2% burn tax. He also shared the transaction details of sending LUNC to the burn address. It shows 12,787,487.63 LUNC tokens sent to the burn address, with 25,575 LUNC tokens as transaction fees.</p>
<blockquote><p><span class="css-901oao css-16my406 r-poiln3 r-bcqeeo r-qvutc0">&#8220;I also burnt all of the ad revenue our </span><span class="r-18u37iz">LUNC</span><span class="css-901oao css-16my406 r-poiln3 r-bcqeeo r-qvutc0"> videos on YouTube have generated this month. Our LUNC focus is burning.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p>Other Terra Classic community members thanked ClassyCrypto for doing was he promised and contributing to the burn effort of the community.</p>
<p>On Tuesday, ClassyCrypto tweeted that Classy&#8217;s Crypto Sphere validator is moving to a 100% commission-burned model. It will be &#8220;moving toward a 100% non-profit, 100% for the community model.&#8221; He revealed the plan to burn billions of LUNC tokens in 2023.</p>
<p>The Terra Classic community has burned over <span id="total" class="badge bg-dark text-end lh-1">36.227 billion LUNC tokens until now. Most of the burn is contributed by crypto exchange <a href="https://coingape.com/breaking-binance-burns-over-6-billion-terra-classic-lunc-tokens/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance with over 20 billion LUNC tokens burned</a>. Also, the community has burned over 11 billion tokens through burn tax.</span></p>
<h2>LUNC Price Falls Amid Market-Wide Selloff</h2>
<p>LUNC price currently trades at $0.00013, down 3% in the last 24 hours. The LUNC price saw massive selling amid <a href="https://coingape.com/why-grayscale-may-be-next-after-ftx-crash/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">selloffs seen in the broader crypto market</a>. The 24-hour low and high are $0.0001295 and $0.0001354, respectively.</p>
<p>Terra Classic core developers <a href="https://coingape.com/terra-classic-lunc-developers-edward-kim-zaradar-leave-terra-rebels/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Edward Kim and Zaradar quit Terra Rebels</a>, putting the future of LUNC in question. However, it was later revealed that Edward Kim and <a href="https://coingape.com/lunc-news-terra-classic-developers-edward-kim-zaradar-to-work-together/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Zaradar will work in a new team</a> and continue contributing to the developments.</p>
<p><strong>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/heres-how-much-your-100-investment-in-terra-classic-will-be-worth-if-lunc-reaches-1-price-prediction/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Here’s How Much Your $100 Investment in Terra Classic Will Be Worth If LUNC Reaches $1</a></strong></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/lunc-news-terra-classic-validator-classycrypto-burns-13-million-lunc/">LUNC News: Terra Classic Validator ClassyCrypto Burns 13 Million LUNC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/28144248/lunc-terra-classic-chart-background-260nw-2163031359-e1662619569544.webp" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Media Organizations To Return Grants By SBF</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/media-organizations-to-return-grants-by-sbf/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Shourya Jha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 08:27:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX CEO]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX collapse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sbf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=132459</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>After the charges were filed by the justice department, the media companies that received money from the former FTX CEO, SBF, or his foundations, are freezing the cash. The business tycoon has been charged with fraud, money laundering, presenting a fake financial picture of his organization, and using customers&#8217; money. He is facing extradition to <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/media-organizations-to-return-grants-by-sbf/" title="Media Organizations To Return Grants By SBF"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/media-organizations-to-return-grants-by-sbf/">Media Organizations To Return Grants By SBF</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/21133016/SBF.jpeg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="SBF Grants" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p>After the charges were filed by the justice department, the media companies that received money from the former FTX CEO, SBF, or his foundations, are freezing the cash.</p>
<p>The business tycoon has been charged with fraud, money laundering, presenting a fake financial picture of his organization, and using customers&#8217; money. He is facing extradition to the U.S.</p>
<h2>The companies reconsidering SBF grants</h2>
<p>ProPublica, a non-profit organization, on Tuesday, announced that they will be returning the 1.6 million USD that they got from SBF’s foundation, Building A Stronger Future. This money was supposed to be used for public health, biosecurity, and coronavirus. It was part of a 3-year grant of 5 million USD. The firm stated that it would find other ways for the fund. On the day, SBF stepped down as the head of FTX and filed for bankruptcy in the U.S. Court, ProPublica suspended all its grants. However, it is still unclear where this money will go.</p>
<p>Vox Media was given 200,000 USD by SBF’s family foundation and the company has also decided to return all the money. The spokeswoman for Vox told that they have already spent 14,000 USD for issues like climate change, fighting global poverty, and other challenges of society, in the month of August, For Vox as well it remains unclear how they will find a new funding partner or return the spent money.</p>
<p><strong>Also read: </strong><a href="https://coingape.com/ftxs-sbf-signs-extradition-paper-will-fly-to-us-on-wednesday/">FTX’s SBF Signs Extradition Paper, Will Fly to US on Wednesday</a></p>
<p>The news organization Intercept is reconsidering the grant of 500,000 USD that was given to them as a part of a 4 million USD grant. “At this time, we are still gathering the information we need to make a principled decision in accordance with our mission and values,” spokesman Rodrigo Brandao said on Tuesday. Earlier the company said that this has left a hole in their funding pocket.</p>
<p>The company Semafor accepted SBF’s grant in the month of May, this year with the hope that they would be able to carry independent journalism. However, they are reconsidering and waiting for the authorities to take a decision.</p>
<p><strong>Also read:</strong> <a href="https://coingape.com/ftx-crypto-traders-news-insurance-exchanges/">Amid FTX Contagion, Crypto Traders Now Face Another Massive Risk</a></p>
<h2>When were these fundings made?</h2>
<p>The funding, investments, and generous gifts made by SBF to newsrooms were part of a larger pattern that included roughly $40 million in political donations this cycle. This was large to Democratic-aligned groups. Before fraud allegations were made public and FTX was largely regarded as one of the more responsible businesses in the cryptocurrency market.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/media-organizations-to-return-grants-by-sbf/">Media Organizations To Return Grants By SBF</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/21133016/SBF.jpeg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Year Ender: Top 3 Metaverse Trends To Watch In 2022</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/year-ender-top-3-metaverse-trends-to-watch-in-2022/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Coingape Staff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 08:25:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Meta]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Metaverse News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=132426</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Metaverse is a collective virtual universe that combines virtual worlds, augmented reality, and the internet. The virtual universe, also known as the metaverse, is a vast digital space that experts believe will eventually replace the internet. People can buy property in this world, make NFT exhibits, sell the digital content they create, or play games <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/year-ender-top-3-metaverse-trends-to-watch-in-2022/" title="Year Ender: Top 3 Metaverse Trends To Watch In 2022"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/year-ender-top-3-metaverse-trends-to-watch-in-2022/">Year Ender: Top 3 Metaverse Trends To Watch In 2022</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/21133950/20221221_133611_0000.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Metaverse Trends" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p><strong><a href="https://coingape.com/blog/what-is-metaverse/">Metaverse</a></strong> is a collective virtual universe that combines virtual worlds, augmented reality, and the internet. The virtual universe, also known as the metaverse, is a vast digital space that experts believe will eventually replace the internet. People can buy property in this world, make <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/nft-non-fungible-token/">NFT</a> exhibits, sell the digital content they create, or play games designed specifically for this virtual world while wearing VR glasses.</p>
<p>The popularity of the Metaverse is increasing, especially with the aid of numerous significant companies, such as Facebook. One of the most divisive investment topics in the future is expected to be <a href="https://coingape.com/blog/year-ender-top-metaverse-projects-to-invest-in-2023-heres-the-list/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">metaverse projects</a>.</p>
<h2>Top 3 Metaverse Trends To Watch In 2022</h2>
<h4>Augmented and Virtual Reality in Gaming</h4>
<p>Virtual gaming relies heavily on 3D technology, AR and VR assemblies, and sonic systems. These technologies have experienced exponential growth as this market has grown, increasing their value and market relevance. The market for AR and VR headsets increased by 60.8% in 2021. However, according to the International Data Corporation&#8217;s (IDC) Quarterly AR/VR Headset Tracker, the APAC region alone shipped 2.19 million units. The gaming industry undergoes new revolutions thanks to these technologies.</p>
<h4>Metaverse Events</h4>
<p>Fortnite concerts Online have drawn in 10.7M users. Live events and advertisements in the Metaverse could cost up to US$800 billion. In 2024, the global market for video game software and hardware could reach $400 billion, with the remaining opportunities coming from live entertainment and social media. Over 75,000 sales for a total of almost US$25 million have been made of the <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/decentraland/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Decentraland</a> pieces of land, NFT tokens, and virtual land plots in the Decentraland Metaverse. Future concerts will be completely altered by this trend.</p>
<h4>The complexity of Metaverse Avatars</h4>
<p>Avatars are likely to become more advanced, according to metaverse trends. Avatars currently come in a wide variety of shapes. This includes photorealistic forms that almost exactly resemble people in the real world as well as 2D avatars.</p>
<p>The advanced, almost photorealistic avatars offered by Meta are well known. Over time, more and more of the company&#8217;s products will support these avatars. Microsoft, meanwhile, focuses on using AI technology to make avatars. However,  that blends in with a business setting thanks to responsive animation. It is simple to create avatars and export them into various metaverse implementations thanks to well-known apps like Zepeto and OSUVOX.</p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/top-5-metaverse-blockchain-projects-to-lookout-for-in-2022-heres-a-list/">Top 5 Metaverse Blockchain Projects To Lookout For In 2022; Here’s A-List</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/year-ender-top-3-metaverse-trends-to-watch-in-2022/">Year Ender: Top 3 Metaverse Trends To Watch In 2022</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/21133950/20221221_133611_0000.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Elon Musk Says Twitter Was Tracking To Spend $5Bln Next Year</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/web-stories/elon-musk-says-twitter-was-tracking-to-spend-5bln-next-year/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jai Pratap]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 08:08:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?post_type=web-story&#038;p=132460</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[		<div class="wp-block-web-stories-embed alignnone">
			<a href="https://coingape.com/web-stories/elon-musk-says-twitter-was-tracking-to-spend-5bln-next-year/">
									<img
						src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/17153518/elon-musk3.jpg"
						width="360"
						height="600"
						alt="Elon Musk Says Twitter Was Tracking To Spend $5Bln Next Year"
																			sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"
												loading="lazy"
						decoding="async"
					/>
								</a>
		</div>
		]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[		<div class="wp-block-web-stories-embed alignnone">
			<a href="https://coingape.com/web-stories/elon-musk-says-twitter-was-tracking-to-spend-5bln-next-year/">
									<img
						src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/17153518/elon-musk3.jpg"
						width="360"
						height="600"
						alt="Elon Musk Says Twitter Was Tracking To Spend $5Bln Next Year"
																			sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"
												loading="lazy"
						decoding="async"
					/>
								</a>
		</div>
		]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/17153518/elon-musk3.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Breaking: RBI Governer Warns Crypto Will Cause Next Financial Crisis</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/web-stories/breaking-rbi-governer-warns-crypto-will-cause-next-financial-crisis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Divya Sinha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 07:38:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?post_type=web-story&#038;p=132432</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[		<div class="wp-block-web-stories-embed alignnone">
			<a href="https://coingape.com/web-stories/breaking-rbi-governer-warns-crypto-will-cause-next-financial-crisis/">
									<img
						src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/21125125/Poster-Image-83.jpg"
						width="360"
						height="600"
						alt="Breaking: RBI Governer Warns Crypto Will Cause Next Financial Crisis"
																			sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"
												loading="lazy"
						decoding="async"
					/>
								</a>
		</div>
		]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[		<div class="wp-block-web-stories-embed alignnone">
			<a href="https://coingape.com/web-stories/breaking-rbi-governer-warns-crypto-will-cause-next-financial-crisis/">
									<img
						src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/21125125/Poster-Image-83.jpg"
						width="360"
						height="600"
						alt="Breaking: RBI Governer Warns Crypto Will Cause Next Financial Crisis"
																			sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"
												loading="lazy"
						decoding="async"
					/>
								</a>
		</div>
		]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/21125125/Poster-Image-83.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Breaking: RBI Chief Reaffirms Crypto Ban, Warns Of Upcoming Financial Crisis</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/crypto-news-rbi-chief-reaffirm-crypto-ban-warn-financial-crisis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ashish Kumar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 07:19:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[India]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[India crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=132404</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto News: The Indian government and watchdogs have been skeptical over the use and implementation of private digital assets in the nation. Authorities have already implied a 30% tax on the capital gains earned from crypto trading in India. However, the Indian Central Bank governor has issued a warning regarding the next financial crisis. RBI <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/crypto-news-rbi-chief-reaffirm-crypto-ban-warn-financial-crisis/" title="Breaking: RBI Chief Reaffirms Crypto Ban, Warns Of Upcoming Financial Crisis"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/crypto-news-rbi-chief-reaffirm-crypto-ban-warn-financial-crisis/">Breaking: RBI Chief Reaffirms Crypto Ban, Warns Of Upcoming Financial Crisis</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/10182211/rbi-gov-min-min-e1653299838129.jpeg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="India crypto" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p><strong>Crypto News:</strong> The Indian government and watchdogs have been skeptical over the use and implementation of private digital assets in the nation. Authorities have already implied a 30% tax on the capital gains earned from crypto trading in India. However, the <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/reserve-bank-of-india/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Indian Central Bank</a> governor has issued a warning regarding the next financial crisis.</p>
<h2>RBI Chief warns of a financial crisis</h2>
<p>In the<a rel='nofollow'  href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5pDiWyN0IWQ&amp;ab_channel=ReserveBankofIndia" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"> BFSI insight Summit</a>, Shaktikanta Das, RBI Governor talked about the recent collapse and developments in the crypto industry. However, he warned of the next possible financial crisis and mentioned that it will come from private digital assets.</p>
<p>Das further asserted that he still holds the same view regarding that digital assets and wants them to be prohibited. Meanwhile, he also added that the crypto has no underlying value. Private Digital assets are major risks for macroeconomic and Financial Stability.</p>
<p>RBI Chief mentioned the recent decline in the crypto market highlighting the major <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://www.binance.com/es/feed/post/126268" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">FTX collapse</a>. These episodes have proved to be a major supporter of the Indian authorities&#8217; stand against crypto. However, Das stated that a change in the value of any product is a function of the market.</p>
<h2>Crypto origin is to bypass the system</h2>
<p>RBI Chief stated that the origin of cryptocurrency is to bypass and break the system. Meanwhile, Das argued that he is yet to hear any credible argument of what public good crypto serves. There is no clarity about it. He marked the crypto as speculative activity and it should be prohibited.</p>
<p>Earlier, Coingape reported that the <a href="https://coingape.com/rbi-india-digital-rupee-launch-cities-cbdc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">RBI launched the pilot phase</a> of Central Bank Digital Currency <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/central-bank-digital-currency-cbdc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">(CBDC)</a>/ Retail digital Rupee on December 1, 2022. The watchdog will be testing the settlement of secondary market transactions.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the Indian government has faced heavy criticism from citizens for imposing high taxes rate on retail crypto trade.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/crypto-news-rbi-chief-reaffirm-crypto-ban-warn-financial-crisis/">Breaking: RBI Chief Reaffirms Crypto Ban, Warns Of Upcoming Financial Crisis</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/10182211/rbi-gov-min-min-e1653299838129.jpeg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Here’s How Much Your $100 Investment in Solana Will Be Worth If SOL Reaches $100</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/heres-how-much-your-100-investment-in-solana-will-be-worth-if-sol-reaches-100/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dhirendra Kumar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 07:17:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOL]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana (SOL)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana Network]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=132425</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>One of the major casualties of the recent FTX-Alameda crash is Solana (SOL). Since Solana Foundation had close relationships with FTX and SBF&#8216;s other companies, it took the fall for the crisis. Solana prices slumped to a record low of $13 (on November 11), days after the news of the FTX liquidity crisis crippled the <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/heres-how-much-your-100-investment-in-solana-will-be-worth-if-sol-reaches-100/" title="Here’s How Much Your $100 Investment in Solana Will Be Worth If SOL Reaches $100"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/heres-how-much-your-100-investment-in-solana-will-be-worth-if-sol-reaches-100/">Here’s How Much Your $100 Investment in Solana Will Be Worth If SOL Reaches $100</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="776" height="515" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/26195208/solanaaaa.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="solanaaaa" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p style="color: #252525">One of the major casualties of the recent <a href="https://coingape.com/blog/is-ftx-crash-an-end-of-crypto-how-this-debacle-unfolded/">FTX-Alameda crash</a> is <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/solana-sol/">Solana (SOL)</a>. Since Solana Foundation had close relationships with FTX and <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/sbf/">SBF</a>&#8216;s other companies, it took the fall for the crisis.</p>
<p style="color: #252525">Solana prices slumped to a record low of $13 (on November 11), days after the news of the FTX liquidity crisis crippled the market. Since then, SOL has struggled to recover.</p>
<p style="color: #252525">The price of Solana hit an all-time high of $260.06 during the bull run of 2021 (on Nov. 6). SOL prices have been declining ever since and are currently trading at $12.08.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-132433" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/21124626/SOLANA.jpg" alt="Solana" width="926" height="642" /></p>
<h4 style="color: #252525">SOL&#8217;s Future Prospects</h4>
<p style="color: #252525">According to several cryptocurrency analysts, it could be challenging for SOL to return to its all-time high ($260) because Solana&#8217;s fully diluted valuation (FDV) of $100 billion was never justified.</p>
<p style="color: #252525">According to <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://cryptopredictions.com/solana/">cryptopredictions.com</a>, SOL can breach the $40 barrier by 2026.</p>
<p style="color: #252525">Given that the value proposition offered by the Solana ecosystem remains more or less the same (despite market sentiments not being in favour of Solana, which is one of the main reasons behind its price crash), it is very likely that SOL will touch the $100 mark in the next bull run.</p>
<p style="color: #252525">Since SOL is in a dip, if you can hold it for the long term, that is, until the next bull run hits and market sentiments are in favour of Solana, you can make decent money from this investment.</p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/here-are-3-altcoins-that-could-boost-your-portfolio-in-ongoing-bear-market-top-best/">Interested In Altcoins? Here Are 3 That Could Boost Your Portfolio In Ongoing Bear Market</a></p>
<h4 style="color: #252525">How Much Money You Would Make if Solana (SOL) Reaches $100?</h4>
<p style="color: #252525">Let&#8217;s say you invest a modest $100 in SOL tokens today. This will get you 8.28 SOL tokens at the current price of $12.08. In the event that SOL hits $100, your $100 investment will become worth $828, giving you an 8x  or 728% return on investment.</p>
<p style="color: #252525">Let&#8217;s assume that you buy $1000 worth of SOL tokens today. At the current rate, you will have approximately 82.78 tokens. Your $1000 investment will be worth $8278 if liquidated at the price of $100. If SOL hits the $100 mark in the next 3 years, you will get an annualised ROI of 102% on your investment.</p>
<p>It is important for anyone considering investing in Solana or any other cryptocurrency to carefully research the asset and understand the risks involved before making any investment decisions.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is not investment advice.</p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/heres-how-much-your-100-investment-in-cardano-will-be-worth-if-ada-reaches-1/">Here’s How Much Your $100 Investment in Cardano Will Be Worth If ADA Reaches $1</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/heres-how-much-your-100-investment-in-solana-will-be-worth-if-sol-reaches-100/">Here’s How Much Your $100 Investment in Solana Will Be Worth If SOL Reaches $100</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/26195208/solanaaaa.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Year Ender : Top 5 Bollywood Celebrities Who Owned NFTs In 2022</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/year-ender-top-5-bollywood-celebrities-who-owned-nfts-in-2022/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Coingape Staff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 06:54:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFT News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFT collection]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFT price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=132399</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NFTs are digital media representations that are securely stored as blockchain-based records and that can be purchased with cryptocurrencies. The original work is worth more than the postcard you purchased from the museum, much like the priceless nature of Matisse or Van Gogh, and the same logic applies to NFTs and their copyrights. Influencers and <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/year-ender-top-5-bollywood-celebrities-who-owned-nfts-in-2022/" title="Year Ender : Top 5 Bollywood Celebrities Who Owned NFTs In 2022"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/year-ender-top-5-bollywood-celebrities-who-owned-nfts-in-2022/">Year Ender : Top 5 Bollywood Celebrities Who Owned NFTs In 2022</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/21120116/20221221_115901_0000.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p><strong><a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/nft-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NFTs</a></strong> are digital media representations that are securely stored as blockchain-based records and that can be purchased with cryptocurrencies. The original work is worth more than the postcard you purchased from the museum, much like the priceless nature of Matisse or Van Gogh, and the same logic applies to NFTs and their copyrights.</p>
<p>Influencers and celebrities aren&#8217;t far behind in the NFT race. The <a href="https://coingape.com/nft/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NFT collections</a> of well-known celebrities like Snoop Dogg, Paris Hilton, Eminem, Bella Hadid, etc. have been released for their fans. The way we think about ownership and digital marketing has changed as a result of NFTs. Unsurprisingly, the NFT industry has been growing faster than ever, and the non-fungible tokens craze hasn&#8217;t spared Indian celebrities.</p>
<h2><strong>Top 5 Bollywood celebrities who owned NFTs in 2022</strong></h2>
<h3><strong>Amitabh Bachchan</strong></h3>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-132411" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/21115021/Amitab-bachchan.jpg" alt="Amitab bachchan NFT" width="752" height="423" /></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The renowned Bollywood actor Amitabh Bachchan joined the NFT movement in November 2021. In addition to autographed Sholay posters and other items related to the movie, he also launched Madhushala, his father&#8217;s celebrated poetry recital. Through an <a href="https://coingape.com/blog/best-nft-marketplaces-where-to-create-and-sell-nfts-in-2022/">NFT marketplace</a>, the collection was auctioned off for Rs. 7.18 crores.</p>
<h3><strong>Salman Khan</strong></h3>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-132412" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/21115116/Salman-khan.jpeg" alt="Salman Khan NFT" width="800" height="448" /></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The Wanted actor debuted his NFT line, which was inspired by his film Dabangg. A total of 200 NFTs, 42 of which were movie scenes, were part of the NFT series he started. Salman Khan announced his NFT series on Twitter on December 25, 2021, and the collection launched on December 30, 2021. Fans could use <a href="https://coingape.com/price/ethereum/">ETH</a> or MATIC tokens to purchase NFTs.</p>
<h3><strong>Rajnikant</strong></h3>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-132413" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/21115200/Rajnikant.jpg" alt="Rajnikant NFT" width="640" height="640" /></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The Thalaiva of the south Indian film industry, Rajinikanth, is also involved with NFTs. He launched his collection in July 2021 in collaboration with the Singapore-based non-fungible token marketplace Diginoor.io. However, his 2007 film Sivaji: The Boss was featured in his non-fungible token collection. On Diginoor.io, customers could use a debit card or a cryptocurrency of their choice to buy their favorite movie moments.</p>
<h3><strong>Sunny Leone</strong></h3>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-132415" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/21115244/Sunny-Leone.jpg" alt="Sunny Leone NFT" width="1200" height="900" /></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Sunny Leone debuts her own non-fungible token collection, Misfitz, making her the first Indian actress to do so. Unusual patterns, boisterous characters, and an eclectic atmosphere characterized the collection. However, in November 2021, the collection, which contained about 9600 non-fungible tokens, quickly ran out of stock.</p>
<h3><strong>Manish Malhotra</strong></h3>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-132256" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/20132601/jpg_20221220_132346_0000.jpg" alt="Manish Malhotra NFT" width="1200" height="800" /></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Manish Malhotra, a famous fashion designer in India, is the first in his profession to enter this market. He unveiled five exclusive sketches and runway GIFs of his clothing in October 2021. However, Lisa Ray, Deepika Padukone, Kareena Kapoor Khan, and Alia Bhatt wore.</p>
<p>However, when the auction went live on the WazirX, it was completely sold out. The Illuminous Showstopper, a famously worn outfit by Kareena Kapoor Khan, generated the highest payment of 3,000 WRX, or roughly USD $4,000. (almost Rs 2.8 lakh).</p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/manish-malhotra-fashion-nft-lehengas-a-glimpse/">Manish Malhotra Fashion NFT Lehengas: A Glimpse</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/year-ender-top-5-bollywood-celebrities-who-owned-nfts-in-2022/">Year Ender : Top 5 Bollywood Celebrities Who Owned NFTs In 2022</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/21120116/20221221_115901_0000.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cryptocurrency Price Today: Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH) Trading In Green; Dogecoin (DOGE), Cardano (ADA) Slips</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/cryptocurrency-price-today-bitcoin-btc-ethereum-eth-trading-in-green-dogecoin-doge-cardano-ada-slips/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Shourya Jha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 06:34:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano (ADA)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin (DOGE)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=132414</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrency Price Today: The crypto price has fallen yet again after seeing a day of optimism. Although Bitcoin and Ethereum are up by a slight percentage, the other major coins plummeted. Bitcoin sees a rise of 0.30% and Ethereum is up by 0.24%. Dogecoin has dipped by 2.94% in the last 24 hours. Cardano is <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/cryptocurrency-price-today-bitcoin-btc-ethereum-eth-trading-in-green-dogecoin-doge-cardano-ada-slips/" title="Cryptocurrency Price Today: Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH) Trading In Green; Dogecoin (DOGE), Cardano (ADA) Slips"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/cryptocurrency-price-today-bitcoin-btc-ethereum-eth-trading-in-green-dogecoin-doge-cardano-ada-slips/">Cryptocurrency Price Today: Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH) Trading In Green; Dogecoin (DOGE), Cardano (ADA) Slips</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="675" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/21115549/cryptocurrency-bitcoin_10-sixteen_nine8.jpeg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Cryptocurrency Price Today" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p><strong>Cryptocurrency Price Today:</strong> The crypto price has fallen yet again after seeing a day of optimism. Although Bitcoin and Ethereum are up by a slight percentage, the other major coins plummeted.</p>
<p><a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> sees a rise of 0.30% and Ethereum is up by 0.24%.</p>
<p>Dogecoin has dipped by 2.94% in the last 24 hours. <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/cardano/">Cardano</a> is down by 2.20%.</p>
<p>XDC Network is the highest gainer in the last 24 hours with a jump of 6.64%. Chain is the biggest loser with a drop of 3.03%.</p>
<p>The global crypto <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/market-capitalization/">market cap</a> is down by 0.03% and stands at 809.91 billion USD. The total crypto market volume is down by 11.33% in the last 24 hours and stands at 32.49 billion USD.</p>
<h2>The top 4 most impacted crypto for today are:</h2>
<h3>Cronos (CRO) is up by 1.58%</h3>
<p>With a jump of 1.58%, Cronos stands as one of the biggest gainers in the last 24 hours. It has a market cap of 1.197 billion USD. Trading volume is seeing a rise of 24.28%. Each CRO token is costing 0.05715 USD. <img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-132419" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/21115619/CRO_1D_graph_coinmarketcap.jpeg" alt="Cryptocurrency Price Today: CRO" width="1858" height="800" />Source: coinmarketcap</p>
<h3>Bitcoin (BTC) is up by 0.30%</h3>
<p>With a slight rise of 0.30% in the last 24 hours, the market cap for crypto Bitcoin is 324.396 billion USD. Trading volume is up by 0.29%. Bitcoin’s dominance has seen an increase of 0.13% over the past day. Each BTC token is selling for 16,847.37 USD. <img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-132420" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/21115654/BTC_1D_graph_coinmarketcap-5.jpeg" alt="Cryptocurrency Price Today: BTC" width="1858" height="800" />Source: coinmarketcap</p>
<h3>Dogecoin (DOGE) is down by 2.94%</h3>
<p><a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/meme-cryptocurrency/">Meme crypto</a>, Dogecoin is seeing a drop of 2.94% in the last 24 hours and the market cap stands at 9.380 billion USD. Each DOGE token is at 0.0726 USD. Trading volume is seeing a downfall of 33.26% compared to the last day. <img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-132421" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/21115738/DOGE_1D_graph_coinmarketcap-10.jpeg" alt="Cryptocurrency Price Today: DOGE" width="1858" height="800" />Source: coinmarketcap</p>
<h3>Cardano (ADA) is down by 2.20%</h3>
<p>The market cap of Cardano stands at 11.828 billion USD, a plunge of 2.20% in the last 24 hours. Trading volume is also down by 23.75%. Each ADA token is currently for 0.2512 USD. <img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-132422" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/21115809/ADA_1D_graph_coinmarketcap-3.jpeg" alt="ADA" width="1858" height="800" />Source: coinmarketcap</p>
<h2>Conclusion</h2>
<p><strong>Cryptocurrency Price Today:</strong> The market is still <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/bear-market-2/">bearish</a> as there is no high jump and nit for even two consecutive days the charts are completely green. We are very near to the end of this year but the <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/bull-market/">bullish</a> momentum seems really far.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/cryptocurrency-price-today-bitcoin-btc-ethereum-eth-trading-in-green-dogecoin-doge-cardano-ada-slips/">Cryptocurrency Price Today: Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH) Trading In Green; Dogecoin (DOGE), Cardano (ADA) Slips</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/21115549/cryptocurrency-bitcoin_10-sixteen_nine8.jpeg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Elon Musk Reveals His Future Role At Twitter; Addresses Twitter Poll</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/web-stories/elon-musk-reveals-his-future-role-at-twitter/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jai Pratap]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 06:12:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?post_type=web-story&#038;p=132403</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[		<div class="wp-block-web-stories-embed alignnone">
			<a href="https://coingape.com/web-stories/elon-musk-reveals-his-future-role-at-twitter/">
									<img
						src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/19173610/Elon-Musk-Tesla-Twitter.jpg"
						width="360"
						height="600"
						alt="Elon Musk Reveals His Future Role At Twitter; Addresses Twitter Poll"
																			sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"
												loading="lazy"
						decoding="async"
					/>
								</a>
		</div>
		]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[		<div class="wp-block-web-stories-embed alignnone">
			<a href="https://coingape.com/web-stories/elon-musk-reveals-his-future-role-at-twitter/">
									<img
						src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/19173610/Elon-Musk-Tesla-Twitter.jpg"
						width="360"
						height="600"
						alt="Elon Musk Reveals His Future Role At Twitter; Addresses Twitter Poll"
																			sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"
												loading="lazy"
						decoding="async"
					/>
								</a>
		</div>
		]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/19173610/Elon-Musk-Tesla-Twitter.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto News Live Updates Dec 21: Bitcoin, Ethereum Price Looks Clueless; BTC Dominance Surges</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/crypto-news-live-updates-dec-21-bitcoin-ethereum-price-looks-clueless/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ashish Kumar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 05:44:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Live News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency market]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=132391</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto News Today Live Updates December and Latest News: (21 December 2022) The global cryptocurrency industry looked clueless on Wednesday morning. The Cumulative digital asset market cap is marginally down over the past day. It now stands at $808.5 billion. The 24 hour trading volume has also dropped by 11% to stand at $32.5 billion. <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/crypto-news-live-updates-dec-21-bitcoin-ethereum-price-looks-clueless/" title="Crypto News Live Updates Dec 21: Bitcoin, Ethereum Price Looks Clueless; BTC Dominance Surges"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/crypto-news-live-updates-dec-21-bitcoin-ethereum-price-looks-clueless/">Crypto News Live Updates Dec 21: Bitcoin, Ethereum Price Looks Clueless; BTC Dominance Surges</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/19165114/bitcoin3.jpeg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Crypto News" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p><strong>Crypto News Today Live Updates December and Latest News: (21 December 2022)</strong> The global cryptocurrency industry looked clueless on Wednesday morning. The Cumulative digital asset market cap is marginally down over the past day. It now stands at $808.5 billion. The 24 hour trading volume has also dropped by 11% to stand at $32.5 billion.</p>
<h1>Crypto News Today Live Updates</h1>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/crypto-news-live-updates-dec-21-bitcoin-ethereum-price-looks-clueless/">Crypto News Live Updates Dec 21: Bitcoin, Ethereum Price Looks Clueless; BTC Dominance Surges</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/19165114/bitcoin3.jpeg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Here’s How Much Your $100 Investment in Filecoin Will Be Worth If FIL Reaches $10</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/heres-how-much-your-100-investment-in-filecoin-will-be-worth-if-fil-reaches-10/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Coingape Staff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 05:43:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FIL]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[filecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Filecoin Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=132389</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Filecoin (FIL) is a cryptocurrency that powers the Filecoin network, a decentralized peer-to-peer file storage network that aims to allow anyone to store, retrieve, and host digital information. FIL tokens are used as payment for these services as well as a financial incentive to guarantee that files are consistently stored over time. As a proof-of-work <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/heres-how-much-your-100-investment-in-filecoin-will-be-worth-if-fil-reaches-10/" title="Here’s How Much Your $100 Investment in Filecoin Will Be Worth If FIL Reaches $10"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/heres-how-much-your-100-investment-in-filecoin-will-be-worth-if-fil-reaches-10/">Here’s How Much Your $100 Investment in Filecoin Will Be Worth If FIL Reaches $10</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="630" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/21111032/Filecoin.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Filecoin" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p>Filecoin (FIL) is a <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/cryptocurrency-5/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">cryptocurrency</a> that powers the Filecoin network, a decentralized peer-to-peer file storage network that aims to allow anyone to store, retrieve, and host digital information. FIL tokens are used as payment for these services as well as a financial incentive to guarantee that files are consistently stored over time.</p>
<p>As a<a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/proof-of-work-pow/"> proof-of-work</a> token, FIL allows the Filecoin community to mine and receive additional coins as payment. Additionally, FIL can be used on the Filecoin network, where users can pay miners to store or retrieve their data. In the event that there are no or insufficient proofs, the token may also be used as collateral.</p>
<h3><b>Filecoin (FIL) Price Analysis</b></h3>
<p>Filecoin’s price today is $2.93, with a market capitalization of $1B and a 24-hour trading volume down by 4.62%. Now it stands at $127 million. At the same time, the circulating supply is approximately 344,966,605 FIL.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-132396" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/21105612/FIL_1D_graph_coinmarketcap1.jpg" alt="Source: coinmarketcap" width="1161" height="500" /></p>
<h6>Source: Coinmarketcap</h6>
<p>Despite the negative market trends, the technical analysis of the Filecoin price shows a significant surge fueled by FIL growth. The Filecoin (FIL) price has increased significantly in comparison to counterparts such as Stellar and <a href="https://coingape.com/price/ethereum/">Ethereum</a>.</p>
<p>Also Read:<a href="https://coingape.com/heres-how-much-your-100-investment-in-chainlink-will-be-worth-if-link-reaches-10/"> Here’s How Much Your $100 Investment In Chainlink Will Be Worth If LINK Reaches $10</a></p>
<h2><b>How Much Money Would You Make If FIL Reaches $10?</b></h2>
<p>According to <strong><a rel='nofollow'  href="https://cryptopredictions.com/filecoin/" rel="nofollow">Cryptopredictions.com</a></strong>, FIL can go as high as $10.9 by December 2025. Let’s assume that you invest a modest $100 in Filecoin today.</p>
<figure id="attachment_132397" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-132397" style="width: 1491px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-132397" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/21105732/Screenshot-2022-12-21-at-10-17-09-Filecoin-FIL-Price-Prediction-2023-2024-2026.png" alt="Filecoin Prediction chart" width="1491" height="847" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-132397" class="wp-caption-text">Filecoin Prediction chart</figcaption></figure>
<p>According to today’s price, which is $2.92, you will have approximately 34.26 FIL. If Filecoin’s price hits $10 in the next few years, your $100 will become approximately $342.6. Let’s say you bought $100 worth of FIL coins today. With the current rate, you will have approximately 34.26 coins. However, you can potentially make $342 when it reaches the $100 mark.</p>
<p><b>Disclaimer</b>: This is not investment advice. Please do your due diligence before investing in any asset.</p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/heres-how-much-your-100-investment-in-polkadot-will-be-worth-if-dot-reaches-10/">Here’s How Much Your $100 Investment in Polkadot Will Be Worth If DOT Reaches $10</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/heres-how-much-your-100-investment-in-filecoin-will-be-worth-if-fil-reaches-10/">Here’s How Much Your $100 Investment in Filecoin Will Be Worth If FIL Reaches $10</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/21111032/Filecoin.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Breaking: Crypto Twitter Reacts To Core Scientific Filing For Chapter 11 Bankruptcy</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/breaking-core-scientific-filing-for-chapter-11-bankruptcy-in-texas-today/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Varinder Singh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 05:40:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[core scientific]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency mining]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=132390</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Core Scientific is filing for Chapter 11 bankruptcy protection in Texas on Wednesday, December 21. It is one of the largest publicly listed crypto mining companies in the U.S. Core Scientific has decided to file for bankruptcy due to falling crypto prices and rising energy prices that deteriorated its finances. Despite the $72 million in <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/breaking-core-scientific-filing-for-chapter-11-bankruptcy-in-texas-today/" title="Breaking: Crypto Twitter Reacts To Core Scientific Filing For Chapter 11 Bankruptcy"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/breaking-core-scientific-filing-for-chapter-11-bankruptcy-in-texas-today/">Breaking: Crypto Twitter Reacts To Core Scientific Filing For Chapter 11 Bankruptcy</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="799" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/23021650/1200x-1-2.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="core scientific" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p>Core Scientific is filing for Chapter 11 bankruptcy protection in Texas on Wednesday, December 21. It is one of the largest publicly listed crypto mining companies in the U.S. Core Scientific has decided to file for bankruptcy due to falling crypto prices and rising energy prices that deteriorated its finances.</p>
<p>Despite the $72 million in financing from its lender B. Riley last week to avoid bankruptcy, the crypto miner was unable to work efficiently and will work on restructuring, <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/KenzieSigalos/status/1605420482005704705" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reported</a> CNBC. Core Scientific plans to keep mining until it restructures its balance sheet.</p>
<p>Core Scientific’s market cap dropped to $78 million on Tuesday, down from a $4.3 billion valuation in July 2021 when it went public. The CORZ stock price has fallen more than 98% in the last year. On Tuesday, the stock price ended at $0.21, up 3.07%.</p>
<p>According to a person familiar with the company’s situation, the company is still generating positive cash flow. However, cash is insufficient to repay the <a href="https://coingape.com/breaking-bitcoin-mining-giant-core-scientific-could-file-for-bankruptcy-soon/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">financing debt owed on mining equipment</a> it was leasing. Core Scientific will not liquidate and operate normally until reaching a deal with senior security noteholders, which hold the majority of the company’s debt.</p>
<h2>Crypto Twitter Reactions To Core Scientific Bankruptcy</h2>
<p>Crypto influencers took to Twitter to report Core Scientific&#8217;s bankruptcy filing. Many crypto miners are facing financial constraints amid the <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/bear-market-2/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">bear market</a>.</p>
<p>Crypto researcher Dylan Leclair reported that the firm owns approximately 5% of the global hash rate. He also shared the situation of listed crypto miners with many having stock prices down over 90% in 2022.</p>
<figure id="attachment_132410" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-132410" style="width: 710px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img decoding="async" class=" wp-image-132410" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/21114843/Crypto-Miners-Performance.jpg" alt="Crypto Miners Performance" width="710" height="378" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-132410" class="wp-caption-text">Crypto Miners Performance</figcaption></figure>
<p>Crypto investor and board member at Iris Energy Mike Alfred said Core Scientific had told him that the company would have 13 EH by July of this year when he first looked at the company in the summer of 2021.</p>
<p>Many people showed concerns over the future of bitcoin mining as several crypto miners such as Argo Blockchain and Iris Energy are facing bankruptcy risks.</p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/bitcoin-price-prediction-crypto-on-chain-analysts-dismiss-santa-claus-rally/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin Price Prediction for 2023</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/breaking-core-scientific-filing-for-chapter-11-bankruptcy-in-texas-today/">Breaking: Crypto Twitter Reacts To Core Scientific Filing For Chapter 11 Bankruptcy</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/23021650/1200x-1-2.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Mining Giant Core Scientific Files for Chapter 11 Bankruptcy</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/bitcoin-mining-giant-core-scientific-files-for-chapter-11-bankruptcy/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 05:40:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Miner]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[core scientific]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=132393</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Core Scientific, the world&#8217;s largest publicly-traded crypto miner based out of the United States is ultimately filing for Chapter 11 bankruptcy in Texas on Wednesday morning. Core Scientific joins the list of other crypto miners who have succumbed to the crash in the crypto space and the soaring energy prices. A month ago, the Bitcoin <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/bitcoin-mining-giant-core-scientific-files-for-chapter-11-bankruptcy/" title="Bitcoin Mining Giant Core Scientific Files for Chapter 11 Bankruptcy"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/bitcoin-mining-giant-core-scientific-files-for-chapter-11-bankruptcy/">Bitcoin Mining Giant Core Scientific Files for Chapter 11 Bankruptcy</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="710" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/02094328/Webp.net-resizeimage-min.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Over 10K Bitcoin (BTC) Moved To Crypto Exchange, Are Miners Selling?" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" srcset="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/02094328/Webp.net-resizeimage-min.jpg 1200w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/02094328/Webp.net-resizeimage-min-300x178.jpg 300w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/02094328/Webp.net-resizeimage-min-768x454.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /><p>Core Scientific, the world&#8217;s largest publicly-traded crypto miner based out of the United States is ultimately filing for Chapter 11 bankruptcy in Texas on Wednesday morning.</p>
<p>Core Scientific joins the list of other crypto miners who have succumbed to the crash in the crypto space and the soaring energy prices. A month ago, the Bitcoin miner had already hinted about <a href="https://coingape.com/breaking-bitcoin-mining-giant-core-scientific-could-file-for-bankruptcy-soon/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">extreme pain in its operations</a> and cash crunch owing to the market conditions.</p>
<p>Core Scientific was mining some proof-of-work digital assets such as Bitcoin. As we know, this requires high-end machinery and hardware while also consuming massive electricity in the process. Over the last year, the price of Core Scientific (NASDAQ: CORZ) stock has tanked by 99% losing more than $4 billion in valuations.</p>
<p>Last year in July 2021, the Bitcoin miner had gone for a public listing via a special purpose acquisition vehicle or SPAC. Although the company still generates a positive cash flow, it&#8217;s not enough to repay the financial debt on equipment, <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/12/20/bitcoin-miner-core-scientific-filing-for-bankruptcy-will-keep-mining.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">said sources</a> familiar with the matter.</p>
<h3>Core Scientific&#8217;s Further Action Plan</h3>
<p>The sources also added that core Scientific is not willing to liquidate, however, it would continue to operate normally while reaching a deal with senior security noteholders, who hold a majority of the company&#8217;s debt.</p>
<p>In their filing earlier in October, Core Scientific said that holders of their common stock might suffer a total loss on their investment. However, the Bitcoin miner&#8217;s deal with its convertible note holders is such that if the market conditions for Bitcoin improve, common equity holders might not get totally wiped out.</p>
<p>Core Scientific has operations currently in North Dakota, North Carolina, Georgia, and Kentucky. It is also one of the largest providers of blockchain infrastructure and hosting.</p>
<p>Core Scientific is not the only Bitcoin miner to face bankruptcy. Compute North, the hosting infrastructure for crypto mining also filed for bankruptcy in September.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/bitcoin-mining-giant-core-scientific-files-for-chapter-11-bankruptcy/">Bitcoin Mining Giant Core Scientific Files for Chapter 11 Bankruptcy</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/02094328/Webp.net-resizeimage-min.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Microsoft Looking To Buy This Streaming Giant</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/web-stories/microsoft-looking-to-buy-this-streaming-giant/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Divya Sinha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 05:21:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?post_type=web-story&#038;p=132392</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[		<div class="wp-block-web-stories-embed alignnone">
			<a href="https://coingape.com/web-stories/microsoft-looking-to-buy-this-streaming-giant/">
									<img
						src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/21104154/Poster-Image-82.jpg"
						width="360"
						height="600"
						alt="Microsoft Looking To Buy This Streaming Giant"
																			sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"
												loading="lazy"
						decoding="async"
					/>
								</a>
		</div>
		]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[		<div class="wp-block-web-stories-embed alignnone">
			<a href="https://coingape.com/web-stories/microsoft-looking-to-buy-this-streaming-giant/">
									<img
						src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/21104154/Poster-Image-82.jpg"
						width="360"
						height="600"
						alt="Microsoft Looking To Buy This Streaming Giant"
																			sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"
												loading="lazy"
						decoding="async"
					/>
								</a>
		</div>
		]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/21104154/Poster-Image-82.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>FTX&#8217;s SBF Signs Extradition Paper, Will Fly to US on Wednesday</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/ftxs-sbf-signs-extradition-paper-will-fly-to-us-on-wednesday/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 04:36:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX collapse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=132388</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Disgraced FTX founder Sam Bankman-Fried has finally decided to drop his fight against extradition to the United States. As per the latest report from ABC News, SBF who&#8217;s currently in the Fox Hill jail of The Bahamas has agreed to his extradition to the US on multiple charges. Reports suggest that SBF has signed his <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/ftxs-sbf-signs-extradition-paper-will-fly-to-us-on-wednesday/" title="FTX&#8217;s SBF Signs Extradition Paper, Will Fly to US on Wednesday"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/ftxs-sbf-signs-extradition-paper-will-fly-to-us-on-wednesday/">FTX&#8217;s SBF Signs Extradition Paper, Will Fly to US on Wednesday</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/19134101/SBF-jail.jpeg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Sam Bankman-Fried extradited United States" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p>Disgraced FTX founder Sam Bankman-Fried has finally decided to drop his fight against extradition to the United States. As per the latest report from ABC News, SBF who&#8217;s currently in the Fox Hill jail of The Bahamas has agreed to his extradition to the US on multiple charges.</p>
<p>Reports suggest that SBF has signed his extradition paper and a hearing for the same will happen on Wednesday in Nassau. The <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2022-12-21/ftx-sam-bankman-fried-signs-extradition-papers/101796332" target="_blank" rel="noopener">development</a> has been confirmed by Bahamas Acting Commissioner of Corrections Doan Cleare.</p>
<p>After signing his surrender documents on Tuesday, the Bahamas Commissioner said that SBF will sign a separate set of papers and finalize his waiver of rights to fight extradition.</p>
<p>Interestingly, the Federal authorities are looking to fly back SBF to the U.S. soon after Wednesday&#8217;s hearing. The Bloomberg <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/sam-bankman-fried-to-fly-to-us-wednesday-escorted-by-fbi-agents-1.1861932" target="_blank" rel="noopener">report</a> notes that the disgraced FTX founder will be accompanied to the US by FBI agents in a non-commercial aircraft. Another source familiar with the matter said that the plane will leave from a private airport in The Bahamas.</p>
<h3>Not A Good Christmas for SBF</h3>
<p>Sam Bankman Fried has been facing severe charges over the misuse of customers&#8217; funds at FTX which led to a dramatic collapse of a $32 billion company. Some previous <a href="https://coingape.com/how-much-jail-time-sbf-is-looking-at-if-convicted/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reports</a> suggest that SBF might face 115 years of prison which is equivalent to life imprisonment.</p>
<p>After getting earlier this month, the Bahamian court also denied bail to SBF last week. Since then, he&#8217;s been placed in one of the most notorious jail facilities of the island nation i.e. Fox Hill.</p>
<p>On Wednesday, the Bahamian authorities will escort Sam Bankman-Fried from the prison to the court. Although initially hesitant, SBF has agreed to the extradition to the U.S. This change in attitude might be partly due to the expectation that SBF could get bail in the US. So far, it isn&#8217;t clear where SBF is planning to land on Wednesday.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/ftxs-sbf-signs-extradition-paper-will-fly-to-us-on-wednesday/">FTX&#8217;s SBF Signs Extradition Paper, Will Fly to US on Wednesday</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/19134101/SBF-jail.jpeg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance In Trouble Over Media Practices</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/web-stories/binance-in-trouble-over-media-practices/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Divya Sinha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 04:24:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?post_type=web-story&#038;p=132380</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[		<div class="wp-block-web-stories-embed alignnone">
			<a href="https://coingape.com/web-stories/binance-in-trouble-over-media-practices/">
									<img
						src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/12151205/Poster-Image-73.jpg"
						width="360"
						height="600"
						alt="Binance In Trouble Over Media Practices"
																			sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"
												loading="lazy"
						decoding="async"
					/>
								</a>
		</div>
		]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[		<div class="wp-block-web-stories-embed alignnone">
			<a href="https://coingape.com/web-stories/binance-in-trouble-over-media-practices/">
									<img
						src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/12151205/Poster-Image-73.jpg"
						width="360"
						height="600"
						alt="Binance In Trouble Over Media Practices"
																			sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"
												loading="lazy"
						decoding="async"
					/>
								</a>
		</div>
		]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/12151205/Poster-Image-73.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Uniswap Allows Users to Buy Crypto Using Cards and Bank Transfers</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/uniswap-allows-users-to-buy-crypto-using-cards-and-bank-transfers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 04:04:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uniswap DEX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[uniswap price analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=132379</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the latest development, decentralized exchange Uniswap (UNI) announced that they are now allowing users to buy digital assets on the Uniswap Web App using a debit card, credit card, or bank transfer. This facility is now available to 160 countries across the world. Currently, Uniswap supports Ethereum, Polygon, Optimism, and Arbitrum. It means over <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/uniswap-allows-users-to-buy-crypto-using-cards-and-bank-transfers/" title="Uniswap Allows Users to Buy Crypto Using Cards and Bank Transfers"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/uniswap-allows-users-to-buy-crypto-using-cards-and-bank-transfers/">Uniswap Allows Users to Buy Crypto Using Cards and Bank Transfers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="700" height="495" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/23170352/uniswap.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="UNI Price Analysis: Uniswap Token Still Trapped In A Descending Broadening Wedge" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p>In the latest development, decentralized exchange Uniswap (UNI) announced that they are now allowing users to buy digital assets on the Uniswap Web App using a debit card, credit card, or bank transfer. This facility is now available to 160 countries across the world.</p>
<p>Currently, Uniswap supports Ethereum, Polygon, Optimism, and Arbitrum. It means over the DEX, users can purchase their respective cryptocurrencies such as DAI, ETH, MATIC, USDC, USDT, WBTC and WETH.</p>
<p>Amid the recent collapse of crypto exchange FTX, trust from <a href="https://coingape.com/uniswap-unveils-new-feature-to-rival-crypto-exchanges/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">centralized exchanges</a> has dropped as many investors are moving their crypto into self-custody. As a result, the demand and trading volumes on decentralized exchanges (DEXs) have also shot up.</p>
<p>DEX&#8217;s offers greater user protection since they have self-custodial wallets, and are permissionless and immutable protocols. But when compared to centralized exchanges, DEXs don&#8217;t offer a very sound onboarding experience. With the latest move, the Uniswap DEX is planning to solve this exactly.</p>
<h3>Uniswap Partners With MoonPay</h3>
<p>In partnership with MoonPay, Uniswap will now allow users to transact in DeFi via the Uniswap Web App and buy crypto using any card and bank transfers. Users just need to connect their wallet to the Uniswap Web app and can buy crypto instantly. The DEX platform <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://uniswap.org/blog/web-fiat-on-ramp" target="_blank" rel="noopener">noted</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We&#8217;re bringing you the best fiat on-ramp experience &#8211; no spread fees on USDC, the lowest processing fees in the market, and instant access!&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Uniswap has also made it clear that they would not collect any financial information of their users such as credit card, debit card, and bank information. Besides, they also don&#8217;t collect any personally identifiable information for their users. Uniswap has also placed minimum and maximum caps for the purchase of different crypto and stablecoins.</p>
<p>After the purchase, users can see their digital assets in their wallets within minutes. So far, the off-ramp facility of moving crypto to a bank account isn&#8217;t available. But the DEX added that they are working on it.</p>
<p>Also, users cannot purchase NFTs directly using cards or bank accounts. They first need to purchase ETH and buy NFTs through it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/uniswap-allows-users-to-buy-crypto-using-cards-and-bank-transfers/">Uniswap Allows Users to Buy Crypto Using Cards and Bank Transfers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/23170352/uniswap.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Elon Musk Reveals Real Intention Behind Finding New Twitter CEO</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/elon-musk-reveals-real-intention-behind-finding-new-twitter-ceo/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Anvesh Reddy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 02:35:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elon Musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[twitter]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=132377</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Elon Musk Twitter News: After conducting a surprise poll on whether he should continue as Twitter CEO, Elon Musk revealed his real intention behind finding a new face to lead the company. Earlier, reports suggested that the billionaire was already in the hunt for his replacement. It may be recalled that Musk had fired former <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/elon-musk-reveals-real-intention-behind-finding-new-twitter-ceo/" title="Elon Musk Reveals Real Intention Behind Finding New Twitter CEO"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/elon-musk-reveals-real-intention-behind-finding-new-twitter-ceo/">Elon Musk Reveals Real Intention Behind Finding New Twitter CEO</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="900" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/10154208/Elon-Musk-Twitter1.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Elon-Musk-Twitter1" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p><strong>Elon Musk Twitter News</strong>: After conducting a surprise poll on whether he should continue as Twitter CEO, Elon Musk revealed his real intention behind finding a new face to lead the company. Earlier, reports suggested that the billionaire was already in the hunt for his replacement. It may be recalled that Musk had fired former CEO Parag Aggarwal among others as his first official act since taking over as the company head. It remains to be seen how his favorite cryptocurrency <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/dogecoin/">Dogecoin (DOGE)</a> will perform if someone replaces Musk.</p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/solana-sol-price-biggest-hurdle-for-recovery-amid-ftx-effect/">Solana (SOL) Price: Biggest Hurdle For Recovery Amid FTX Effect</a></p>
<h2>Software And Servers</h2>
<p>In a reaction to the Twitter poll on his leadership, Musk said he will still have some oversight on the company even if someone takes charge as new CEO. In line with his aggressive approach in leading the social media company, Musk said he would like to lead the software and servers teams. This is regardless of if he continues to be the CEO or not. Also, it will be interesting to see how soon would Musk be able to find his replacement. It may be recalled that he said his role as Twitter CEO would be temporary.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;I will resign as CEO as soon as I find someone foolish enough to take the job! After that, I will just run the software &amp; servers teams.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/bitcoin-price-prediction-crypto-on-chain-analysts-dismiss-santa-claus-rally/?utm_source=priceanalysisbar">Bitcoin Price Prediction: Crypto And On-Chain Analysts Dismiss Santa Claus Rally</a></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Should I step down as head of Twitter? I will abide by the results of this poll.</p>
<p>&mdash; Elon Musk (@elonmusk) <a href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1604617643973124097?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 18, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The discussion around new Twitter CEO came after Musk said he would abide by the poll results on whether he should step down as CEO. Meanwhile, the DOGE price is currently trading at a monthly low range. As of writing, DOGE price stands at $0.07382, up 0.33% in the last 24 hours, according to price tracking platform CoinMarketCap.</p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/how-much-1000-worth-ethereum-classic-etc-hits-100/">Here’s How Much Your $1000 Investment In Ethereum Classic Will Be Worth If ETC Hits $100</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/elon-musk-reveals-real-intention-behind-finding-new-twitter-ceo/">Elon Musk Reveals Real Intention Behind Finding New Twitter CEO</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/10154208/Elon-Musk-Twitter1.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Solana Price Prediction: RSI Divergence Hints Upcoming Recovery In SOL</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/markets/solana-price-prediction-rsi-divergence-hints-upcoming-recovery-in-sol/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brian Bollinger]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 21:06:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana (SOL)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[solana price prediction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?post_type=markets&#038;p=132376</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Solana price prediction: a bearish breakdown of the month-long range setup puts Solana&#8217;s price in a longer correction. Thus, losing the $12.75 support may intensify the ongoing selling pressure and push the prices back to the last swing low of $11.35. But will this support replenish the bullish momentum or encourage prolonged downfall? Key points <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/markets/solana-price-prediction-rsi-divergence-hints-upcoming-recovery-in-sol/" title="Solana Price Prediction: RSI Divergence Hints Upcoming Recovery In SOL"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/markets/solana-price-prediction-rsi-divergence-hints-upcoming-recovery-in-sol/">Solana Price Prediction: RSI Divergence Hints Upcoming Recovery In SOL</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/01174358/solana.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="solana SOL price" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Solana price prediction: a bearish breakdown of the month-long range setup puts <a href="https://coingape.com/solana-sol-price-biggest-hurdle-for-recovery-amid-ftx-effect/">Solana&#8217;s price</a> in a longer correction. Thus, losing the $12.75 support may intensify the ongoing selling pressure and push the prices back to the last swing low of $11.35. But will this support replenish the bullish momentum or encourage prolonged downfall?</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Key points</span></h2>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The $12.75 breakdown sets Solana coin price for a 7.5% downfall.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">An evident bullish divergence in the daily-RSI slope indicates a potential bullish reversal from $11.35</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The 24-hour trading volume in the Solana coin is $192 Million, indicating a 0.3% gain.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><img decoding="async" src="https://s3.tradingview.com/snapshots/d/DaNmqCfB.png" alt="TradingView Chart" />Source-</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Tradingview</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">For nearly a month, the Solana price wobbled in a fixed range from $15 to $12.75. This long consolidation was supposed to bolster the coin price for higher recovery once it breached the overhead resistance of $15.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">However, the recent sell-off in the crypto market triggered by <a href="https://coingape.com/massive-bnb-selling-amid-binance-fud-where-is-it-heading/">FUD surrounding Binance</a> and hearsay for US Fed to tighten interest rate hikes caused significant outflow in Solana coin. As a result, the coin price ended the range setup in the seller&#8217;s favor with a breakdown of $12.75 support.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On December 16th, the Solana price breached the $12.75 support with increasing volume, indicating the sellers are aiming to visit lower levels. However, with the ongoing uncertainty in the crypto market, this altcoin is stuck in a retest phase.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Today, the SOL price trades at $12.25 with an intraday gain of 2.35% Furthermore, the higher price rejection candle attached to this daily candle indicates the intense selling pressure from above.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If this selling pressure persists, the <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/altcoins/">altcoin</a> should eventually drop 7.5% lower to pierce the $11.35 support. </span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Conversely, if the recent selling pressure was solely due to panic selling in the market, the Solana price should rebound from the $11.35 mark.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Technical indicator</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><strong>Relative strength index:</strong> Despite the sideways price action, the higher high movement in the daily <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/rsi-relative-strength-index/">RSI slope</a> indicates growth in underlying bullishness and a higher possibility for price reversal.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><strong>EMA&#8217;s:</strong> the large gap between the crucial EMAs(20, 50, 100, and 200) indicates the overall trend is bearish.</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">Resistance level- $12.7 and $15</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">Support levels- $11.35 and $10</span></li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/markets/solana-price-prediction-rsi-divergence-hints-upcoming-recovery-in-sol/">Solana Price Prediction: RSI Divergence Hints Upcoming Recovery In SOL</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/01174358/solana.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
