<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 11:29:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>CME Group and CF Benchmarks Floats BTC and ETH Reference Rates in APAC</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/cme-group-btc-eth-reference-rates-apac/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/cme-group-btc-eth-reference-rates-apac/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 11:23:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cf benchmarks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cme group]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reference Rates]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267237</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cme-group-btc-eth-reference-rates-apac/">CME Group and CF Benchmarks Floats BTC and ETH Reference Rates in APAC</a></p>
<p>This strategic collaboration aims to provide market participants with accurate and timely pricing information, fostering greater transparency and confidence in the evolving digital asset space.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cme-group-btc-eth-reference-rates-apac/">CME Group and CF Benchmarks Floats BTC and ETH Reference Rates in APAC</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cme-group-btc-eth-reference-rates-apac/">CME Group and CF Benchmarks Floats BTC and ETH Reference Rates in APAC</a></p>
<p>The world’s leading derivatives platform, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/cme-group/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CME Group Inc</a> (NASDAQ: CME) has partnered with CF Benchmarks to launch <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> (BTC) and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a> (ETH) reference rates, cementing crypto&#8217; growing significance in the Asia-Pacific (APAC) region.</p>
<p>CME Group stated in a <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/cme-group-and-cf-benchmarks-to-launch-apac-reference-rates-for-bitcoin-and-ether-on-september-11-301903064.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">press release</a> that the two new reference rates, CME CF Bitcoin Reference Rate APAC and the CME CF Ether-Dollar Reference Rate APAC will go live on September 11. These reference rates will offer a once-a-day snapshot of the US dollar price of Bitcoin and Ethereum, respectively, at 4 p.m. Hong Kong/Singapore time.</p>
<p>Giovanni Vicioso, Global Head of Crypto Products at CME Group, emphasized the importance of these reference rates in the context of the crypto ecosystem. “These new reference rates are designed to meet the ever-evolving needs of global participants in the growing digital asset space,” Vicioso stated.</p>
<p>It is worth mentioning that CME Group and CF Benchmarks have earlier solidified their partnership by <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cme-group-cf-benchmarks-metaverse-reference/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">introducing</a> three new Metaverse reference rates.</p>
<p>The three Metaverse reference rates introduced features Axie Infinity (AXS), Chiliz (CHZ), and Decentraland (MANA). These tokens are key players in the metaverse landscape, each contributing unique aspects to the virtual realm. With their inclusion in reference rates, CME Group and CF Benchmarks acknowledge the increasing influence and potential of the metaverse space.</p>
<h2>CME Group in APAC Market: Core Benefits</h2>
<p>The introduction of Bitcoin and Ethereum reference rates in the APAC region is a significant step forward for the cryptocurrency ecosystem. APAC has been at the forefront of crypto adoption and innovation, with countries like Japan, South Korea, and Singapore leading the way.</p>
<p>Vicioso pointed out that 37% of crypto volume at CME Group year-to-year has been traded during non-US hours, with a noteworthy 11% of trades originating from the APAC region. Therefore, providing accurate reference rates tailored to this region&#8217;s trading hours and market dynamics is essential for attracting institutional investors and further legitimizing the crypto market.</p>
<p>One of the primary advantages of these reference rates is the potential for improved risk management and hedging strategies. Institutional investors, who frequently require precise and trustworthy data, will be able to make more informed judgments concerning their Bitcoin exposure.</p>
<p>Additionally, these rates are anticipated to significantly impact the risk management methods of institutions entering the crypto space, improving their ability to mitigate possible market swings. This partnership couldn&#8217;t come at a better time as the crypto market is expanding rapidly, with popular usage increasing as complemented by growing institutional interest.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the introduction of these reference rates contributes to the ongoing process of legitimizing the crypto market within the regulatory framework. As governments and financial watchdogs increasingly engage with the crypto space, these reference rates can be seen as a responsible step towards meeting regulatory expectations.</p>
<div id="gtx-trans" style="position: absolute; left: 140px; top: 56.7778px;">
<div class="gtx-trans-icon"></div>
</div>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-crypto-futures-approval-big-deal/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cme-group-btc-eth-reference-rates-apac/">CME Group and CF Benchmarks Floats BTC and ETH Reference Rates in APAC</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/cme-group-btc-eth-reference-rates-apac/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase’s Crypto Futures Approval Seen as a Big Deal </title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-crypto-futures-approval-big-deal/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-crypto-futures-approval-big-deal/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 11:03:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[a16z]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cftc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[us sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267235</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-crypto-futures-approval-big-deal/">Coinbase&#8217;s Crypto Futures Approval Seen as a Big Deal </a></p>
<p>For many in the crypto industry, this approval signifies a notable regulatory achievement for both the company and the broader crypto landscape due to the ongoing legal battle between the exchange and the US SEC. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-crypto-futures-approval-big-deal/">Coinbase&#8217;s Crypto Futures Approval Seen as a Big Deal </a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-crypto-futures-approval-big-deal/">Coinbase&#8217;s Crypto Futures Approval Seen as a Big Deal </a></p>
<p>On August 16, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase</a>, one of the world&#8217;s largest crypto exchanges, received regulatory approval to become the first native crypto company to operate as a Futures Commission Merchant (FCM). In June, the SEC accused Coinbase of evading the registration of its product offerings and thereby violating the country&#8217;s federal securities laws.</p>
<p>During the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-regulatory-approval-crypto-futures-trading/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">announcement</a> yesterday, Coinbase said the FCM registration was approved by the National Futures Association (NFA), a self-regulatory organization under the Commodities Futures Trading Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/cftc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CFTC</a>) purview. After two years of deliberation, the NFA accepted the application, granting Coinbase permission to provide crypto futures contracts to US residents.</p>
<h2>A Big Deal for Coinbase</h2>
<p>With the registration granted to Coinbase, crypto community members have pointed out the discrepancy between CFTC&#8217;s stance on crypto and the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>&#8216;s reservations about its regulatory status.</p>
<p>Avichal Garg, the founder of investment management firm Electric Capital, said on X, formerly <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/twitter/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Twitter</a>, that getting FCM approved by the commodities regulator takes years of work. Adding that if he were the judge handling the SEC vs Coinbase case, he would question the regulator why it claimed that Coinbase was unwilling to register its product offerings within its jurisdiction.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="474" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Getting an FCM via the <a href="https://twitter.com/CFTC?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@CFTC</a> is a big deal. It takes years of work.</p>
<p>If I were a judge I&#39;d wonder why somehow <a href="https://twitter.com/coinbase?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@coinbase</a> manages to register with the <a href="https://twitter.com/CFTC?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@CFTC</a> yet the <a href="https://twitter.com/SECGov?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@SECGov</a> claims that Coinbase is unwilling to do the hard work to register. <a href="https://t.co/axDHt8ya3F">https://t.co/axDHt8ya3F</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Avichal &#8211; Electric ϟ Capital (@avichal) <a href="https://twitter.com/avichal/status/1691850120785264868?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 16, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Brian Quintenz, former CFTC Commissioner and now policy head at crypto investment firm <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/a16z/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">a16z</a>, also commented on the approval, emphasizing the value of an open and constructive dialogue between regulators and the technology sector. This approach, he believes, is conducive to nurturing innovation while safeguarding consumer interests.</p>
<p>&#8220;Coinbase has consistently demonstrated its dedication to regulatory compliance, and here is yet another strong example. Customers and innovation can both win when a regulator is open to having a constructive dialogue around new technology,&#8221; Quintenz said in the <a href="https://twitter.com/BrianQuintenz/status/1691912210430501306?s=20" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">tweet</a>.</p>
<h2>Coinbase to Compete with Non-Crypto Companies</h2>
<p>The FCM approval has placed Coinbase in direct competition with non-crypto firms such as Chicago Mercantile Exchange (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/cme-group/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CME</a>) and the Chicago Board Options Exchange (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/cboe/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CBOE</a>).</p>
<p>Both firms already offer US customers Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a>) and Ethereum (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ETH</a>) futures contracts.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Coinbase said in its announcement yesterday that the derivatives market contributes up to 75% of the total trading volumes. Earlier this year, CoinGecko disclosed that the global directives market stands at $3 trillion.</p>
<p>Market experts believe the approval will significantly increase Coinbase&#8217;s total addressable market.</p>
<p>&#8220;Since the global crypto derivatives market can be three to four times larger than the spot, this approval increases Coinbase&#8217;s total addressable market,&#8221; said Dan Dolev, an analyst at Mizuho Securities, as <a href="https://www.barrons.com/articles/bitcoin-ethereum-price-crypto-markets-today-fa72efc0" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reported</a> by Barron&#8217;s.</p>
<p>In terms of its stock performance, Coinbase&#8217;s stock (COIN) remained relatively unaffected by the news, experiencing a 1.56% drop on the same day. However, the bigger picture reveals a positive trajectory, with Coinbase shares having surged by 130% so far this year.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/analyst-tips-bitcoin-surge-past-150k/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-crypto-futures-approval-big-deal/">Coinbase&#8217;s Crypto Futures Approval Seen as a Big Deal </a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-crypto-futures-approval-big-deal/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Analyst Tips Bitcoin to Surge Past $150K on One Condition</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/analyst-tips-bitcoin-surge-past-150k/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/analyst-tips-bitcoin-surge-past-150k/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 10:40:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price predicition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blackrock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tom lee]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267225</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/analyst-tips-bitcoin-surge-past-150k/">Analyst Tips Bitcoin to Surge Past $150K on One Condition</a></p>
<p>The approval of spot Bitcoin ETFs is expected to tip Bitcoin’s supply-demand dynamics in the direction of a significant price surge.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/analyst-tips-bitcoin-surge-past-150k/">Analyst Tips Bitcoin to Surge Past $150K on One Condition</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/analyst-tips-bitcoin-surge-past-150k/">Analyst Tips Bitcoin to Surge Past $150K on One Condition</a></p>
<p>The price of Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a>) may have slipped below $29,000, but that hasn&#8217;t deterred renowned analyst Tom Lee, from making a wildly bullish price prediction. Lee, who is Fundstrat’s managing partner and head of research, remains adamant that BTC is destined to attain greatness in the coming months.</p>
<p>In a Wednesday <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ir8jYyrBY5s" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">interview</a> with CNBC, Lee insists that he sees BTC surging by over 400% from its current levels. He added that the BTC price could easily surpass the $150,000 mark by 2024 end. But that is only if the pending US spot-Bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) are approved.</p>
<p>According to Lee, approval of those applications would inadvertently tip Bitcoin’s supply-demand dynamics in the direction of a significant price surge. He said partly:</p>
<blockquote><p>“If the spot Bitcoin (ETF) gets approved, I think the demand will be greater than the daily supply of Bitcoin, so the clearing price [&#8230;] is over $150,000, it could even be like $180,000.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Lee also noted that his prediction specifically has to do with the approval of a United States-approved spot Bitcoin ETF. And that would be understandable, given that the U.S. currently accounts for about 97.7% of the global trading volume for crypto-based ETFs. More so, there are already spot Bitcoin ETFs in Europe.</p>
<h2>It&#8217;s a Win-Win Situation for Bitcoin, Says Tom Lee</h2>
<p>Away from the Bitcoin surge that is dependent on the approval of spot Bitcoin ETFs, there is another reason for the asset to surge in price. Lee expects another push to happen from Bitcoin’s <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/next-bitcoin-halving-800000th-block/">next halving event</a>, which is expected to take place in April 2024.</p>
<p>According to Lee, this halving will cause supply to drop, therefore, making it necessary for the clearing price to increase. He, however, was quick to add that the price surge from halving will not bring the BTC price to six figures.</p>
<p>Presently, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-2023-high-blackrock-etf/">BlackRock</a> and several other Wall Street giants have submitted applications for a Bitcoin spot ETF with the SEC. But they might not know their fate until 2024. That is considering that the regulator has a total of 240 days to decide after it starts reviewing an application.</p>
<div id="gtx-trans" style="position: absolute; left: 37px; top: 328.333px;">
<div class="gtx-trans-icon"></div>
</div>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shib-plunge-shibarium-tokens-bridging-problems/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/analyst-tips-bitcoin-surge-past-150k/">Analyst Tips Bitcoin to Surge Past $150K on One Condition</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/analyst-tips-bitcoin-surge-past-150k/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shib Ecosystem Tokens Plunge Up to 22% Following Reports of a Problem with Bridging Shibarium Tokens</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/shib-plunge-shibarium-tokens-bridging-problems/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/shib-plunge-shibarium-tokens-bridging-problems/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 10:31:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bone]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[doge killer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[leash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[shib]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[shiba inu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[shibarium]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267220</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shib-plunge-shibarium-tokens-bridging-problems/">Shib Ecosystem Tokens Plunge Up to 22% Following Reports of a Problem with Bridging Shibarium Tokens</a></p>
<p>SHIB, BONE, and LEASH tokens have all crashed over the past 24 hours because of a problem that allegedly resulted in lost Shibarium tokens.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shib-plunge-shibarium-tokens-bridging-problems/">Shib Ecosystem Tokens Plunge Up to 22% Following Reports of a Problem with Bridging Shibarium Tokens</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shib-plunge-shibarium-tokens-bridging-problems/">Shib Ecosystem Tokens Plunge Up to 22% Following Reports of a Problem with Bridging Shibarium Tokens</a></p>
<p>Tokens in the Shib universe have plunged to different levels following a problem with bridging on the recently-launched Shibarium. Members of the community holding these tokens were left disappointed as many expected the Shibarium launch to bring good tidings and spike prices.</p>
<p>At the time of this writing, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/shiba-inu/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SHIB</a> has fallen over 8% in the last 24 hours, with Shibarium governance token BONE losing more than 17%, according to data from CoinMarketCap. The ecosystem’s Doge Killer (LEASH) token had the worst plunge, at 22% over the last day.</p>
<p>The reactions follow a reported issue after a few screenshots suggested a problem with the Shibarium network launch. One such screenshot reportedly showed a Telegram message sent by lead developer Shytoshi Kusama admitting a problem. Kusama was allegedly saying that the team had lost ETH bridged to the network.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="474" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">In case yall were wondering how Shibarium is going <a href="https://t.co/S5vjTxoMDk">pic.twitter.com/S5vjTxoMDk</a></p>
<p>&mdash; ʎppɐꓷ ɯooɹɥS (@shroom_daddy) <a href="https://twitter.com/shroom_daddy/status/1691953231289528683?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 16, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>In a <a href="https://twitter.com/zachxbt/status/1691960557727846777" target="_blank" rel="noopener">tweet</a>, blockchain enthusiast ZachXBT said Shib had more than 954 ETH in the bridge contract, worth more than $1.7 million ETH at the time. In another tweet, ZachXBT said the BONE lost was worth over $762k. The blockchain enthusiast said that although they may not be able to confirm the loss, the “RPC is dead.” ZachXBT said the Shibarium launch was “sloppy” and described the block explorer as “awful.” The RPC runs key blockchain software.</p>
<p>In another <a href="https://twitter.com/shroom_daddy/status/1691953830252917234" target="_blank" rel="noopener">post</a> part of the first screenshot revealing Shytoshi’s admittance, the user added that they couldn’t receive the BONE sent to them because the block scanner was faulty. The account also <a href="https://twitter.com/shroom_daddy/status/1691953687994757292" target="_blank" rel="noopener">confirmed</a> the faulty RPC, stating that the block height is “changing up and down” when it should “only go up as block number only increases.”</p>
<p>At press time, Shibarium’s RPC <a href="https://www.shibrpc.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">website</a> is not working. Also, Shibarium has not officially commented on the problem.</p>
<h2>Shibarium Problem Shows Layer 2 Network Has Launch Issues</h2>
<p>According to Shibarium blockchain <a href="https://www.shibariumscan.io/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">data</a>, there have been no activities for 4 hours as of writing time. In addition to these problems, a CoinDesk <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/08/17/shib-plunges-9-on-apparent-shibarium-bridge-issues/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">report</a> revealed that users on a Discord community forum have been unable to send messages since reports began to spread.</p>
<p>The problematic Shibarium launch is disappointing considering that members of the Shib community have anticipated the network for a while. Last month, Coinspeaker <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shibarium-layer-2-blockchain-august/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a> that Shytoshi hinted at an August launch during a Toronto conference. As part of the announcement, Shytoshi also hinted at a decentralized autonomous organization (DAO) called DoggyDAO. The DAO will help to fund Shibarium projects under the control and direction of SHIB holders.</p>
<p>In March, Shiba Inu launched a testnet called PuppyNet for anyone to develop and launch decentralized applications (dApps). PuppyNet also functioned as a decentralized governance module and a crypto payments processor for businesses interested in cryptocurrency transactions. By June, the total number of PuppyNet transactions had scaled 20 million across at least 17.7 million addresses. The testnet also had an average block time of 5 seconds.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitgo-100-million-fundraise/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shib-plunge-shibarium-tokens-bridging-problems/">Shib Ecosystem Tokens Plunge Up to 22% Following Reports of a Problem with Bridging Shibarium Tokens</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/shib-plunge-shibarium-tokens-bridging-problems/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>BitGo Successfully Completes $100 Million Fundraise Despite Rough Market Conditions</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitgo-100-million-fundraise/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitgo-100-million-fundraise/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 09:50:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitgo]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mt gox]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267218</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitgo-100-million-fundraise/">BitGo Successfully Completes $100 Million Fundraise Despite Rough Market Conditions</a></p>
<p>Despite challenging market conditions, BitGo secures massive funding as it successfully navigates through the uncertainties in crypto regulations. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitgo-100-million-fundraise/">BitGo Successfully Completes $100 Million Fundraise Despite Rough Market Conditions</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitgo-100-million-fundraise/">BitGo Successfully Completes $100 Million Fundraise Despite Rough Market Conditions</a></p>
<p>On Wednesday, August 16, crypto custodian <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/bitgo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BitGo</a> announced its plans to raise $100 million at a staggering valuation of $1.75 billion. The company said that it will use these funds for strategic acquisitions as well as to expand its secure and regulated wallet, custody, and other solutions.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="474" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">BitGo has secured $100M Series C funding.</p>
<p>Trust is not given, it is earned. We believe in delivering it to our clients and the industry. Being a custodial and infrastructure leader is an undertaking, one we have consistently provided for over a decade.</p>
<p>This funding will allow… <a href="https://t.co/TlPO7722Ha">pic.twitter.com/TlPO7722Ha</a></p>
<p>&mdash; BitGo (@BitGo) <a href="https://twitter.com/BitGo/status/1691802052849201443?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 16, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>From January 2023 onwards, BitGo has experienced a 60% surge in newly registered clients and a 20% growth in Assets Under Custody (AUC). Besides, it has also registered a remarkable 200% rise in fiat custody, and an extraordinary 40-fold expansion in staked assets. Notably, BitGo also handles custody services for <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a> creditors&#8217; funds under the leadership of John Ray III. Previously, it was serving as the distributor for <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/mt-gox/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Mt. Gox</a> creditors as well.</p>
<p>Mike Belshe, the Chief Executive Officer, recognized that the current market is undoubtedly challenging. However, he pointed out that the company&#8217;s emphasis on obtaining licenses and adhering to regulations has distinguished it in the midst of a legal environment characterized by uncertainties regarding the classification of digital assets as securities. &#8220;Regulatory safety is a top concern for everyone at the moment,&#8221; Belshe stated. Speaking further on the matter, Belshe <a href="https://www.prweb.com/releases/bitgo-secures-100m-series-c-funding-at-1-75b-valuation-301901731.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">added</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Not only are we seeing growing demand for regulated custody solutions in the US, but we&#8217;re also seeing the demand on a global scale. We are very pleased to announce our <span class="xn-money">$100M</span> Series C for the purpose of meeting this growing need and to provide institutions, brands, coin foundations, and others with secure and seamless participation in the digital asset ecosystem.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Latest Funding from New Investors</h2>
<p>The company, headquartered in Palo Alto, California, secured the funding exclusively from fresh investors, as <a href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/bitgo-bucks-crypto-downturn-to-raise-funding-at-1-75-billion-valuation-1.1959756" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">stated</a> by Belshe. While he refrained from revealing the participants in the round, he did mention that they hailed from both the US and Asia, and some were not from the cryptocurrency sector. Among BitGo&#8217;s earlier investors were <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/goldman-sachs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Goldman Sachs Group Inc.</a>, DRW Holdings, and Galaxy Digital Ventures.</p>
<p>The startup&#8217;s current valuation significantly exceeds its value in 2021, a period during which <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/galaxy-digital/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Galaxy Digital Holdings</a> intended to acquire the company for $1.2 billion. However, this deal was eventually abandoned.</p>
<p>BitGo&#8217;s previous fundraising was in 2017, during which it obtained a Series B funding of $42.5 million. This round was spearheaded by Valor Equity Partners and saw involvement from individuals like former PayPal COO David Sacks, former Remarq CEO Bill Lee, and the trading firm DRW. Notably, the list of earlier investors in the crypto custodian encompasses names like Goldman Sachs, Craft Ventures, and Pantera Capital.</p>
<p>Recently, crypto custodian BitGo <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitgo-cancels-acquisition-prime-trust/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">decided</a> to cancel the acquisition of Prime Trust, just after a few days of its preliminary agreement.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-iphone-15-production-outside-china/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitgo-100-million-fundraise/">BitGo Successfully Completes $100 Million Fundraise Despite Rough Market Conditions</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitgo-100-million-fundraise/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Apple Begins iPhone 15 Production Outside China</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-iphone-15-production-outside-china/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-iphone-15-production-outside-china/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 09:01:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[china]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[foxconn]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[iphone 15]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[united states]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267189</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-iphone-15-production-outside-china/">Apple Begins iPhone 15 Production Outside China</a></p>
<p>Apple CEO Tim Cook is claiming that India simply offers a “huge opportunity”, so, the firm has been ramping up iPhone production in the region.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-iphone-15-production-outside-china/">Apple Begins iPhone 15 Production Outside China</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-iphone-15-production-outside-china/">Apple Begins iPhone 15 Production Outside China</a></p>
<p>It appears that <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/apple-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Apple Inc</a> (NASDAQ: AAPL) may be attempting to diversify the production of its iPhones from its manufacturing base in China. This follows after a recent Bloomberg <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-08-16/apple-supplier-foxconn-begins-iphone-15-production-in-india">report</a> revealed that Apple supplier Foxconn is set to begin producing the company&#8217;s next-generation iPhone 15 in India. Interestingly, this will be the first time that a new iPhone will be made outside China before an official unveiling.</p>
<p>According to the report, the new phones will be manufactured at a Foxconn plant in Sriperumbudur, Tamil Nadu. And more importantly, they will be ready for delivery only a few weeks after they begin shipping from China-based factories.</p>
<h2>Apple Says There&#8217;s Huge Opportunity in India</h2>
<p>It might be worth noting that Apple has been aiming to make some key changes to its supply chain. That is even as tensions continue to grow between the United States and China. While the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/joe-biden/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Biden</a>-led administration has been sceptical about allowing the flow of key technologies and investments into China, China <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/intel-drops-tower-acquisition-us-china-tension/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">has also placed</a> regulatory pressure on many US entities.</p>
<p>However, Apple CEO <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/tim-cook/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tim Cook</a> is claiming that India simply offers a “huge opportunity”. And in line with this potential, the firm has been ramping up iPhone production in the region. According to Bloomberg, Apple assembled over $7 billion worth of devices in India in the last fiscal year.</p>
<p>It is also worth mentioning that, before the iPhone 14 was released, iPhone production in India lagged behind that of China by up to six to nine months. However, that difference in the production timeline is now set to significantly change.</p>
<p>For what it&#8217;s worth though, the scale of ‌iPhone 15‌ production in India will certainly depend on the availability of imported components and the ramp-up of production lines. But Pegatron and Wistron factories will soon be joining Foxconn to assemble the ‌iPhone 15‌.</p>
<p>Apple will unveil the iPhone 15 at its annual event in September. The model is expected to have major camera updates and an improved processor.</p>
<div id="gtx-trans" style="position: absolute; left: 996px; top: 224.778px;">
<div class="gtx-trans-icon"></div>
</div>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ledger-partners-paypal-crypto-purchases/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-iphone-15-production-outside-china/">Apple Begins iPhone 15 Production Outside China</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-iphone-15-production-outside-china/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ledger Partners with PayPal to Allow Users Make Crypto Purchases</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ledger-partners-paypal-crypto-purchases/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ledger-partners-paypal-crypto-purchases/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 08:49:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin cash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ledger]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[paypal]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267172</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ledger-partners-paypal-crypto-purchases/">Ledger Partners with PayPal to Allow Users Make Crypto Purchases</a></p>
<p>In an announcement on August 16, the company said it had integrated its Ledger Live app with PayPal.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ledger-partners-paypal-crypto-purchases/">Ledger Partners with PayPal to Allow Users Make Crypto Purchases</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ledger-partners-paypal-crypto-purchases/">Ledger Partners with PayPal to Allow Users Make Crypto Purchases</a></p>
<p>Crypto security firm <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ledger/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ledger</a>, known for its hardware wallets, has joined forces with <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">PayPal,</a> an online payment platform based in the United States, to provide on-ramp payment solutions to users. Through this integration, customers can purchase cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a>), Ethereum (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ETH</a>), Litecoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/litecoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">LTC</a>), and Bitcoin cash (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin-cash/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BCH</a>) directly through the Ledger Live app using their verified PayPal accounts.</p>
<p>Ledger Live, known for its user-friendly interface, presents a smooth experience for both novices and seasoned crypto enthusiasts. The platform, which has about 1.5 million active users, allows customers to buy crypto using fiat currencies.</p>
<p>According to the <a href="https://www.ledger.com/ledger-and-paypal-team-up-to-simplify-entry-into-the-world-of-cryptocurrency" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announcement</a>, users who have previously transacted cryptocurrencies through PayPal will not have to undergo additional verification while using the app. However, new users must create a PayPal account and undergo compulsory know-your-customer (KYC) verification before using the services.</p>
<h2>PayPal Joins Ledger List of Partners for On-ramp Solutions</h2>
<p>Through this collaboration with Ledger, PayPal has joined the list of payment partners for on-ramp solutions. Before the partnership, Ledger users had alternatives such as MoonPay, Wyre, and Coinify to choose from for on-ramp solutions.</p>
<p>However, the new integration with PayPal has a twist as it eliminates the need for intermediary steps. Once a purchase is made using PayPal, the acquired digital currencies are promptly transferred to the user&#8217;s Ledger wallet, reducing customer wait times.</p>
<p>&#8220;We&#8217;re combining the uncompromising security of Ledger with PayPal&#8217;s leadership in protected payments technology to help facilitate a seamless platform for user crypto transactions. Ledger is committed to simplifying the world of crypto, and PayPal is committed to making the movement of money as simple, reliable, and affordable as possible,&#8221; said Pascal Gauthier, Chairman and CEO of Ledger.</p>
<h2>PayPal Integration Only Available to US Customers</h2>
<p>Ledger said in the announcement that the PayPal integration is currently limited to US users only. However, the usage is subject to applicable state laws. Over time, the company plans to make the service available in other jurisdictions.</p>
<p>Additionally, both Ledger and PayPal plan to roll out more features to the on-ramp solution in the coming months. The collaboration between PayPal and Ledger comes as the payment firm faces competition from new ventures introduced by tech giants like <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/google/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Google</a> and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/apple-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Apple</a>. Due to the increased competition in the payment market, the company has expanded its involvement with crypto to establish a stronger presence.</p>
<p>The firm recently <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-paypal-usd-stablecoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">launched</a> its native stablecoin pegged 1:1 to the value of the US dollar. The stablecoin dubbed PYUSD is based on the Ethereum network.</p>
<p>Shortly after the launch of the stablecoin the company also <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-cryptocurrencies-hub-pyusd/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">introduced</a> its Cryptocurrency Hub, where users can interact with different digital assets directly on the platform.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/valkyrie-ethereum-strategy-etf-sec/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ledger-partners-paypal-crypto-purchases/">Ledger Partners with PayPal to Allow Users Make Crypto Purchases</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ledger-partners-paypal-crypto-purchases/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Valkyrie Funds File for New Ethereum Strategy ETF with the US SEC</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/valkyrie-ethereum-strategy-etf-sec/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/valkyrie-ethereum-strategy-etf-sec/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 08:41:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[valkyrie]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267182</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/valkyrie-ethereum-strategy-etf-sec/">Valkyrie Funds File for New Ethereum Strategy ETF with the US SEC</a></p>
<p>Along with investing in Ether Futures, the Valkyrie Ethereum Strategy ETF will invest in other instruments like cash, cash-like instruments, or high-quality securities.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/valkyrie-ethereum-strategy-etf-sec/">Valkyrie Funds File for New Ethereum Strategy ETF with the US SEC</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/valkyrie-ethereum-strategy-etf-sec/">Valkyrie Funds File for New Ethereum Strategy ETF with the US SEC</a></p>
<p>On Wednesday, August 16, Valkyrie Funds filed with the US Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) for a new fund that would specifically invest in Ether Futures. With this, Valkyrie joins the likes of Volatility Shares, Bitwise, and others, who have already submitted their applications for the Ethereum futures ETF.</p>
<p>Dubbed the Valkyrie Ethereum Strategy ETF, the fund aims to offer investors capital appreciation by investing in the ETF contracts on Ether as well as other &#8220;collateral investments&#8221;. This includes high-quality securities such as commercial papers and Treasury bonds. Note that, unlike the spot ETF contracts, the fund won&#8217;t directly invest in Ethereum (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ETH</a>). In its filing on Wednesday, August 16, Valkyrie <a href="https://www.sec.gov/Archives/edgar/data/1877493/000138713123009893/valkyrie-485apos_081523.htm" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">noted</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Ether and ether futures are a relatively new asset class. They are subject to unique and substantial risks, and historically, have been subject to significant price volatility. The value of an investment in the Fund could decline significantly and without warning, including to zero. You should be prepared to lose your entire investment.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The filed document highlights that Ether&#8217;s classification could vary as either a currency or digital commodity, depending on its role in specific transactions. While some retailers accept it as payment, its use for commercial and retail transactions remains limited. Additionally, Ether can serve as a store of value, despite experiencing notable price volatility at times.</p>
<p>Along with investing in Ether Futures, the Valkyrie Ethereum Strategy ETF will invest in other instruments like cash, cash-like instruments, or high-quality securities. Valkyrie&#8217;s application notes that the ETF investment in Ether futures contracts shall be limited to 8,000 contracts per month. This will be in compliance with position limits offered by the Chicago Mercantile Exchange (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/cme-group/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CME</a>).</p>
<h2>Race for Ethereum Futures ETFs</h2>
<p>After a strong wave of spot bitcoin ETF applications, the race for Ethereum futures ETFs is also catching up fast. Applications for Ethereum futures ETFs have been submitted by Bitwise, VanEck, ProShares, Grayscale, Volatility Shares, and Roundhill, totaling six companies.</p>
<p>Volatility Shares has been leading the race and was the first to apply on July 28. Volatility Shares has recently stated that its Ethereum Strategy ETF will be live on October 12. The ETF by Volatility Shares centers around trading cash-settled Ethereum futures contracts on the CBOE.</p>
<p>Some market analysts believe that the US SEC is more likely to approve the Ethereum futures ETF than the spot Bitcoin ETF. Bloomberg ETF analysts James Seyffart and Eric Balchunas have raised the likelihood of the US SEC approving a spot Bitcoin ETF this year to 65% from the previous estimate of 50% a few weeks ago. Meanwhile, the probability of an Ethereum ETF approval stands at 75%, although Balchunas suggests a 95% likelihood for Ether futures.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-vs-sec-investment-banker-declarant/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/valkyrie-ethereum-strategy-etf-sec/">Valkyrie Funds File for New Ethereum Strategy ETF with the US SEC</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/valkyrie-ethereum-strategy-etf-sec/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple vs SEC: Court Approves Investment Banker Declarant</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-vs-sec-investment-banker-declarant/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-vs-sec-investment-banker-declarant/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 08:33:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment Banking Declarant]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ripple labs inc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267187</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-vs-sec-investment-banker-declarant/">Ripple vs SEC: Court Approves Investment Banker Declarant</a></p>
<p>This move holds significant implications for the case as it introduces a new perspective to the legal proceedings.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-vs-sec-investment-banker-declarant/">Ripple vs SEC: Court Approves Investment Banker Declarant</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-vs-sec-investment-banker-declarant/">Ripple vs SEC: Court Approves Investment Banker Declarant</a></p>
<p>In a recent development, Judge Analisa Torres has granted <a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.nysd.551082/gov.uscourts.nysd.551082.888.0.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener">permission</a> for an investment banker declarant to make an appearance in the legal proceedings involving <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ripple-labs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ripple Labs Inc</a> and the US Securities and Exchange Commission.</p>
<h2>The Role of the Investment Banker Declarant</h2>
<p>An investment banker declarant is an individual who provides expert testimony and insights based on their professional experience in the financial and investment sector. In this case, Andrew A. Kunsak, a representative from the law firm Sidley Austin LLP, will serve as an investment banker declarant in the SEC vs Ripple Labs lawsuit.</p>
<p>One of the main issues in the ongoing case is the rejection of the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>’s plea to seal documents related to the Hinman speech. This speech, delivered by former SEC official William Hinman in 2018, has immense significance as it could potentially shed light on the SEC’s stance on whether <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/xrp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">XRP</a> qualifies as a security.</p>
<p>Simultaneously, Ripple’s request to seal information about XRP sales, including programmatic and institutional sales, further adds to the complexity. Amidst these intricate legal maneuvers, Kunsak’s role becomes pivotal. As an expert in the financial and investment sector, his insights hold the potential to reshape the court&#8217;s understanding of XRP&#8217;s nature and implications.</p>
<p>Kunsak’s objective aligns with safeguarding stakeholders- a group that encompasses investors, market participants, and Ripple itself. His expert testimony will seek to present a holistic view of the financial aspects surrounding XRP, offering a counterpoint to the SEC’s arguments.</p>
<h2>SEC Submits an Interlocutory Appeal Motion</h2>
<p>Meanwhile, the SEC is <a href="https://www.docdroid.net/jbnzuoG/latest-file-pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener">seeking</a> an interlocutory appeal following Judge Analisa Torres’ verdict,  marking a significant shift in the legal proceedings. The verdict, which ruled that programmatic sales of XRP did not fall under the classification of securities as per the Howey Test, has implications that resonate beyond the immediate case.</p>
<p>The SEC’s appeal seeks to challenge this determination and potentially redefine the regulatory boundaries for digital assets like XRP.</p>
<p>Additionally, the SEC has taken the additional step of requesting a suspension of ongoing proceedings until its concerns are adequately addressed through court clarification. This move, while procedural, holds the potential to influence the pace and trajectory of legal proceedings.</p>
<p>In response to these developments, Ripple’s Chief Legal Officer, Stuart Alderoty, has <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-sec-appeal-court/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">offered</a> a clarification that sheds light on Ripple’s intentions. Alderoty emphasized that the organization’s pursuit of court authorization to lodge an appeal is not indicative of a challenge to the ruling on XRP&#8217;s classification.</p>
<p>This clarification underscores Ripple’s commitment to pursuing legal avenues within the established framework. Recently, some lawmakers in the US have <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-crypto-legislation-coinbase-ceo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">chastised</a> the SEC for using enforcement action against the crypto business rather than developing a solid framework for legal clarity.</p>
<div id="gtx-trans" style="position: absolute; left: 443px; top: 200.778px;">
<div class="gtx-trans-icon"></div>
</div>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-1b-fintech-fund-support-growth-stage-companies/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-vs-sec-investment-banker-declarant/">Ripple vs SEC: Court Approves Investment Banker Declarant</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-vs-sec-investment-banker-declarant/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>UK Launches £1 Billion FinTech Growth Fund to Support Growth Stage Companies</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-1b-fintech-fund-support-growth-stage-companies/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-1b-fintech-fund-support-growth-stage-companies/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Darya Rudz]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 08:27:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FinTech News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Startups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FinTech]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fintech companies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fintech hub]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[uk fintech]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[uk fintech growth fund]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267173</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-1b-fintech-fund-support-growth-stage-companies/">UK Launches £1 Billion FinTech Growth Fund to Support Growth Stage Companies</a></p>
<p>Such companies as Barclays plc, National Westminster Bank (NatWest), Mastercard Incorporated (NYSE: MA), London Stock Exchange Group, and Peel Hunt have backed FinTech Growth Fund.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-1b-fintech-fund-support-growth-stage-companies/">UK Launches £1 Billion FinTech Growth Fund to Support Growth Stage Companies</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-1b-fintech-fund-support-growth-stage-companies/">UK Launches £1 Billion FinTech Growth Fund to Support Growth Stage Companies</a></p>
<p>UK FinTech Growth Partners LLP has <a href="https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20230815937510/en/UK-FinTech-Growth-Partners-Announces-the-Launch-of-its-Growth-Stage-FinTech-Fund" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announced</a> the launch of the FinTech Growth Fund – an investment fund aimed at supporting companies at the early stages of their business until they can go public. The move aims to back UK&#8217;s image as a fintech hub as well as allow the country to compete with Silicon Valley.</p>
<p>Basically, FinTech Growth Fund will provide four to eight investments per year, with investments between £10 million and £100 million, as well as offer strategic support to its portfolio companies to help them bring their corporate ambitions to life. The fund is set to make the first investments as soon as the fourth quarter of this year.</p>
<p>Such companies as <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/barclays/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Barclays plc</a>, National Westminster Bank (NatWest), <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/mastercard/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Mastercard Incorporated</a> (NYSE: MA), <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/london-stock-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">London Stock Exchange Group</a>, and Peel Hunt have backed FinTech Growth Fund.</p>
<p>Lord Dominic Johnson CBE, Minister of State, Department for Business and Trade, commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;UK Fintech remains one of this country’s crown jewels, casting a shining light to global investors that attracted $12.5 billion of inward investment in 2022. Second only to the US and larger than the next 13 European markets combined, UK Fintech can still reach new heights with new UK-based growth funds. I welcome the launch of the Fintech Growth Fund and wish them well in their fundraising.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The leading team of the fund has also been formed. Its board of partners includes experts in the industry, such as Angel Issa &#8211; former Global Head of Corporate Development &amp; Strategic Investments at Nomura, Joe Parkin – former Managing Director &#8211; Head of Banks, Digital Channels and UK Inorganic at BlackRock, Kaushalya Somasundaram &#8211; Former Executive Director and UK Head of Payments, Partnerships &amp; Industry Relations at Square; and Phil Vidler – CEO of FinTech Alliance.</p>
<h2>UK&#8217;s FinTech Climate</h2>
<p>Earlier, Britain was facing criticism saying that the UK government put barriers to fintech entrepreneurs and forced them to consider listings overseas, especially after the country’s exit from the European Union, which undermined the UK&#8217;s status as a global financial centre.</p>
<p>In response to scepticism, the London Stock Exchange has undergone a number of reforms to encourage fintech firms to float in the UK rather than in the US. Besides, the government created initiatives to promote innovation and growth, such as the Fintech Delivery Panel and the Fintech Sector Strategy. As a result, the UK is now the leading fintech hub in Europe.</p>
<p>Fintech is one of the UK&#8217;s strongest startup sectors, with more than 1,500 high-growth fintech companies currently active, 20 fintech unicorns (around half of the UK&#8217;s billion-dollar startups), and more venture capital investment than any other industry. The sector is home to many of the world’s largest fintech companies and is comprised of more than 1,600 firms. This number is projected to double by 2030.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-equities-down-nasdaq-corrects-fed-inflation/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-1b-fintech-fund-support-growth-stage-companies/">UK Launches £1 Billion FinTech Growth Fund to Support Growth Stage Companies</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-1b-fintech-fund-support-growth-stage-companies/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4230 metric#misses=50 metric#hit-ratio=98.8 metric#bytes=1055623 metric#prefetches=208 metric#store-reads=28 metric#store-writes=5 metric#store-hits=216 metric#store-misses=11 metric#sql-queries=37 metric#ms-total=93.00 metric#ms-cache=5.58 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.1745 metric#ms-cache-ratio=6.0 -->