<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 13:55:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Microsoft Encounters Stumbling Block in Britain Regarding Activision Deal</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-britain-activision-deal/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-britain-activision-deal/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 13:55:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Deals News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gaming News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[activision blizzard]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cma]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[microsoft]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=252411</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-britain-activision-deal/">Microsoft Encounters Stumbling Block in Britain Regarding Activision Deal</a></p>
<p>Following the CMA's decision to veto the Microsoft-Activision deal in Britain, the computer software giant plans to appeal. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-britain-activision-deal/">Microsoft Encounters Stumbling Block in Britain Regarding Activision Deal</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-britain-activision-deal/">Microsoft Encounters Stumbling Block in Britain Regarding Activision Deal</a></p>
<p>Britain&#8217;s Competition and Markets Authority <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/04/26/britain-blocks-microsoft-acquisition-of-activision-blizzard.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">has </a><a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/04/26/britain-blocks-microsoft-acquisition-of-activision-blizzard.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">blocked</a> Microsoft&#8217;s acquisition of gaming publisher <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/blizzard/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Activision Blizzard</a> (NASDAQ: ATVI). On Wednesday, the top UK regulator opposed Microsoft&#8217;s acquisition of the &#8220;Call of Duty&#8221; publisher. This verdict comes <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/activision-shares-higher-microsoft/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">a month after</a> the UK CMA deemed the tech giant&#8217;s impending control of Activision non-threatening to video gaming competition. However, the British competition regulator now believes that Microsoft&#8217;s ownership of Activision could hamper competition in the cloud gaming market.</p>
<p>In a press release, the CMA explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Allowing Microsoft to take such a strong position in the cloud gaming market just as it begins to grow rapidly would risk undermining the innovation that is crucial to the development of these opportunities.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The London-based non-ministerial government department also fears that Microsoft Corporation (NASDAQ: MSFT) could commandeer Activision&#8217;s games exclusively for its cloud gaming platform. Such a potential move would allow only Xbox Game Pass access to the publisher&#8217;s vaunted library at the expense of other key players.</p>
<h2>Microsoft Rues CMA Decision to Block Activision Deal in Britain</h2>
<p>The CMA&#8217;s decision to block Microsoft&#8217;s $69 billion acquisition of the gaming publisher is a massive blow to the computer software giant. Microsoft had hoped to convince authorities in Britain that its ownership of Activision would still benefit competition. Nonetheless, the Redmond, Washington-based company plans to appeal the decision.</p>
<p>Although cloud gaming is still in its early phase, Microsoft has already identified the technology as the next mainstream way to play games. The tech giant previously attempted to assuage the CMA&#8217;s concerns regarding any perceived monopolistic tendencies – but fell short. Microsoft&#8217;s concessions include sharing specific Activision gaming properties with other rivals for a sustained period.</p>
<p>However, the CMA wondered if such agreements would hold up over time in an increasingly dynamic market. Given the terms and conditions offered by Microsoft, the UK regulator said that &#8220;there are significant risks of disagreement and conflict between Microsoft and cloud gaming service providers, particularly over a ten-year period in a rapidly changing market&#8221;.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, expressing Microsoft&#8217;s unwavering commitment to the Activision acquisition, Microsoft Vice Chair and President Brad Smith said:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We remain committed to reinforcing these agreements through regulatory remedies.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Smith further explained that Microsoft had already signed contracts that would make Activision&#8217;s games available on hundreds of millions of devices. The company&#8217;s Vice Chair expressed disappointment at the CMA&#8217;s decision after &#8220;lengthy deliberations&#8221;. According to Smith, the CMA&#8217;s verdict rejects a practical way of addressing competition concerns and reflects a flawed understanding of the cloud gaming market. In addition, Smith pointed out that the CMA&#8217;s stance discourages tech innovation and investment.</p>
<h2>Activision CEO Confident of Favorable Hearing in Appeal Process</h2>
<p>Activision CEO Bobby Kotick intimated staff on the video game publisher&#8217;s joint appeal process with Microsoft in a letter to employees. Kotick was confident about a fair hearing from the UK Competition Appeals Tribunal because the deal was good for competition.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/trust-wallet-web3-integration/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-britain-activision-deal/">Microsoft Encounters Stumbling Block in Britain Regarding Activision Deal</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-britain-activision-deal/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Trust Wallet to Simplify Web3 Onboarding with This New Integration</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/trust-wallet-web3-integration/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/trust-wallet-web3-integration/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andy Watson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 13:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[trust wallet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web3auth]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=252423</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/trust-wallet-web3-integration/">Trust Wallet to Simplify Web3 Onboarding with This New Integration</a></p>
<p>With the growing importance of Web3, adopting Two-Factor Wallets is seen as a significant step in improving security measures in the crypto industry.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/trust-wallet-web3-integration/">Trust Wallet to Simplify Web3 Onboarding with This New Integration</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/trust-wallet-web3-integration/">Trust Wallet to Simplify Web3 Onboarding with This New Integration</a></p>
<p>Trust Wallet, one of the largest self-custodial and multi-chain wallets, has partnered with Web3Auth to simplify Web3 onboarding using social logins. This collaboration allows users to access Web3 services using their existing social login credentials and other security factors.</p>
<p>Trust Wallet&#8217;s newly deployed Multi-Party Computation (MPC) solution, powered by Web3Auth, eliminates the current requirement of a written-down seed phrase, safeguarding users from human error and a single point of failure, thus strengthening account safety and security. Before their recent partnership with Web3Auth, users had limited options when accessing major wallets, choosing between a custodial solution with easier access but lower transparency or a fully custodial solution with more risk and complexity.</p>
<p>According to the official announcement, the partnership aims at improving the user experience and accelerating the mass adoption of Web3. Users can access <a href="https://trustwallet.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Trust Wallet</a> services using their existing Google, Apple, Telegram, and Discord accounts, significantly reducing the barrier to entry for new Web3 users. For enhanced security and ease of use, users also have the option to use SMS OTP and email recovery.</p>
<h2>Web3Auth CEO Sees Two-Factor Wallets as Crucial to Crypto Security</h2>
<p>In a statement, Zhen Yu Yong, the Co-founder, and CEO of <a href="https://web3auth.io/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Web3Auth</a>, highlighted the significant risk of crypto loss associated with lost seed phrases. Yong emphasized the importance of the long-term adoption of Two-Factor Wallets as a crucial step towards greater security in the industry. According to Yong, the recent partnership with Trust Wallet is a significant step forward in Web3Auth&#8217;s mission to democratize enterprise-grade MPC and provide everyone with a more secure crypto experience.</p>
<p>With the growing importance of Web3, adopting Two-Factor Wallets is seen as a significant step in improving security measures in the crypto industry. Trust Wallet&#8217;s MPC solution and Web3Auth&#8217;s two-factor authentication provide a secure and seamless onboarding process for new Web3 users. This Integration enables users to access the Web3 world with ease while maintaining complete control and ownership of their digital assets.</p>
<h2>Crypto Wallets Need a Makeover?</h2>
<p>The Web3 onboarding experience should be smooth, and wallets are essential. As the first point of interaction, news users spend most of the time on web3 wallets to perform various actions, including store, transact, swap, trade, connect, stake, and others. However, it&#8217;s been a long since self-custodial wallets have taken innovation seriously.</p>
<p>Complex UI/UX, lack of security measures, and cranky user experience have turned crypto into an unpleasant adventure for inexperienced users. However, things are changing with the latest <a href="https://ethereum.org/en/roadmap/account-abstraction/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">&#8220;Account Abstraction&#8221;</a> upgrade providing greater user flexibility and fulfilling the long-term vision of the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a> community. What was proven to be difficult and intimidating for new users will now make wallets more accessible.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/lg-energy-solution-q1-2023-results/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/trust-wallet-web3-integration/">Trust Wallet to Simplify Web3 Onboarding with This New Integration</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/trust-wallet-web3-integration/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>LG Energy Solution Posts Q1 2023 Results Sees Profits Swell More than Double</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/lg-energy-solution-q1-2023-results/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/lg-energy-solution-q1-2023-results/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 12:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[general motors]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[lg]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[lg energy solution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tesla]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=252398</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/lg-energy-solution-q1-2023-results/">LG Energy Solution Posts Q1 2023 Results Sees Profits Swell More than Double</a></p>
<p>The US Inflation Reduction Act propelled LG Energy Solution to an astounding income haul in its Q1 2023 results. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/lg-energy-solution-q1-2023-results/">LG Energy Solution Posts Q1 2023 Results Sees Profits Swell More than Double</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/lg-energy-solution-q1-2023-results/">LG Energy Solution Posts Q1 2023 Results Sees Profits Swell More than Double</a></p>
<p>LG Energy Solution Ltd recently posted its Q1 2023 earnings, revealing a more than double profit haul. For the first quarter of the year, the Seoul-based battery company posted a 145% jump in profit and a 101% revenue rise to 8.7 trillion won. LG Energy Solution&#8217;s reported operating profit for the year&#8217;s first three months was 633 billion won (S$633.1 million). A year ago, the company realized a much smaller haul of 259 billion won.</p>
<p>For the first quarter of 2023, LG Energy Solution Ltd also reported a net profit of 500.6 billion won ($374 million), beating consensus expectations. The company&#8217;s shares rose 2.4% during the early Seoul trading session and are up approximately 30% this year.</p>
<p>In reporting its Q1 2023 figures, LG Energy Solution factored in subsidies from the US Inflation Reduction Act. Furthermore, the prominent battery maker also considered solid sales of electric vehicles in Western markets, which analysts attributed as the reason for the profit jump.</p>
<h2>US Inflation Reduction Act Applicability</h2>
<p>The increase in sales of EVs in the US was boosted by the Inflation Reduction Act tax credit that grants consumers up to $7,500 off. However, the US Inflation Reduction Act requires half of the battery component value to be produced or assembled in North America for eligibility for perks. These associated perks include a $3,750 credit and 40% of critical mineral value sourced from the US. Also, the Act necessitates the production of 50% of battery components in North America. This requirement helps to qualify for a free trade partner that offers $3,750 in credit.</p>
<p>LG Energy Solution acknowledged it received requests from prominent auto-manufacturing clients regarding boosting battery supply since the US law took effect. Although this development could lead to additional orders, the company also foresees lower metal prices impacting future revenue. LG Energy Solution revealed it signed &#8220;cost pass-through&#8221; contracts with its clientele to better manage material costs. Lee Chang-sil, the chief financial officer of the company which supplies automakers such as <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/tesla/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tesla</a> (NASDAQ: TSLA) and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/general-motors/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">General Motors</a> (NYSE: GM), said:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;EV demand in North America remains very strong. Although demand in Europe seems to be limited and metals prices are falling, we&#8217;re pretty sure we can meet our initial goal for 30% sales growth for 2023.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The company added that changes in metal costs would likely reflect in the second half of 2023. However, the profitability impact would also likely remain limited.</p>
<h2>Following Q1 2023 Performance, LG Energy Solution Expects to Continue Beating Chinese Rivals in the US</h2>
<p>One of the largest EV battery makers globally, LG Energy Solution is confident about outpacing Chinese rivals in the US. According to Lee, conquering the American market is no small feat and requires extensive prior experience. As LG Energy Solution CFO put it:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;It won&#8217;t be easy for the Chinese companies to enter the US. It&#8217;s not just a matter of investment. You need a lot of experience to build supply chains and operate plants. It takes a lot of time.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>LG Energy Solution is currently testing cylindrical cell batteries used by Tesla at a facility in Korea. The Seoul-based battery company plans to begin mass production by the end of 2023.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/pony-ai-driverless-robotaxi-china/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/lg-energy-solution-q1-2023-results/">LG Energy Solution Posts Q1 2023 Results Sees Profits Swell More than Double</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/lg-energy-solution-q1-2023-results/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pony.ai Receives Authorization to Operate Driverless Robotaxi Services in Guangzhou, China</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/pony-ai-driverless-robotaxi-china/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/pony-ai-driverless-robotaxi-china/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 12:46:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Transportation News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pony.ai]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=252400</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/pony-ai-driverless-robotaxi-china/">Pony.ai Receives Authorization to Operate Driverless Robotaxi Services in Guangzhou, China</a></p>
<p>Pony.ai is the first and only company to receive such a permit in Guangzhou.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/pony-ai-driverless-robotaxi-china/">Pony.ai Receives Authorization to Operate Driverless Robotaxi Services in Guangzhou, China</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/pony-ai-driverless-robotaxi-china/">Pony.ai Receives Authorization to Operate Driverless Robotaxi Services in Guangzhou, China</a></p>
<p>Software company Pony.ai has received a permit to operate its driverless robotaxi services in Guangzhou city of China. The startup, which is backed by Toyota Motor Corp., now has the authorization to offer its service in the Chinese city. The vehicles will have no safety operator nor human beings in the driver’s seat, as Pony.ai provides full driverless robotaxi services in Guangzhou. Pony.ai began driverless testing in the city in June 2021, meaning it has almost a two-year record of safe driverless experience. During the period, the vehicles operated in extreme weather conditions, including heavy fog, thunderstorms, and rain, as part of the testing process. Pony.ai also tried its driverless robotaxis with complex road scenarios like intersections and narrow roads to test its ability.</p>
<p>As of April 2023, the company has recorded almost 200,000 fee-charging robotaxi orders globally. It also boasts over a million kilometers (more than 621,000 miles) of driverless testing.</p>
<h2>Pony.ai Becomes First to Secure License to Operate Driverless Robotaxi Service in Guangzhou</h2>
<p>According to a <a href="https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20230425006213/en/Pony.ai-is-First-to-Receive-Permit-to-Provide-Public-Facing-Fully-Driverless-Robotaxi-Service-in-Guangzhou" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">press release</a> announcing the new feat, Pony.ai is the first company to receive such a permit in Guangzhou. Before the recent approval in Guangzhou, Pony.ai and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/baidu-beijing-driverless-robotaxi-tests/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Baidu got similar permits in Beijing last year</a>. The new generation robotaxi model was successfully launched in Beijing on April 14, 2023. This means that the company can operate its public-facing, fully driverless robotaxis in two cities in China- Beijing and Guangzhou.</p>
<p>Henceforth, riders can place orders for their Pony.ai robotaxi to residential and business districts, subway stops, parks, etc., using the PonyPilot+ app. After choosing their destinations, the app users can also customize the color of the vehicle’s welcome light before its arrival. As no human is driving the robotaxis, Pony.ai explained that Guangzhou residents need to scan the QR code on the rear right door to unlock the vehicle. Also, riders must buckle their seat belts before the full-driverless journey to their preferred destinations begins.</p>
<p>Additionally, the press release states:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Pony.ai’s next generation robotaxi model equipped with its sixth-generation self-driving software and hardware systems, based on the seven-seat Toyota Sienna Autono-MaaS (S-AM) model, has obtained test licenses in Beijing and Guangzhou and is testing on the road. While initial testing of the S-AM model vehicles include a safety driver, it has passed the exams and expert review required for a driverless permit, and it is anticipated that S-AM model driverless robotaxi services will commence in the near future.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Last month, Pony.ai announced that it has partnered with Meituan to develop driverless vehicles for food delivery services. The joint venture expects at least 10,000 delivery robots equipped with Pony’s autonomous driving controller in China’s first-tier cities by the end of 2024.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-employee-insider-trading-10-months/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/pony-ai-driverless-robotaxi-china/">Pony.ai Receives Authorization to Operate Driverless Robotaxi Services in Guangzhou, China</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/pony-ai-driverless-robotaxi-china/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Former Coinbase Employee Guilty of Insider Trading Wants to Limit Jail Term to 10 Months</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-employee-insider-trading-10-months/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-employee-insider-trading-10-months/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 12:43:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=252384</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-employee-insider-trading-10-months/">Former Coinbase Employee Guilty of Insider Trading Wants to Limit Jail Term to 10 Months</a></p>
<p>Ishan Wahi has cited reasons such as “modest, law-abiding and admirable life” and mental health for the court to consider a jail term no more than 10 months. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-employee-insider-trading-10-months/">Former Coinbase Employee Guilty of Insider Trading Wants to Limit Jail Term to 10 Months</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-employee-insider-trading-10-months/">Former Coinbase Employee Guilty of Insider Trading Wants to Limit Jail Term to 10 Months</a></p>
<p>In the latest court filing, crypto exchange <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/04/26/former-coinbase-employee-seeks-to-limit-jail-term-to-10-months-in-insider-trading-case/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Coinbase</a> former product manager Ishan Wahi, who&#8217;s guilty of insider trading, has asked for a jail term of no more than 10 months. The lawyers representing Wahi have made an appeal to the court in their recent filings.</p>
<h2>First-Ever Insider Crypto Trading Case</h2>
<p>Wahi pleaded guilty to the first-ever insider trading case concerning crypto assets. He has a sentencing hearing next month on May 9. In its filing to the court, Wahi&#8217;s lawyers <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/04/26/former-coinbase-employee-seeks-to-limit-jail-term-to-10-months-in-insider-trading-case/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">noted</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“The Defendant respectfully submits that a sentence of no more than 10 months incarceration, together with several other consequences of Ishan’s conviction, would impose a sufficient, but not excessive, punishment for the crimes of conviction”.</p></blockquote>
<p>Furthermore, Tuesday&#8217;s filings also explain the reason behind considering this leniency. It adds that significant public attention and Wahi’s previous “modest, law-abiding and admirable life” and mental health conditions are the reasons that need to be considered.</p>
<p>The court filing document noted:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Ishan is a man of outstanding character who crossed the line. His promising career has ended instantly, with no realistic prospects of similar employment in the future.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Earlier this year on February 7, Wahi pleaded guilty to committing wire fraud by sharing the details of the future Coinbase crypto token listings with his brother Nikhil Wahi along with another contact Sameer Ramani. Judge Loretta Preska in the Southern District of New York is currently presiding over this case.</p>
<p>Earlier this year in January 2023, Nikhil Wahi was sentenced to a 10-month prison for his involvement in the crime. In February, Ishan Wahi entered into a plea deal with the US government wherein he will supposedly face a tentative sentence of three to five in jail and a fine between $15,000-$150,000.</p>
<h2>Coinbase and Regulators</h2>
<p>The recent development comes at a time when crypto exchange Coinbase has been having a tough battle with the US regulators, especially the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>. Last month, the SEC issued a Wells Notice to Coinbase hinting that they could slap a lawsuit over the allegations of selling several digital assets as unregistered securities.</p>
<p>Besides, it could also hold Coinbase accountable for offering staking services without informing the SEC. However, Coinbase has lashed out at the securities regulator claiming no wrongdoing and stating that they have been informing the SEC at every step of their journey. Coinbase has also lashed out at the SEC for not maintaining enough clarity on securities rules for crypto.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-sell-ledgerx-50m/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-employee-insider-trading-10-months/">Former Coinbase Employee Guilty of Insider Trading Wants to Limit Jail Term to 10 Months</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-employee-insider-trading-10-months/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bankrupt Crypto Firm FTX Finally Agrees to Sell Its Derivatives Platform LedgerX for $50M</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-sell-ledgerx-50m/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-sell-ledgerx-50m/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 12:42:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Deals News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ledgerx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mih]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=252310</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-sell-ledgerx-50m/">Bankrupt Crypto Firm FTX Finally Agrees to Sell Its Derivatives Platform LedgerX for $50M</a></p>
<p>FTX got the nod earlier this year to sell some of its business units.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-sell-ledgerx-50m/">Bankrupt Crypto Firm FTX Finally Agrees to Sell Its Derivatives Platform LedgerX for $50M</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-sell-ledgerx-50m/">Bankrupt Crypto Firm FTX Finally Agrees to Sell Its Derivatives Platform LedgerX for $50M</a></p>
<p>The <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a> exchange has now reached an agreement to sell its crypto derivatives platform LedgerX in a deal worth about $50 million. According to a Reuters <a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/ftx-debtors-sell-futures-options-clearinghouse-unit-ledgerx-2023-04-25/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a>, FTX has agreed sale terms with an affiliate of Miami International Holdings Inc. However, the sale is still subject to approval from the US court overseeing FTX&#8217;s bankruptcy proceedings. To this end, a sale hearing has been slated for May 4, and hopefully, the exchange will be able to secure the necessary approval for the sale to go through.</p>
<h2>FTX Keen on Helping Stakeholders to Recover Funds</h2>
<p>It should be noted that FTX has been working tirelessly to raise the money it owes creditors. Since <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-exchange-files-for-bankruptcy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">filing for bankruptcy</a> in November, it has recovered no less than $7.3 billion in cash and liquid crypto assets. This is according to the most recent report that the FTX exchange published this April.</p>
<p>To make its work even easier,  FTX got the nod earlier this year to sell some of its business units. So, selling LedgerX to MIH is a product of that approval, per FTX CEO John Ray. Ray said in a statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We are pleased to reach this agreement with MIH, which is an example of our continuing efforts to monetize assets to deliver recoveries to stakeholders.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Meanwhile, the FTX exchange still has several business units also lined up for possible sale. Some of them include FTX Europe, FTX Japan, and Embed Financial Technologies, among others. And according to court filings, about 117 potential buyers have so far expressed their interest in its various businesses. The firm continues to raise funds by all means necessary, recently agreeing to sell its stake in Web3.0 firm Mysten Labs. The deal is reportedly worth $95 million.</p>
<p>After raising these funds, it remains unclear, exactly how FTX intends to repay its creditors and customers. But there&#8217;s a possibility that it restarts its crypto exchange which was an industry giant at some point. Or it may also sell the exchange as part of its recovery process. Nonetheless, Skybridge Capital founder Anthony Scaramucci <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-revival-anthony-scaramucci/">believes</a> that a revival is highly unlikely.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-cloud-prices/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-sell-ledgerx-50m/">Bankrupt Crypto Firm FTX Finally Agrees to Sell Its Derivatives Platform LedgerX for $50M</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-sell-ledgerx-50m/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alibaba Slashes Cloud Prices by Half to Foster Growth Ahead of Possible IPO</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-cloud-prices/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-cloud-prices/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 12:07:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cloud Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[IPO News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alibaba]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tencent]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=252343</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-cloud-prices/">Alibaba Slashes Cloud Prices by Half to Foster Growth Ahead of Possible IPO</a></p>
<p>Chinese tech giant Alibaba will cut the prices of its cloud services by up to 50% starting today as it hopes to grow the sector.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-cloud-prices/">Alibaba Slashes Cloud Prices by Half to Foster Growth Ahead of Possible IPO</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-cloud-prices/">Alibaba Slashes Cloud Prices by Half to Foster Growth Ahead of Possible IPO</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/alibaba-group/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Alibaba Group</a> (NYSE: BABA) recently announced cutting its cloud prices by 50% to spur business growth. The Chinese tech giant seeks to carve out a bigger share of its local cloud market amid increasing competition. By drastically reducing the prices of cloud-based products and services, Alibaba hopes to better compete with the likes of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/tencent/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tencent</a>.</p>
<p>Reports state the price cuts will kick into effect today as Alibaba leverages a demand surge driven by artificial intelligence applications. The company’s cloud price development also comes as it is mulling spinning off its Aliyun business ahead of a <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-split-6-groups-ipo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">possible IPO</a>.</p>
<p>Alibaba Cloud’s website says prices for elastic computing services that use Arm and Intel-based semiconductors will drop 15% to 20%. The platform further stated that elastic computing services that use Nvidia’s V100 and T4 graphics processing units would see a price reduction of between 41% and 47%.</p>
<p>Although the price cuts could help Alibaba attract more customers, a Chinese cloud computing research analyst offered another take. According to Canalys’ Zhang Yi, the actual impact of Alibaba’s price reductions will depend on the specific services bought by clients.</p>
<h2>Prime Mover Alibaba Cloud Facing Intense Competition</h2>
<p>Founded in 2009, Alibaba Cloud is one of China’s earliest local venturers in the cloud computing space. Although the service currently caters to over a third of the sector in China, it has faced escalating domestic competition in recent years. These include Chinese carriers such as China Telecom and China Unicom, as well as tech conglomerate Tencent.</p>
<p>Alibaba and Tencent compete to provide the requisite raw computing power for popular AI platforms like ChatGPT. The desire to gain the upper hand sees Alibaba slash its Aliyun subsidiary’s core products up to 50% from May 7th. Although Alibaba Cloud provides data processing and storage services to countless businesses, developers, and governments in over 200 countries, the company pushes for more. Alibaba stressed that it remains committed to growing its cloud business because it is a potentially exponential growth driver.</p>
<h2>Bloomberg Intelligence Analysts Predict How Cloud Price Cuts Can Impact Company’s Short-Term Bottomline</h2>
<p>Despite the perceived optimism from Alibaba’s cloud services price cuts, <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-04-26/alibaba-cutting-cloud-prices-as-much-as-50-to-drive-user-growth#xj4y7vzkg?leadSource=uverify%20wall" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Bloomberg Intelligence</a> analysts believe the company might incur short-term fiscal shortfalls. According to Catherine Lim and Trini Tan:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Alibaba’s price cuts of up to 50% for its cloud services raise a risk that the unit’s adjusted Ebita in fiscal 2024 ending March will trail consensus expectations, even after a more than 5% decline in estimates over the past two weeks.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Furthermore, Lim and Tan also added:</p>
<blockquote><p>“The cuts raise the likelihood that Alibaba will cede 2024 cloud profit gains to spur revenue growth and fend off increased cloud and generative-AI rivalry from peers such as Tencent and Baidu this year.”</p></blockquote>
<p>In other news, Alibaba announced Wednesday that over 200,000 companies have requested to join its Tongyi Qianwen beta testing program. The tech giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-chatgpt-rival-tongyi-qianwen/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">announced</a> its AI-powered large language model earlier this month.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-28000-first-republic-bank-crisis/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-cloud-prices/">Alibaba Slashes Cloud Prices by Half to Foster Growth Ahead of Possible IPO</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-cloud-prices/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Breaches $28,000 amid Renewed First Republic Bank Crisis</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-28000-first-republic-bank-crisis/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-28000-first-republic-bank-crisis/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 10:56:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[first republic bank]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=252363</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-28000-first-republic-bank-crisis/">Bitcoin Breaches $28,000 amid Renewed First Republic Bank Crisis</a></p>
<p>While Bitcoin still maintains a somewhat close correlation to the S&#038;P 500, the digital currency is now being pitched as a better alternative to traditional banking.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-28000-first-republic-bank-crisis/">Bitcoin Breaches $28,000 amid Renewed First Republic Bank Crisis</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-28000-first-republic-bank-crisis/">Bitcoin Breaches $28,000 amid Renewed First Republic Bank Crisis</a></p>
<p>The price of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> (BTC) is dramatically on the rise despite starting the day with a bearish slump. At the time of writing, the premier digital currency is changing hands at $28,810.19 after <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/bitcoin/markets/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">printing</a> a 5.41% growth over the past 24 hours. Riding on its current outlook, the cryptocurrency is now paring off the losses it accrued in the trailing 7-day period in what might spell a positive close to the week. Surprisingly, Bitcoin’s latest upsurge comes at the heels of growing concerns about the future of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/first-republic-bank/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">First Republic Bank</a> (NYSE: FRC) which has been recording some forms of stability in both its liquidity and share price.</p>
<p>In its latest earnings report, First Republic Bank revealed that its deposits plummeted as much as $100 billion for the first quarter.</p>
<p>The performance figures the company <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/first-republic-bank-shares-q1-2023/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a> showed that its revenue plunged by 13.4%. The regional bank’s net income also came in at $269 million, a figure that represented a 32.9% slump from the year-ago period. Despite the obvious hole in its balance sheet, the company’s Founder and Executive Chairman, Jim Herbert, and CEO Mike Roffler, tried to allay investors’ fears in a joint statement.</p>
<p>“With the stabilization of our deposit base and the strength of our credit quality and capital position, we continue to take steps to strengthen our business. We remain fully committed to serving our communities, and we are grateful for the ongoing support of our clients and colleagues,” the duo said.</p>
<p>Despite these reassurances, the shares of the bank recorded one of its worst days since it went public, dropping as much as 49.37% to $8.10 per share. The 4.69% recovery in the Pre-Market is yet to allay the concerns that FRC may end up like Silicon Valley Bank (SVB).</p>
<h2>First Republic Bank Crisis: Bitcoin to the Rescue</h2>
<p>There are a number of solutions that have been directed to help FRC get back on its feet and Bitcoin is the less clamored one. While Bitcoin still maintains a somewhat close correlation to the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-the-sp-500-index/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">S&amp;P 500 Index</a> (INDEXSP: .INX), the digital currency is now being pitched as a better alternative to traditional banking for anyone looking to keep custody of their money.</p>
<p>It is ironic that Bitcoin picked up pace as First Republic Bank was seeing a major selloff, however, this can be tagged a crucial vote of confidence on the asset’s technology, ecosystem, and underlying economics.</p>
<p>The digital currency has been on a promising year for the better part of April. While this week started roughly, the current resurgence has helped Bitcoin maintain a 74.39% growth in the Year-to-Date (YTD) period. This not only surpasses the S&amp;P 500 but is also significantly higher than many digital currencies around today.</p>
<p>Bitcoin’s decentralization, immunity from control, and growing demand has been cited as some of the reasons why the cryptocurrency is a better investment asset than FRC or most stocks.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/21shares-ark-investment-bitcoin-etf/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-28000-first-republic-bank-crisis/">Bitcoin Breaches $28,000 amid Renewed First Republic Bank Crisis</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-28000-first-republic-bank-crisis/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>21Shares and Cathy Wood’s Ark Investment Renew Bitcoin ETF Bid amid BTC Price Rebound</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/21shares-ark-investment-bitcoin-etf/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/21shares-ark-investment-bitcoin-etf/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mercy Tukiya Mutanya]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 10:52:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funds & ETFs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[21shares]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ark investment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc etc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=252360</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/21shares-ark-investment-bitcoin-etf/">21Shares and Cathy Wood&#8217;s Ark Investment Renew Bitcoin ETF Bid amid BTC Price Rebound</a></p>
<p>The new filing comes as cryptocurrencies, and risk assets in general, are in recovery after a bad 2022.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/21shares-ark-investment-bitcoin-etf/">21Shares and Cathy Wood&#8217;s Ark Investment Renew Bitcoin ETF Bid amid BTC Price Rebound</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/21shares-ark-investment-bitcoin-etf/">21Shares and Cathy Wood&#8217;s Ark Investment Renew Bitcoin ETF Bid amid BTC Price Rebound</a></p>
<p>Crypto exchange-traded-product issuer 21Shares and investment firm Ark Investment Management are once again trying to get a spot <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> exchange-traded fund (ETF) approved. This comes after the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) rejected two previous attempts. The firms argue that such a fund would offer protection currently not available to investors in the United States.</p>
<p>The  ARK 21Shares Bitcoin ETF would trade under the ARKB ticker and would track the price of Bitcoin as measured by the S&amp;P Bitcoin Index. The application faces deep-seated resistance from US regulators. The SEC has rejected dozens of such applications including one filed by 21Shares in 2021 and another in May 2022.</p>
<p>“American investors have been hurt by crypto scams that are primarily international – and especially because there aren’t available, easy, regulated options at home,” Hany Rashwan, chief executive officer and co-founder of 21Shares, <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-04-25/21shares-cathie-wood-revive-bitcoin-etf-bid-after-price-rebound" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a> in an interview. “We are very excited about the future of crypto as a firm and we think the United States is going to play a very big part of it.”</p>
<p>An ETF is an investment product linked to commodities, currencies, stocks or bonds that allows investors to invest without owning the actual asset. A Bitcoin ETF allows investors to buy shares that track the price of Bitcoin without having to hold the cryptocurrency.</p>
<p>The new filing comes as cryptocurrencies, and risk assets in general, are in recovery after a bad 2022. Some investors even argue that digital currency has the potential to act as an alternative to traditional banks.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/grayscale/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Grayscale Investments</a> has sued the SEC as part of its efforts to turn its Bitcoin trust into an ETF. Market watchers say the investment firm’s odds of conversion have increased following oral arguments in the case.</p>
<p>As several issuers seek approval for Bitcoin-linked products, 21Shares CEO Rashwan says his company is uniquely positioned because it provides inverter protection through and through</p>
<p>“We have seen greater demand from American investors for American-built products, especially over the past few months with bank failures and especially over the last year with international crypto blowups,” he said. “That’s why we’re excited about pushing crypto in a regulatory-friendly way.”</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-ai-health-coaching-service/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/21shares-ark-investment-bitcoin-etf/">21Shares and Cathy Wood&#8217;s Ark Investment Renew Bitcoin ETF Bid amid BTC Price Rebound</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/21shares-ark-investment-bitcoin-etf/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Apple Working on AI-Powered Health Coaching Service</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-ai-health-coaching-service/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-ai-health-coaching-service/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Darya Rudz]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 10:47:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple ai]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple artificial intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple health coach]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple healthcare]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[artificial intelligence]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=252252</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-ai-health-coaching-service/">Apple Working on AI-Powered Health Coaching Service</a></p>
<p>According to those familiar with the matter, the Quartz healthcare coaching app will have a monthly subscription fee. The launch date is not yet confirmed, it might be 2024 or later.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-ai-health-coaching-service/">Apple Working on AI-Powered Health Coaching Service</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-ai-health-coaching-service/">Apple Working on AI-Powered Health Coaching Service</a></p>
<p>Tech giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/apple-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Apple Inc</a> (NASDAQ: AAPL) is reportedly <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-04-25/apple-aapl-developing-ai-health-coaching-service-ipados-17-health-app" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">developing</a> an application that will employ artificial intelligence (AI) and serve as a health coach. Codenamed &#8220;Quartz&#8221;, the application is designed to motivate users to take care of their health, keep track of their sleep, exercise, and make their eating habits better. The app is supposed to use AI and data from an Apple Watch to make suggestions and offer coaching programs based on the activity of a specific user.</p>
<p>According to those familiar with the matter, Quartz will have a monthly subscription fee, as it will be a separate application. The launch date is not yet confirmed, it might be 2024 or later.</p>
<p>The AI-powered health coaching app that Apple is currently working on is pretty similar to its LumiHealth initiative designed in collaboration with the government of Singapore back in 2020. As we <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-lumihealth-singapore/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a> at that time, the LumiHealth program included personalized reminders for health and fitness-related activities, offered access to activity coaching, as well as allowed users to receive incentives for keeping to the scheduled tasks. The difference between LumiHealth and the upcoming Quartz is that the former could pay out monetary awards to users who stayed healthy. In other words, the Singaporean government promised up to $380 to participants who complete the tasks through the two years span of the LumiHealth program.</p>
<p>Before the launch of AI-powered Quartz, Apple will complete its work on an iPad version of its iPhone Health app. The launch of the app on a bigger screen is expected to take place this year, most probably during its Worldwide Developers Conference (WWDC) in June.</p>
<h2>Apple&#8217;s Focus on Health-Related Services</h2>
<p>Apple entered the healthcare market later than its competitors but has already acquired a significant share of the sector. The company&#8217;s first foray into healthcare took place in 2014, with the release of the Health app. Powered by Healthkit, a set of tools that allowed developers to build bespoke apps around health and well-being, from sleep monitoring and stress reduction to exercise and blood testing, the app was initially designed to track various health data and metrics.</p>
<p>In 2015, with the launch of the first Apple Watch in 2015, Apple introduced a wide range of innovative health and fitness features that improved the functionality of the Health app. The goal was to provide users with easy-to-understand, meaningful insights to empower them to live a healthier life. Now, users can store over 150 different types of health data from Apple Watch, iPhone, and connected third-party apps and devices in one central view in the Health app.</p>
<p>To further encompass the healthcare sector and win over its rivals, Apple has hired a lot of professionals in the industry. Among them were Sumbul Desai – a clinical associate professor of medicine at Stanford, Ricky Bloomfield – a high-profile physician from Duke University, Mike Evans – a Toronto physician and the owner of a popular medical channel on YouTube, Stephen Friend – the president and co-founder of Sage Bionetworks, and more.</p>
<p>Apple&#8217;s upcoming mixed-reality headset is also expected to expand the company&#8217;s current health efforts.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-whitepaper-removed-apple-macos/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-ai-health-coaching-service/">Apple Working on AI-Powered Health Coaching Service</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-ai-health-coaching-service/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=PhpRedis metric#hits=4547 metric#misses=43 metric#hit-ratio=99.1 metric#bytes=1371058 metric#prefetches=197 metric#store-reads=20 metric#store-writes=14 metric#store-hits=202 metric#store-misses=4 metric#sql-queries=34 metric#ms-total=113.58 metric#ms-cache=6688.36 metric#ms-cache-median=0.00 metric#ms-cache-ratio=5,888.7 -->