<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 11:15:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Algorand focuses on delivering the tech without unnecessary effort hype, says interim CEO</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/algorand-focuses-on-delivering-the-tech-without-unnecessary-effort-hype-says-interim-ceo/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/algorand-focuses-on-delivering-the-tech-without-unnecessary-effort-hype-says-interim-ceo/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 11:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Interview]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Algorand News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/algorand-focuses-on-delivering-the-tech-without-unnecessary-effort-hype-says-interim-ceo/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Algorand has produced a scalable platform since it was launched in 2019, the CEO said. Algorand is working hard to deliver the tech without unnecessary effort, hype and speculation. The company wants to forge ahead with institutional partnerships. Algorand has always focused on delivering the tech Algorand Interim CEO Sean Ford, told Cryptoslate in a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/algorand-focuses-on-delivering-the-tech-without-unnecessary-effort-hype-says-interim-ceo/">Algorand focuses on delivering the tech without unnecessary effort hype, says interim CEO</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Algorand has produced a scalable platform since it was launched in 2019, the CEO said.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Algorand is working hard to deliver the tech without unnecessary effort, hype and speculation.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The company wants to forge ahead with institutional partnerships.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Algorand has always focused on delivering the tech</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Algorand Interim CEO Sean Ford, told Cryptoslate in a recent interview, that the blockchain project has always focused on delivering the tech. He added that Algorand has never focused on unnecessary hype and instead delivers on its technology.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/algorand/what-is-algorand/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Algorand is a public blockchain network</u></a> that was created by MIT professor Silvio Micali and has been around since 2017. Ford highlighted that credibility is important for the crypto space to move forward following the LUNA and FTX crashes that occurred earlier this year. He said;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;Keeping our promises is one of the major ways that web3 could regain credibility. Algorand, unlike many other projects, has always made this a priority &mdash; working hard to deliver the tech without unnecessary effort hype and speculation. Since its launch in 2019, Algorand has produced a scalable platform that provides security, fast finality, and (as Sean emphatically emphasizes), &ldquo;zero downtime.&rdquo;</em></p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Algorand to focus on institutional partnerships</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Algorand has entered some very important partnerships this year, including one with FIFA, the official governing body of football. Algorand became the official blockchain platform of FIFA following and&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/should-you-buy-algorand-ahead-of-the-world-cup-amid-a-sponsorship-deal/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>sponsorship and technical partnership deal</u></a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As FIFA&rsquo;s official blockchain partner, Algorand has launched a marketplace for collectibles tied to FIFA&rsquo;s digital archives. Algorand&rsquo;s interim CEO explained that</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;There are many ways the partnership could evolve, from issuing bonds to creating composable tickets that &ldquo;take on a life of their own. The first step on its innovation journey is to start embracing new technology and drive benefits to engage more closely with fans.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p dir="ltr">Moving forward, Ford said Algorand would focus on establishing institutional relationships. He said;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;Traditional financial institutions have been more thoughtful and rigorous about understanding the technology and the benefits and pressure-testing the capabilities of technical partners. They are more rigorous because they have a fiduciary responsibility, and there are things they can&rsquo;t accept like downtime, lack of security, or lack of finality.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p dir="ltr">Ford concluded that despite the slow rate of adoption, the presence of institutional entities in the crypto market is inevitable. He said;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;I haven&rsquo;t seen a big pullback if you consider adopting new infrastructure &mdash; at least in our world. Our partners worldwide, like Koibanx in Latin America, are working with dozens of financial institutions and banks to adopt blockchain and Algorand and leverage it for their infrastructure. They&rsquo;re very active even in this climate.&rdquo;</em></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/algorand-focuses-on-delivering-the-tech-without-unnecessary-effort-hype-says-interim-ceo/">Algorand focuses on delivering the tech without unnecessary effort hype, says interim CEO</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/algorand-focuses-on-delivering-the-tech-without-unnecessary-effort-hype-says-interim-ceo/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Metacade vs Apecoin: MCADE likely to overtake APE in 2023</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-vs-apecoin-mcade-likely-to-overtake-ape-in-2023/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-vs-apecoin-mcade-likely-to-overtake-ape-in-2023/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice Davies]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 11:09:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-vs-apecoin-mcade-likely-to-overtake-ape-in-2023/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Apecoin was one of the most talked-about crypto assets near the end of the last bull run. It&#8217;s still one of the top 50 projects by market cap as well. But in 2023 and beyond, there&#8217;s a high chance every Apecoin price prediction will be outpaced by MCADE. This article will explain why your Apecoin [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-vs-apecoin-mcade-likely-to-overtake-ape-in-2023/">Metacade vs Apecoin: MCADE likely to overtake APE in 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Apecoin was one of the most talked-about crypto assets near the end of the last bull run. It&rsquo;s still one of the <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/apecoin" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>top 50 projects by market cap</u></a> as well. But in 2023 and beyond, there&rsquo;s a high chance every Apecoin price prediction will be outpaced by MCADE.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This article will explain why your Apecoin price prediction may be too high in the sections below.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Apecoin (APE)?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">In the spring of 2022, Bored Ape Yacht Club released a utility and governance token for the APE ecosystem, Apecoin (APE). Holders of APE tokens not only have exclusive access to merch, games, services, and events but also have a say in what partnerships and programmes the Ape Foundation will support. In addition, third-party developers can also reward their participants with APE tokens.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Can APE compete with MCADE in the future?</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Metacade (MCADE)?</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://metacade.co/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade</u></a> is a virtual gathering spot and community hub that&rsquo;s set to be home to the latest, greatest GameFi and P2E games, similar to the way Steam operates for PC games. With so many different titles in the works, there will be something for everyone to enjoy in the Metacade. That&rsquo;s part of what makes the project so promising.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Another reason for the optimism surrounding Metacade is its commitment to the community. It serves the community by offering many avenues for earning income online, such as P2E games, staking, prize draws, and even competitive tournaments.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Plus, <a href="https://metacade.co/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade</u></a> will give out funding via Metagrants to aspiring developers from the community with big ideas. The community will vote on who receives these grants to give users more of a say over what Metacade looks like moving forward. This will also help to ensure that there are always fun, new games to try on the platform with a valuable reason to keep coming back.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Metacade will be more successful than Apecoin &ndash; Here&rsquo;s why</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Now that we&rsquo;ve covered what Metacade is let&rsquo;s look at why the price prediction for it is higher than our Apecoin price prediction. Here are four factors to consider while you evaluate your Apecoin price prediction moving forward.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Metacade Offers Something for Everyone</h3>
<p dir="ltr">What makes Metacade special is its inclusion of many different Web3 gaming titles on one platform. Most projects only offer a single game for users to play. This means that if someone doesn&rsquo;t enjoy that game, they have no reason to continue engaging with the platform.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade&rsquo;s increasing library of titles gives users an ever-expanding list of reasons to engage with the platform. This helps keep user levels high and ensures long-term growth.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Apecoin Has Limited Appeal</h3>
<p dir="ltr">One thing to consider when making your Apecoin price prediction is that the project is an extension of the Bored Ape Yacht Club NFT collection. This NFT collection is one of the most popular on the market but also one of the most widely ridiculed in the crypto community.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Many crypto enthusiasts dislike Bored Ape Yacht Club and its holders. These people are unlikely to ever engage with Apecoin which could hold the project back in 2023 and beyond.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Metacade is For More Than Just Gaming</h3>
<p dir="ltr">As a platform, Metacade does more than just give people access to the best games. It&rsquo;s also a socially active place where friends can spend time together and meet new people. Individuals who wish to work in Web3 could one day find their first jobs, doing things like testing games and managing communities.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In this sense, Metacade has the scope to become like a virtual community square or town hall, providing an important social space for the future of the metaverse. Its potential goes beyond the gaming sector.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Apecoin Is Dependent on Too Much Going the Right Way</h3>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://www.yuga.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Apecoin</u></a> will serve as the native currency of Yuga Labs&rsquo; upcoming Otherside metaverse world project. That&rsquo;s why Apecoin has managed to hold a relatively high market cap.</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, if anything goes wrong with Otherside &ndash; such as not having many users at launch or experiencing delays &ndash; then Apecoin will suffer. The same is true of the Bored Ape Yacht Club ecosystem in general.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This means that Apecoin is too dependent on other projects to succeed on its own. It&rsquo;s important to remember this while making an Apecoin price prediction.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Metacade (MCADE) seems to be the better investment opportunity</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Given everything this article has covered, it should be easier to see why the Apecoin price prediction is lower than the prediction for MCADE. Metacade offers a vast range of utilities across its platform and a potentially massive combined target audience from an exploding gaming sector. A platform with a variety of gaming experiences is much more likely to capture and successfully retain users at a significantly higher rate than a single-title experience.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The project&rsquo;s presale pricing began at 125 MCADE for $1 and will gradually increase in price to 50 MCADE for $1 by the time it ends. Metacade and its MCADE token stand to become one of the very best investments of 2023 and beyond. Potential investors should get into it before the hordes descend. The earlier a solid investment is made, the greater the potential to profit.</p>
<p><strong>You can participate in the Metacade pre-sale&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://metacade.co/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong><u>here</u></strong></a><strong>.</strong></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-vs-apecoin-mcade-likely-to-overtake-ape-in-2023/">Metacade vs Apecoin: MCADE likely to overtake APE in 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-vs-apecoin-mcade-likely-to-overtake-ape-in-2023/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The rising need for sound currency systems could ignite the next bull run, says OKCoin&#8217;s CEO</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/the-rising-need-for-sound-currency-systems-could-ignite-the-next-bull-run-says-okcoins-ceo/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/the-rising-need-for-sound-currency-systems-could-ignite-the-next-bull-run-says-okcoins-ceo/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 10:01:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Interview]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OKCoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/the-rising-need-for-sound-currency-systems-could-ignite-the-next-bull-run-says-okcoins-ceo/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>OKCoin&#8217;s CEO believes that the rising need for sound currency systems could result in the next bull run. More countries will follow El Salvador&#8217;s footsteps and adopt digital currencies, the CEO added. The next Bitcoin halving in 2024 could also trigger a surge in crypto prices. Three catalysts could ignite the next bull run Okcoin [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-rising-need-for-sound-currency-systems-could-ignite-the-next-bull-run-says-okcoins-ceo/">The rising need for sound currency systems could ignite the next bull run, says OKCoin&#8217;s CEO</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">OKCoin&rsquo;s CEO believes that the rising need for sound currency systems could result in the next bull run.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">More countries will follow El Salvador&rsquo;s footsteps and adopt digital currencies, the CEO added.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The next Bitcoin halving in 2024 could also trigger a surge in crypto prices.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Three catalysts could ignite the next bull run</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Okcoin CEO Hong Fang, revealed in a&nbsp;<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sRJDlDOUopY" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>recent interview</u></a>, that he believes three catalysts could trigger the next Bitcoin bull run. He mentioned this while talking to Kitco News earlier this week.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to Fang, the rising need for sound currency systems, caused by the failures of current centralised monetary systems, could serve as a catalyst for the next crypto bull market.</p>
<p dir="ltr">He added that he envisions a scenario where more countries will follow El Salvador&rsquo;s footsteps and make Bitcoin a legal tender. Fang said;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;I think from a macro perspective, we continue to see challenges out there&hellip; I think the World Bank recently came out saying that a dozen countries may default on their own country&rsquo;s debt next year, which is a failure of a centralized monetary system. I would suspect that the fundamental need for a more sound money will continue to build in the background, something like El Salvador, but maybe of a larger size.&rdquo;</em></p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Bitcoin halving could trigger the next bull cycle</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">According to Fang, the next&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/halvening-explained-infographic/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Bitcoin halving</u></a> event in 2024 could also trigger a bull cycle. He stated that;</p>
<p><em>&ldquo;Bitcoin has its own [halving] cycle. I don&rsquo;t know if it&rsquo;s coincidental that the past crypto cycles have somewhat coincided with the Bitcoin [halving] cycle, but that may also be another catalyst&hellip;I think the third potential catalyst is real projects. Every time we have a bull market with Bitcoin, with DeFi [decentralized finance] and NFTs [non-fungible tokens], that was because a lot of builders, they built projects in the last bear market. So I think that all of the projects that are being built right now, when there is a little more substance that can be felt by the customers that they tend to serve, [it] will trigger another bull market.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p>The leading cryptocurrency has been underperforming in recent months, with the&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>price of Bitcoin</u></a> now close to the $17k mark.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-rising-need-for-sound-currency-systems-could-ignite-the-next-bull-run-says-okcoins-ceo/">The rising need for sound currency systems could ignite the next bull run, says OKCoin&#8217;s CEO</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/the-rising-need-for-sound-currency-systems-could-ignite-the-next-bull-run-says-okcoins-ceo/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The new FTX management has located $1B in assets, including $720M cash</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/the-new-ftx-management-has-located-1b-in-assets-including-720m-cash/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/the-new-ftx-management-has-located-1b-in-assets-including-720m-cash/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 09:54:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/the-new-ftx-management-has-located-1b-in-assets-including-720m-cash/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Poor record keeping is making the unwinding of the collapse FTX exchange difficult. The new FTX management is trying to trace millions of dollars from several bank accounts. So far, the new management has identified over $1 billion. FTX&#8217;s new management, which took over from the founder Sam Bankman-Fried, on Tuesday told a procedural hearing [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-new-ftx-management-has-located-1b-in-assets-including-720m-cash/">The new FTX management has located $1B in assets, including $720M cash</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Poor record keeping is making the unwinding of the collapse FTX exchange difficult.</li>
<li>The new FTX management is trying to trace millions of dollars from several bank accounts.</li>
<li>So far, the new management has identified over $1 billion.</li>
</ul>
<p>FTX&rsquo;s new management, which took over from the founder Sam Bankman-Fried, on Tuesday told a procedural hearing that it has identified assets worth more than $1 billion since it <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ftx-begins-strategic-review-of-all-company-assets/">started a strategic review of its assets</a>. It also said that it had located about $720 million held by US financial institutions, which it is yet to consolidate.</p>
<p>The US financial institutions were authorized to hold funds by the US Department of Justice and about $500 million are already confirmed held in US institutions.</p>
<p>The new FTX chief financial officer (CFO), Mary Cilia speaking under oath during the bankruptcy hearings said:</p>
<p><em>&ldquo;We are reaching out to all of those banks and changing the signatories on the accounts so that we can get access to the accounts and move the cash as much as we can to authorized depository institutions.&rdquo;</em></p>
<h2>$423 million held at a single broker</h2>
<p>The CFO also mentioned that about $423 million held by US authorities are from a single broker though she never mentioned the broker by name. Cilia said, &ldquo;$485 million are already in an authorized deposit institution&rdquo;</p>
<p>Besides the funds held in the US, there is about $130 million in cash that is locked up in Japan where local authorities have ring-fenced the funds for local customers.</p>
<p>Steve Coverick, a senior director at FTX&rsquo;s financial advisors Alvarez &amp; Marsal told the hearing that the new management is working to identify FTX&rsquo;s international crypto assets and transfer them to cold wallets using custodial providers like <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ftx-to-hire-bitgo-to-safeguard-its-assets-during-bankruptcy/">Bitgo, which FTX hired in November</a>.</p>
<h2>Difficulties in winding up FTX</h2>
<p>While the Chapter 11 bankruptcy hearings are supposed to wind up the FTX exchange, there have been complications due to poor record keeping and weak governance under the former CEO, SBF. The new management is being forced to look for details by reviewing customer terms and conditions stored in a variety of places including Slack and Google Drive.</p>
<p>As a result, the exchange is yet to file a statement of its financial position or of its assets as required under the US bankruptcy law. It however estimates it could do so in April next year.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-new-ftx-management-has-located-1b-in-assets-including-720m-cash/">The new FTX management has located $1B in assets, including $720M cash</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/the-new-ftx-management-has-located-1b-in-assets-including-720m-cash/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>OKB surges by 4% after OKX announces the listing of rival BNB token</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/okb-surges-by-4-after-okx-announces-the-listing-of-rival-bnb-token/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/okb-surges-by-4-after-okx-announces-the-listing-of-rival-bnb-token/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 09:43:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/okb-surges-by-4-after-okx-announces-the-listing-of-rival-bnb-token/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>OKX has listed BNB token, the native token of its rival exchange Binance, on its platform.&#160; OKB is up by more than 4%, outperforming the other major cryptocurrencies. The broader cryptocurrency market has been underperforming after a positive start to the week. BNB is now live on the OKX exchange OKX, one of the leading [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/okb-surges-by-4-after-okx-announces-the-listing-of-rival-bnb-token/">OKB surges by 4% after OKX announces the listing of rival BNB token</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">OKX has listed BNB token, the native token of its rival exchange Binance, on its platform.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">OKB is up by more than 4%, outperforming the other major cryptocurrencies.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The broader cryptocurrency market has been underperforming after a positive start to the week.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>BNB is now live on the OKX exchange</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/okx-review-a-one-stop-platform-for-crypto-defi-dapps-nfts-and-gamefi/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>OKX</u></a>, one of the leading cryptocurrency exchanges in the world, announced a few hours ago that it had <a href="https://www.okx.com/support/hc/en-us/articles/11602083672205" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>listed BNB trading pairs</u></a> on its platform. BNB is the native token of <a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/binance/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Binance</u></a>, one of OKX&rsquo;s major rivals.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The BNB (BNB/USDT and BNB/USDC) trading pairs are now available on the OKX spot trading platform. This <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>latest cryptocurrency news</u></a> has pushed OKB up by more than 4% in the last 24 hours, making it the best performer amongst the top 50 cryptocurrencies by market cap.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&nbsp;The broader cryptocurrency market has retreated after a positive start to the week. The total crypto market cap is down by less than 1% and currently stands below $810 billion.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin is up by less than 1% but continues to struggle to move past the $17k resistance level.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Key levels to watch</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The OKB/USDT 4-hour chart has turned positive, as OKB has been performing well over the last 24 hours. The technical indicators show that OKB&rsquo;s performance could improve in the near term.</p>
<div class="fr-img-space-wrap"><span class="fr-img-caption fr-fic fr-dib fr-draggable fr-fil" style="width: 600px"><span class="fr-img-wrap">
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2022/11/21/1671615628058-be114cc1-86c5-4b99-a6bc-b383aa94db62.png" style="width: 600px" class="fr-fic fr-dib fr-fil" width="600" height="261"><span class="fr-inner"><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/OKBUSDT/?exchange=OKX"><u>OKB/USDT Chart By TradingView</u></a></span></p>
<p></p></span></span>
<p class="fr-img-space-wrap2">&nbsp;</p>
</div>
<p dir="ltr">The 14-day RSI of 57 shows that OKB is neutral at the moment but could enter the overbought region if the rally continues. The MACD line just crossed into the positive line, indicating that the bulls have taken control of the OKB market.</p>
<p dir="ltr">At press time, OKB is trading at $22.592. If the bullish trend continues, OKB could surge past the $24.245 resistance level before the end of the day. The positive trend could continue over the next few days and rally toward the $26.5 resistance level.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Where to buy OKB now</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    CoinEx</h3>

    <p>Founded in December 2017, CoinEx is a global and professional cryptocurrency exchange service provider. CoinEx supports multiple languages and are providing global trading services in nearly 100 countries/regions.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/coinex-crypto?guid=OTgwMzY&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=CA&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy OKB with CoinEx today            </a>
    </p><h3>
    Swapzone</h3>

    <p>Swapzone is a crypto exchange aggregator that operates as a gateway between the cryptocurrency community and exchange services. Swapzone aims to provide a convenient interface, safe user flow, and crystal-clear data for users to find the best exchange rates among the whole cryptocurrency market.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/swapzone-crypto?guid=OTgwMzY&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=CA&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy OKB with Swapzone today            </a>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/okb-surges-by-4-after-okx-announces-the-listing-of-rival-bnb-token/">OKB surges by 4% after OKX announces the listing of rival BNB token</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/okb-surges-by-4-after-okx-announces-the-listing-of-rival-bnb-token/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Can Alchemy Pay top the $0.0080 resistance level after Weex&#8217;s integration?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/can-alchemy-pay-top-the-0-0080-resistance-level-after-weexs-integration/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/can-alchemy-pay-top-the-0-0080-resistance-level-after-weexs-integration/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 09:41:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/can-alchemy-pay-top-the-0-0080-resistance-level-after-weexs-integration/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>WEEX crypto exchange is set to integrate Alchemy Pay&#8217;s Fiat Onramp Solution. ACH is now up by more than 3% and could rally higher soon. The broader crypto market is trading in the red zone after a positive start to the week. WEEX crypto exchange to integrate Alchemy Pay The Alchemy Pay team announced a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/can-alchemy-pay-top-the-0-0080-resistance-level-after-weexs-integration/">Can Alchemy Pay top the $0.0080 resistance level after Weex&#8217;s integration?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">WEEX crypto exchange is set to integrate Alchemy Pay&rsquo;s Fiat Onramp Solution.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">ACH is now up by more than 3% and could rally higher soon.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The broader crypto market is trading in the red zone after a positive start to the week.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>WEEX crypto exchange to integrate Alchemy Pay</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">The Alchemy Pay team announced a few hours ago that cryptocurrency exchange WEEX is set to integrate its Fiat Onramp Solution. The integration means that WEEX&rsquo;s users can pay with their preferred fiat payment methods directly to buy cryptocurrencies and fund their accounts.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">&#129395; <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/AlchemyPay?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#AlchemyPay</a> Fiat Onramp Solution will be integrated into <a href="https://twitter.com/WEEX_Official?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@WEEX_Official</a> in the near future! </p>
<p>With this collaboration, WEEX's users can pay with their preferred fiat payment methods directly to buy <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/cryptocurrencies?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#cryptocurrencies</a> and fund their accounts.</p>
<p>Stay tuned for the demo! <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24ACH&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$ACH</a> <a href="https://t.co/s0I9rLSILQ">pic.twitter.com/s0I9rLSILQ</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Alchemy Pay: Fiat-Crypto Payment Gateway (@AlchemyPay) <a href="https://twitter.com/AlchemyPay/status/1605086251258114050?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 20, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">This <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>latest cryptocurrency news</u></a> has seen ACH outperform the broader cryptocurrency market. ACH has added more than 3% in the last 24 hours and is now trading at around $0.00784 per coin.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The broader cryptocurrency market is underperforming after a positive start to the week. The total crypto market cap is down by less than 1% and currently stands below $810 billion.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin, the world&rsquo;s leading cryptocurrency by market cap, is still trading in the positive zone. It is up by less than 1%, and the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>price of Bitcoin</u></a> currently stands above $16,800.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Key levels to watch</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The ACH/USD 4-hour chart is still bearish despite Alchemy Pay outperforming the broader market today. However, the technical indicators show that ACH&rsquo;s sentiment is improving.</p>
<div class="fr-img-space-wrap"><span class="fr-img-caption fr-fic fr-dib fr-draggable fr-fil" style="width: 600px"><span class="fr-img-wrap">
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2022/11/21/1671615628056-0862763e-3bee-4083-993b-1da9d01ba4b9.png" style="width: 600px" class="fr-fic fr-dib fr-fil" width="600" height="284"><span class="fr-inner"><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ACHUSD/?exchange=KRAKEN"><u>ACH/USD Chart By TradingView</u></a></span></p>
<p></p></span></span>
<p class="fr-img-space-wrap2">&nbsp;</p>
</div>
<p dir="ltr">The MACD line remains below the neutral zone, indicating that the bears are yet to relinquish control of the ACH market. The 14-day relative strength index of 49 shows that ACH is no longer in the oversold region, and its sentiment has been improving.</p>
<p dir="ltr">If the positive momentum is maintained, ACH could rally past the $0.0080 resistance level before the end of the day.</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, it would need the support of the broader crypto market before it can attempt to reach the $0.0102 psychological level in the near term.</p>
<p></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Where to buy Alchemy Pay now</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    Uphold</h3>

    <p>Uphold is a platform which has over 50 cryptocurrencies to choose from.

It's users can make crypto trades with a bank account, credit card or crypto debit card. It has variable fees and allows users to automate trades.

Users who are on Brave's internet browser can also earn BAT tokens based on their browsing habits.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/uphold-crypto?guid=OTgwMzQ&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=CA&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy ACH with Uphold today            </a>
    </p><h3>
    Swapzone</h3>

    <p>Swapzone is a crypto exchange aggregator that operates as a gateway between the cryptocurrency community and exchange services. Swapzone aims to provide a convenient interface, safe user flow, and crystal-clear data for users to find the best exchange rates among the whole cryptocurrency market.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/swapzone-crypto?guid=OTgwMzQ&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=CA&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy ACH with Swapzone today            </a>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/can-alchemy-pay-top-the-0-0080-resistance-level-after-weexs-integration/">Can Alchemy Pay top the $0.0080 resistance level after Weex&#8217;s integration?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/can-alchemy-pay-top-the-0-0080-resistance-level-after-weexs-integration/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tezos activates the 12th upgrade “Lima”</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/tezos-activates-the-12th-upgrade-lima/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 08:38:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tezos News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/tezos-activates-the-12th-upgrade-lima/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Lima upgrade is the 12th upgrade on the Tezos protocol. Tezos is referred to as the &#8220;self-amending blockchain&#8221; for its ability to seamlessly upgrade using its on-chain governance. Lima upgrade reduces the risk of bugs in smart contracts among other benefits. Tezos, one of the original Proof-of-Stake (PoS) blockchains, has activated its 12th upgrade, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tezos-activates-the-12th-upgrade-lima/">Tezos activates the 12th upgrade “Lima”</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>The Lima upgrade is the 12<sup>th</sup> upgrade on the Tezos protocol.</li>
<li>Tezos is referred to as the &ldquo;self-amending blockchain&rdquo; for its ability to seamlessly upgrade using its on-chain governance.</li>
<li>Lima upgrade reduces the risk of bugs in smart contracts among other benefits.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://coinjournal.net/tezos/what-is-tezos/">Tezos</a>, one of the original <a href="https://coinjournal.net/glossary/proof-of-stake-pos/">Proof-of-Stake (PoS)</a> blockchains, has activated its 12<sup>th</sup> upgrade, the Lima upgrade, which was voted upon and approved by the Tezos community. The new upgrade which introduces several new features also reduces the risk of bugs in smart contracts.</p>
<p>Lima marks the fourth protocol upgrade in 2022 and the 12<sup>th</sup> upgrade since the Tezos protocol was unveiled. Tezos is known for its ability to seamlessly upgrade through its on-chain governances which allows the protocol participants to propose and vote on upgrades and changes that they believe are important for the protocol.</p>
<h2>Key improvements introduced by Lima upgrade</h2>
<p>The Lima upgrade introduces several key improvements to Tezos functionality including faster processing speeds, the introduction of consensus keys, and improvements to tickets.</p>
<p>The Lima upgrade continues with the &lsquo;Pipelining validation project&rsquo; that speeds up the processing of blocks and operations on Tezos by separating validation processes from application processes. A new block on Tezos is first validated before being forwarded to other peers; a feature that speeds up block propagation on the network and reduces the block time to 15 seconds and increases the overall throughput for the blockchain.</p>
<p>The consensus keys will allow validators (known as bakers in Tezos) to designate a special key for signing blocks and consensus operations. This feature prevents backers from losing delegators due to a change in setup or the need to coordinate with delegators <a href="https://coinjournal.net/glossary/off-chain/">off-chain</a> to move them to a new address.</p>
<p>Tickets are a type of data unique to Tezos smart contracts and a great foundation for the scalable solutions that have allowed for many use cases including tokenization, authentication, and voting among others. Lima upgrade in particular deprecates the creation, storage and transfer of zero-amount tickets thus reducing the risk of bugs in smart contracts.</p>
<p>In addition to the improvements to the current Layer 1 Tezos solutions, the Lima upgrade also finalizes the development work towards Smart Rollups, which is an innovative Layer 2 scaling solution that is expected to debut in the subsequent Tezos upgrade proposal.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tezos-activates-the-12th-upgrade-lima/">Tezos activates the 12th upgrade “Lima”</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin price prediction as hopes for a Santa rally fade</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-price-recoils-as-hopes-for-a-santa-rally-fade/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 01:01:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-price-recoils-as-hopes-for-a-santa-rally-fade/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin price has moved sideways in the past few weeks. The Federal Reserve sounded more hawkish than expects. It has formed a rising wedge pattern. Bitcoin price continued recoiling on Monday as investors remained concerned about monetary policy and the crypto industry. The BTC coin was trading at $16,750, where it has been in the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-price-recoils-as-hopes-for-a-santa-rally-fade/">Bitcoin price prediction as hopes for a Santa rally fade</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin price has moved sideways in the past few weeks.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The Federal Reserve sounded more hawkish than expects.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">It has formed a rising wedge pattern.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/what-is-bitcoin/"><u>Bitcoin</u></a> price continued recoiling on Monday as investors remained concerned about monetary policy and the crypto industry. The BTC coin was trading at $16,750, where it has been in the past few days. This price is a few points below last week&rsquo;s high of $16,867.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitcoin price prediction: no Santa rally?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The BTC/USD price has continued consolidating in the past few weeks. After staging a comeback last week, the pair suffered a pullback as investors reflected on the latest Federal Reserve interest rate decision.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In its decision last week, the Fed decided to hike interest rates by 0.50% in its final decision of the year. It had previously increased rates by 75 basis points in the previous four monetary policy meeting. Also, the bank decided to continue with it quantitative tightening policy, as we wrote <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-retreats-below-18k-as-fed-raises-interest-rate-to-a-15-year-high/"><u>here</u></a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The most important change was that the Fed would continue hiking rates in the coming months. That statement helped the market to change its view about monetary policy. Before the meeting, analysts were expecting that the central bank to sound a bit dovish since inflation has started cooling.</p>
<p dir="ltr">After the decision, American and global stocks collapsed while bond yields rose to their highest level in a few week. The US dollar index, which was recently falling, has made a strong recovery in the past few days.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The other main reason why Bitcoin price has been recoiling is the rising outflows from most exchanges. Binance, the biggest exchange in the world, has seen its outflows rise to more than $7.5 billion in the past 7 days. In the same period, Bitfinex has seen over $335 million in outflows while Crypto.com lost over $76 million.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, all these actions mean that the Santa rally has not happened.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitcoin price forecast</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2022/11/19/1671450377573-ab2cf34d-9533-46a2-8688-dbeced009a33.png" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="286" height="318"></p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/?exchange=COINBASE"><u>BTC/USD chart by TradingView</u></a></p>
<p dir="ltr">So, is it safe to <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/buy/"><u>buy Bitcoin</u></a>? The BTC price has been in a tight range in the past few days. In this period, it has remained below the important resistance level at $16,867. It is also consolidating at the 25-day and 50-day moving averages.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">At the same time, the Reltive Strength Index (RSI) has formed a bullish divergence pattern, which is a bullish sign. It has also formed a rising wedge, which is usually a bearish sign. Therefore, there is a likelihood that the coin will have a bearish breakout. If this happens, it could drop to $15,000.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-price-recoils-as-hopes-for-a-santa-rally-fade/">Bitcoin price prediction as hopes for a Santa rally fade</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Apes give up as ApeCoin now stares at a possible drop below $3</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/apes-give-up-as-apecoin-now-stares-at-a-possible-drop-below-3/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/apes-give-up-as-apecoin-now-stares-at-a-possible-drop-below-3/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Motiur Rahman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 21:03:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/apes-give-up-as-apecoin-now-stares-at-a-possible-drop-below-3/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>ApeCoin has lost the battle at the resistance of $4.2 The cryptocurrency has been hit by the general weak crypto sentiment APE could drop to $3 if the bear pressure mounts ApeCoin (APE/USD) traded at $3.5 as the cryptocurrency came under bear pressure from the $4.2 resistance. Buyers have been defending the $4.2 resistance for [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/apes-give-up-as-apecoin-now-stares-at-a-possible-drop-below-3/">Apes give up as ApeCoin now stares at a possible drop below $3</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">ApeCoin has lost the battle at the resistance of $4.2</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The cryptocurrency has been hit by the general weak crypto sentiment</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">APE could drop to $3 if the bear pressure mounts</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">ApeCoin (APE/USD) traded at $3.5 as the cryptocurrency came under bear pressure from the $4.2 resistance. Buyers have been defending the $4.2 resistance for some time, giving hopes of a potential breakout and the start of a bull market. Apes seem to have now been defeated as the cryptocurrency looks at a possible decline to $3.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Recent strengths in ApeCoin coincided with the launch of the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/glossary/staking/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>staking</u></a> feature earlier this month. Despite witnessing a lot of success, the users of the staking service have been warned of numerous phishing attacks. Horizen Lab, the developer of the staking feature, has told users to only use the official link,<em>&nbsp;ApeStake.io,</em> for the service.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Nonetheless, from the price outlook, APE seems to be getting hit by the overall crypto sentiment. The decline comes despite Ape-coin-linked NFTs continuing to record leading sales volumes. A technical outlook shows APE still trapped in a descending channel.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>APE slides from $4.2 resistance as weakness develop</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2022/11/20/1671570146723-d0f47cbd-cfbd-48b5-afc2-3246bee8baf4.png" style="width: 600px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="600" height="286"></p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/APEUSD/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>APE/USD Chart by TradingView</u></a></p>
<p dir="ltr">APE initiated a bearish MACD crossover on the daily chart. The indicator has shifted to the negative territory after the latest price decline.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The cryptocurrency now trades below $4.2 resistance after bears took control. APE price has now crashed back to the descending channel. The price is gaining stability at $3.5, but the established support lies at $3.0.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Concluding thoughts&nbsp;</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">If bulls do not take control of APE at $3.5, the next decline could take the cryptocurrency to $3.0.&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/apecoin/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>APE price</u></a> must overcome resistance at $4.2 and the descending channel to become bullish.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Where to buy APE&nbsp;</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>

    <p>eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=OTgwMTQ&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=CA&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy APE with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    Public</h3>

    <p>Public is an investing platform that allows you to invest stocks, ETFs, crypto, and alternative assets like fine art and collectibles&mdash;all in one place.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/public-crypto?guid=OTgwMTQ&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=CA&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy APE with Public today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptocurrency execution and custody services are provided by Apex Crypto LLC (NMLS ID 1828849) through a software licensing agreement between Apex Crypto LLC and Public Crypto LLC. Crypto trading on Public platforms is served by Public Crypto LLC and offered through APEX Crypto. Please ensure that you fully understand the risks involved before trading." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/apes-give-up-as-apecoin-now-stares-at-a-possible-drop-below-3/">Apes give up as ApeCoin now stares at a possible drop below $3</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/apes-give-up-as-apecoin-now-stares-at-a-possible-drop-below-3/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
