<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 17:13:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Get Ready for the Next 100x Opportunity With Metacade (MCADE)</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/get-ready-for-the-next-100x-opportunity-with-metacade-mcade/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/get-ready-for-the-next-100x-opportunity-with-metacade-mcade/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice Davies]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 17:13:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/get-ready-for-the-next-100x-opportunity-with-metacade-mcade/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The metaverse industry has felt the brunt of the long-term bearish crypto market conditions during 2022, with several leading metaverse coins sinking alarmingly in value. The good news is that some new metaverse projects are bucking the trend and performing bullishly. One such newcomer to the metaverse industry is Metacade, which has the target to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/get-ready-for-the-next-100x-opportunity-with-metacade-mcade/">Get Ready for the Next 100x Opportunity With Metacade (MCADE)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">The metaverse industry has felt the brunt of the long-term bearish crypto market conditions during 2022, with several leading metaverse coins sinking alarmingly in value. The good news is that some new metaverse projects are bucking the trend and performing bullishly.</p>
<p dir="ltr">One such newcomer to the metaverse industry is Metacade, which has the target to become the leading blockchain GameFi provider over the next year with their virtual video game arcade. Their presale performance has led to predictions that their MCADE token could be the next to provide investors with 100x gains.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>MCADE could turn out the be the buy of the year</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade had captured the imagination of GameFi fans and crypto investors before the presale launched in November 2022. The hype around the blockchain play-to-earn (P2E) gaming platform is fully justified. The beta presale of the MCADE token sold out within three weeks of release, raising well over $1.6 million in the process.</p>
<p dir="ltr">With the value of MCADE tokens set to rise throughout each phase of the presale stage from its beta price of $0.008 each to $0.02 by the time the ninth and final stage concludes, handsome returns are on offer for the bullish early investor. Thousands have already flocked to Metacade to maximize their gains MCADE goes public on decentralized exchanges (DEX) after the presale ends.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade&rsquo;s attractive <a href="https://metacade.co/whitepaper.pdf" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>white paper</u></a> shows the depth of the platform&rsquo;s plans, extending well beyond just being a traditional P2E platform. These plans that offer ground-breaking and ultimately lead to a transition to a fully-fledged and self-governing decentralized autonomous organization (DAO) by Q4 2024 have led to experts predicting that Metacade could be the next metaverse project to achieve 100x gains for investors in 2023.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>How high could MCADE go in 2023?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">The value of MCADE is already guaranteed to increase with each phase of the Metacade presale. When MCADE hits the&nbsp;<a href="https://global.bittrex.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Bittrex Exchange&nbsp;</u></a>for global public consumption, the token price will be $0.02, offering some of the best value within the metaverse industry.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade has a total fixed supply of two billion MCADE tokens. This increased exposure of MCADE tokens on public exchanges, combined with the momentum built up over the token&rsquo;s presale, is expected to result in a surge in price as demand increases significantly. Existing token holders that got in early during the presale will likely hold onto their shareholding, expecting the price to skyrocket, leading to potentially rich gains.</p>
<p dir="ltr">MCADE&rsquo;s built-in utility, the flourishing platform roadmap, and multi-layered features mean that the price could exceed the $1 mark in 2023. This can lead to potential 100x gains for those shrewd investors that took advantage of the undervalued presale MCADE price.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>What is Metacade?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://metacade.co/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade</u></a> uses Ethereum blockchain technology and cutting-edge Web3 development techniques to build the metaverse industry&rsquo;s leading virtual video arcade. The arcade promises an ever-evolving and increasing library of play-to-earn (P2E) titles offering GameFi players the opportunity to access addictive games from classic arcade titles of yesteryear to brand new titles developed exclusively for Metacade.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Other features of Metacade are what truly sets it apart from rival GameFi titles, adding several layers of depth rarely found in the metaverse gaming industry. From the innovative Metagrants initiative launching in Q3 2023 to several opportunities to earn additional passive income streams.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The transition to becoming a complete DAO, handing over critical roles, responsibilities, and control of the multi-signatory treasury wallet to community members, begins in Q2 2023, ahead of the conclusion by the end of 2024. By this point, complete control of the platform&rsquo;s governance and future development will be in the hands of the users.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>How does it work?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">While prominent, the P2E element of the platform is only one strand of Metacade&rsquo;s appeal. Users have additional routes to earn income through their Create2Earn, Compete2Earn, and Work2Earn schemes. MCADE token holders will gain rewards for social interactions with the platform, such as writing game reviews and sharing GameFi knowledge, by staking tokens to enter tournaments and prize draws and, from Q1 2024, through applying for Web3 employment opportunities posted on the jobs board.</p>
<p dir="ltr">These rewards, along with the brand new Metagrants program, will be entirely self-funded through multiple internal and income streams. These include access to pay-to-play titles, selling advertising space on the platform, and charging for external companies to post job adverts and release their own game titles on Metacade.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Metacade: Promoting GameFi development</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade aims to lead the metaverse industry in GameFi development through its Metagrants scheme. This program allows budding developers to present proposals to receive funding to support the development of new exclusive titles. MCADE token holders vote for these proposals, with the most successful ideas receiving funding to create new blockchain games.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Is Metacade worth the investment?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade has already set the metaverse industry alight with its presale performance. While the opportunity to invest at the lowest possible value has gone after the beta phase sold out so quickly, there is room for excellent gains by investing now at the current price of $0.01.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The earlier investors purchase their MCADE tokens, the better their chance of reaping up to 100x gains as the Metacade hype hits the open markets. With a robust roadmap and future alongside the momentum of a highly prosperous presale performance, the outlook for Metacade is exceptionally favorable for 2023 and beyond.</p>
<p><strong>You can participate in the MCADE presale&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://metacade.co/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong><u>here</u></strong></a><strong>.</strong></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/get-ready-for-the-next-100x-opportunity-with-metacade-mcade/">Get Ready for the Next 100x Opportunity With Metacade (MCADE)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/get-ready-for-the-next-100x-opportunity-with-metacade-mcade/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Outlook 2030: Why You Should Invest in Cardano (ADA), Solana (SOL), and Metacade (MCADE)</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-outlook-2030-why-you-should-invest-in-cardano-ada-solana-sol-and-metacade-mcade/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-outlook-2030-why-you-should-invest-in-cardano-ada-solana-sol-and-metacade-mcade/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice Davies]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 17:06:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-outlook-2030-why-you-should-invest-in-cardano-ada-solana-sol-and-metacade-mcade/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The crypto market is constantly evolving, making it tricky to know which coins are worth investing in for the long term. In this article, you&#8217;ll discover three crypto tokens with plenty of promise and a strong potential for future growth. They are Cardano (ADA), Solana (SOL), and an up-and-comer known as Metacade (MCADE). Why Invest [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-outlook-2030-why-you-should-invest-in-cardano-ada-solana-sol-and-metacade-mcade/">Crypto Outlook 2030: Why You Should Invest in Cardano (ADA), Solana (SOL), and Metacade (MCADE)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">The crypto market is constantly evolving, making it tricky to know which coins are worth investing in for the long term. In this article, you&rsquo;ll discover three crypto tokens with plenty of promise and a strong potential for future growth. They are Cardano (ADA), Solana (SOL), and an up-and-comer known as Metacade (MCADE).</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Why Invest in Cardano (ADA)?</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://cardano.org/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Cardano</u></a> is one of the leading layer-1 solutions, currently ranked ninth in the list of the top cryptocurrencies by market cap. While it performs much of the same function as Ethereum, Cardano sets itself apart in a few ways that make it an attractive investment.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The first is its academic-based approach. Each upgrade undergoes rigorous academic testing before being rolled out. For example, its consensus protocol, Ouroboros, is mathematically secure and, as a result, well-hardened against attack.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Secondly, Cardano is making some significant changes to its network in 2023. It&rsquo;s launching the Djed stablecoin, which will likely accelerate Cardano&rsquo;s growing position in the DeFi space. Cardano developers are also expected to implement Hydra and Midnight soon. Hydra is a scaling solution that could one day enable the network to one day to achieve 1 million transactions per second (TPS). Midnight is a protocol designed around privacy regulations.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Cardano (ADA) Crypto Outlook 2030</h2>
<p dir="ltr">These upcoming upgrades have undoubtedly strengthened the ADA crypto outlook for 2030. Fundamental factors, like its rigorous approach to innovation, rockstar development team, and strategic alliances, only boost Cardano&rsquo;s long-term potential. In 2030, ADA will likely be worth somewhere between $6.50 and $11, depending on how the future plays out. This is well above ADA&rsquo;s current price of $0.27.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Why Invest in Solana (SOL)?</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://solana.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Solana</u></a>, like Cardano, is a layer-1 solution that aims to rival Ethereum&rsquo;s dominance. It&rsquo;s currently the world&rsquo;s 17th most valuable cryptocurrency, falling from the top ten after FTX&rsquo;s collapse.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Despite taking a beating recently, Solana&rsquo;s fundamentals haven&rsquo;t changed. In fact, its core aspects and future developments could be the catalyst for much higher prices. For instance, Solana is one of the fastest and cheapest blockchains on the planet, able to handle up to 65,000 TPS at a negligible cost.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Firedancer, a new validator client built by Jump Crypto to improve efficiency on the Solana network, has been shown to be capable of handling 600,000 TPS in a test environment. This is much higher than Ethereum&rsquo;s expected TPS of 100,000 once sharding is implemented later this year.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Moreover, the Solana Saga smartphone, expected soon, could prompt a new wave of adoption for Solana. The Saga &ldquo;sets a new standard for the Web3 experience on mobile,&rdquo; and developers will be given all the tools they need to develop Web3-ready mobile apps, according to a blog post by Solana Mobile.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Solana (SOL) Crypto Outlook 2030</h2>
<p dir="ltr">While Solana isn&rsquo;t as popular as Cardano, the network seems to have a bright future. By 2030, SOL will likely be worth at least $450, with optimistic estimates putting the token between $600 and $750. If SOL reaches $450, investors that bought in at today&rsquo;s price of $13 would be up over 3,300%!</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Why Invest in Metacade (MCADE)?&nbsp;</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade</u></a> is a play-to-earn (P2E) community hub that&rsquo;s aiming to become a focal point of the GameFi revolution. It&rsquo;s a platform where users can link up with like-minded gamers, discover how to make the most of the latest P2E games, and even play a part in producing the games they&rsquo;ll be playing.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Community-based features, like forums, live chats, reviews, competitions, and tournaments, have the potential to attract thousands of players looking for a place to call home in the nascent GameFi space. There are even MCADE rewards offered to players posting reviews, tips, and other content for the community to learn from.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Later this year, Metacade is expecting to give away its first Metagrant. Metagrants are a way for the Metacade community to direct funding toward developers building the P2E games players are most excited about playing. To receive them, developers simply submit their ideas and whoever earns the most votes for their project is awarded funding. The finished title is added to Metacade&rsquo;s virtual arcade, sporting dozens of other community-backed and classic games.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">With plans for a decentralized autonomous organization (DAO), a job and gig board, and several big-ticket giveaways, it&rsquo;s safe to say that Metacade is putting the players first. Given that GameFi is expected to explode at 10x the rate of traditional gaming by 2025 (<a href="https://crypto.com/research/gamefi-past-present-and-future-overview-traditional-gaming-industry" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Crypto.com</u></a>), Metacade could be the best performer out of the three cryptos discussed here by 2030.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Metacade (MCADE) Crypto Outlook 2030</h2>
<p dir="ltr">With these aspects in mind, Metacade could quickly become Web3&rsquo;s number one community space for P2E gaming. Its long-term crypto outlook looks positive, with MCADE expected to reach at least $2 by 2030 &ndash; a 9,900% return on its final presale price of $0.02. If users flock to the platform as expected, then MCADE could be worth as much as $25 by the end of this decade, meaning investors that got involved in presale could be up 24,900%!</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Which Token Should You Invest In?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">It&rsquo;s clear to see that these three cryptocurrencies have the potential to rocket in the coming years. But, after examining each, Metacade takes the lead when it comes to projected long-term returns.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">With the MCADE token still in presale and a community-first philosophy, Metacade is likely to be a massive hit with investors. In fact, over $2.2m of MCADE has been sold so far, and this number is expected to keep rising. If you&rsquo;re looking for a token with one of the strongest crypto outlooks on the market, check out the MCADE presale immediately!</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>You can buy Solana (SOL) and Cardano (ADA) at eToro&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://coinjournal.net/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=OTk0NDg" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong><u>here</u></strong></a><strong>.</strong></p>
<p><strong>You can participate in the Metacade presale&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong><u>here</u></strong></a><strong>.</strong></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-outlook-2030-why-you-should-invest-in-cardano-ada-solana-sol-and-metacade-mcade/">Crypto Outlook 2030: Why You Should Invest in Cardano (ADA), Solana (SOL), and Metacade (MCADE)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-outlook-2030-why-you-should-invest-in-cardano-ada-solana-sol-and-metacade-mcade/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Best Altcoins for 2023 That Could Make You a Fortune</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/best-altcoins-for-2023-that-could-make-you-a-fortune/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/best-altcoins-for-2023-that-could-make-you-a-fortune/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice Davies]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 16:50:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Link]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/best-altcoins-for-2023-that-could-make-you-a-fortune/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The best altcoins often make insane gains for investors. To make the most out of the return potential, it is always best to buy altcoins during their earliest stages; however, there are also some established altcoins that look like great investments over the coming years. Here are the top five best altcoins for 2023: Metacade [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/best-altcoins-for-2023-that-could-make-you-a-fortune/">Best Altcoins for 2023 That Could Make You a Fortune</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">The best altcoins often make insane gains for investors. To make the most out of the return potential, it is always best to buy altcoins during their earliest stages; however, there are also some established altcoins that look like great investments over the coming years.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Here are the top five best altcoins for 2023:</p>
<ol>
<li dir="ltr">Metacade (MCADE)</li>
<li dir="ltr">Litecoin (LTC)</li>
<li dir="ltr">The Sandbox (SAND)</li>
<li dir="ltr">XRP (XRP)</li>
<li dir="ltr">ChainLink (LINK)</li>
</ol>
<h2 dir="ltr">1. Metacade (MCADE)</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>Metacade is the first community-driven and biggest decentralized arcade in the world, making its MCADE token the best altcoin for 2023</strong>. The platform offers both casual and competitive gameplay, enabling players to earn cryptocurrency rewards by playing various arcade-style titles.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Built on the Ethereum blockchain, Metacade delivers advanced Play2Earn (P2E) mechanics. Gamers are given more control over their gaming experience and can vote on what new games are launched on the platform through its Metagrants program. The Metagrants scheme will award developers with winning proposals funding to develop their game on the platform. Metacade&rsquo;s community is set to award its first grant in the second half of 2023.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade</u></a> offers some additional user benefits and a variety of ways to earn a crypto income on the platform. The Work2Earn feature will help the Metacade community to launch a career in Web3, as players can access job opportunities with Metacade partners for short-term gigs and freelance positions.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Gamers can also access new titles before they are officially launched through the platform&rsquo;s beta-testing roles. The community can provide feedback to game developers while playing new titles, uncovering and reporting any bugs that need fixing before launch.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade&rsquo;s Create2Earn feature will reward members of the community for providing useful contributions to other members. Rewards are earned for posting game reviews, sharing GameFi alpha, and interacting with other users, as Metacade aims to become a central hub for blockchain gamers over time.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Why buy MCADE?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">The MCADE token recently launched its presale event, which has been a major success. During the start of Metacade&rsquo;s presale 230 million tokens were sold, which raised $2.1 million worth of funding to build the Metacade platform.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>Metacade could become one of the most widely-used GameFi platforms, with a long-term price prediction of over $1 &ndash; a 50x rise from the end of the presale</strong>. Early investors could make serious gains, which is why it is the number one best altcoin for 2023 and beyond.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>&gt;&gt;&gt; You can participate in the Metacade presale&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong><u>here</u></strong></a><strong>&nbsp;&lt;&lt;&lt;</strong></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">2. Litecoin (LTC)</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The second best altcoin for 2023 is Litecoin &ndash; a cryptocurrency created as a Bitcoin fork. It is often referred to as the silver to Bitcoin&rsquo;s gold, delivering much of the same functionality but with improved scalability.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Litecoin can achieve block finality in 3.5 minutes &ndash; significantly faster than Bitcoin&rsquo;s ten minutes. The project refers to itself as the second most popular pure cryptocurrency, as its core function is to send money over the internet using a secure, transparent, and trustless blockchain.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Unlike other blockchains, Litecoin does not support the development of decentralized applications (dApps). Instead, the LTC token focuses solely on being a medium of exchange for individuals and merchants worldwide.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Over 2000 shops and other retailers accept LTC for payments, as it has been a reliable method for processing peer-to-peer transactions since its inception in 2011. Litecoin is one of the original cryptocurrencies, being created just 2 years after Bitcoin&rsquo;s genesis block was mined.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Why buy LTC?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">The core team behind the Litecoin project are experienced developers with distinguished careers, with Charlie Lee being the founder. The team continues to build in the Litecoin ecosystem with the aim of making LTC an alternative payment method to BTC that is better suited to day-to-day use.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/litecoin-ltc-rises-4-4-as-mimblewimble-takes-effect/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>The Mimblewimble Extension Block (MWEB)</u></a> went live on the Litecoin network in early 2022, which was touted as the biggest upgrade to the blockchain since it was first launched. The upgrade improves Litecoin&rsquo;s scalability and can help LTC to become a cash-like cryptocurrency.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The LTC price is currently $62.59. It has an all-time high of over $400 and has the potential to breach $1000 in value over time. At the current price level, LTC is one of the best altcoins for 2023 as it shows major promise for the future of decentralized finance (DeFi).</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">3. The Sandbox (SAND)</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The Sandbox is the third-best altcoin for 2023. The project is an open-world metaverse game that allows users to build their own gaming experiences. Players can buy, sell, and create digital assets that can then be monetized within The Sandbox gameworld.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The project prioritizes user-generated content (<a href="https://hotplay.games/why-user-generated-content-ugc-can-be-the-future-of-gaming/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>UGC</u></a>) at the foundation of the game. By allowing users to create their own games in The Sandbox, the scope and scale of the virtual landscape are constantly evolving. Users can explore this landscape and participate in a variety of different pastimes, as well as earn crypto tokens in P2E games that other users have built.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>The Sandbox provides a toolkit to allow users to create games with customizable rulesets</strong>. This allows anyone to become a game developer with little to no programming experience, which can help to boost the overall level of innovation in GameFi over time.</p>
<p dir="ltr">All games can be minted as NFTs and sold on the platform&rsquo;s marketplace using SAND tokens. SAND can also be used to purchase other gaming assets, such as character upgrades and other unique items. The level of customizability that players can get while playing The Sandbox is a primary reason for its popularity.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Why buy SAND?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">The Sandbox is one of the most widely-used blockchain games, with the SAND token regularly being the top metaverse project by market capitalization. Gameplay has been compared to Minecraft, the most purchased PC game of all time.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The popularity of UGC as a gameplay feature is reflected in the early successes of The Sandbox. Over time, the project is expected to grow as the wider GameFi sector becomes more popular among mainstream users.</p>
<p dir="ltr">SAND is currently worth $0.40, down from its all-time high of $7.50. The token has the potential to rise significantly in value over time, which makes it one of the best altcoins for 2023.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">4. XRP (XRP)</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The fourth best altcoin for 2023 is XRP &ndash; a decentralized cryptocurrency that can provide instant liquidity for international settlements. Ripple, the parent company of the XRP cryptocurrency, has formed major partnerships with financial institutions to develop solutions for global transactions using digital assets in various ways.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The XRP token can facilitate near-instant global transactions at almost zero cost to the sender. This represents a major improvement on traditional finance, which typically takes days to confirm cross-border payments and charges a premium for large transaction processing.</p>
<p dir="ltr">For this reason, XRP and other digital assets can reasonably improve the level of efficiency for traditional financial operations. This is the utility being promised by Ripple, which is the foundation of its partnerships with major institutions such as JP Morgan, Santander, and <a href="https://www.bankofengland.co.uk/research/fintech/proofs-of-concept/ripple" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>the Bank of England</u></a>.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Why buy XRP?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">XRP has been the subject of a long-term court case with the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). The case against XRP sets out to prove that the token is a security instead of a cryptocurrency; however, it is widely expected that XRP wins the case and gains regulatory approval as a cryptocurrency.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The price of XRP was likely held back during the 2021 bull market due to its ongoing case with the SEC. XRP still remains in the top 10 cryptocurrencies to this day and has a market capitalization of almost $20 billion during the bear market.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>The SEC case is expected to end in 2023, with XRP emerging as a legitimate cryptocurrency in the eyes of US prosecutors</strong>. XRP could skyrocket in value after this point, which makes it one of the best altcoins for 2023.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">5. ChainLink (LINK)</h2>
<p dir="ltr">ChainLink is the fifth-best altcoin for 2023. It is a multichain oracle that records data from multiple blockchains, enabling secure interoperability between different networks and helping dApps to share and use data from various off-chain sources.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The protocol enables smart contracts to be read and deployed across different blockchain ecosystems, and stores data from off-chain in a transparent, automatically-updating oracle built on-chain. The oracle can be used to instantly share data that can be used with various applications, such as decentralized exchanges (DEXs) and more.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The off-chain data recorded on ChainLink allows developers to utilize more information in smart contracts and increase the complexity of dApps. ChainLink is one of the most widely used oracle solutions, providing services to major crypto platforms, including Aave and Huobi.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Why buy LINK?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">LINK is the native token for the ChainLink ecosystem. The token represents a stake in the protocol, as investors can purchase the token as an investment, store of value, or to send money across the world on a number of different blockchains.</p>
<p dir="ltr">ChainLink also plans to introduce staking for the LINK token, which will increase utility in the future. The staking service will provide passive rewards to validators for securing the network infrastructure.</p>
<p dir="ltr">LINK is currently priced at $5.71, with an all-time high of over $50. The token is expected to reclaim its previous highs and produce major gains over the coming years. For this reason, it is one of the best altcoins for 2023 at the current price level.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Metacade: The best altcoin for 2023</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade</u></a> is, without doubt, the best altcoin for 2023. After rapidly selling 140m MCADE tokens during the beta round, the MCADE token is expected to sell out every other phase of the presale. The event will see the price of MCADE rise from $0.008 to $0.02 per token, which gives investors a limited time to get involved at the current price of $0.01.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The project offers unique functions to Web3 users and a host of different methods for earning an income paid in crypto. Metacade has the potential to become one of the biggest GameFi platforms around, so investors need to be quick to acquire the best altcoin for 2023 before the presale sells out.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>You can buy the crypto coins on this list at eToro&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://coinjournal.net/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=OTk0NDU" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong><u>here</u></strong></a><strong>.</strong></p>
<p><strong>You can participate in the Metacade presale&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong><u>here</u></strong></a><strong>.</strong></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/best-altcoins-for-2023-that-could-make-you-a-fortune/">Best Altcoins for 2023 That Could Make You a Fortune</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/best-altcoins-for-2023-that-could-make-you-a-fortune/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>If You Think DOGE Is Worth the Hype After Musk’s Twitter Acquisition, Take a Closer Look at Metacade, Which Has Generated $2 Million in Presale So Far</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/if-you-think-doge-is-worth-the-hype-after-musks-twitter-acquisition-take-a-closer-look-at-metacade-which-has-generated-2-million-in-presale-so-far/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/if-you-think-doge-is-worth-the-hype-after-musks-twitter-acquisition-take-a-closer-look-at-metacade-which-has-generated-2-million-in-presale-so-far/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice Davies]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 16:12:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elon Musk]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/if-you-think-doge-is-worth-the-hype-after-musks-twitter-acquisition-take-a-closer-look-at-metacade-which-has-generated-2-million-in-presale-so-far/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Just when you thought there couldn&#8217;t be any more hype around Dogecoin (DOGE), Elon Musk&#8217;s Twitter acquisition sent the rumor mill into overdrive again. Could Musk really intend to&#160;incorporate DOGE on Twitter? It&#8217;s an intriguing proposition and one that would have serious &#8211; read upward &#8211; implications for DOGE. But not everyone buys into the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/if-you-think-doge-is-worth-the-hype-after-musks-twitter-acquisition-take-a-closer-look-at-metacade-which-has-generated-2-million-in-presale-so-far/">If You Think DOGE Is Worth the Hype After Musk’s Twitter Acquisition, Take a Closer Look at Metacade, Which Has Generated $2 Million in Presale So Far</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Just when you thought there couldn&rsquo;t be any more hype around Dogecoin (DOGE), Elon Musk&rsquo;s Twitter acquisition sent the rumor mill into overdrive again. Could Musk really intend to&nbsp;<a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/billybambrough/2022/12/06/leaked-twitter-code-reveals-secret-crypto-bombshell-raising-serious-bitcoin-and-dogecoin-questions/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>incorporate DOGE on Twitter</u></a>? It&rsquo;s an intriguing proposition and one that would have serious &ndash; read upward &ndash; implications for DOGE.</p>
<p dir="ltr">But not everyone buys into the hype around DOGE, Musk, and his Twitter acquisition. When all the noise dies down, things could actually go the other way. Musk could return his focus to Tesla and SpaceX. Twitter could lose market share as Twitterati leave the platform in protest at the new owner. And the familiar negatives around DOGE are still there: unlimited token supply, negligible development, minimal functionality, and lack of widespread acceptance for payment.</p>
<p dir="ltr">For those reasons, many investors are looking beyond DOGE and Musk&rsquo;s Twitter acquisition, believing great opportunities lie elsewhere. And that&rsquo;s where Metacade comes in. This GameFi newcomer has created a real buzz in the market, having already generated $2 million in it&rsquo;s presale raise . Read on to learn why so many people believe it&rsquo;s the next crypto-gaming sensation.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Metacade?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">There&rsquo;s a tangible sense of excitement around GameFi newcomer&nbsp;<a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade (MCADE)</u></a>. In a sector where some companies have placed too much emphasis on the &ldquo;Fi&rdquo; and not enough on the &ldquo;Game,&rdquo; Metacade (MCADE) gets the balance just right. It features a stunning selection of futuristic metaverse and virtual games alongside much-loved, classic arcade games. Currently available at a&nbsp;<a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>great presale price</u></a>,&nbsp;<strong>Metacade (MCADE) delivers the ultimate GameFi experience.</strong></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How Metacade Works</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade (MCADE) brings together all sides of the crypto gaming and GameFi industry. Players, designers, developers, crypto fanatics, and investors are all enriched &ndash; literally &ndash; by the connections, synergies, and shared experiences that <a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade (MCADE)</u></a> facilitates. Acting as a Web3 community hub for GameFi, here&rsquo;s how Metacade works:&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>Blockchain gamers</strong> can have fun and generate income from Metacade&rsquo;s Play2Earn, Compete2Earn, Create2Earn, and Work2Earn functionality.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>Designers and developers</strong> can test, showcase, market, and launch new games, organize competitions, communicate directly with players and investors, and recruit new hires.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>Crypto fanatics and investors&nbsp;</strong>can stake MCADE tokens and benefit from exciting investment opportunities.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>Metacade (MCADE)</strong> earns revenues from paid games, advertisements, new game launches, paid tournaments, and job postings.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Alongside its fantastic selection of games, new and old, Metacade (MCADE) is also looking to the future with its Metagrants program. This forward-looking initiative provides funding for the development of the next generation of games on the platform. So Metacade doesn&rsquo;t just host the best games: it&rsquo;s also actively developing the best new ones! What&rsquo;s more, part of the revenues from new games will be fed back into the Metacade community.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Mainstream and social media often focus on bad news stories like the FTX crash or big news events like Elon Musk&rsquo;s Twitter acquisition. That&rsquo;s a shame because it means they miss out on really interesting stories like the huge potential rise of GameFi and companies like Metacade (MCADE).</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Should Investors Choose Metacade Over Dogecoin?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Currently, there aren&rsquo;t too many bright spots in the crypto industry, but the burgeoning P2E sector is an exception to that rule. Many analysts and experts are predicting the market will soar in 2023, giving the crypto market some much-needed good news. <strong>Although Dogecoin (DOGE) got a boost in the aftermath of Musk&rsquo;s Twitter acquisition, it&rsquo;s Metacade (MCADE) in the P2E sector that looks like it could really take the market by storm.</strong></p>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade (MCADE) holds the upper hand for a number of other reasons, too. The supply of MCADE tokens is limited, and they offer greater functionality. Next up, the company has been fully audited by Certik to underpin investor security and safety. And finally, the <a href="https://metacade.co/whitepaper.pdf" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade (MCADE) roadmap</u></a> includes a commitment to becoming a DAO, thus giving community members governance rights and rewards for their involvement in the company.</p>
<p dir="ltr">All that said, the bottom line is that investment is ultimately about making a profit. Again, Metacade (MCADE) has the advantage over Dogecoin (DOGE). New investors can benefit from an early mover advantage and likely a worthwhile return on the attractive Metacade (MCADE) presale price. But it&rsquo;s post-launch that things could get really interesting, with some experts speculating on the prospect of 100x gains or more as P2E really takes off.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Elon Musk is the second richest man in the world, so it&rsquo;s no surprise that his Twitter acquisition and subsequent comments on Dogecoin (DOGE) have driven investors towards this token. But scratch beneath the surface, and it&rsquo;s not so obvious whether DOGE is genuinely worth the hype.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">DOGE or MCADE: The Verdict</h2>
<p dir="ltr">As with everything he says and does, Elon Musk&rsquo;s Twitter acquisition created a media frenzy, including stories about Dogecoin (DOGE). But once everything settled down, the DOGE price is still only showing a small premium since the Twitter take-over. Beyond all the DOGE hype, savvy investors are taking a closer look instead at Metacade (MCADE), especially in light of its impressive presale performance.</p>
<p dir="ltr">But you need to be quick if you want a piece of the action. The first phase of the Metacade (MCADE) presale is nearly sold out, so act now to <a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>buy in at the best price</u></a>.</p>
<p><strong>You can participate in the Metacade presale&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong><u>here</u></strong></a><strong>.</strong></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/if-you-think-doge-is-worth-the-hype-after-musks-twitter-acquisition-take-a-closer-look-at-metacade-which-has-generated-2-million-in-presale-so-far/">If You Think DOGE Is Worth the Hype After Musk’s Twitter Acquisition, Take a Closer Look at Metacade, Which Has Generated $2 Million in Presale So Far</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/if-you-think-doge-is-worth-the-hype-after-musks-twitter-acquisition-take-a-closer-look-at-metacade-which-has-generated-2-million-in-presale-so-far/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>13% of Bitcoin supply in profit as BTC rallies above $18,200</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/13-of-bitcoin-supply-in-profit-as-btc-rallies-above-18200/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/13-of-bitcoin-supply-in-profit-as-btc-rallies-above-18200/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 14:52:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Glassnode]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/13-of-bitcoin-supply-in-profit-as-btc-rallies-above-18200/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin price jumped more than 5% on Thursday to hit levels above $18,400. According to on-chain data from Glassnode, the price rally has helped return 13% more BTC into profit; now 60.5% of circulating supply is in profit. Only 47%-48% of BTC had been in profit between November 2022 and the start of January, 2023. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/13-of-bitcoin-supply-in-profit-as-btc-rallies-above-18200/">13% of Bitcoin supply in profit as BTC rallies above $18,200</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>Bitcoin price jumped more than 5% on Thursday to hit levels above $18,400.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>According to on-chain data from Glassnode, the price rally has helped return 13% more BTC into profit; now 60.5% of circulating supply is in profit.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><strong><em>Only 47%-48% of BTC had been in profit between November 2022 and the start of January, 2023</em></strong>.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a>&rsquo;s breakout to prices above $18,200 has seen 13% more of circulating supply return into profit, on-chain data from Glassnode <a href="https://twitter.com/glassnode/status/1613405398551367681" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">says</a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Per the platform, the sharp surge in percentage of supply in profit amid the latest crypto rally confirms a buy the dip scenario as prices fell in late 2022. Indeed, the metric suggests a large volume of the benchmark cryptocurrency was acquired at prices between $16,500 and $18,200.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">As <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Bitcoin</a> rallies to $18.2k, over 13% of the Circulating Supply has returned to profit.</p>
<p>The observed sharp move upwards in this metric helps to confirm that a large volume of <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24BTC&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$BTC</a> was acquired between $16.5k and $18.2k.<a href="https://t.co/yflZloDbSP">https://t.co/yflZloDbSP</a> <a href="https://t.co/J8egLvYt3w">pic.twitter.com/J8egLvYt3w</a></p>
<p>&mdash; glassnode (@glassnode) <a href="https://twitter.com/glassnode/status/1613405398551367681?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 12, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitcoin supply in profit jumps amid BTC rally</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">Bitcoin price</a> hit lows of $15,600 in November 2022 after a violent market reaction to the collapse of cryptocurrency exchange FTX. The price bounced to above $18,000 in mid-December before bulls hit resistance and BTC tumbled to below $17,000.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The supply in profit or supply in loss metric considers the on-chain history of a coin, determining the price at which it last moved. Coins are in profit if the price at which they last moved is lower than the current price of BTC, while the percent in loss is when the current price of BTC is higher than the value of the coins when they last moved on-chain.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to Glassnode, more than half of Bitcoin circulating supply fell into loss between November and January this year. Approximately 47%-48% of BTC supply was in profit during the period.</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, with 2023 starting positively for cryptocurrencies and BTC&rsquo;s push to highs of $18,420 on 12 January, the percentage of circulating supply on profit has increased to 60.5%.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As of writing, Bitcoin price is 5.2% up in the past 24 hours and data from CoinGecko shows the flagship cryptocurrency has rallied nearly 9% in the past week.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/13-of-bitcoin-supply-in-profit-as-btc-rallies-above-18200/">13% of Bitcoin supply in profit as BTC rallies above $18,200</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/13-of-bitcoin-supply-in-profit-as-btc-rallies-above-18200/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>NEXO offices in Bulgaria raided by authorities, money laundering claims</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/nexo-offices-in-bulgaria-raided-by-authorities-money-laundering-claims/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 13:08:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/nexo-offices-in-bulgarian-raided-by-authorities-money-laundering-claims/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Nexo offices in Bulgaria were raided by authorities early this morning. There are claims one of the users was financing terrorism. Nexo has confirmed the incident and said it is cooperating with authorities. There are reports that the Bulgarian offices of crypto lender Nexo are being investigated by authorities for alleged money laundering, fraud, and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/nexo-offices-in-bulgaria-raided-by-authorities-money-laundering-claims/">NEXO offices in Bulgaria raided by authorities, money laundering claims</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Nexo offices in Bulgaria were raided by authorities early this morning.</li>
<li>There are claims one of the users was financing terrorism.</li>
<li>Nexo has confirmed the incident and said it is cooperating with authorities.</li>
</ul>
<p>There are reports that the Bulgarian offices of crypto lender Nexo are being investigated by authorities for alleged money laundering, fraud, and tax offences. The Bulgarian Prosecutor&rsquo;s Office has issued a <a href="https://www.facebook.com/Press.PRB/videos/3449803885284375">statement regarding the issue</a> saying that investigations were underway to neutralize what they say is &ldquo;criminal activity&rdquo; of Nexo.</p>
<p>According to the authorities, more than 300 people are currently involved in the operation making it a major operation in Bulgaria. According to the statement:</p>
<p><em>&ldquo;Active investigation actions are underway in the capital to neutralize illegal criminal activity of the Nexo crypto bank &hellip; Evidence has been collected that a person who used the platform and transferred cryptocurrencies has been officially declared a terrorist financing person.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p>In a <a href="https://twitter.com/Nexo/status/1613477472586338305">Twitter thread</a>, Nexo has said that it cooperating with the authorities and regulators. A Nexo spokesperson also confirmed the raid at their Bulgarian office but said that they are one of the most stringent entities when it comes to KYC/AML. The spokesperson said:</p>
<p><em>&ldquo;There are authorities at one of Nexo&rsquo;s offices in Bulgaria which is, as you know the most corrupt country in the EU. They are making AML and tax-related inquiries about a Bulgarian entity of the group that is not customer facing, but only has back office functions &ndash; payroll, customer support, compliance. We are one of the most stringent entities with regards to KYC/AML.&rdquo;</em></p>
<h2>Taking out crypto-backed loans for cash</h2>
<p>Nexo allows users to take out crypto-backed loans for cash and also provides products that allow users to earn interest on their crypto assets instead of letting them lie idle. Last year, Nexo became the first to <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/nexo-becomes-first-to-offer-up-to-12-apr-on-apecoin/">offer a 12% APR on Apecoin</a>.</p>
<p>The crypto lender has grown to become of the largest crypto lenders around the world with offices in various parts of the world including in countries like Bulgaria. It also ranks among the top <a href="https://coinjournal.net/compare/best-cryptocurrency-apps/">ten best crypto apps for beginners</a> as recorded in our earlier post.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/nexo-offices-in-bulgaria-raided-by-authorities-money-laundering-claims/">NEXO offices in Bulgaria raided by authorities, money laundering claims</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Orange Financial To Launch Innovative Yield Farming Treasury &#8211; Stablecoin Rewards for NFT Holders</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/orange-financial-to-launch-innovative-yield-farming-treasury-stablecoin-rewards-for-nft-holders/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/orange-financial-to-launch-innovative-yield-farming-treasury-stablecoin-rewards-for-nft-holders/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire  ]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 12:55:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=99431</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Geneva, Switzerland, 12th January, 2023, Chainwire Orange Financial, a multi-chain yield farming treasury, is excited to announce its public mint date on February 1st, 2023. As the only NFT project to offer stablecoin rewards through yield farming to its holders, Orange Financial will revolutionize the world of yield farming and NFTs. Through its innovative approach, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/orange-financial-to-launch-innovative-yield-farming-treasury-stablecoin-rewards-for-nft-holders/">Orange Financial To Launch Innovative Yield Farming Treasury &#8211; Stablecoin Rewards for NFT Holders</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Geneva, Switzerland, 12th January, 2023, Chainwire</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://orange.financial" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Orange Financial</a>, a multi-chain yield farming treasury, is excited to announce its public mint date on February 1st, 2023. As the only NFT project to offer <a href="https://orange.financial" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">stablecoin rewards </a>through yield farming to its holders, Orange Financial will revolutionize the world of yield farming and NFTs.</p>
<p>Through its innovative approach, Orange Financial has created a basket of DeFi assets and farming opportunities to provide yield for its NFT holders. The Treasury takes care of all the compounding and harvesting on behalf of its holders and routes the returns back through USDC, making it a convenient and secure choice for hands-off diversification.</p>
<p>One of the key features of <a href="https://orange.financial" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Orange Financial</a> is that the Treasury rewards users in stablecoins as opposed to using a native token. This allows holders to receive real-yield instead of devaluing volatile assets. The treasury participates in a wide range of yield farming opportunities to provide the best returns for its holders. With no native token and no fixed interest rate, the Treasury&rsquo;s payout schedule is purely dependent on market conditions and is transparently posted on a weekly basis.</p>
<p>In addition to its <a href="https://orange.financial" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">diversified DeFi Treasury</a>, Orange Financial is also Polygon native and does not require any staking or interaction from NFT holders after they mint their NFTs. All <a href="https://orange.financial" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">USDC rewards</a> are air-dropped directly to the wallet of each holder, making it a hassle-free way to participate in yield farming.</p>
<p>Orange Financial NFT&rsquo;s can be stored on cold wallets with no connection to the internet, making it a safe and convenient way to receive stablecoin rewards. With a low cost of entry and no minimum stake requirement, Orange Financial allows NFT holders to diversify into a basket of high-cost-of-entry <a href="https://orange.financial" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">yield farming projects</a> and receive all the compounding benefits without any additional effort.</p>
<p>Be sure to catch the launch of Orange Financial on <b>February 1st, 2023</b> and keep an eye out for updates on Orange Financial&rsquo;s progress as we work to revolutionize the DeFi industry and offer real-yield opportunities for NFT holders.</p>
<h2>About Orange Financial</h2>
<p><b></b>Orange Financial was created from a desire to have a service in the web3 space that simply did not exist: A efficient, yet incredibly transparent yield farming treasury that has no native token and no fixed interest. A treasury that pays rewards to holders only when they are due- and always in an asset that never loses value (USDC).</p>
<p>As DeFi continues to grow the price of entry for certain projects continues to rise. Orange Financial believes everyone should have the opportunity to participate in DeFi. With a low cost of entry, <a href="https://orange.financial" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Orange Financial</a> NFT holders are able to diversify into a basket of high-cost of entry-yield farming projects and receive all the compounding benefits without lifting a finger.</p>
<p>Social media:<br>
<a href="https://orange.financial/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Website</a> | <a href="https://twitter.com/orangefi_" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Twitter</a> | <a href="https://discord.gg/orangefinancial" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Discord</a></p>
<h2>Contact</h2>
<p>Chief Marketing Officer, John Talbot, Orange Financial, pr@orange.financial</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/orange-financial-to-launch-innovative-yield-farming-treasury-stablecoin-rewards-for-nft-holders/">Orange Financial To Launch Innovative Yield Farming Treasury &#8211; Stablecoin Rewards for NFT Holders</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/orange-financial-to-launch-innovative-yield-farming-treasury-stablecoin-rewards-for-nft-holders/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto short traders lose $200M to liquidations as Ether hits a two-month high</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-short-traders-lose-200m-to-liquidations-as-ether-hits-a-two-month-high/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-short-traders-lose-200m-to-liquidations-as-ether-hits-a-two-month-high/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 11:56:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-short-traders-lose-200m-to-liquidations-as-ether-hits-a-two-month-high/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The cryptocurrency market capitalization has risen by about 3.18% in the past 24 hours. Ether has hit a two-month high trading at about $1400. The crypto market in general has risen against the cautious tone in the US stock market. Crypto traders who had bet on a market decline have been caught off-guard by the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-short-traders-lose-200m-to-liquidations-as-ether-hits-a-two-month-high/">Crypto short traders lose $200M to liquidations as Ether hits a two-month high</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>The cryptocurrency market capitalization has risen by about 3.18% in the past 24 hours.</li>
<li>Ether has hit a two-month high trading at about $1400.</li>
<li>The crypto market in general has risen against the cautious tone in the US stock market.</li>
</ul>
<p>Crypto traders who had bet on a market decline have been caught off-guard by the broad recovery in the crypto market. As a result, about $200 million worth of short trades against price rises has been liquidated in the past 24 hours.</p>
<p>Another more than $150 million worth of short trades were also liquidated earlier this week as <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/what-is-ethereum/">Ethereum </a>(ETH) and bitcoin (BTC) broke past key resistance levels according to <a href="https://www.coinglass.com/LiquidationData">data from CoinGlass</a>. Other major altcoins like XRP and Solana also registered gains of about 20%.</p>
<p>Ether-tracked futures also saw liquidations worth about $110 million in both long and short positions. <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/what-is-bitcoin/">Bitcoin </a>saw liquidations worth about $77 million, while AVAX and GALA saw $4.5 million in liquidations.</p>
<h2>Ethereum&rsquo;s strong performance</h2>
<p>Despite the cautious tone around the US stock futures, Ethereum (ETH) has rallied to a two-month high, confirming that the crypto is well prepared for a recovery in 2023 if the bullish trend is sustained.</p>
<p>Ethereum&rsquo;s bullish trend is further projected to gain momentum ahead of the scheduled March Shanghai upgrade, which is designed to de-risk staking by allowing people to withdraw ETH staked into the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/glossary/beacon-chain/">Beacon Chain</a>. There was some Ether that ware locked/staked into the Beacon Chain in December 2020.</p>
<p>The Shanghai upgrade is expected to boost staking demand causing a decrease in the circulation supply of ether, which the law of demand and supply dictates would result in a rise in ETH prices.</p>
<p>According to Thielen, the upgrade:</p>
<p><em>&ldquo;Will motivate many ETH holders to stake their ETH as only 14% of the ETH is being staked now, compared to 58% for other Layer 1 protocols. Hence, another $20 billion of ETH can be easily staked. More ETH staked means less ETH available to sell when negative news hits the market. Hence, this is bullish.&rdquo;</em></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-short-traders-lose-200m-to-liquidations-as-ether-hits-a-two-month-high/">Crypto short traders lose $200M to liquidations as Ether hits a two-month high</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-short-traders-lose-200m-to-liquidations-as-ether-hits-a-two-month-high/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Robinhood announces plans to delist Bitcoin SV (BSV) before end of January</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/robinhood-announces-plans-to-delist-bitcoin-sv-bsv-before-end-of-january/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/robinhood-announces-plans-to-delist-bitcoin-sv-bsv-before-end-of-january/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 10:30:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin SV News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robinhood]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/robinhood-announces-plans-to-delist-bitcoin-sv-bsv-before-end-of-january/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Robinhood on Wednesday said it has stopped accepting Bitcoin SV. It has also said that it will delist the cryptocurrency starting January 25. Any Bitcoin SV in customers&#8217; accounts after January 25 will be automatically sold. Online trading app Robinhood on Wednesday said through a statement on its website that it has stopped accepting Bitcoin [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/robinhood-announces-plans-to-delist-bitcoin-sv-bsv-before-end-of-january/">Robinhood announces plans to delist Bitcoin SV (BSV) before end of January</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Robinhood on Wednesday said it has stopped accepting Bitcoin SV.</li>
<li>It has also said that it will delist the cryptocurrency starting January 25.</li>
<li>Any Bitcoin SV in customers&rsquo; accounts after January 25 will be automatically sold.</li>
</ul>
<p>Online trading app Robinhood on Wednesday said through a <a href="https://robinhood.com/us/en/support/articles/bitcoin-sv-update/">statement on its website</a> that it has stopped accepting Bitcoin SV (BSV) deposits as it prepares to delist the cryptocurrency on January 25.</p>
<p>Between now and January 25, users hold and sell BSV but after the deadline, the platform will not support Bitcoin SV trades, purchases, or transfers. Additionally, any BSV held in users&rsquo; accounts will be sold at market value and the proceeds will be given to the respective users.</p>
<h2>Regular review of supported cryptocurrencies</h2>
<p>While making the announcement, Robinhood said the move has been arrived at based on its regular review of the cryptocurrencies that it offers. It, however, never gave a specific reason for dropping the cryptocurrency.</p>
<p>The company&rsquo;s statement read:</p>
<p><em>&ldquo;We have a rigorous framework in place to help us regularly review the crypto we offer on Robinhood,&rdquo; a spokesperson told CoinDesk in a statement. &ldquo;We are extremely selective about the assets we offer as we build toward our goal of making Robinhood Crypto the most trusted, lowest cost, and easiest to use on-ramp to crypto.&rdquo;</em></p>
<h2>What is Bitcoin SV (BSV)?</h2>
<p>BSV is the native token of the Bitcoin Satoshi Vision (Bitcoin SV) blockchain which was launched in 2018 following a hard fork from the&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin-cash/what-is-bitcoin-cash/">Bitcoin Cash</a> blockchain. Bitcoin Cash is itself a hard fork of the original <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/what-is-bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> blockchain.</p>
<p>The BSV was added to Robinhood almost immediately after the hard fork from Bitcoin Cash.</p>
<p>Following the announcement, the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin-sv/">price of BSV</a> dropped from a high of $44.41 to as low as $37 although it had slightly retraced upwards to trade at $40.73 at press time.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/robinhood-announces-plans-to-delist-bitcoin-sv-bsv-before-end-of-january/">Robinhood announces plans to delist Bitcoin SV (BSV) before end of January</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/robinhood-announces-plans-to-delist-bitcoin-sv-bsv-before-end-of-january/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
