<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 15:37:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Nikola’s CEO Michael Lohscheller Steps Down, Company Releases Q2 2023 Report</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nikolas-ceo-q2-2023/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nikolas-ceo-q2-2023/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 15:33:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Transportation News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nikola]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=265848</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nikolas-ceo-q2-2023/">Nikola’s CEO Michael Lohscheller Steps Down, Company Releases Q2 2023 Report</a></p>
<p>Nikola's second-quarter results not only revealed insights into its financial situation but also demonstrated the company’s aggressive measures to strengthen its financial base. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nikolas-ceo-q2-2023/">Nikola’s CEO Michael Lohscheller Steps Down, Company Releases Q2 2023 Report</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nikolas-ceo-q2-2023/">Nikola’s CEO Michael Lohscheller Steps Down, Company Releases Q2 2023 Report</a></p>
<p dir="ltr">Electric truck manufacturer <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/nikola-corporation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Nikola Corp</a> (NASDAQ: NKLA) has announced the immediate departure of its CEO, Michael Lohscheller, alongside the release of its second-quarter financial report.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">A New Chapter Begins for Nikola</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Lohscheller’s decision ascribed to a “family health matter”, has prompted the company’s existing board chair, former General Motors vice chairman Steve Girsky, to take over as CEO. Nikola outlined per a CNBC <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/08/04/nikola-nkla-q2-2023-earnings.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a> that Lohscheller would remain in an advisory capacity until the end of September to ensure a smooth transition.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Accompanying the leadership transition was Nikola’s second-quarter earnings report, providing insight into the company’s financial performance over the past quarter. In terms of net loss per share, Nikola managed to surpass estimates, reporting a loss of 20 cents per share.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This exceeded Refinitiv’s projected loss of 22 cents per share. On the other hand, the company’s net revenue for the quarter was reported at $15.36 million, slightly lower than the estimated $15.4 million.</p>
<p dir="ltr">A closer look at Nikola’s financial numbers reveals a net loss of $217.8 million for the quarter or 31 cents per share. It is important to note that this stated net loss includes a significant charge of $77.8 million, or 11 cents per share. This fee is for ceased operations, notably the shutdown of the defunct Romeo Power battery-pack manufacturing in California.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Comparing the current results to the previous year&#8217;s data, Nikola&#8217;s financial landscape has undergone changes. A year ago, the company reported a loss of $173 million, or 41 cents per share.</p>
<p dir="ltr">On an adjusted basis, it incurred a loss of 25 cents per share in the same period of the previous year. Revenue for the quarter was $15.4 million, a decrease from $18.1 million reported in Q2 of 2022.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Nikola’s Q2 2023 Report</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Nikola&#8217;s second-quarter results not only revealed insights into its financial situation but also demonstrated the company’s aggressive measures to strengthen its financial base.</p>
<p dir="ltr">During the quarter, Nikola successfully raised $233.2 million in cash through stock sales and the sale of certain physical assets. This capital infusion contributed to an extraordinary growth in the company&#8217;s cash on hand, which stood at $226.7 million as of June 30, up from $121.1 million on March 31.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Nikola said it delivered 45 battery-electric semitrucks to dealers, as well as the sale of 66 of these vehicles to end users. This achievement represents Nikola’s best quarterly retail performance to date, underscoring the demand for its cutting-edge electric trucks.</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, the company announced the halt of production of battery-electric trucks in May to seamlessly integrate the assembly of both battery-electric and fuel-cell trucks on the same line.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Nikola’s latest model, a longer-range fuel-cell-powered version of its Tre semitruck, went into production on July 31; deliveries are slated to begin in September. Notably, Nikola has received orders for 202 fuel-cell trucks from 18 fleet clients, the company announced earlier this week.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/philcoin-human-blockchain-platform/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nikolas-ceo-q2-2023/">Nikola’s CEO Michael Lohscheller Steps Down, Company Releases Q2 2023 Report</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nikolas-ceo-q2-2023/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Philcoin – Human-Focused Blockchain Platform Backed by World Champions</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/philcoin-human-blockchain-platform/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/philcoin-human-blockchain-platform/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andy Watson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 15:17:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[philcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[phl token]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=265844</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/philcoin-human-blockchain-platform/">Philcoin &#8211; Human-Focused Blockchain Platform Backed by World Champions</a></p>
<p>Philcoin is an exciting project seeking to make real, palpable, and positive changes in the world. Its philanthropic mission is multi-purpose oriented and aims to help as many people in need as possible.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/philcoin-human-blockchain-platform/">Philcoin &#8211; Human-Focused Blockchain Platform Backed by World Champions</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/philcoin-human-blockchain-platform/">Philcoin &#8211; Human-Focused Blockchain Platform Backed by World Champions</a></p>
<p><a href="https://philcoin.io/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Philcoin</a> is a blockchain-based ecosystem focusing on improving the world through peer-to-peer philanthropy. We are looking at a unique project promoting the innovative Give-to-Earn concept, where users earn by donating and creating life-enhancing opportunities. To date, Philcoin has raised over 1.7 million in their native token and donated it across various charities worldwide.</p>
<p>The project&#8217;s activity has attracted the support of prestigious people and brands. For instance, its most recent partner is world-renowned boxing champion Roy Jones Jr., considered one of the greatest boxers of all time by many. Their collaboration includes an exclusive <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NFT</a> collection that should bring the sports community to blockchain and increase support for charitable causes.</p>
<p>At the heart of <a href="https://t.me/philcoinphilanthropychat" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Philcoin</a> is PHILApp &#8211; an all-in-one mobile application providing educational resources, social networks, communications tools, e-commerce marketplaces, games, entertainment, and donation platforms. Anyone worldwide can use it, even with a weak internet connection, to access life-improving possibilities.</p>
<p>In this <a href="https://twitter.com/Philcoin_com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Philcoin</a> review, we look closer at one of the most unique and exciting projects in the blockchain world. Read on as we unveil why respectable celebrities and world champions are rushing to support it.</p>
<h2>What Is Philcoin and How Does It Work?</h2>
<p>In first-world countries, access to present-day technologies, like the Internet, is often taken for granted. However, numerous developing countries do not enjoy the same privileges. This is often due to poor infrastructure or the utter lack of it. Unfortunately, this means countless individuals need help accessing digital services, monetization options, or accurate information. As a result, entire communities are left in the dark regarding growth and thriving opportunities.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/philcoin/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Philcoin</a> seeks to solve these issues and help provide fair access to the digital world for underprivileged communities. The project uses advanced mesh network technology to democratize access to Web3 and offer better protection for personal data through quantum-proof encryption.</p>
<p>The project&#8217;s ecosystem comprises social platforms, learning materials, entertainment options, communication, and charity initiatives. People worldwide can use Philcoin to enter the emerging digital economy and improve their living standards.</p>
<p>Philcoin connects individuals and communities through its proprietary application, PHILApp, which promotes peer-to-peer (P2P) interactions via the project&#8217;s native token, Philcoin (PHL). Furthermore, the app ensures users remain connected despite low internet connectivity.</p>
<p>The project&#8217;s integrated give-to-earn feature enables PHILApp users to gain by sharing first with others. Their donations go toward humanitarian causes, such as abuse victims, food drives, medical support, children&#8217;s homes, rehoming families affected by tragedies, etc.</p>
<h2>PHILApp &amp; Roy Jones Jr. &#8211; Partnership for the Future of Sportsmen Worldwide</h2>
<p>Philcoin is gaining traction in the blockchain industry and beyond as more people want to join its cause. The latest to do so is <a href="https://royjonesjrofficial.com/">Roy Jones Jr.</a>, one of the greatest boxers in the world, who partnered with Philcoin to bring the sports community to blockchain.</p>
<p>This collaboration will produce exclusive NFT collections and a pension fund to help secure the future of boxers worldwide. The initiative will help many former athletes overcome the financial hardships that commonly surface post-retirement.</p>
<p>Philcoin will use its social-powered philanthropy app, PHILApp, to bring the sports community into the blockchain space. The platform will connect crypto and sports enthusiasts around the world and enable them to promote their talents while earning tokens and giving back to those in need.</p>
<p>Roy Jones Jr. is also a renowned music artist advocating for a fairer and more transparent music industry. Philcoin will use PHILApp&#8217;s streaming feature, PHILStream, to provide a platform where musicians can promote their music and reward listeners for their support and engagement. This concept is unique among music platforms and should be a groundbreaking event for the music industry.</p>
<p>PHILApp&#8217;s streaming feature is another critical element of this partnership. Roy Jones Jr. is a renowned music artist advocating for better rights and transparency in the music industry. PHILStream will give musicians a place to promote their music while rewarding listeners for their support and engagement &#8211; a first for any music platform!</p>
<p>Roy Jones Jr. is widely regarded as one of the greatest boxers of all time. He was named Fighter of the Year in 1994 by The Ring magazine and received the same accolade in 2003 from the World Boxing Hall of Fame.</p>
<h2>Other PHILApp Features</h2>
<p>PHILApp is a growing ecosystem of features and utilities, including:</p>
<ul>
<li>PHILSocial &#8211; A communication feature connecting users worldwide, enabling them to build projects and raise funds for charitable causes.</li>
<li>PHILEducation &#8211; A comprehensive collection of educational materials and US-accredited courses. Also, it is a meeting place for business owners and entrepreneurs seeking to monetize their knowledge and skills.</li>
<li>PHILCast &#8211; A directory containing interviews with experts and industry professionals, news, and tips.</li>
<li>PHILChat &#8211; The app&#8217;s chat messenger feature enables audio and video calls between users.</li>
<li>PHILGaming &#8211; A platform containing games and other applications enabling users to earn tokens for playing.</li>
<li>Staking &#8211; A feature enabling users to stake their tokens and earn up to 15%, out of which they can keep half and donate the rest to charity.</li>
</ul>
<h2>PHL Token</h2>
<p>Philcoin&#8217;s native token, PHL, binds together all the platform&#8217;s features, utilities, and mechanisms. For instance, users can earn PHL by participating in activities, providing services, and helping maintain the network. Furthermore, it is necessary for in-app transactions and donations as part of the give-to-earn concept.</p>
<p>You can purchase PHL tokens on PancakeSwap, XT.COM, BitForex, MEXC, and BitMart.</p>
<h2>Bottom Line</h2>
<p><a href="https://www.instagram.com/philcoin/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Philcoin</a> is an exciting project seeking to make real, palpable, and positive changes in the world. Its philanthropic mission is multi-purpose oriented and aims to help as many people in need as possible. Furthermore, it provides better access to information and digital services to remote communities at a time when being online is fundamental to growth and self-realization.</p>
<p>The project&#8217;s recent partnership with Roy Jones Jr. is a testament to Philcoin&#8217;s commitment to building a new digital community providing life-enhancing opportunities to everyone worldwide. The upcoming NFT collection is an excellent chance for well-intended investors and NFT collectors to help make the world a better place.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alphabet-offloads-90-stake-robinhood/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/philcoin-human-blockchain-platform/">Philcoin &#8211; Human-Focused Blockchain Platform Backed by World Champions</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/philcoin-human-blockchain-platform/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Google-parent Alphabet Offloads 90% Stake in Robinhood, HOOD Shares Drop 7%</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/alphabet-offloads-90-stake-robinhood/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/alphabet-offloads-90-stake-robinhood/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 13:12:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investors News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alphabet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[robinhood]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[robinhood markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=265832</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alphabet-offloads-90-stake-robinhood/">Google-parent Alphabet Offloads 90% Stake in Robinhood, HOOD Shares Drop 7%</a></p>
<p>Alphabet sold 90% of its Robinhood stake after the trading app announced a profit for the first time as a public company.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alphabet-offloads-90-stake-robinhood/">Google-parent Alphabet Offloads 90% Stake in Robinhood, HOOD Shares Drop 7%</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alphabet-offloads-90-stake-robinhood/">Google-parent Alphabet Offloads 90% Stake in Robinhood, HOOD Shares Drop 7%</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/robinhood/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Robinhood Markets Inc</a> (NASDAQ: HOOD) shares closed Thursday trading at $11.54, down 7.23 percent from the day’s opening price. The sudden drop in HOOD shares happened after Google-parent company <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/alphabet-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Alphabet Inc</a> (NASDAQ: GOOGL) announced that it has slashed nearly 90 percent of its stake in Robinhood. Notably, Alphabet liquidated its HOOD position despite the crypto hand stock trading app announcing profit for the first time since its IPO.</p>
<p>Alphabet highlighted in its regulatory filing that it has around 612,214 HOOD shares as of June 30, compared with a 4.9 million stake during the first quarter that ended on March 31. Technically, Alphabets holds about $7 million worth of Robinhood shares.</p>
<h2>Robinhood Market Outlook</h2>
<p>Robinhood has grown to a reputable financial market application with deep liquidity in both crypto assets and stock trading. According to the company’s official website, it has about 10.8 million monthly active users with more than $89 billion in assets under custody. The trading platform has, however, experienced significant competition from other crypto trading platforms like Coinbase Global Inc. (NASDAQ: COIN), and Binance with over $250 million in registered users combined.</p>
<p>Earlier this week, Robinhood reported net revenue of about $486 million during the second quarter, up 10 percent from the prior quarter. Notably, the company’s transaction-based revenue decreased by approximately 7 percent during the second quarter to about $193 million. Robinhood’s cryptocurrency trading business was largely affected with its transaction-based revenue declining approximately 18 percent to about $31 million.</p>
<p>The company’s net deposit during the second quarter came in at about $4.1 billion, signifying more growth in the coming quarter if the monthly active users keep growing exponentially.</p>
<p>“Reaching GAAP profitability is a testament to the work our team has done to transform the business and better position Robinhood to drive shareholder value,” <a href="https://s28.q4cdn.com/948876185/files/doc_financials/2023/q2/Q2-2023-Robinhood-Exhibit-99-1-vF.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a> Jason Warnick, Chief Financial Officer of Robinhood Markets. “With five consecutive quarters of revenue and Adjusted EBITDA growth, we’re continuing to drive efficiency across our operations while investing in customer experience. Looking ahead, we remain focused on delivering for customers and growing our business.”</p>
<p>With a crucial investor like Alphabet almost out of the picture, Robinhood is forced to widen its revenue collection avenue in a bid to remain competitive in the future. As a result, the company announced that it acquired the X1 platform, which offers a no-fee stainless steel credit card with rewards on each purchase.</p>
<p>Worth noting that the company’s stock has gained approximately 42 percent YTD to a market capitalization of about $11.23 billion. Perhaps Alphabet just exercised the slogan that states, buy the rumors and sell the news.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/block-cash-app-q2-2023-bitcoin/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alphabet-offloads-90-stake-robinhood/">Google-parent Alphabet Offloads 90% Stake in Robinhood, HOOD Shares Drop 7%</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/alphabet-offloads-90-stake-robinhood/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Block Inc’s Cash App Records 34% Surge in Q2 2023 Bitcoin Sales</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/block-cash-app-q2-2023-bitcoin/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/block-cash-app-q2-2023-bitcoin/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 13:06:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[block]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[block inc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cash app]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=265817</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/block-cash-app-q2-2023-bitcoin/">Block Inc’s Cash App Records 34% Surge in Q2 2023 Bitcoin Sales</a></p>
<p>One of the standout aspects of Block’s financial report is its strategic approach to Bitcoin investments.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/block-cash-app-q2-2023-bitcoin/">Block Inc’s Cash App Records 34% Surge in Q2 2023 Bitcoin Sales</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/block-cash-app-q2-2023-bitcoin/">Block Inc’s Cash App Records 34% Surge in Q2 2023 Bitcoin Sales</a></p>
<p>American multinational financial technology company <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/square/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Block Inc</a> (NYSE: SQ) has reported a staggering 34% increase in <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> (BTC) sales on its Cash App platform, resulting in a remarkable $2.4 billion in the second quarter.</p>
<p>The company stated in its recent <a href="https://s29.q4cdn.com/628966176/files/doc_financials/2023/q2/2Q23_Block_Shareholder-Letter.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">earnings report</a> that gross profit from these sales stood at $44 million, marking a commendable 7% rise from the previous year. This remarkable feat highlights the growing appetite for digital assets and the intriguing dynamics within the crypto market.</p>
<h2>Cash App Bitcoin Surge: Factors Responsible</h2>
<p>Block credits its remarkable financial achievements to two key factors: an increase in the quantity of Bitcoin supplied to clients and the offsetting impact of a fall in the crypto’s average market price.</p>
<p>The success of Block’s Bitcoin sales is indicative of the essential role that user-friendly platforms play in driving crypto adoption. The ease of use, intuitive interfaces, and seamless experience provided by Cash App have likely contributed significantly to the platform’s ability to sustain growth.</p>
<p>Another aspect that can be attributed to the increased Bitcoin sales is the introduction of innovative features such as the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/block-cash-app-paychecks-bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">“Paid in Bitcoin” feature</a> on the Cash App. This feature allows users to invest a portion of their paycheck automatically in the premier digital currency.</p>
<p>Cash App effectively democratizes access to digital assets by allowing users to direct a portion of their money to Bitcoin. This simplified strategy lowers entry barriers, making it easier for both newbies and seasoned investors to participate in the ever-expanding crypto industry.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the company’s financials for the second quarter of 2023 depict a robust performance across key metrics. Block’s revenue increased significantly, rising to $5.53 billion from $4.40 billion in the same period last year.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the company’s gross profit increased significantly, hitting $1.87 million compared to $1.47 million at the same time last year. This steady increase in gross profit is consistent with Block’s overall good trajectory and demonstrates a strong financial foundation to support its ongoing endeavors and innovations.</p>
<h2>Block’s Strategic Bitcoin Investment</h2>
<p>One of the standout aspects of Block’s financial report is its strategic approach to Bitcoin investments. The company’s decision to invest $50 million in the fourth quarter of 2020 and a substantial $170 million in the first quarter of 2021 highlights its forward-thinking approach.</p>
<p>As of June 30, 2023, the value of Block’s Bitcoin investments had surged to an impressive $245 million, indicating a significant increase from the original investment. This success underscores the potential rewards for companies willing to embrace crypto as part of their investment portfolios.</p>
<p>While Block continues to make impressive strides in its financial performance, it’s important to note that its shares is down by 4.66% to $70.12 in the pre-market according to TradingView. Nonetheless, the stock’s overall performance for the year remains positive, with a notable 10.9% rally so far in 2023. This fluctuation underscores the inherent volatility within both traditional and crypto markets.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/revolut-close-us-crypto-services/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/block-cash-app-q2-2023-bitcoin/">Block Inc’s Cash App Records 34% Surge in Q2 2023 Bitcoin Sales</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/block-cash-app-q2-2023-bitcoin/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Revolut to Close US Crypto Services Due to Uncertain Regulatory Position</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/revolut-close-us-crypto-services/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/revolut-close-us-crypto-services/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 13:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FinTech News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cftc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[revolut]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=265801</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/revolut-close-us-crypto-services/">Revolut to Close US Crypto Services Due to Uncertain Regulatory Position</a></p>
<p>From October 3, customers in the US will no longer be able to use Revolut to buy, sell, or hold any cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/revolut-close-us-crypto-services/">Revolut to Close US Crypto Services Due to Uncertain Regulatory Position</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/revolut-close-us-crypto-services/">Revolut to Close US Crypto Services Due to Uncertain Regulatory Position</a></p>
<p>UK-based fintech <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/revolut/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Revolut</a> has announced it is terminating all crypto services in the United States. Revolut has decided to abandon crypto in the US because of the regulatory uncertainty in the country’s crypto market.</p>
<p>Revolut says the option to place buy orders will no longer be available to US customers from the 2nd of September this year. After a month, on the 3rd of October, all access to hold, sell, or buy any digital asset will no longer be possible. Revolut is likely hoping the period between the announcement and October 3 would be enough for customers to move their assets off the platform.</p>
<p>A Revolut <a href="https://decrypt.co/151272/revolut-shutter-us-crypto-operations-due-regulatory-environment" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">told</a> Decrypt that the decision was a joint one with the platform’s banking partner:</p>
<blockquote><p>“As a result of the evolving regulatory environment and the uncertainties around the crypto market in the US, we’ve taken the difficult decision, together with our US banking partner, to suspend access to cryptocurrencies through Revolut in the US. This decision has not been taken lightly, and we understand the disappointment this may cause.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Revolut has officially informed all US customers of the decision.</p>
<h2>Revolut Suspends US Crypto Services as Authorities Continue Crackdown</h2>
<p>Government authorities have been actively cracking down on crypto firms in the US. The United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) believes that nearly all cryptocurrencies should be classified as securities and must follow specific rules. Crypto companies disagree and have been at loggerheads with these authorities.</p>
<p>Recently, the SEC indicted major crypto exchanges <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a> and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase</a> for several alleged malpractices and have been going at both crypto giants for a while now. As part of the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-binance-matic-sol-lawsuit/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance indictment</a>, the SEC designated several cryptocurrencies as securities, including Polygon’s MATIC, Cardano’s ADA, and SOL. According to the SEC, Decentraland, Filecoin, Algorand, Sandbox, and Axie Infinity tokens are also securities. In response, Revolut <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-07-03/revolut-to-delist-solana-cardano-polygon-tokens-for-us-users#xj4y7vzkg" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announced</a> it would delist SOL, ADA, and MATIC, and permanently restrict access on September 18. The company said it will automatically convert all tokens held after this date to dollar deposits for the customers. Robinhood Markets also <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-06-09/robinhood-removes-3-crypto-tokens-following-regulatory-crackdown#xj4y7vzkg" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announced</a> it would delist the same three tokens by June 27.</p>
<h2>Some Wins for Crypto in the US</h2>
<p>Despite the SEC’s continuous crackdown, there might be some respite on the crypto side. For instance, Ripple recently got a <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/xrp-price-ripple-win-sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">partial victory against the SEC</a> for a case initiated in December 2020. US Judge Analisa Torres ruled that while the institutional sale of XRP tokens violated federal securities laws, selling Ripple on exchanges did not meet the requirements of an investment contract. Ripple had maintained that XRP is a security and that all sale of the tokens violates laws.</p>
<p>In addition to Ripple’s victory, lawmakers have <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-crypto-legislation-coinbase-ceo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">criticized the SEC</a> for going after crypto, putting some pause on the Commission’s regulatory powers. According to a recent bill attempting to design a regulatory framework for digital assets, the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/cftc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CFTC</a>) should be the primary regulator. Interestingly, the lawmakers also accuse the SEC of using enforcement action on the market instead of ensuring all players have the much-needed clarity.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tiktok-payment-license-indonesia/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/revolut-close-us-crypto-services/">Revolut to Close US Crypto Services Due to Uncertain Regulatory Position</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/revolut-close-us-crypto-services/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>TikTok Is Working to Secure Payment License in Indonesia</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tiktok-payment-license-indonesia/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tiktok-payment-license-indonesia/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 11:43:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FinTech News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bytedance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tiktok]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=265802</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tiktok-payment-license-indonesia/">TikTok Is Working to Secure Payment License in Indonesia</a></p>
<p>Securing this license would mean that TikTok would be directly competing with big e-commerce companies like Shopee and Lazada in Southeast Asia.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tiktok-payment-license-indonesia/">TikTok Is Working to Secure Payment License in Indonesia</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tiktok-payment-license-indonesia/">TikTok Is Working to Secure Payment License in Indonesia</a></p>
<p>Short video platform TikTok&#8217;s parent company <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/bytedance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ByteDance</a> is recently in the early stages of discussions in order to secure a payment license in Indonesia.</p>
<p>This shall further help TikTok to bolster its e-commerce objectives in a major market, amid the heightened scrutiny from global authorities, especially the US. Getting a payment license would be a big advantage for people who create and sell things on TikTok. It would let TikTok make money from transaction fees. This means TikTok would be competing with big e-commerce companies like Shopee and Lazada in Southeast Asia.</p>
<p>Following TikTok CEO Shou Zi Chew&#8217;s announcement in June about investing billions of dollars in Indonesia and Southeast Asia, the news about the payments license came up. According to two sources familiar with the matter, TikTok, which is owned by Chinese tech giant ByteDance, is in discussions with Indonesia&#8217;s central bank, and the application is being viewed positively.</p>
<p>A spokesperson for TikTok confirmed the talks on Friday and mentioned that having an Indonesian payment license would benefit local creators and sellers on their platform. The sources requested to remain anonymous as the negotiations were confidential. Bank Indonesia, the central bank, did not respond to a request for comment.</p>
<h2>TikTok&#8217;s Strong Presence in Indonesia</h2>
<p>TikTok is very popular in Indonesia, with 125 million users each month. It&#8217;s similar to its popularity in Europe and a bit less than in the US, where it has 150 million users. The central bank of Indonesia is looking at TikTok&#8217;s request for a payments license positively.</p>
<p>In China, TikTok&#8217;s counterpart called Douyin, which is also owned by ByteDance, got a payments license in 2020. However, it&#8217;s not clear if TikTok has gotten a payments license in any other part of the world.</p>
<p>Indonesia is a big country with over 270 million people, and in 2020, there was almost $52 billion worth of online shopping transactions there. Around 5% of these transactions happened on TikTok, especially through live-streaming features.</p>
<p>Even though TikTok is popular for shopping, it has decided not to start an online shopping platform in Indonesia. This decision comes after concerns were raised by senior officials about the potential increase in Chinese-made products coming into the country.</p>
<p>The US government has shared concerns about potential Chinese influence on TikTok. As a result, there&#8217;s a ban on using TikTok on government devices. However, TikTok has always been clear that it doesn&#8217;t share U.S. user data with the Chinese government and has taken strong steps to protect user privacy and security.</p>
<p>Similar restrictions have also been put in place in Australia and Canada. Despite facing these challenges, TikTok&#8217;s effort to get a payments license shows that it is committed to expanding its e-commerce services in Southeast Asia.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-court-filing-sec/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tiktok-payment-license-indonesia/">TikTok Is Working to Secure Payment License in Indonesia</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tiktok-payment-license-indonesia/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase to Submit New Court Filing Today as Exchange Seeks to Have  SEC’s Case ‘Entirely’ Dismissed</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-court-filing-sec/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-court-filing-sec/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 11:40:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brian armstrong]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gary gensler]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[securities and exchange commission]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=265737</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-court-filing-sec/">Coinbase to Submit New Court Filing Today as Exchange Seeks to Have  SEC&#8217;s Case &#8216;Entirely&#8217; Dismissed</a></p>
<p>Coinbase is now full of confidence as they approach the court and inch closer to a final ruling.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-court-filing-sec/">Coinbase to Submit New Court Filing Today as Exchange Seeks to Have  SEC&#8217;s Case &#8216;Entirely&#8217; Dismissed</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-court-filing-sec/">Coinbase to Submit New Court Filing Today as Exchange Seeks to Have  SEC&#8217;s Case &#8216;Entirely&#8217; Dismissed</a></p>
<p>The ongoing US Securities and Exchange Commission’s (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-sec-coinbase-unregistered-exchange/">lawsuit</a> against Coinbase may be about to take a new turn. This follows after the defendant – <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase</a> – confirmed that it will be filing an order to the same effect in court today. According to the American crypto exchange, the filing will seek to have the court throw out the entire case of &#8220;securities law violation&#8221; that the SEC has built against it so far.</p>
<p>For what it&#8217;s worth, Coinbase has long argued that the regulator has not been about rulemaking. As Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong put it, the SEC has been employing the “regulation by enforcement approach.”</p>
<p>Furthermore, Coinbase accused the SEC of misleading it. The exchange claimed that the mere fact that the regulator approved its registration statement in 2021 has already put to bed any questions that may arise about the legality of its business activities.</p>
<p>In line with these arguments, Coinbase is now full of confidence as they approach the court and inch closer to a final ruling.</p>
<p>Sharing the firm&#8217;s expectations, the chief legal officer at Coinbase, Paul Grewal <a href="https://s27.q4cdn.com/397450999/files/doc_financials/2023/q2/Shareholder-Letter-Q2-2023.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“With respect to litigation with the SEC, I want to be very clear &#8211; we do think we can win, we expect to win.”</p></blockquote>
<p>However, Grewal quickly added that Coinbase is not only keen to win the court case. Rather, the exchange is willing to work hand-in-hand with the SEC and lawmakers to obtain “regulatory clarity,” he added.</p>
<h2>‘Coinbase Knows It Violated Securities Laws,’ SEC Argues</h2>
<p>Meanwhile, SEC lawyers have also pushed back at Coinbase. The regulator argued last month that the exchange&#8217;s claim about the 2021 registration statement does not mean that its enforcement action is not valid. And by SEC Chair Gary Gensler&#8217;s accounts, the crypto industry in itself is largely non-compliant.  So, he has urged crypto platforms to come under the agency&#8217;s fold and duly register.</p>
<p>During a financial markets conference in May, Gensler remarked that their agency “has put out rules about what it is to be an exchange, what it means to be a broker-dealer, what it is to be an adviser of custody and assets, and how to register a securities offering.”</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shipping-maersk-q2-earnings/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-court-filing-sec/">Coinbase to Submit New Court Filing Today as Exchange Seeks to Have  SEC&#8217;s Case &#8216;Entirely&#8217; Dismissed</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-court-filing-sec/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shipping Giant Maersk Outperforms Forecasts in Q2 2023 Earnings Results Despite 72% Profit Drop </title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/shipping-maersk-q2-earnings/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 10:46:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ibm]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[maersk]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=265743</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shipping-maersk-q2-earnings/">Shipping Giant Maersk Outperforms Forecasts in Q2 2023 Earnings Results Despite 72% Profit Drop </a></p>
<p>Amid muted global macroeconomic growth and mounting pressure from higher interest rates, Maersk revised its profit forecast for the whole year.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shipping-maersk-q2-earnings/">Shipping Giant Maersk Outperforms Forecasts in Q2 2023 Earnings Results Despite 72% Profit Drop </a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shipping-maersk-q2-earnings/">Shipping Giant Maersk Outperforms Forecasts in Q2 2023 Earnings Results Despite 72% Profit Drop </a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/maersk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">AP Moeller Maersk</a>, a significant player in the container shipping industry, is bracing for a challenging year ahead as global economic growth remains subdued and container rates continue to face headwinds. The company reported a massive decline in second-quarter earnings on August 4, reflecting the impact of falling container rates and decreased volumes. The Danish shipping giant Maersk posted a Q2 profit before interest, tax, depreciation, and amortization (EBITDA) of $2.91 billion, a far cry from the record-breaking $10.3 billion it achieved in the same quarter last year. Despite the steep drop, Maersk managed to surpass market expectations, with analysts having projected an EBITDA of $2.41 billion.</p>
<p>The normalization of ocean freight rates affected the company&#8217;s performance, which saw a sharp decline following a stellar <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/maersk-record-earnings-2022/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">2022</a>. As expected, revenue slumped by 40% year-on-year, decreasing from $21.65 billion to $12.99 billion in the second quarter, as container rates continued to fall and volumes remained weak.</p>
<h2>A Change of Heart: Maersk Revises Its Profit Forecasts</h2>
<p>In an official <a href="https://www.maersk.com/news/articles/2023/08/04/maersk-reports-robust-q2-financial-results-in-difficult-market-conditions" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announcement</a> on Friday, Maersk&#8217;s CEO, Vincent Clerc, acknowledged the impact of market conditions on their first-half performance. The company responded proactively to the changing landscape, adopting cost containment measures and managing contract portfolios to cushion some of the effects of market normalization. He also emphasized the importance of cost focus in managing a subdued market outlook, which is expected to persist until the end of the year.</p>
<p>&#8220;Our decisive actions on cost containment, together with our contract portfolio, cushioned some of the effects of this market normalization. Cost focus will continue to play a central role in dealing with a subdued market outlook that we expect to continue until the end year,&#8221; he said.</p>
<p>Amid muted global macroeconomic growth and mounting pressure from higher interest rates, Maersk revised its profit forecast for the whole year. The company now anticipates underlying EBITDA to range between $9.5 billion and $11 billion, narrowing its previous guidance from $8 billion to $11 billion.</p>
<p>Additionally, the company warned of a steeper decline in global demand for shipping containers, with container volumes now expected to fall by as much as 4%. The muted economic growth has prompted customers to reduce inventories, adding to the challenges faced by the container shipping industry.</p>
<h2>Maersk Holds A 17% Market Share in the Shipping Industry</h2>
<p>Despite the hurdles, Maersk remains a crucial player in the container shipping industry, holding a market share of around 17%. The company&#8217;s wide-ranging operations involve transporting goods to major retailers and consumer companies, including Walmart, Nike, and Unilever.</p>
<p>As the global economic landscape remains uncertain, Maersk&#8217;s ability to navigate the challenges and adapt to evolving market conditions will be critical. The company&#8217;s strategic decisions and operational resilience will determine its success in weathering the current economic slowdown and becoming a stronger player in the container shipping industry.</p>
<p>While the firm has made significant progress in its shipping business, it<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/maersk-ibm-discontinue-tradelens/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"> announced</a> last year that it would discontinue TradeLens, a blockchain-focused delivery <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/maersk-partners-ibm-apply-blockchain-tech-container-shipping/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">solution</a> launched in collaboration with IBM, International Business Machines Corp in 2018. At the time, Maersk cited the company&#8217;s inability to meet financial expectations as the reason for the suspension, which was slated to happen earlier this year.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/brave-image-video-search/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shipping-maersk-q2-earnings/">Shipping Giant Maersk Outperforms Forecasts in Q2 2023 Earnings Results Despite 72% Profit Drop </a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Brave Search Launches Image and Video Search with Privacy Protection</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/brave-image-video-search/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Babafemi Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 10:43:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brave]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brave browser]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[google]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=265583</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/brave-image-video-search/">Brave Search Launches Image and Video Search with Privacy Protection</a></p>
<p>Despite the fact that Brave has announced its image and video search options, the feature is still being improved.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/brave-image-video-search/">Brave Search Launches Image and Video Search with Privacy Protection</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/brave-image-video-search/">Brave Search Launches Image and Video Search with Privacy Protection</a></p>

<p>Brave Search, the privacy-focused search engine, has <a href="https://brave.com/image-video-search/">announced</a> the launch of its own image and video search features. Consequently, users will now be served image and video search results directly from the search engine&#8217;s index.</p>
<p>According to Brave, the new feature will allow its users to enjoy a censorship-resistant and privacy-preserving search experience. This was previously impossible with available search engines like Google and Bing.</p>
<p>Recall that Brave’s plans for its image and video search option began after Reuters reported that Microsoft Bing served no image results for the Tiananmen Square protests Tank Man. While Microsoft attributed this to human error, Brave rejected their explanation. By April, the browser had removed the Bing API from its search engine.</p>
<h2>Major Milestone for Brave Search</h2>
<p>The launch of image and video search is a significant milestone for Brave Search, which was first introduced in June 2021 as a beta version. At that time, 13% of its queries used third-party provider indexes. Within a year, it had reduced that number to 7% of all query results.</p>
<p>However, in April 2023, the search engine announced that it had severed ties with all third-party APIs and became fully independent. However, users who wanted to search for images or videos had to be redirected to Google or Bing while the company developed its own solution.</p>
<p>According to Brave, the redirect option was not popular with some of its users.</p>
<p>“This was a temporary decision to help users find results with minimum hassle, while we worked to offer a sustainable, privacy-preserving, and independent image and video search option,” the company said.</p>
<p>Now, users can access as much content as they want without leaving the Brave ecosystem. Additionally, users will enjoy greater speed and privacy than when they relied on third-party providers.</p>
<h2>In the Cocoon of Development</h2>
<p>Despite the fact that Brave has announced its image and video search options, the feature is still being improved. The company noted that advanced filters like license type or aspect ratio are still unavailable. “For now, we believe offering a clear alternative is more important than complete feature parity,” it concluded.</p>
<p>Again, Brave said it will continue to listen to user feedback and improve its search engine based on user preferences. Currently, the search engine is available for use at search.brave.com. It is also the default search engine in the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/brave-security-anonymity/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Brave browser</a>.</p>
<p>In the future, Brave plans to provide more products for users who want choice and transparency while they search for information online.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/polygon-zero-matter-labs-code/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/brave-image-video-search/">Brave Search Launches Image and Video Search with Privacy Protection</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Polygon Zero Accuses Matter Labs’ Developers of Copying Source Code</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/polygon-zero-matter-labs-code/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Darya Rudz]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 10:38:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[boojum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[matter labs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[matter labs boojum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[plonky2]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[polygon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[polygon matter labs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[polygon plonky2]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[polygon zero]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=265745</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/polygon-zero-matter-labs-code/">Polygon Zero Accuses Matter Labs’ Developers of Copying Source Code</a></p>
<p>While Polygon Zero is claiming the code was used without the original copyrights or clear attribution to the original authors, Matter Labs stated that the code was "prominently attributed" in a line atop one of the files in question.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/polygon-zero-matter-labs-code/">Polygon Zero Accuses Matter Labs’ Developers of Copying Source Code</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/polygon-zero-matter-labs-code/">Polygon Zero Accuses Matter Labs’ Developers of Copying Source Code</a></p>
<p>Polygon and Matter Labs continue their competition on building zero-knowledge rollups. Polygon&#8217;s unit Polygon Zero, which is standing behind a layer 2 scaling solution for Ethereum (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ETH</a>), has accused an award-winning innovation lab Matter Labs of plagiarism. According to Polygon Zero, Matter Labs developers employed &#8220;a substantial amount of source code&#8221; from its Plonky2 library without permission.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="474" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Crypto runs on the open source ethos. When projects don’t follow it, the ecosystem suffers.</p>
<p>We were disappointed to see that <a href="https://twitter.com/zksync?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@zksync</a> copied our code without attribution and made misleading claims about the original work, so we wrote this post.<br /> <a href="https://t.co/8VnoYVWgI8">https://t.co/8VnoYVWgI8</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Polygon Zero 💜 (@0xPolygonZero) <a href="https://twitter.com/0xPolygonZero/status/1687153310699057152?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 3, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>While Polygon Zero is claiming the code was used without the original copyrights or clear attribution to the original authors, Matter Labs stated that the code was &#8220;prominently attributed&#8221; in a line atop one of the files in question.</p>
<h2>Plonky2 vs Boojum</h2>
<p>Back in January, Polygon <a href="https://polygon.technology/blog/introducing-plonky2" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">launched</a> its Plonky2 – a zero-knowledge proving system that represents a major breakthrough for zero-knowledge (ZK) tech. This recursive SNARK is claimed to be 100x faster than existing alternatives and natively compatible with Ethereum. It works by using large proofs when speed matters and small proofs when size matters. Its flexibility allows Plonky2 to optimize for speed and cost.</p>
<p>Recently, Matter Labs has also come up with a proof solution based on a new Rust-based cryptographic library from zkSync that powers the prover’s upgraded zero-knowledge circuits – vital components of zkSync Era and ZK Stack. Called Boojum, the solution is promised to be 10x faster than Plonky2.</p>
<p>Following Matter Labs&#8217; release, Polygon Zero has found multiple similarities in the underlying tech of Plonky2 and Boojum. The company&#8217;s team has compared both solutions in its <a href="https://mirror.xyz/0x70DF15b0208eFCeFaA541Da9A0ED6C4A884554Fc/gNi8coqXjd1ybFsQBAG7QARUkPHZECu7ihIRkpiVx2Y" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">blog post</a> and accused Matter Labs of plagiarism.</p>
<p>Polygon Zero developers wrote:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Matter Labs, developers of zkSync, recently released a proving system called Boojum that includes a substantial amount of source code that is copy-pasted from performance-critical components of the Plonky2 library. This code is included without the original copyrights or clear attribution to the original authors. As an aside, it’s very difficult to fail to abide by the terms of the MIT/Apache licenses, but this is how to do it.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The document also includes screenshots of both codes&#8217; comparisons.</p>
<p>In response, Matter Labs called Polygon&#8217;s claims &#8220;untrue&#8221; and highlighted that the similarity between the solutions is mentioned in the first line of its module.</p>
<p>Matter Labs representative said:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The new Boojum high-performance proof system leverages 5% from Plonky2, which is prominently attributed in the first line of our module. Where else, other than the very first line of our library would this have been included if we wanted it to be more prominent?&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Matter Labs and Polygon have been competing in developing zkEVM rollups for quite a long. The plagiarism accusations that have taken place in their case are not the first time something similar happens. Another example of copying the code is Shibarium layer-2 beta testnet that had allegedly used Shiba Inu code without permission.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/elon-musk-trading-hub-x/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/polygon-zero-matter-labs-code/">Polygon Zero Accuses Matter Labs’ Developers of Copying Source Code</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4070 metric#misses=43 metric#hit-ratio=99.0 metric#bytes=1120433 metric#prefetches=201 metric#store-reads=22 metric#store-writes=3 metric#store-hits=208 metric#store-misses=4 metric#sql-queries=35 metric#ms-total=115.32 metric#ms-cache=6.55 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.2731 metric#ms-cache-ratio=5.7 -->