<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 14:43:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>UK Plans to Regulate Digital Currency Ecosystem Are Being Finalized</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-plans-digital-currency-ecosystem/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-plans-digital-currency-ecosystem/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 14:43:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fca]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[uk treasury]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=228057</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-plans-digital-currency-ecosystem/">UK Plans to Regulate Digital Currency Ecosystem Are Being Finalized</a></p>
<p>The approach by the UK government and parliament to bring sweeping regulations to guide the crypto industry is not negating the overall perception that the technology powering the digital currency ecosystem is unique and futuristic.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-plans-digital-currency-ecosystem/">UK Plans to Regulate Digital Currency Ecosystem Are Being Finalized</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-plans-digital-currency-ecosystem/">UK Plans to Regulate Digital Currency Ecosystem Are Being Finalized</a></p>
<p>The United Kingdom (UK) under the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/pro-crypto-rishi-sunak-uk-prime-minister/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">leadership of Prime Minister Rishi Sunak</a> is looking at granting the Financial Conduct Authority (FCA) more powers to regulate the digital currency ecosystem. According to a <a href="https://www.ft.com/content/481d45d8-943e-484b-84ca-3b11f02c0ee4" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a> from the Financial Times, the collapse and eventual bankruptcy of FTX Derivatives Exchange have injected a renewed sense of urgency by all regulators to exert extra control on the industry.</p>
<p>The new rules which are being handled by the UK Treasury will restrain the activities of foreign crypto firms that are selling their products in the country.</p>
<p>The United Kingdom from the era of Rishi Sunak as the Chancellor of the Exchequer has detailed plans to float such rules that will make the crypto industry a major hub for digital currencies. The proposed new rules will limit the activities of stakeholders in this space serving as an antagonistic policy to its initial plans.</p>
<p>Amongst the oversight, the FCA will now exert censoring how crypto firms advertise their products in the UK in order to ensure that they are not misleading. The proposal will also detail plans or approaches by which companies can be wound down, in case they need to leave the UK or in the advent of bankruptcy.</p>
<p>All firms will be required to register with the FCA and pass the regulator’s Anti-Money Laundering (AML) tests. According to Nikhil Rathi, the FCA’s Chief Executive Officer, the agency has recorded more firms, to the tune of 85%, failing to pass its AML tests. With the already stringent measures to issue licenses to firms, more stringent rules may further push others away.</p>
<p>Despite not currently having absolute powers, the FCA boss said the agency is very proactive in publicly warning on “the risks of investing in crypto, the potential to lose all your money.”</p>
<h2>UK Recognizes the Tech Powering the Digital Currency Ecosystem</h2>
<p>The approach by the UK government and parliament to bring sweeping regulations to guide the crypto industry is not negating the overall perception that the technology powering the digital currency ecosystem is unique and futuristic.</p>
<p>City Minister, Andrew Griffith noted in a statement last week that despite the bouts of bankruptcies in the industry, the focus of the government remains unchanged.</p>
<p>“Yes, there are questions about the future of crypto &#8211; but we’d be foolish to ignore the potential of the underlying technology,” he said adding that the financial services bill would establish a framework for <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-crypto-industry-stablecoins/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">regulating crypto assets and stablecoins</a> and that the government would be “consulting on a world-leading regime for the rest of the cryptoasset market later this year.”</p>
<p>While the crypto industry bill is a part of the larger Financial Services Bill, its acceleration is evident in the consistent collapse of key firms in the space, and the need to safeguard the interest of consumers and investors in the United Kingdom.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-news-congress-journalism-bill/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-plans-digital-currency-ecosystem/">UK Plans to Regulate Digital Currency Ecosystem Are Being Finalized</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-plans-digital-currency-ecosystem/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Meta Threaten to Pull US News if Congress Passes Journalism Bill</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-news-congress-journalism-bill/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-news-congress-journalism-bill/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 13:09:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alphabet inc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalism Bill]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meta platforms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[us congress]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=228025</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-news-congress-journalism-bill/">Meta Threaten to Pull US News if Congress Passes Journalism Bill</a></p>
<p>Meta Platform’s threat to remove news from its platform is something it had actually done before.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-news-congress-journalism-bill/">Meta Threaten to Pull US News if Congress Passes Journalism Bill</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-news-congress-journalism-bill/">Meta Threaten to Pull US News if Congress Passes Journalism Bill</a></p>
<p>Social media and multinational tech conglomerate <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/meta/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Meta Platforms Inc</a> (NASDAQ: META) has threatened to pull off US-related news content from its apps if the American Congress passes the controversial Journalism Bill.</p>
<p>Billed as a National Security initiative, the Journalism Competition, and Preservation Act, if passed, will give the power to news outlets to negotiate the revenues they can get from their content that goes on tech giant’s platforms.</p>
<p>The controversial bill will not only be disadvantageous to Meta Platforms, but it will also affect outlets like <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/alphabet-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Alphabet Inc</a> (NASDAQ: GOOGL) both of which dominate the ads scene.</p>
<p>Sharing the plans, Andy Stone, Meta Platform’s Head of Policy Communications said the bill is bound to set a very bad precedent for American businesses. He noted that if the Bill becomes law, news support on Facebook and Instagram may have to be removed.</p>
<p>“If Congress passes an ill-considered journalism bill as part of national security legislation, we will be forced to consider removing news from our platform altogether,” he said in a tweet shared on Tuesday.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="474" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Meta statement on the Journalism Competition and Preservation Act: <a href="https://t.co/kyFqKQw7xs">pic.twitter.com/kyFqKQw7xs</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Andy Stone (@andymstone) <a href="https://twitter.com/andymstone/status/1599857809126195201?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 5, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The Journalism Bill was introduced in 2021 on accounts that tech giants beat and squeeze out news publishers in terms of revenue generation for the content. With the Bill set to force the likes of Facebook and Google to pay for news content, the bill will be benefiting these newsmakers across the board.</p>
<p>Stone reiterated in his statement that Congress has failed to recognize that newsmakers put up their content on Facebook because it helps their bottom line and not the way around.</p>
<p>“Put simply: the government creating a cartel-like entity which requires one private company to subsidise other private entities is a terrible precedent for all American businesses,” he said.</p>
<h2>Will Meta Platforms and US Congress Reach Compromise on News Compensation?</h2>
<p>It should be recalled that Meta Platform’s threat to remove news from its platform is something it had actually done before. The company removed Australian news back in 2021 when the government requested that the company pay for the news content, drawing on a similar bill that the American government is now trying to pass.</p>
<p>The company later sat on the negotiation table with the Australian Government and was able to reach a compromise that worked for all sides.</p>
<p>The Canadian Government has also been threatened with such, underscoring Meta Platform’s lack of readiness to rethink its position about revenue sharing across the board. Whether or not this negotiation approach will ensue between the US government and Meta Platforms is too soon to predict, however, should the tech giant pull news from its platform, chances are that it will cause more harm than good and the government may not be willing to overlook things then.</p>
<p>There are entities in support of the bill as well as others who are against the government’s approach. Those in Meta Platform’s favor <a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/tech/facebook-meta-us-news-congress-bill-b2239628.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">submitted</a> that the bill can &#8220;create an ill-advised antitrust exemption for publishers and broadcasters.&#8221;</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-sony-10-year-deal-playstation/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-news-congress-journalism-bill/">Meta Threaten to Pull US News if Congress Passes Journalism Bill</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-news-congress-journalism-bill/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Microsoft Offers Sony 10-Year Deal to Share Call of Duty Game with PlayStation</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-sony-10-year-deal-playstation/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-sony-10-year-deal-playstation/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 13:01:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Deals News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gaming News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[activision blizzard]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[microsofft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sony]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=228023</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-sony-10-year-deal-playstation/">Microsoft Offers Sony 10-Year Deal to Share Call of Duty Game with PlayStation</a></p>
<p>Microsoft has proffered a deal to Sony for COD to be available on PlayStation for 10 years upon completion of the Activision acquisition. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-sony-10-year-deal-playstation/">Microsoft Offers Sony 10-Year Deal to Share Call of Duty Game with PlayStation</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-sony-10-year-deal-playstation/">Microsoft Offers Sony 10-Year Deal to Share Call of Duty Game with PlayStation</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/microsoft-corporation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Microsoft</a> (NASDAQ: MSFT) has <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/12/06/microsoft-offers-sony-10-year-deal-for-call-of-duty-on-playstation-.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reportedly</a> offered <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sony/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Sony</a> (TYO: 6758) a provisional 10-year deal regarding Call of Duty’s licensing rights on the PlayStation console. Should Microsoft’s massive <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/blizzard/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Activision</a> deal go through, the American tech giant is willing to make Activision’s Call of Duty available on PlayStation alongside Xbox.</p>
<p>According to Microsoft’s President Brad Smith, the deal offered to Sony to share each new Call of Duty release spans 10 years. Furthermore, the Washington-based tech corporation hopes that this gesture will assuage the antitrust fears of its rivals and regulators. Smith agrees that Microsoft should extend an olive branch to Sony upon completion of the Activision deal, as the alternative would be “economically irrational”. The Microsoft President also acknowledges that the popularity of cross-play games makes it imperative to make concessions with Sony. Furthermore, in addition to Activision raking a vital part of COD revenue from PlayStation game sales, Smith wants to avoid alienating video gamers.</p>
<blockquote><p>“That’s why we’ve offered Sony a 10-year contract to make each new ‘Call of Duty’ release available on PlayStation the same day it comes to Xbox. We’re open to providing the same commitment to other platforms and making it legally enforceable by regulators in the US, UK, and European Union,” he explains.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Japanese Gaming Stakeholder Weighs in On Proposed Microsoft Deal to Sony PlayStation</h2>
<p>On the heels of Microsoft’s 10-year deal offer to Sony PlayStation, Serkan Toto, CEO of Kantan Games, said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“A 10-year commitment sounds significant; Sony would be indeed ‘safe’ during the lifecycle of the PlayStation 5 but could run into trouble by the time the next console generation begins.”</p></blockquote>
<p>The chief executive of the Tokyo-based games consultancy further explained that the offer might hold forth only short-term. However, it may be just enough to assuage regulators so that they do not stand in Microsoft’s way toward completion. As Toto put it:</p>
<blockquote><p>“So I believe the offer will not be enough to squash Sony’s concerns, but it might calm down regulators to some extent.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>Pending FTC Antitrust Lawsuit</h2>
<p>Last month, <a href="https://www.politico.com/news/2022/11/23/exclusive-feds-likely-to-challenge-microsofts-69-billion-activision-takeover-00070787" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reports</a> stated the US Federal Trade Commission would <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftc-could-block-microsoft-activision-deal/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">likely file an antitrust lawsuit</a> to pause Microsoft’s planned $69 billion takeover of Activision. The way FTC Chair Lina Khan sees it, Microsoft’s sole ownership of the popular video game publisher is bad news for competitors. Khan reckons that Microsoft would have exclusive rights to wildly popular intellectual property like Call of Duty, thus attaining an unfair competitive advantage. The anticipated FTC lawsuit represents the largest of its kind under Khan’s watch and marks her latest attempt to rein in global tech power.</p>
<p>However, Smith <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/microsofts-activision-blizzard-acquisition-is-good-for-gamers-competition-sony-cross-play-ftc-11670260780" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">recently responded</a> to the FTC’s allegations of unjust Microsoft monopoly in the gaming space. Criticizing any potential lawsuit, the Microsoft President defended the Activision acquisition as good for gamers. Furthermore, Smith also added that an FTC lawsuit would be detrimental to consumers, competition, and countless game developers.</p>
<p>Despite Microsoft’s latest gesture of goodwill towards Sony and concerned regulators, how Sony responds remains to be seen. Questions arise as to whether the Japanese tech powerhouse will accept the terms of the deal.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/celsius-network-exclusive-period/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-sony-10-year-deal-playstation/">Microsoft Offers Sony 10-Year Deal to Share Call of Duty Game with PlayStation</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-sony-10-year-deal-playstation/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Celsius Network Secures Approval for Extension of Its Exclusive Period</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/celsius-network-exclusive-period/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/celsius-network-exclusive-period/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 12:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[celsius network]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[goldman sachs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=228004</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/celsius-network-exclusive-period/">Celsius Network Secures Approval for Extension of Its Exclusive Period</a></p>
<p>The company now intends to use the extended time to keep strategizing on how to put this entire menace behind it. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/celsius-network-exclusive-period/">Celsius Network Secures Approval for Extension of Its Exclusive Period</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/celsius-network-exclusive-period/">Celsius Network Secures Approval for Extension of Its Exclusive Period</a></p>
<p>Bankrupt digital currency lending platform Celsius Network has <a href="https://twitter.com/CelsiusNetwork/status/1599957794299711490" target="_blank" rel="noopener">announced</a> that the Court has extended its exclusive period to submit a proposal for its Chapter 11 reorganization plan until February 15 next year.</p>
<h2>Exclusive Period for Celsius Network</h2>
<p>The beleaguered crypto firm took to Twitter to make this revelation, noting that the approval for the extension came after two hearings it participated in on Monday. One of the hearings also involved the plans by the company to sell off some of its stablecoin holdings to continue its operations and return value to stakeholders.</p>
<p>“Celsius participated in two hearings today and continued to advance the dialogue on key matters with important stakeholders in our cases,” Celsius Network said in the tweet, “This morning, we discussed our motion requesting approval to permit the sale of stablecoin, aimed at providing liquidity for our continued operations as we work to maximize value for all stakeholders. The Judge has indicated that he will share his decision soon, likely next week.”</p>
<p>Should the stablecoin sale request be granted as projected, Celsius Network will no longer be cash strained as its bankruptcy proceedings drag along.</p>
<p>Celsius Network was among the first cryptocurrency firms to hit the rocks earlier this year riding on the aftermath of the collapse of Terra (LUNA) and the entire crypto market at the time. After much resistance, the company later <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/celsius-files-chapter-11-bankruptcy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">filed for bankruptcy</a> in July, setting up an avalanche of related filings for other entities facing their own individual distress calls.</p>
<p>The company now intends to use the extended time to keep strategizing on how to put this entire menace behind it.</p>
<p>“This afternoon, the Court approved an extension to our Exclusivity Periods until 2/15/2023. This is the period within which Celsius has the exclusive right to submit a chapter 11 plan of reorganization. We thank the UCC and ad hoc groups for their collaboration on this matter,” Celsius said, “We intend to use this time to continue developing a plan for a stand-alone business, as we explore all value-maximizing opportunities available to us, for the benefit of our customers and other stakeholders.”</p>
<h2>Celsius Network Pioneered Bankruptcy Apocalypse</h2>
<p>The digital currency ecosystem has been through a lot this year and the foundations set by Celsius Network and firms like Voyager Digital that pioneered bankruptcy in the industry set off the collapse of FTX Derivatives Exchange.</p>
<p>Today, the trust investors and traders have for protocols in the space has reduced remarkably, and journeying into 2023, this might affect the general rate of capital inflow into the ecosystem. While this is concerning, more investors are now beginning to pitch tents with regulated and more established firms offering crypto trading and investment options.</p>
<p>As <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/goldman-sachs-crypto-firms/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a> earlier by Coinspeaker, investors are beginning to favor <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/goldman-sachs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Goldman Sachs Group Inc</a> (NYSE: GS), as the head of digital assets in the company, Matthew McDermott said the firm has seen increased trading volume since FTX imploded last month.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/defi-panoptic-uniswap-4-5m/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/celsius-network-exclusive-period/">Celsius Network Secures Approval for Extension of Its Exclusive Period</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/celsius-network-exclusive-period/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>DeFi Protocol Panoptic Based on Uniswap Raises $4.5 Million</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/defi-panoptic-uniswap-4-5m/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/defi-panoptic-uniswap-4-5m/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 12:09:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investors News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[panoptic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[uni]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[uniswap]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=228001</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/defi-panoptic-uniswap-4-5m/">DeFi Protocol Panoptic Based on Uniswap Raises $4.5 Million</a></p>
<p>Panoptic seeks to revolutionize the decentralized options trading market and will use these funds in building a decentralized protocol for perpetual options.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/defi-panoptic-uniswap-4-5m/">DeFi Protocol Panoptic Based on Uniswap Raises $4.5 Million</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/defi-panoptic-uniswap-4-5m/">DeFi Protocol Panoptic Based on Uniswap Raises $4.5 Million</a></p>
<p>Uniswap-based decentralized finance (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-decentralized-finance-defi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">DeFi</a>) protocol Panoptic has recently secured a $4.5 million fundraising for building a decentralized protocol for perpetual options.</p>
<h2>DeFi Protocol Panoptic</h2>
<p>On Monday, December 5, Panoptic announced that Gumi Cryptos Capital led the round along with other investors such as Coinbase Ventures, Uniswap Labs Ventures, Avalanche Foundation&#8217;s Blizzard fund, Jane Street, and others.</p>
<p>Panoptic co-founder and COO Jesper Kristensen noted that they have secured the funding through an equity plus token warrant arrangement. Kristensen, a former head of research at Advanced Blockchain AG, and Guillaume Lambert established Panoptic earlier this year in July.</p>
<p>Just as Uniswap provides decentralized crypto spot trading, Panoptic seeks to revolutionize the decentralized options trading market. Kristensen added that the first version of Panoptic will be based on Uniswap&#8217;s automated market maker (AMM).</p>
<p>In the later stage of their journey, the protocol will support several other popular and successful AMMs. &#8220;We can integrate with other concentrated liquidity AMMs if and when needed,&#8221; he said in an <a href="https://www.theblock.co/post/192207/uniswap-based-defi-protocol-panoptic-raises-4-5-million" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">interview</a> with The Block.</p>
<p>The Panoptic co-founder also added that with fresh capital in hand, they are planning to expand the team. Additionally, they have also planned to build their native protocol and audit their code. Kristensen added that as of now, there are six people working on the team. They plan to add two more people in the coming months.</p>
<p>Panoptic co-founders noted that they are set to launch the platform in the first quarter of 2023. It seems that after a long lull period DeFi projects are once again beginning to start getting VC funds.</p>
<h2>Unsiwap (UNI) Price Rally</h2>
<p>Over the last week, UNI &#8211; the native token of the decentralized exchange Uniswap &#8211; witnessed a strong price action and is up 10.5% on the weekly chart. At one point, the UNI price rallied all the way to $6.5.</p>
<p>However, it has partially retraced since then and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/uniswap/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">UNI</a> is currently trading at $6.11 with a market cap of $4.6 billion. The UNI price pump last week came as the platform announced the launch of its NFT aggregator.</p>
<p>Being an aggregator, Uniswap will offer listings from all major <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NFT</a> marketplaces including OpenSea, X2Y2, LooksRare, Sudoswap, and much more. This will allow users to buy NFTs at the best possible price available. In the official announcement, Uniswap <a href="https://twitter.com/Uniswap/status/1597953698449494022" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">noted</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;NFTs are officially live on Uniswap!!  Starting today, you can trade NFTs across major marketplaces to find more listings and better prices. We&#8217;re also airdropping ~$5M USDC to historical Genie users &amp; offering gas rebates to the first 22,000 buyers.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Read other <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/crypto/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">crypto news</a> on Coinspeaker.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tether-gold-euro-tether/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/defi-panoptic-uniswap-4-5m/">DeFi Protocol Panoptic Based on Uniswap Raises $4.5 Million</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/defi-panoptic-uniswap-4-5m/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tether Announced Upcoming Launch of Tether Gold (XAU₮) and Euro Tether (EUR₮) Starting December 8th</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tether-gold-euro-tether/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tether-gold-euro-tether/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 12:05:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[euro tether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tether gold]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[usdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=227998</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tether-gold-euro-tether/">Tether Announced Upcoming Launch of Tether Gold (XAU₮) and Euro Tether (EUR₮) Starting December 8th</a></p>
<p>Huobi Global says that customers will soon be able to access Tether Gold and Euro Tether stablecoins, representing ownership of assets. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tether-gold-euro-tether/">Tether Announced Upcoming Launch of Tether Gold (XAU₮) and Euro Tether (EUR₮) Starting December 8th</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tether-gold-euro-tether/">Tether Announced Upcoming Launch of Tether Gold (XAU₮) and Euro Tether (EUR₮) Starting December 8th</a></p>
<p>According to reports, Tether is launching two new stablecoins &#8211; Tether Gold (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/tether-gold/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">XAUT</a>) and Euro Tether (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/euro-tether/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">EURT</a>) &#8211; on popular crypto exchange Huobi Global. This development means that the exchange&#8217;s customers will now have access to stablecoins representing <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tether-gold-margin-trading-bitfinex/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ownership of physical gold</a> and <a href="https://twitter.com/tether_to/status/1599778503108530178" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Euro-pegged tokens</a>.</p>
<p>Commenting on the new development, Paolo Ardoino, chief technical officer at the stablecoin issuer, said:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We are thrilled to be launching XAU₮ and EUR₮ on one of the oldest and leading exchanges in the world.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>In addition, the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/tether/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tether</a> CTO stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;By gaining access to the stablecoin that represents ownership of physical gold and the Euro-pegged stablecoin that&#8217;s backed by the same company behind the first, most stable, and trusted stablecoin, we believe the Huobi Community will be poised to thrive and continue to grow.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Huobi Lists Tether Gold &amp; Euro Tether Despite Crypto Winter</h2>
<p>Huobi&#8217;s decision to list Tether Gold and Euro Tether comes amid the general underperformance of digital assets (crypto winter). In addition, the exchange&#8217;s announcement comes roughly a month after the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-exchange-files-for-bankruptcy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">demise</a> of another prominent crypto exchange – <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX.</a> The once second-largest, Bahamian-based exchange filed for Chapter 11 Bankruptcy in the US on November 11th. Since then, FTX&#8217;s management has gone into hiding amid a torrent of allegations and investigations regarding the mismanagement of customers&#8217; funds.</p>
<p>In the wake of FTX&#8217;s collapse, Tether&#8217;s stablecoins have faced increasing scrutiny as the crypto space remains on edge. Several leading mainstream media outlets recently renewed their focus on the stablecoin&#8217;s alleged reserves, which appears to agitate the company&#8217;s top execs. The Wall Street Journal <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/rising-tether-loans-add-risk-to-stablecoin-crypto-world-11669875590" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">published</a> an article on December 1st expressing doubt over Tether&#8217;s sufficient reserves claims. According to the WSJ, the stablecoin issuer&#8217;s rising loans add substantial risk to an already-frayed digital asset marketplace. Furthermore, the international daily newspaper suggested that Tether might need to be more capable of backing its $65 billion worth of USDT in circulation.</p>
<p>The WSJ also addressed the lack of disclosure and limited transparency of Tether&#8217;s alleged robust reserves as cause for concern. A previous Tether report disclosed only US dollar amounts for the loans while not specifying whether the rest were in Tether tokens. In addition, the company report alluded to full collateralization by liquid assets of said loans. However, the WSJ article quoted Crane Data President Peter Crane&#8217;s skepticism of the Tether claims. According to Crane at the time, he has &#8220;been very skeptical and in disbelief that they can get away with the lack of disclosure and with the limited transparency. If you do have reserves, why wouldn&#8217;t you show them?&#8221;</p>
<h2>Tether</h2>
<p>Launched in 2014, Tether is an asset-backed crypto stablecoin and is the largest stablecoin issuer by market cap. Its USDT stablecoin pegs to the US dollar at a 1:1 ratio, and as of July 2022 was minted on ten blockchains and protocols.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gamestop-conduct-mass-layoffs/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tether-gold-euro-tether/">Tether Announced Upcoming Launch of Tether Gold (XAU₮) and Euro Tether (EUR₮) Starting December 8th</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tether-gold-euro-tether/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>GameStop Latest Company to Conduct Mass Layoffs</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/gamestop-conduct-mass-layoffs/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/gamestop-conduct-mass-layoffs/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sanaa Sharma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 10:53:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[axios]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bybit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gamestop]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=227970</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gamestop-conduct-mass-layoffs/">GameStop Latest Company to Conduct Mass Layoffs</a></p>
<p>Several ex-employees have shared their ordeals on social media/ LinkedIn, including one Blockchain and iOS engineer Brandon Jenniges, who has also been affected by the company's layoff.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gamestop-conduct-mass-layoffs/">GameStop Latest Company to Conduct Mass Layoffs</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gamestop-conduct-mass-layoffs/">GameStop Latest Company to Conduct Mass Layoffs</a></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/gamestop/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">GameStop</a>, which is an American video game retailer, has <a href="https://www.axios.com/2022/12/05/gamestop-begins-layoff" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">fired</a> a significant number of employees before its upcoming earnings report, according to social media posts of the involved company members. The team working on the firm&#8217;s crypto wallet was effectively hit hard. Daniel Williams, GameStop&#8217;s Lead Software Engineer has also confirmed the massive round of layoffs at GameStop presently in action. However, the company&#8217;s official statement is yet to come out.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Several ex-employees have shared their ordeals on social media/LinkedIn, including one Blockchain and iOS engineer Brandon Jenniges, who has also been affected by the company&#8217;s layoff. GameStop inaugurated an <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NFT</a> marketplace this year that specifically targets the Ethereum environment, especially on the Immutable X sidechain. In May, the firm revealed the launch of its own Ethereum wallet, a browser-based plugin akin to MetaMask. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ethan Gach, a senior reporter at gaming publication Kotaku posted later that GameStop Chief Executive Officer Matt Furlong confirmed mass layoff in an email to employees. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to Furlong&#8217;s email, the company is trying to ascertain the right number of corporate employees required to earn profitability and development goals. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to the tech industry, more than two hundred tech and finance firms have slashed the number of employees since the start of November. More than ten percent of the firms listed were associated with the crypto industry. Moreover, it is reported that nine-hundred sixteen tech firms fired employees in 2022 and 144,554 employees&#8217; livelihoods have been affected. As disclosed earlier, Bybit is the latest crypto company to slash down its staff this week. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">News of the latest layoff was initially reported by Axios, which stated the community of GameStop&#8217;s blockchain wallet was the most affected. Many software engineers and staff in the e-commerce department have posted on LinkedIn describing how they were fired from the firm. Furlong, in his email, refrained from specifying the extent of the layoffs, which instead made cryptic relation to several &#8220;headcount reductions&#8221; across several teams. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Additionally, the CEO explained in the mail that the latest completion of a few projects was part of the initial phase of transformation and allowed the enterprise to function with enhanced efficiency. Furlong also called this approach a more proactive but difficult decision to fire people in part of the increasing inflation and weakened customer confidence in the difficult job market. </span></p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sam-bankman-fried-ftx-ceo-john-ray/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gamestop-conduct-mass-layoffs/">GameStop Latest Company to Conduct Mass Layoffs</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/gamestop-conduct-mass-layoffs/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sam Bankman-Fried Says New FTX CEO John Ray’s Testimony Is False</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sam-bankman-fried-ftx-ceo-john-ray/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sam-bankman-fried-ftx-ceo-john-ray/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 10:49:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Alameda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alameda research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[john ray]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sam bankman-fried]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=227961</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sam-bankman-fried-ftx-ceo-john-ray/">Sam Bankman-Fried Says New FTX CEO John Ray’s Testimony Is False</a></p>
<p>Embattled former CEO SBF recently stated that John Ray’s testimony on FTX and its operational affairs is false.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sam-bankman-fried-ftx-ceo-john-ray/">Sam Bankman-Fried Says New FTX CEO John Ray’s Testimony Is False</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sam-bankman-fried-ftx-ceo-john-ray/">Sam Bankman-Fried Says New FTX CEO John Ray’s Testimony Is False</a></p>
<p><a href="https://cms.megaphone.fm/channel/theblock-thescoop?selected=BLOCK7074136408" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">According to</a> former <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a> CEO <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/sam-bankman-fried/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Sam Bankman-Fried</a> (SBF), his successor’s testimony regarding the operational affairs of the sunken crypto exchange is false. The Bahamas-based ex-CEO claimed that several legally-admissible statements from John J Ray III’s camp were incorrect. However, Bankman-Fried added that he remains unsure if the falsehood is an honest mistake or deliberate malicious misinformation.</p>
<p>Bankman-Fried also claimed that John J Ray III and his team have snubbed him since they took over. According to the embattled former CEO, “John Ray and his team do not communicate with me. They have not responded and he has not responded to a single message I’ve sent him. His team does not in general work with me or, you know, care about what I have to say.”</p>
<p>SBF also suggested that the new CEO’s plan would be better executed by talking to people involved in the company before he took over. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“I think it’s pretty hard, if you try and take over a company and refuse to talk with anyone who was involved in running that company, to, in a short period of time, know where any of the relevant data would be.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>John J Ray III’s Lambasts FTX Management &amp; Operations</h2>
<p>Further elaborating on his claim that Ray refuses to consult with the former FTX management over record-keeping, Bankman-Fried disputed Ray’s allegations of zero financial controls. His rebuff directly addressed a question regarding his successor’s review of FTX’s financial controls. In an earlier disposition, Ray said the bankrupt exchange’s corporate controls were the worst in his 40-year career. In addition, the attorney and insolvency professional, who also oversaw Enron’s bankruptcy, described FTX’s management as “inexperienced, unsophisticated and potentially compromised individuals.”</p>
<p>According to Ray, the defunct crypto exchange did not have appropriate records, books, or security controls for its digital assets. He also revealed in court filings that FTX lacked a proper staff structure and payroll system. Ray’s scathing assessment of FTX’s management and operations also extended to its sister firm, Alameda Research. The insolvency specialist alleged that the hedge fund and related businesses did not keep complete records of their investments. Furthermore, he advised the court to refrain from relying on audited financial statements, which he suggested are questionable.</p>
<h2>SBF Rebuttal to New FTX CEO &#8216;False Testimony&#8217; Is Another Attempt to Remove Himself from Bankruptcy Mess</h2>
<p>SBF’s sharp response to what he believes is false testimony is the most recent media outing for the embattled founder. Bankman-Fried has been highly vocal on social media and in several interviews since his once-lauded crypto exchange collapsed. Meanwhile, according to some legal experts, the former crypto-wunderkind <a href="https://www.theblock.co/post/186175/criminal-charges-against-sbf-on-the-table-after-ftxs-epic-collapse" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">might soon face criminal charges</a> as he continues to tell his side of the story.</p>
<p>As SBF suggested, a focal point of FTX’s collapse is its relationship with Alameda Research. The former billionaire alleged that the crypto exchange’s downfall began when Alameda took on overleveraged collateral and got liquidated. The effect created a substantial deficit in FTX’s balance sheet, which set the company back. SBF also claimed that FTX harbored a stub account from when it could not secure bank accounts which amounted to a massive obscure debt position.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-com-coca-cola-nfts-cro/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sam-bankman-fried-ftx-ceo-john-ray/">Sam Bankman-Fried Says New FTX CEO John Ray’s Testimony Is False</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sam-bankman-fried-ftx-ceo-john-ray/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto.com Partners with Coca-Cola to Launch World Cup NFTs as CRO Token Surges 10%</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-com-coca-cola-nfts-cro/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-com-coca-cola-nfts-cro/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 10:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coca cola]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cro]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cro token]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cronos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto.com]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nft]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=227911</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-com-coca-cola-nfts-cro/">Crypto.com Partners with Coca-Cola to Launch World Cup NFTs as CRO Token Surges 10%</a></p>
<p>Player "heatmaps" from the ongoing FIFA World Cup 2022 Matches will be used to create 10,000 NFTs that will be hosted on Crypto.com’s blockchain.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-com-coca-cola-nfts-cro/">Crypto.com Partners with Coca-Cola to Launch World Cup NFTs as CRO Token Surges 10%</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-com-coca-cola-nfts-cro/">Crypto.com Partners with Coca-Cola to Launch World Cup NFTs as CRO Token Surges 10%</a></p>
<p>Top crypto exchange Crypto.com has teamed up with American multinational beverage corporation <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coca-cola/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coca-Cola</a> to launch a collection of non-fungible tokens (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NFTs</a>) it calls the &#8220;Piece of Magic&#8221; NFTs. The partnership will see about 10,000 NFTs hosted on Crypto.com’s blockchain. Whereas Coca-Cola for its part will be responsible for creating the NFTs with the help of digital artist GMUNK. The collection has a theme that aligns with the 2022 FIFA World Cup that is currently going on in Qatar.</p>
<h2>Crypto.com NFTs Aimed at Memorializing World Cup Moments</h2>
<p>According to the official announcement, the NFTs were created by tracking the heatmaps of players. This refers to the amount of space covered by an individual player throughout a particular match at the Qatar World Cup.</p>
<p>According to the chief marketing officer at Crypto.com, Steven Kalifowitz, this partnership is a great deal. He expressed his excitement, adding that the partnership brings a completely new form of creating memories. But more importantly, it sets a trend, given that a body as big as FIFA is embracing Web 3.0 technology for the first time. Kalifowitz said:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;It’s a privilege to partner with Coca-Cola and GMUNK to memorialize these historical matches that will forever be captured on the blockchain.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>But speaking about how fans may access the NFTs, interested buyers must first create a Crypto.com NFT platform account. And for them to stand a chance of winning one of the Coca-Cola “Piece of Magic” NFTs, they must also register on Coca-Cola’s fan zone website.</p>
<h2>CRO Surges 10%</h2>
<p>Expectedly, the news of the NFT launch immediately drove the native token of Crypto.com (CRO) to the skies. According to CoinMarketCap <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/cronos/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">data</a>, CRO saw gains of over 10% on the heels of the news. However, as of publication, it has now lost about 5% of those gains in the last 24 hours, to be trading at $0.6671.</p>
<p>Despite the recent appreciable gains though, CRO remains down by over 50% in the last month. But that can be linked to the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-exchange-files-for-bankruptcy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">collapse</a> of the FTX exchange which had a telling effect on the general crypto market.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-prices-traditional-markets/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-com-coca-cola-nfts-cro/">Crypto.com Partners with Coca-Cola to Launch World Cup NFTs as CRO Token Surges 10%</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-com-coca-cola-nfts-cro/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Prices Rise as Traditional Markets and Tech Stocks Decline</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-prices-traditional-markets/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-prices-traditional-markets/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 10:38:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Indices]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[block]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[microstrategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nasdaq 100]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[s&p 500]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=227964</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-prices-traditional-markets/">Crypto Prices Rise as Traditional Markets and Tech Stocks Decline</a></p>
<p>Block, MicroStrategy, and Coinbase experienced drawdowns alongside traditional markets even as crypto prices experienced a rise on Monday.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-prices-traditional-markets/">Crypto Prices Rise as Traditional Markets and Tech Stocks Decline</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-prices-traditional-markets/">Crypto Prices Rise as Traditional Markets and Tech Stocks Decline</a></p>
<p>Monday saw a rise in crypto prices, with the leading token Bitcoin <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">(BTC</a>) up 0.3% to $17,087, while Ether (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ETH</a>) climbed 0.5% to $1,266. However, the traditional markets slumped to coincide with this rise in crypto prices yesterday. Furthermore, the shares of some prominent digital and tech companies also declined in line with US stock indices. Some of these companies include <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/square/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Block</a> (NYSE: SQ), <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/microstrategy-incorporated/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">MicroStrategy</a> (NASDAQ: MSTR), <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase</a> (NASDAQ: COIN), and Silvergate Capital (NYSE: SI). In addition, the US Dollar Index traded to its lowest since August on Monday, after being on a downswing in the last few days.</p>
<p>BTC is changing hands at an even $17K as of press time and is still substantially less than a third of its November 2021 all-time high.</p>
<h2>Analysis of Prices Development</h2>
<p>Although BTC peaked above $17K after trading at that level since Sunday, the leading crypto began to show weakness later on Monday. In addition to Bitcoin and Ether, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance&#8217;s</a> native BNB Coin was up 0.5%, while <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ripple-labs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ripple&#8217;s</a> native <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/xrp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">XRP</a> token climbed 0.2%. Furthermore, Litecoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/litecoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">LTC</a>) saw the most substantial gains for the period, surging 7% between Sunday and Monday.</p>
<p>The US Dollar Index was trading at a four-month low of 104.83, further validating an established pattern with Bitcoin. Historically, Bitcoin&#8217;s dollar price tends to climb higher when the dollar weakens. The US dollar has already <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2022-12-05/dollar-erases-more-than-half-of-this-year-gains-on-fed-rate-bets?leadSource=uverify%20wall" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">erased</a> more than 50% of gains made this year on bets that the Fed will slow interest rate hikes. According to the CME Group&#8217;s FedWatch tool, the probability of a 50-basis point increase in the second week of December is now 77%. The FedWatch analytical tool based its findings on the pricing data of Fed funds futures.</p>
<p>Another reason for the steep easing of US dollar gains is the growing optimism surrounding China&#8217;s reopening plans. The Chinese cities of Shanghai and Hangzhou recently relaxed some Covid restrictions, widely viewed as a significant step towards a full reopening. Speaking on this development, Christopher Wong, currency strategist at Overseas Chinese Banking Corp in Singapore, stated:</p>
<p>&#8220;Anticipation of China reopening, Fed policy calibration are key thematics that should keep risk proxies such as commodity-linked currencies supported. The strong non-farm payrolls report last Friday only saw a kneejerk bounce in the US dollar.&#8221;</p>
<h2>Digital, Tech, Crypto Players Slide as Prices of Digital Currencies Rise</h2>
<p>In other pricing-related news, the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-the-sp-500-index/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">S&amp;P 500</a> dipped 0.8%, while the Nasdaq 100 declined 0.7%. Meanwhile, the shares of leading American crypto exchange Coinbase were down 0.9% at $47, according to Nasdaq data. Furthermore, mobile payment facilitator Block also saw its stock dip 4.7% to $64.92, with MicroStrategy declining over 5% to $195. At the beginning of the week, shares of the business intelligence, mobile software, and cloud-based service provider were trading above $200.</p>
<p>Other drawdowns for the period saw Silvergate shares slipping 5.2%, while Grayscale&#8217;s GBTC fund was trading at a 42.3% discount. In addition, the asset manager also saw the discount on its ETHE product slump to a new record low of 45.7%.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/goldman-sachs-crypto-firms/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-prices-traditional-markets/">Crypto Prices Rise as Traditional Markets and Tech Stocks Decline</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-prices-traditional-markets/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>