<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 10:39:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>User Data of Gaming Gear Maker Razer on Sale Online after Recent Hack</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/user-data-razer-sale-hack/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/user-data-razer-sale-hack/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 10:39:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cybersecurity News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gaming News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[monero]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[razer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xmr]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=262410</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/user-data-razer-sale-hack/">User Data of Gaming Gear Maker Razer on Sale Online after Recent Hack</a></p>
<p>Razer reset all user accounts while asking people to change their passwords.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/user-data-razer-sale-hack/">User Data of Gaming Gear Maker Razer on Sale Online after Recent Hack</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/user-data-razer-sale-hack/">User Data of Gaming Gear Maker Razer on Sale Online after Recent Hack</a></p>
<p>As per the latest report, gaming hardware maker Razer has allegedly suffered a data breach. Last Saturday, July 8, a hacker forum had a post informing about the attack with the hacker offering the stolen data for $135,000.</p>
<p>“I have stolen the source code, encryption keys, database, backend access logins, etc,” the hacker <a href="https://www.hackread.com/razer-data-breach-database-backend-access-sold/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">declared</a>. The hacker further added that “[I] will be selling this one time” for a set price of $100,000 in privacy coin Monero (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/monero/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">XMR</a>). However, the hacker is open to considering lower offers as well.</p>
<p>The Strat Times has seen a sample of users&#8217; email addresses on offer, with the hacker claiming that it was from a list having a total of 404,000 entries. The publication also confirms that the data for sale includes the source code as well as the back-end access logins for Razer’s website and its products.</p>
<p>This included folders with names like zVault, which was Razer&#8217;s digital wallet launched in March 2017 and later replaced by Razer Gold in December 2018. The leaked data also supposedly contained encryption keys and files related to Razer&#8217;s reward system.</p>
<p>One sample examined by ST revealed alleged email addresses of customers who had virtual credit in their Razer Gold accounts. The seller claimed to possess 404,000 accounts, but this information could not be independently verified.</p>
<h2>Razer Is Investigating the Matter</h2>
<p>In a tweet on Sunday, July 9, Razer said that they have been investigating the potential breach. Furthermore, Razer reset all user accounts while asking them to change passwords.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">We have been made aware of a potential breach and are currently investigating.</p>
<p>— R Λ Z Ξ R (@Razer) <a href="https://twitter.com/Razer/status/1678212940967624705?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 10, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Razer was hit by another hack, adding to the ongoing aftermath of a data breach that occurred in 2020. On July 10, a Singaporean court heard an appeal by Capgemini, an IT vendor, regarding a $6.5 million award granted to Razer in December.</p>
<p>The 2020 data breach involved the personal information of approximately 100,000 users. It occurred when a programmer from Capgemini allegedly manipulated a line of code, leaving the data exposed between June and September 2020. The breach was detected by a security consultant in September 2020.</p>
<p>Founded in 2005, Razer has offices in the US and Singapore. Back in 2017, the company launched digital currencies for rewards and credits. As per reports, the data stolen during the recent July 8 hack belongs to the old version of the system.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/terra-co-founder-daniel-shin-court/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/user-data-razer-sale-hack/">User Data of Gaming Gear Maker Razer on Sale Online after Recent Hack</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/user-data-razer-sale-hack/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Terra Co-Founder Daniel Shin Appears in South Korean Court with Seven Others</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/terra-co-founder-daniel-shin-court/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/terra-co-founder-daniel-shin-court/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mercy Tukiya Mutanya]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 10:26:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[do kwon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[terra luna]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[terraform]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=262441</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/terra-co-founder-daniel-shin-court/">Terra Co-Founder Daniel Shin Appears in South Korean Court with Seven Others</a></p>
<p>Daniel Shin, who co-founded Terraform Labs with Do Kwon, allegedly sold about $118 million in LUNA before the token crashed in May of 2022.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/terra-co-founder-daniel-shin-court/">Terra Co-Founder Daniel Shin Appears in South Korean Court with Seven Others</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/terra-co-founder-daniel-shin-court/">Terra Co-Founder Daniel Shin Appears in South Korean Court with Seven Others</a></p>
<p>Terraform Labs co-founder Shin Hyun-Seong, also known as Daniel Shin, reportedly had his first trial preparation hearing on Monday, July 10 for charges related to “unfair profits” from the sale of Terra (LUNA). This comes after the founder’s indictment in April on charges of fraud and violation of capital markets law.</p>
<p>According to <a href="https://www.news1.kr/articles/?5101793" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">local media</a>, Shin and seven others we summoned to appear before a Seoul Southern District Court to face charges of fraud, breach of duty, embezzlement and Violation of the Capital Markets Act. Shin reportedly did not appear in person but was represented by his legal team. Prosecutors allege that the accused deceived investors by presenting the Terra project as more successful than it was in reality. The eight are accused of manipulating the prices of digital assets through transactions and inaccurate media reports starting in 2018. The groups reportedly realised about 462.9 billion Korean won (about $357 million) in illicit profits.</p>
<p>Daniel Shin, who co-founded Terraform Labs with Do Kwon, allegedly sold about $118 million in LUNA before the token crashed in May of 2022. He is accused of using similar tactics with the intention of profiting from investor funds at Chai Corporation, the fintech company he went on to create following his departure from Terraform Labs.</p>
<p>Shin’s defence has denied reports that he “sold Luna at a high point and realized profits or that he made profits through other illegal methods”. It is also worth noting that while Shin’s LinkedIn profile suggests that he had not been involved with Terraform Labs’ operations since January 2020, it is not clear if he still had any investments in the company’s shares or tokens.</p>
<p>The founder’s defence requested more time from Judge Jang Seong-hoon who granted the motion.</p>
<p>“We will check the opinions of the lawyers and reopen the trial preparation date to decide the opportunity for defence and the order of interrogation,” Judge Seong-hoon ruled.</p>
<p>A new hearing is scheduled for August 28.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, South Korean authorities are seeking extradition for Terra’s other co-founder Do Kwon who is currently serving a four-month sentence in Montenegro following his arrest in March for using forged travel documents. He was sentenced in June and faces extradition to either his home country of South Korea or the United States once his sentence is complete.</p>
<p>South Korean authorities issued an arrest warrant for Do Kwon in September 2022 following the May 2022 <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-korea-exchanges-terra-collapse/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">collapse</a> of Terra platform and the depegging of its USTC algorithmic stablecoin. Following the collapse, authorities decided to look into Do Kwon and Daniel Shin&#8217;s alleged illegal transactions before and during the crash.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/vara-dubai-bitoasis-license/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/terra-co-founder-daniel-shin-court/">Terra Co-Founder Daniel Shin Appears in South Korean Court with Seven Others</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/terra-co-founder-daniel-shin-court/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>VARA, Dubai Crypto Regulator, Makes BitOasis License Non-Operational</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/vara-dubai-bitoasis-license/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/vara-dubai-bitoasis-license/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Temitope Olatunji]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 10:12:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitoasis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bybit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[okx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vara]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=262412</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/vara-dubai-bitoasis-license/">VARA, Dubai Crypto Regulator, Makes BitOasis License Non-Operational</a></p>
<p>VARA is exercising its authority to supervise and monitor compliance, assure fulfillment of prescribed conditions, impose remedial measures, and take necessary enforcement actions, including but not limited to holding BitOasis' License status as non-operational.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/vara-dubai-bitoasis-license/">VARA, Dubai Crypto Regulator, Makes BitOasis License Non-Operational</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/vara-dubai-bitoasis-license/">VARA, Dubai Crypto Regulator, Makes BitOasis License Non-Operational</a></p>
<p>Dubai cryptocurrency regulator, the Virtual Assets Regulatory Authority (VARA), has suspended the license of BitOasis because the exchange failed to fulfill certain conditions the regulator set within a specified timeframe.</p>
<p>BitOasis is a crypto exchange operating in Dubai, the United Arab Emirates. The exchange was founded in 2014 by Ola Doudin and is one of the earliest and most popular cryptocurrency exchanges in the Middle East and North Africa region. The VARA provides regulatory oversight to make sure exchanges operate within the scope of the law and in the best interest of the people.</p>
<p>The license VARA granted BitOasis in April was a Minimal Viable Product license, which permitted the exchange to operate if it could meet some requirements within 30 to 60 days, which the exchange failed to do.</p>
<p>VARA was not specific about the particular requirements that the exchange had failed to meet. However, as a result of the shortcoming, the exchange has become non-operational and cannot provide regulated retail or institutional services.</p>
<p>In an official statement on its website, the regulator <a href="https://www.vara.ae/en/regulations/regulatory-notices/market-alert-bitoasis-technologies-fze-bitoasis/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;VARA is exercising its authority to supervise and monitor compliance, assure fulfillment of prescribed conditions, impose remedial measures, and take necessary enforcement actions, including but not limited to holding BitOasis&#8217; License status as non-operational.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The MVP license prevents exchanges from having a full operation. Having this license shows that BitOasis met some initial requirements that allowed it to operate within specific limitations. The MVP is like an interim step in the full regulatory process. For BitOasis to have full operations, it has to meet certain conditions that will qualify it for a Full Market Product (FMP) license.</p>
<p>VARA will continue to make sure that BitOasis takes the necessary actions to comply with regulatory standards. The regulators also made it clear that the announcement is only to notify the public of what is going on and should not replace individual investors carrying out their own research when trying to choose an exchange to trade with.</p>
<h2>Dubai Remains Crypto-Friendly Despite VARA Regulations</h2>
<p>In April, Dubai regulators issued a warning to OPNX, a crypto exchange, accusing it of operating without a license and ordering the firm to immediately cease its activities.</p>
<p>Even though the regulator is doing its job and maintaining strict conditions that exchanges must meet, Dubai has remained one of the finest places for crypto and crypto exchanges. <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase</a> and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ripple-labs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ripple</a> are currently looking at the possibility of establishing their presence in the region.</p>
<p>Some exchanges like Bybit, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a>, and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/okex/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">OKX</a> have gotten Dubai&#8217;s Minimal Viable Product license, which authorizes them to operate in the area.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-layoffs-2023-financial-year/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/vara-dubai-bitoasis-license/">VARA, Dubai Crypto Regulator, Makes BitOasis License Non-Operational</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/vara-dubai-bitoasis-license/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Microsoft Announces New Layoffs after Completing 2023 Financial Year</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-layoffs-2023-financial-year/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-layoffs-2023-financial-year/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 10:01:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Meta]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[microsoft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[salesforce]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=262399</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-layoffs-2023-financial-year/">Microsoft Announces New Layoffs after Completing 2023 Financial Year</a></p>
<p>Microsoft will begin layoffs affecting over 270 people including remote workers after thousands of other layoffs since last year.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-layoffs-2023-financial-year/">Microsoft Announces New Layoffs after Completing 2023 Financial Year</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-layoffs-2023-financial-year/">Microsoft Announces New Layoffs after Completing 2023 Financial Year</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/microsoft-corporation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Microsoft Corp</a> (NASDAQ: MSFT) announced a new round of layoffs on Monday to trim its staff strength further. The tech giant <a href="https://www.geekwire.com/2023/new-round-of-microsoft-job-cuts-hits-customer-service-support-and-sales-teams/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">confirmed</a> the internal announcement to GeekWire but did not indicate when the layoffs would begin or how many people would lose their jobs.</p>
<p>However, although Microsoft did not specify, data from the Worker Adjustment and Retraining Notification (<a href="https://esd.wa.gov/about-employees/WARN" target="_blank" rel="noopener">WARN</a>) system from Washington state’s Employment Security Department indicates the layoffs would affect 276 people, including 210 in Redmond and Bellevue &#8211; both in Washington and 66 remote positions. The job cuts are coming just as Microsoft concluded its 2023 fiscal year.</p>
<p>In a statement referenced by GeekWire, a company spokesperson said making personnel changes is crucial to the success of the company:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Organizational and workforce adjustments are a necessary and regular part of managing our business. We will continue to prioritize and invest in strategic growth areas for our future and in support of our customers and partners.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>Earlier Microsoft Layoffs</h2>
<p>In January, Microsoft <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-lay-off-employees/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">announced</a> layoffs that could affect up to 11,000 employees. The company’s aim was to achieve cost-effective operations as the global economy dwindled.</p>
<p>The decision to conduct the staff layoffs also likely stemmed from the ill effects of the global economic downturn. In addition to Microsoft’s Azure cloud platform not performing as expected, MSFT was also declining. CEO <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/satya-nadella/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Satya Nadella</a> had said that “the next two years are probably going to be the most challenging”. According to him, the company would likely experience some “normalization” following the “acceleration” experienced during the pandemic. Nadella also added that a real recession could affect Microsoft as well.</p>
<p>Last October, Microsoft quietly conducted a round of layoffs that affected less than 1,000 positions. A <a href="https://www.businessinsider.com/microsoft-layoffs-widespread-xbox-azure-government-2022-10?r=US&amp;IR=T" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a> stated that the layoff mainly affected divisions, including its Xbox division and the Microsoft Strategic Missions and Technology organization. According to a company spokesperson, the decision resulted from evaluating priorities and making structural adjustments.</p>
<h2>Tech Layoffs since 2022</h2>
<p>Microsoft’s recent round of layoffs follows multiple, seemingly unending layoffs in the global technology sector. According to a TechCrunch <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2023/07/06/tech-industry-layoffs-2023/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a>, there were 10,524 layoffs in June 2023, including Microsoft, Meta, Y Combinator, Twitter, Waymo, GitHub, and Yahoo. The report states a higher number for May, with layoffs affecting 14,555 employees. The highest month was January, with a record 84,714 employees laid off.</p>
<p>According to tracker Layoffs.fyi, 844 tech companies have laid off 216,364 employees in 2023, as of July 11. Crunchbase <a href="https://news.crunchbase.com/startups/tech-layoffs/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">states</a> that so far, Amazon has had the largest number of layoffs in 2023, affecting 16,000 roles. Alphabet had the second largest at 12,000.</p>
<p>Layoffs.fyi puts 2022 tech layoffs at a total of 164,709 across 1,058 companies. In November, Meta <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/zuckerberg-meta-employee-layoffs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">announced</a> 11,000 job cuts, while Amazon.com Inc cut off 18,000 employees, 6% of the company’s workforce. Salesforce also <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/salesforce-workforce-pandemic/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">revealed</a> it would lay off 10% of its workforce, affecting over 7,000 people. As of July 11, 2023, the company has more than 72,000 employees globally.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/drop-bayc-apecoin-all-time-low/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-layoffs-2023-financial-year/">Microsoft Announces New Layoffs after Completing 2023 Financial Year</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-layoffs-2023-financial-year/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Drop in BAYC NFT Prices Pushes ApeCoin to All-Time Low</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/drop-bayc-apecoin-all-time-low/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/drop-bayc-apecoin-all-time-low/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 09:53:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[animoca brands]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ape]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ape foundation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bored ape]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[decentraland]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nayc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sand]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sandbox]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=262403</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/drop-bayc-apecoin-all-time-low/">Drop in BAYC NFT Prices Pushes ApeCoin to All-Time Low</a></p>
<p>The drop in the floor price of the BAYC NFTs has a spillover effect into ApeCoin (APE), which is an important part of Yuga Labs' virtual world called Otherside.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/drop-bayc-apecoin-all-time-low/">Drop in BAYC NFT Prices Pushes ApeCoin to All-Time Low</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/drop-bayc-apecoin-all-time-low/">Drop in BAYC NFT Prices Pushes ApeCoin to All-Time Low</a></p>
<p>The NFT market has been currently under pressure with floor prices for some of the top <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NFT</a> projects hitting new lows. A week back, the floor price of prominent collections like the Bored Ape Yacht Club (BAYC) dropped to its 20-month low. The floor price of BAYC NFTs dropped to 30 ETH, which is approximately $58,000 as of the current price. However, this BAYC drop has had a spillover effect on Apecoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/apecoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">APE</a>) recently.</p>
<p>As per <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/apecoin" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">data</a> from CoinGecko, the cryptocurrency associated with Yuga Labs&#8217; Bored Ape NFT collection has experienced a 15% decline in the past two weeks, reaching a new all-time low of $1.85 on Friday.</p>
<p>Amidst the challenges faced by the NFT market, ApeCoin continues to face downward pressure. Although the floor price of Bored Ape NFTs has seen a slight recovery from its recent lows, ApeCoin came very close to reaching a new bottom on Monday. It was just two cents away from its previous low set on Friday.</p>
<p>Last year on March 22, during the peak of the NFT market, ApeCoin made a strong debut. Soon in April 2022, the APE price touched an all-time high of $26.70 with its market cap reaching close to $7.6 billion. But since then, the price of ApeCoin (APE) has corrected more than 93% as of date.</p>
<h2>ApeCoin and Yuga Labs</h2>
<p>ApeCoin is an important part of Yuga Labs&#8217; virtual world called Otherside. It acts as the main currency within the virtual world. In March, around 7,200 Voyagers participated in a playtest of Otherside, giving them a preview of the upcoming game.</p>
<p>The token was introduced by the ApeCoin DAO, which is a community-driven organization that allows members, including Bored Ape holders, to have a say in projects and rules.</p>
<p>The APE Foundation is responsible for managing the token and overseeing the operations of the DAO. Recently, new members were voted into the foundation&#8217;s special counsel, filling the seats left by Animoca Brands Chairman Yat Siu and Reddit co-founder Alexis Ohanian.</p>
<p>When ApeCoin was introduced, Bored Ape holders and those who owned NFTs from the Mutant Ape Yacht Club collection were eligible to claim a specific number of tokens.</p>
<p>Despite ApeCoin&#8217;s price is at a low point, its market capitalization is approximately $700 million, which is comparable to the total value of tokens used in other metaverse projects. CoinGecko data shows that this market capitalization is similar to The Sandbox&#8217;s <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/the-sandbox/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SAND</a> ($769 million) and Decentraland&#8217;s <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/decentraland/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">MANA</a> ($699 million).</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/developer-loopholes-brazil-cbdc/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/drop-bayc-apecoin-all-time-low/">Drop in BAYC NFT Prices Pushes ApeCoin to All-Time Low</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/drop-bayc-apecoin-all-time-low/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Developer Digs Out Control Loopholes in Brazil’s CBDC Code</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/developer-loopholes-brazil-cbdc/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/developer-loopholes-brazil-cbdc/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 09:47:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[banco central do brasil]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital real]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=262409</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/developer-loopholes-brazil-cbdc/">Developer Digs Out Control Loopholes in Brazil&#8217;s CBDC Code</a></p>
<p>Brazil is one of several countries around the world in various phases of CBDC implementation and adoption.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/developer-loopholes-brazil-cbdc/">Developer Digs Out Control Loopholes in Brazil&#8217;s CBDC Code</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/developer-loopholes-brazil-cbdc/">Developer Digs Out Control Loopholes in Brazil&#8217;s CBDC Code</a></p>
<p>Pedro Magalhães, a prominent blockchain developer and founder of tech consulting firm Iora Labs, is said to have reverse-engineered the source code of Brazil&#8217;s pilot <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-central-bank-digital-currency-cbdc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Central Bank Digital Currency</a> (CBDC) and uncovered a stunning finding.</p>
<p>The developer <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/posts/pemagalhaes_github-ioralabsrealdigitalsmartcontracts-activity-7082009809549484032-Beqi/?utm_source=share&amp;utm_medium=member_desktop" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">claims</a> to have discovered code features that might potentially offer a central authority the ability to freeze funds or change balances. This finding raises questions about the supposed decentralized nature of blockchain technology and the consequences for financial sovereignty.</p>
<h2>Brazil’s CBDC Experiment</h2>
<p>The recent <a href="https://github.com/bacen/pilotord-kit-onboarding" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">publication</a> of the source code for Brazil&#8217;s Digital Real pilot project on the GitHub portal has drawn attention to the country&#8217;s efforts in building a CBDC. The Brazilian Central Bank stressed that the project is only for testing purposes and that the disclosed architecture may be modified further.</p>
<p>This approach allows for the identification and rectification of any potential issues or vulnerabilities before the CBDC progresses to a live operational stage. Following the publication, Pedro Magalhães made significant claims regarding his ability to &#8220;reverse engineer&#8221; the open source code of Banco Central do Brazil&#8217;s Digital Real.</p>
<p>His analysis has revealed various functions within the code that provide significant control over the digital currency. These functions include the ability to freeze and unfreeze accounts, manipulate balances, transfer Digital Real between addresses, and create or burn Digital Real from specific addresses.</p>
<p>The developer has since argued that these functions could serve certain beneficial purposes despite the fact that they were initially viewed as a potential threat to the decentralized nature of blockchain technology, Magalhães suggests that Brazil&#8217;s Central Bank may likely maintain these functions to facilitate secured loan functions and other financial operations on Decentralized Finance (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-decentralized-finance-defi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">DeFi</a>) protocols.</p>
<h2>Focus of the Brazilian CBDC</h2>
<p>Brazil is one of several countries around the world in various phases of CBDC implementation and adoption. Brazil’s Central Bank’s initiative to introduce the Digital Real as an extension of the country’s physical currency represents a significant step toward greater financial inclusion.</p>
<p>The Digital Real can be exchanged on a one-to-one basis with the traditional currency, maintaining the same price and value. This unique approach combines the stability of fiat currencies with the benefits of decentralized technology, allowing for faster and more secure transactions.</p>
<p>According to <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bank-of-brazil-participants-cbdc-pilot/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reports</a>, Banco Central do Brasil, has strategically chosen to focus its Digital Real solution primarily on wholesale transactions rather than retail. This decision is motivated by the fact that Brazil already has a highly effective digital payment system known as Pix.</p>
<p>Pix, which was launched back in 2020 by the Brazilian central bank, has quickly gained popularity, with over 60% of Brazilians currently using it for e-commerce payments. Rather than competing with Pix, the Central Bank aims to follow its successful model in other areas of financial services, particularly at the wholesale level.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/grayscale-sec-bitcoin-based-etf/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/developer-loopholes-brazil-cbdc/">Developer Digs Out Control Loopholes in Brazil&#8217;s CBDC Code</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/developer-loopholes-brazil-cbdc/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Grayscale Criticizes SEC for Approving Leveraged Bitcoin-Based ETF, While Its Own Application Was Rejected</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/grayscale-sec-bitcoin-based-etf/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/grayscale-sec-bitcoin-based-etf/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Darya Rudz]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 09:31:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funds & ETFs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin etf regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[grayscale]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[grayscale etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[grayscale investments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[grayscale sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[grayscale sec lawsuit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec bitcoin etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[volatility shares trust]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=262387</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/grayscale-sec-bitcoin-based-etf/">Grayscale Criticizes SEC for Approving Leveraged Bitcoin-Based ETF, While Its Own Application Was Rejected</a></p>
<p>According to Grayscale, the only way to eliminate SEC’s unequal treatment of BTC ETPs is "to allow proposed spot bitcoin ETPs like Grayscale’s to begin trading".</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/grayscale-sec-bitcoin-based-etf/">Grayscale Criticizes SEC for Approving Leveraged Bitcoin-Based ETF, While Its Own Application Was Rejected</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/grayscale-sec-bitcoin-based-etf/">Grayscale Criticizes SEC for Approving Leveraged Bitcoin-Based ETF, While Its Own Application Was Rejected</a></p>
<p>One of the leaders in digital currency investing <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/grayscale/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Grayscale Investments LLC</a> has criticized the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) for approving a leveraged Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a>) exchange-traded fund (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-cryptocurrency-etf/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ETF</a>). Previously, the SEC had rejected Grayscale&#8217;s spot Bitcoin ETF application. Now, Grayscale is suing the regulatory agency over a violation of the Administrative Procedures Act.</p>
<p>On June 27, Volatility Shares Trust’s leveraged Bitcoin futures ETF was listed on Cboe BZX Exchange, without the interference from SEC in the process. Meanwhile, Volatility Shares Trust was expecting a denial since SEC has a pattern of rejecting numerous crypto-linked ETF applications. Neither SEC nor the US Commodity Futures Trading Commission approved or disapproved the proposed ETF, and Volatility Shares Trust&#8217;s registration statement came into effect. The fund looks for investment returns that are equivalent to double the return of the CME Bitcoin Futures Daily Roll Index.</p>
<p>Observing the listing, Grayscale could not ignore the fact that the SEC has not approved any spot crypto ETFs but has approved ones tied to BTC futures. Back in June 2022, the SEC rejected Grayscale’s own proposal to convert its Bitcoin Trust into an ETF. Grayscale immediately sued the regulator, alleging the commission violated the Administrative Procedure Act and the Securities Exchange Act of 1934 by discriminating between issuers of the two types of ETFs on an &#8220;arbitrary and capricious&#8221; basis.</p>
<p>Yesterday, Grayscale lawyers notified the US Court of Appeals for the District of Columbia Circuit of the listing of Volatility Shares Trust’s leveraged BTC futures ETF.</p>
<p>In the <a href="https://grayscale.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Grayscale-28j-letter-re-2x-BTC-futures-ETF-7.7.23.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">letter</a>, Grayscale&#8217;s lawyers stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The fact that the Commission has allowed a leveraged bitcoin futures ETP to begin trading demonstrates that the Commission continues to arbitrarily treat spot bitcoin ETPs differently than bitcoin futures ETPs.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>They further added:</p>
<div title="Page 2">
<div>
<div>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;While the Commission could theoretically correct its discriminatory treatment of spot bitcoin ETPs by rescinding its approval of all bitcoin-based ETPs, the Commission’s apparent willingness to permit even a leveraged bitcoin futures ETP &#8211; a particularly high-risk version of a bitcoin futures product &#8211; makes clear that the Commission has no intention of doing so.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>According to Grayscale, the only way to eliminate SEC’s unequal treatment of BTC ETPs is &#8220;to allow proposed spot bitcoin ETPs like Grayscale’s to begin trading&#8221;.</p>
<p>In addition, Grayscale has stated that Volatility Shares’ 2x Bitcoin Strategy ETF (or BITX) exposes investors to a much riskier investment product than traditional Bitcoin futures exchange-traded products (ETPs). The latter encompasses risks related to both the futures and spot Bitcoin markets. However, SEC believes that futures products are harder to manipulate. As the agency explained, they are based on prices from the CME, which is regulated by the Commodity Futures Trading Commission.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/brian-armstrong-old-tweets-twitter/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/grayscale-sec-bitcoin-based-etf/">Grayscale Criticizes SEC for Approving Leveraged Bitcoin-Based ETF, While Its Own Application Was Rejected</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/grayscale-sec-bitcoin-based-etf/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Brian Armstrong Deletes Tons of Old Tweets but Crypto Twitter Recovers Them</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/brian-armstrong-old-tweets-twitter/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/brian-armstrong-old-tweets-twitter/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 09:10:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brian armstrong]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brian armstrong coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sam bankman-fried]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sbf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=262395</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/brian-armstrong-old-tweets-twitter/">Brian Armstrong Deletes Tons of Old Tweets but Crypto Twitter Recovers Them</a></p>
<p>The move has raised concerns within the crypto community on Twitter even as many continue to read various meanings to the decision.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/brian-armstrong-old-tweets-twitter/">Brian Armstrong Deletes Tons of Old Tweets but Crypto Twitter Recovers Them</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/brian-armstrong-old-tweets-twitter/">Brian Armstrong Deletes Tons of Old Tweets but Crypto Twitter Recovers Them</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase</a> CEO <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/brian-armstrong/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Brian Armstrong</a> recently went on a deletion spree, taking down many of his old tweets on social media app Twitter. Simultaneously, the trusted internet archive The WayBack Machine has also removed all evidence of Armstrong&#8217;s tweets from its archive as well.</p>
<p>These moves have now raised concerns within the crypto community on Twitter even as many continue to read various meanings to the decision.</p>
<p>To this end, the community, led by pro-Bitcoin tweeter @Pledditor, has now launched a hunt to recover the deleted tweets.</p>
<p>According to @Pledditor, the hunt will find links to Brian&#8217;s old tweets via alternative archival services. And while these tweets will be between 2015 and 2018, the new archive will focus only on “tweets with verifiable archive links”, he says.</p>
<h2>Why Did Brian Armstrong Delete Old Tweets?</h2>
<p>Meanwhile, the reason behind Armstrong&#8217;s decision to delete his old tweets remains unclear. However, some believe that the decision may be a result of the ongoing regulatory scrutiny that Coinbase is currently facing. That is with the US Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>). And of which, Armstrong&#8217;s intentions may now be questionable.</p>
<p>More so, the tweets recovered so far border around several topics. These topics range from ordinary daily updates about Coinbase to more controversial views on its future and crypto at large.</p>
<p>For example, in one of the recovered tweets, Armstrong suggested a for-profit Bitcoin fork. At another time, he mentioned a 4% ETH pump after Coinbase listed it.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, it should be noted that Armstrong is not alone when it comes to crypto CEOs becoming unsure about some of their old takes on social media.</p>
<p>Back in November 2022, digital asset information platform, The Tie, put together a <a href="https://twitter.com/TheTieIO/status/1592366871386681344" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">list</a> of all tweets that former FTX chief <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/sam-bankman-fried/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Sam Bankman-Fried</a> (SBF) deleted.</p>
<p>More recently, Justin Sun’s exchange Poloniex was also found to have taken down several tweets relating to an ‘SEC-focused token’ giveaway. That was after crypto Twitter kicked and raised concerns.</p>
<p>As of publication, the tech mogul is yet to publicly comment on his reasons for the deleting rampage. However, the recovery of his old tweets remains an ongoing project.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-global-currency-boe/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/brian-armstrong-old-tweets-twitter/">Brian Armstrong Deletes Tons of Old Tweets but Crypto Twitter Recovers Them</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/brian-armstrong-old-tweets-twitter/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Remains Largely Speculative Asset than Global Currency, Says BoE’s Andrew Bailey</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-global-currency-boe/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-global-currency-boe/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 09:06:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bank of england]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[boe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=262393</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-global-currency-boe/">Bitcoin Remains Largely Speculative Asset than Global Currency, Says BoE’s Andrew Bailey</a></p>
<p>The Bank of England’s governor reiterated that fiat currencies will not be replaced by crypto like Bitcoin since they are extremely speculative assets.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-global-currency-boe/">Bitcoin Remains Largely Speculative Asset than Global Currency, Says BoE’s Andrew Bailey</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-global-currency-boe/">Bitcoin Remains Largely Speculative Asset than Global Currency, Says BoE’s Andrew Bailey</a></p>
<p>The current impasse between the fiat market and the crypto assets industry has undeniably put most central banks, including the Bank of England (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/bank-of-england/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BoE</a>), in an alert mode. Over the years, experts have argued how internet money will prove problematic to tax collection. Furthermore, most <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> holders are long-term, and there are few mechanisms to tax unrealized profits in the industry. Additionally, the ability to self-custody in the cryptocurrency market has significantly reduced the need for traditional banks, especially with the emergence of the neo-banking sector.</p>
<p>As a result, the antagonism between the traditional banking sector and the cryptocurrency industry is evidently ongoing, particularly during the cryptocurrency winter. Nonetheless, traditional investment fund managers, led by the largest hedge fund with nearly $10 trillion in AUM, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/blackrock/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BlackRock Inc</a> (NYSE: BLK) have increased their interest in the cryptocurrency market amid rising global inflation.</p>
<h2>BoE Governor Speaks on Bitcoin and Economic Outlook</h2>
<p>According to BoE Governor Andrew Bailey, the high increase in borrowing cost has undeniably widened the use of Bitcoin as a speculative asset as more investors navigate the high cost of living. The high inflation and a possible economic recession incoming, which has been predicted to happen during the second half of 2023, have seen most investors flee the fiat market to the crypto industry. Currently, the United Kingdom’s inflation stands at about 8.7 percent, more than four times higher than the desired 2 percent.</p>
<p>“Some of that tightening is still to come through the policy pipeline, and we expect underlying inflationary pressures to recede as headline inflation falls,” Bailey <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-07-10/boe-governor-says-uk-inflation-likely-to-drop-markedly-in-2023" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a> in the text on Monday.</p>
<p>Bailey further noted that the energy crisis, which was mostly exacerbated by the Russia-Ukraine war, is expected to ease in the coming months. A drop in energy prices is a direct ease in food prices.</p>
<p>“Looking ahead, headline inflation is set to fall markedly over the remainder of the year. This largely owes to lower energy prices as last year’s substantial increases drop out of the annual calculation. Food prices should fall too as lower commodity prices feed through to prices in the shops,” he added.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Bailey criticized the cryptocurrency industry including the stablecoins market for failing to meet the standards of safe money. Worth noting that the Bank of England is actively working on rolling out a Central Bank Digital Currency that operates in a similar manner to the stablecoins. However, some central banks have been criticized for using the digital currency industry to suppress financial freedom.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">BOE&#8217;S BAILEY: BITCOIN-TYPE CRYPTO BEST SEEN AS EXTREMELY SPECULATIVE ASSETS</p>
<p>— *Walter Bloomberg (@DeItaone) <a href="https://twitter.com/DeItaone/status/1678420646315827203?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 10, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Nonetheless, the United Kingdom has already enacted regulatory policies to safely adopt the cryptocurrency market through blockchain technology.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/arkham-hashing-referral-links/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-global-currency-boe/">Bitcoin Remains Largely Speculative Asset than Global Currency, Says BoE’s Andrew Bailey</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-global-currency-boe/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Arkham Slammed for Using Weak Hashing Method on Referral Links</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/arkham-hashing-referral-links/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/arkham-hashing-referral-links/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 09:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[arkham]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[arkm]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=262390</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/arkham-hashing-referral-links/">Arkham Slammed for Using Weak Hashing Method on Referral Links</a></p>
<p>The security weakness in the Arkham protocol raises a lot of questions in the entire network.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/arkham-hashing-referral-links/">Arkham Slammed for Using Weak Hashing Method on Referral Links</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/arkham-hashing-referral-links/">Arkham Slammed for Using Weak Hashing Method on Referral Links</a></p>
<p>Arkham (ARKM) network, a blockchain data provider that <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-arkham-arkm-launchpad/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">announced</a> its token sale to raise $2.5M on Binance Launchpad, has been <a href="https://www.theblock.co/post/238764/arkham-referral-links-appear-to-reveal-user-email-addresses" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">slammed</a> for using weak methods to store users’ private data. After launching its token sale on Binance, Arkham unveiled a program to allow users to invite others for base rewards in ARKM. However, some Twitter Inc. users were quick to spot the weakness in the referral hashing method. Notably, by using a simple decoding tool, like base64decode, anyone can decipher the email of Arkham users sharing their referral links through social media platforms.</p>
<p>Incidentally, Arkham protocol previously responded to the allegations of sharing users’ private information by deeming it a feature of its network. As a result, most crypto users who prefer to have their private information anonymous for their safety were angered by the move to have their private info publicly available.</p>
<p>Notably, all Arkham referral program users who shared their links through the internet have their emails already publicly available. The blockchain data provided puts most users at risk of being attacked through phishing links among other internet-related challenges.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">ABSOLUTE LMAO. ALL <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/ARKHAM?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#ARKHAM</a> REFERRAL LINKS SHARED ON TWITTER IS DOXXING EVERYONE BECAUSE THE EMAIL IS IN THE REFERRAL URL. <a href="https://twitter.com/inversebrah?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@inversebrah</a><a href="https://t.co/HM6veJOmNp">https://t.co/HM6veJOmNp</a> -&gt; bkatmis012@gmail.com <a href="https://t.co/1INvtXLEva">https://t.co/1INvtXLEva</a> <a href="https://t.co/m38VnNMS8k">pic.twitter.com/m38VnNMS8k</a></p>
<p>— m4gicpotato ⟁ (@m4gicpotato) <a href="https://twitter.com/m4gicpotato/status/1678462447005618176?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 10, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The security weakness in the Arkham protocol raises a lot of questions in the entire network that has taken several months to launch and also get a chance to scale via Binance Launchpad. Although the company claims it is an internal feature, the thought of having private information readily available on the internet is scary to most users in their days and age.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">It&#8217;s not a bug it&#8217;s a feature <a href="https://t.co/EV0SIbLbEJ">https://t.co/EV0SIbLbEJ</a></p>
<p>— Tree of Alpha (@Tree_of_Alpha) <a href="https://twitter.com/Tree_of_Alpha/status/1678475809344856086?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 10, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2>Closer Look at Arkham (ARKM) Protocol</h2>
<p>The Arkham protocol uses artificial intelligence (AI) to deanonymize the blockchain, thus showing users the people and companies behind definite cryptocurrency transactions. Notably, the Arkham network has its own proprietary artificial intelligence engine dubbed ULTRA, to algorithmically match addresses with real-world entities. Through its intel-to-earn program, Arkham introduces an economy that matches buyers and sellers of blockchain data at scale.</p>
<p>The ARKM token is the governance crypto unit used in the Arkham rewards program, particularly on the intel exchange. Moreover, token holders are entitled to governance rights and earn programs through staking.</p>
<p>The Arkham project has attracted significant crypto investors’ attention having raised more than $10 million in two rounds as of July 10. Reportedly, the latest funding round saw the Arkham project valued at approximately $150 million, with strategic backing from Tim Draper, Bedrock Capital, Wintermute Trading, GSR Markets, and the co-founders of Palantir and OpenAI.</p>
<p>However, the company could lose its retail customers due to its poor methods of storing users’ data. Nonetheless, the Arkham protocol has minimal competition in the cryptocurrency industry, thus being able to navigate easily.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/astra-share-price-stock-split/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/arkham-hashing-referral-links/">Arkham Slammed for Using Weak Hashing Method on Referral Links</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/arkham-hashing-referral-links/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4103 metric#misses=41 metric#hit-ratio=99.0 metric#bytes=1100871 metric#prefetches=167 metric#store-reads=49 metric#store-writes=2 metric#store-hits=218 metric#store-misses=2 metric#sql-queries=34 metric#ms-total=111.99 metric#ms-cache=8.66 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.1732 metric#ms-cache-ratio=7.7 -->