<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 19:29:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>ARK amends spot Bitcoin ETF filing to include surveillance sharing agreement</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/ark-amends-spot-bitcoin-etf-filing-to-include-surveillance-sharing-agreement/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 19:29:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ARK Investment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/ark-amends-spot-bitcoin-etf-filing-to-include-surveillance-sharing-agreement/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>ARK&#8217;s amended 19b-4 includes a surveillance sharing agreement with CBOE and a US crypto exchange. ARK Invest founder and CEO Cathie Wood says the Ark 21Shares Bitcoin ETF is first in line for approval as &#8220;oldest&#8221; filing before the SEC. BlackRock&#8217;s spot Bitcoin ETF also included a SSA with Coinbase. ARK Invest and 21Shares have&#160;amended [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ark-amends-spot-bitcoin-etf-filing-to-include-surveillance-sharing-agreement/">ARK amends spot Bitcoin ETF filing to include surveillance sharing agreement</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">ARK&rsquo;s amended 19b-4 includes a surveillance sharing agreement with CBOE and a US crypto exchange.</li>
<li dir="ltr">ARK Invest founder and CEO Cathie Wood says the Ark 21Shares Bitcoin ETF is first in line for approval as &ldquo;oldest&rdquo; filing before the SEC.</li>
<li dir="ltr">BlackRock&rsquo;s spot Bitcoin ETF also included a SSA with Coinbase.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/ark-investment/">ARK Invest</a> and 21Shares have<a href="https://cdn.cboe.com/resources/regulation/rule_filings/pending/2023/SR-CboeBZX-2023-028-Amendment-No-1.pdf" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">&nbsp;<u>amended their 19b-4</u></a> for the ARK 21Shares Bitcoin ETF &nbsp;refiled in April and which is due a decision from the SEC in August.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Specifically, the companies have informed the SEC that they have entered into a surveillance sharing agreement (SSA) with the CBOE BZX Exchange and a US-based crypto exchange provider of spot trading for <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Speculation is that the exchange in question is Coinbase, the largest US-based crypto platform that incidentally was sued by the SEC over allegations of securities violations.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What does ARK&rsquo;s amended 19b-4 mean?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The amended filing means the ARK 21Shares Bitcoin ETF now has a similar structure to that of BlackRock, and puts the ETF first in line for approval as the &ldquo;oldest filing&rdquo; before the regulator.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>Since 2015, with increasing conviction, ARK has researched the crypto space and has invested in crypto related equities. On April 25, 2023, in partnership with 21Shares, we filed for the ARK 21Shares Bitcoin ETF and are proud to have the oldest active filing before the SEC and expect to be first in line to be considered for approval,</em>&rdquo; Cathie Wood, founder and CEO of ARK Invest<a href="https://www.21shares.com/blog/21shares-spot-btc-etf-usa" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">&nbsp;<u>said</u></a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Eric Balchunas, a senior ETF analyst for Bloomberg, has <a href="https://twitter.com/EricBalchunas/status/1674059620027883520" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">noted</a> that ARK&rsquo;s move adds a new twist to the spot ETF plot. He points to the anticipated decision on the ETF in August and the fact that BlackRock would likely want to be first to market.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">A decision on the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/grayscale/">Grayscale</a> lawsuit against the SEC is also due around the same time.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Nate also brings up another twist: would BlackRock (who doesn't play) even allow Coinbase to enter into a SSE agreement with another that would help another issuer beat them to market? If so ARK would need another crypto exchange to use.  <a href="https://t.co/nBKdNxY1bH">https://t.co/nBKdNxY1bH</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Eric Balchunas (@EricBalchunas) <a href="https://twitter.com/EricBalchunas/status/1674059620027883520?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 28, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">BlackRock filed their spot Bitcoin ETF on June 15, including an SSA. Other asset managers have followed suit and the industry is buzzing on the prospects of an approval. Bitcoin price has reacted higher in the wake of the bullish sentiment, hitting highs above $31k. &nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ark-amends-spot-bitcoin-etf-filing-to-include-surveillance-sharing-agreement/">ARK amends spot Bitcoin ETF filing to include surveillance sharing agreement</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>ZEN will no longer be a privacy coin after Horizen update</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/zen-will-no-longer-be-a-privacy-coin-after-horizen-update/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/zen-will-no-longer-be-a-privacy-coin-after-horizen-update/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 18:02:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/zen-will-no-longer-be-a-privacy-coin-after-horizen-update/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Horizen is removing privacy from mainchain shielded pools ZEN will no longer be a privacy coin when the deprecation is activated. The upcoming deprecation of the Horizen mainchain shielded pools comes after the adoption of ZenIP 42204 Horizen is going ahead with plans to remove support for shielded transactions on the mainchain, a move that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/zen-will-no-longer-be-a-privacy-coin-after-horizen-update/">ZEN will no longer be a privacy coin after Horizen update</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Horizen is removing privacy from mainchain shielded pools</li>
<li dir="ltr">ZEN will no longer be a privacy coin when the deprecation is activated.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The upcoming deprecation of the Horizen mainchain shielded pools comes after the adoption of ZenIP 42204</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Horizen is going ahead with plans to remove support for shielded transactions on the mainchain, a move that will see the native ZEN token no longer considered a privacy coin.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The blockchain platform <a href="https://blog.horizen.io/upcoming-deprecation-of-the-horizen-mainchain-shielded-pools/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">announced</a> on Wednesday that an upcoming deprecation of the mainchain shielded pools will proceed after the community approved ZenIP 42204. The change is expected to activate via a hard fork and will see shielded transactions with transparent inputs prevented at the consensus level.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">The deprecation of <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Horizen?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Horizen</a> mainchain shielded pools means privacy features will be removed from the Horizen main blockchain at the consensus level. This means <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24ZEN&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$ZEN</a> will no longer be a privacy coin after this change. Learn more about this upcoming change: <a href="https://t.co/HSno4RJaqO">https://t.co/HSno4RJaqO</a> <a href="https://t.co/GbMMrX9T48">pic.twitter.com/GbMMrX9T48</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Horizen (@horizenglobal) <a href="https://twitter.com/horizenglobal/status/1673819482383437827?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 27, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>After the deprecation of mainchain shielded pools, all privacy features will be removed from Horizen main blockchain at the consensus level. This also means ZEN will no longer be a privacy coin after this change</em>,&rdquo; the announcement read.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Horizen explains deprecation </h2>
<p dir="ltr">According to the Grayscale-backed layer 0 blockchain platform, the deprecation is being taken as a step to driving sustainable and growth for the ecosystem while mitigating against regulatory threats.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The goal is to ensure privacy technology is handled the right way, with the topic a hot one and which continues to impact the leading privacy-focused coins <a href="https://coinjournal.net/monero/">Monero</a> (XMR), <a href="https://coinjournal.net/zcash/">Zcash</a> (ZEC) and Dash (DASH).</p>
<p dir="ltr">Horizen also notes that its shielded transactions rely on Sprout, an &ldquo;outdated&rdquo; privacy technology by ZCash. With the original Zcash release deprecated for sapling and blossom, the platform suggests its move allows it to improve and innovate.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Timelines for the removal of the mainchain shielded pools are put around August 2023 for the testnet and September 2023 for the mainnet.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/zen-will-no-longer-be-a-privacy-coin-after-horizen-update/">ZEN will no longer be a privacy coin after Horizen update</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/zen-will-no-longer-be-a-privacy-coin-after-horizen-update/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance opens trading for Maverick Protocol (MAV)</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-opens-trading-for-maverick-protocol-mav/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-opens-trading-for-maverick-protocol-mav/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 16:12:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-opens-trading-for-maverick-protocol-mav/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Binance opens trading for Pantera Capital and Coinbase backed Maverick Protocol (MAV) Maverick&#8217;s native token will trade against Bitcoin, USDT and TUSD. Binance added Maverick Protocol to its launchpool incubator earlier this month. Binance has opened trading for Maverick Protocol (MAV), the native token of a DeFi project backed by Founders Fund, Pantera Capital, Coinbase [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-opens-trading-for-maverick-protocol-mav/">Binance opens trading for Maverick Protocol (MAV)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Binance opens trading for Pantera Capital and Coinbase backed Maverick Protocol (MAV)</li>
<li dir="ltr">Maverick&rsquo;s native token will trade against Bitcoin, USDT and TUSD.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Binance added Maverick Protocol to its launchpool incubator earlier this month.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/binance/">Binance</a> has opened trading for Maverick Protocol (MAV), the native token of a <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/defi/">DeFi</a> project backed by Founders Fund, Pantera Capital, Coinbase Ventures and Binance Labs among others.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to an announcement by the leading crypto exchange, support will initially be for three trading pairs: MAV/BTC, MAV/USDT and MAV/TUSD. Maverick trading on Binance went live on June 28, 2023 at 08:00 (UTC).</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Binance?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Binance</a> will open trading for <a href="https://twitter.com/mavprotocol?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@mavprotocol</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24MAV&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$MAV</a>.<a href="https://t.co/8S7gg1aSGl">https://t.co/8S7gg1aSGl</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Binance (@binance) <a href="https://twitter.com/binance/status/1673617808419086338?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 27, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">Traders will benefit from zero fee trading on the MAV/TUSD pair &ldquo;until further notice,&rdquo; the exchange announced.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Binance&rsquo;s listing of Maverick Protocol comes a few weeks after the exchange added the token in its Launchpool. Apart from Binance, MAV can also be traded on Bitget and DigiFinex.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Maverick (MAV)?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Maverick Protocol is a composable decentralised exchange (DEX) powered by the Maverick AMM (automated market maker). As a DeFi infrastructure provider, Maverick focuses on improving capital efficiency for liquidity providers (LPs).</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;Maverick&rsquo;s goal is to eliminate inefficiency from DeFi by helping users put their liquidity where it can do the most work,&rdquo; the protocol recently posted on its Twitter account.</p>
<p dir="ltr">MAV is live on the Ethereum mainnet, zkSync and BNB Chain and has seen significant growth since it <a href="https://twitter.com/mavprotocol/status/1673937463616872451" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">launched</a> its Dynamic Distribution AMM. Trading volume on the DEX has hit over 2.5 billion.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">A few hours before the MAV token goes live on <a href="https://twitter.com/binance?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@binance</a>! Let's review some highlights of Maverick:</p>
<p>&bull; Hit top 5 DEXs on all chains by volume<br>&bull; Supported 2.5 B+ volume on chain<br>&bull; Supporting 30%+ <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/LST?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#LST</a> daily trading volume on chain<br>&bull; Backed by <a href="https://twitter.com/foundersfund?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@foundersfund</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/PanteraCapital?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@PanteraCapital</a></p>
<p>1/6</p>
<p>&mdash; Maverick Protocol (@mavprotocol) <a href="https://twitter.com/mavprotocol/status/1673937463616872451?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 28, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">The price of MAV rose to its all-time high above $0.58, with market cap rising to over $141 million. Circulating supply currently stands at 250 million MAV, and total supply at 2 billion tokens.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-opens-trading-for-maverick-protocol-mav/">Binance opens trading for Maverick Protocol (MAV)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-opens-trading-for-maverick-protocol-mav/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Fear and Greed Index Points to Bitcoin Price Path to $40K</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-fear-and-greed-index-points-to-bitcoin-price-path-to-40k/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-fear-and-greed-index-points-to-bitcoin-price-path-to-40k/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 15:59:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-fear-and-greed-index-points-to-bitcoin-price-path-to-40k/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The crypto fear and greed index has moved to the greed area of 62. Bitcoin price has more upside in the next few weeks to hit $40k. Crypto fear and greed index has moved to the greed area ahead of the upcoming Bitcoin options expiry.&#160;Bitcoin price was trading at $30,392 on Wednesday, where it has [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-fear-and-greed-index-points-to-bitcoin-price-path-to-40k/">Crypto Fear and Greed Index Points to Bitcoin Price Path to $40K</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The crypto fear and greed index has moved to the greed area of 62.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin price has more upside in the next few weeks to hit $40k.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Crypto fear and greed index has moved to the greed area ahead of the upcoming Bitcoin options expiry.&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/"><u>Bitcoin</u></a> price was trading at $30,392 on Wednesday, where it has been in the past few days. This price is a few points below the year-to-date high of $31,478. At its peak, the coin jumped by more than 104% from the lowest level in 2022.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Fear and greed index points to greed</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The crypto fear and greed index has made a strong recovery in the past few weeks. It has moved from the fear zone of 41 to the greed area of 62. This means that investors are getting modestly greedy helped by the recent ETF news. The most recent Bitcoin news came on Tuesday when Fidelity announced that it had filed its ETF proposal with the SEC.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/05/28/1687967901450-458d3f0b-b389-4a15-a72f-eb00073a0f39.jpg" style="width: 547px;height: 213.161px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="547" height="213.161"></p>
<p dir="ltr">Investors believe that a spot ETF will lead to more demand for Bitcoin from institutional investors. Still, this view should be taken with a grain of salt since ProShares Bitcoin Strategy ETF (BITO) has had modest growth in the past few years. It now has about $1 billion in assets. While BITO tracks Bitcoin futures, it has a close correlation with Bitcoin itself.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The fear and greed index points to more upside for Bitcoin since investors tend to buy it when there is greed in the market. Perhaps, these gains will happen ahead or after the upcoming Bitcoin options expiry scheduled for Friday this week.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Data shows that most of these options are calls with a strike price of about $30,000. This explains why Bitcoin has barely moved this week.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitcoin price prediction</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/05/28/1687967942418-19d4b27f-b7af-4223-9ef0-0b7ae8235e20.png" style="width: 619px;height: 301.697px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="619" height="301.697"></p>
<p dir="ltr">A good technical analysis can help you predict the next price action of a cryptocurrency or other assets. Turning to the daily chart, we see that Bitcoin is oscillating at the 50% Fibonacci Retracement level. This is an important level that traders look at.</p>
<p dir="ltr">At the same time, this is an important price since it was the highest point on April 14th. Most importantly, the coin has formed what looks like a bullish pennant pattern. Therefore, there is a likelihood that the price will soon have a bullish breakout as buyers target the next key level at $35,000. This price is about 15% above the current level. A move above this level will see it jump to the next resistance point at $40,000.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-fear-and-greed-index-points-to-bitcoin-price-path-to-40k/">Crypto Fear and Greed Index Points to Bitcoin Price Path to $40K</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-fear-and-greed-index-points-to-bitcoin-price-path-to-40k/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin correlation with gold drops, highlighting risk-on nature remains</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-correlation-with-gold-drops-highlighting-risk-on-nature-remains/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dan Ashmore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 14:30:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US Federal Reserve]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-correlation-with-gold-drops-highlighting-risk-on-nature-remains/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key Takeaways Bitcoin&#8217;s correlation with gold is currently at its lowest level since FTX collapsed in November Our Head of Research writes that while one day Bitcoin may become a store of value, the numbers say it currently trades like an extreme risk-on asset Bitcoin lost 76% of its value amid the pullback in risk [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-correlation-with-gold-drops-highlighting-risk-on-nature-remains/">Bitcoin correlation with gold drops, highlighting risk-on nature remains</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2 dir="ltr">Key Takeaways</h2>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Bitcoin&rsquo;s correlation with gold is currently at its lowest level since FTX collapsed in November</li>
<li dir="ltr">Our Head of Research writes that while one day Bitcoin may become a store of value, the numbers say it currently trades like an extreme risk-on asset</li>
<li dir="ltr">Bitcoin lost 76% of its value amid the pullback in risk assets once central banks around the world transitioned to tight monetary policy amid the inflation crisis</li>
<li dir="ltr">Meanwhile, gold traded flat and is currently close to all-time highs</li>
<li dir="ltr">Bitcoin&rsquo;s correlation with growth stocks and riskier sectors of the stock market remains tight</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p dir="ltr">One of the ultimate bull scenarios for Bitcoin is that it morphs into some kind of digital gold.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">For whatever reason, humans have been obsessed with this weird, shiny metal for thousands of years. Stories date back even further, but we have concrete evidence that gold was an important symbol of wealth in Ancient Egypt in 3000 BC, as well as part of everyday life and mythology.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin, on the other hand, was not around in Ancient Egypt. Nor was it around for the Middle Ages, the Great Depression in the early 20th century, a World War (yet?), the inflation and energy crisis of the 1970s, and it even missed most of the subprime mortgage crisis of 2008.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">In fact, Bitcoin was launched in January 2009, the Genesis blocked mined only two months before the stock market bottomed. Over the next twelve years, not only did the stock market recover, but it went absolutely bananas. Between the 2009 trough and the peak at the end of 2021, the S&amp;P 500 multiplied 7X while the Nasdaq jumped nearly 13X. In other words, Bitcoin was launched into one of the most explosive and longest bull markets in history. Until 2022, <em>it had never known anything</em> but basement-level interest rates and up-only markets.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Gold&rsquo;s hedge properties are what Bitcoin seeks</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Once 2022 came, risk assets sold off. The Nasdaq shed a third of its value; the S&amp;P 500 fell 20%. Bitcoin had dipped plenty before, but make no mistake: this was the first time it was staring a bear market in the wider economy in the face.</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14279740">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">&nbsp;Despite certain enthusiasts claiming Bitcoin would act as a hedge asset, this did <em>not&nbsp;</em>happen. By the end of 2022, Bitcoin was 76% off its high. In the most explosive inflationary environment since the 1970s and Bitcoin&rsquo;s first bear market, the asset was getting crushed. There was no debate: Bitcoin was trading like a risk-on asset. And today, it still is. &nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">That is not to say that the narrative could flip in the future. Personally, that is what I view as Bitcoin&rsquo;s upside: a store of value akin to gold. But while we can debate whether that may one day happen, it is unequivocal that Bitcoin currently trades like a risk-on asset. These are the facts of the case, and these are undisputed, to borrow Kevin Bacon&rsquo;s phrase from the absolute classic that is <em>A Few Good Men.&nbsp;</em></p>
<p dir="ltr">Gold, on the other hand, traded flat during 2022, and is currently trading close to all-time highs.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitcoin and gold correlation dipping</h2>
<p dir="ltr">For all the reasons discussed above, the correlation between gold and Bitcoin is particularly interesting to track. Using the 60-Day Pearson indicator, I have plotted it on the below chart.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14279413">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">Immediately, the past month jumps out. The correlation was a near-perfect 0.86 at the start of June, and had been around this level since late April. And then, it fell. It currently sits at 0.16, the lowest mark since FTX collapsed in November, sending the crypto market into a tailspin. But why?</p>
<p dir="ltr">Well, I don&rsquo;t really know. And that is kind of the point. Bitcoin, as it tends to do sometimes, is rising at the moment. Most likely, this is due to news of asset managers Blackrock and Fidelity filing ETFs, but maybe it&rsquo;s just Bitcoin doing its thing. Perhaps it is merely bouncing back from the sharp fall it took after the Binance and Coinbase lawsuits were announced back-to-back two weeks ago.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">But if we stretch out the time horizon on the previous graph, we see that the correlation between gold and Bitcoin bounces around a lot.</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14279889">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">It is challenging to put any pattern on that, to say the least. I thought I might try a different metric, so in the next graph I have used 90-Day Pearson instead of 60-Day. Predictably, the trend is less volatile, but there still appears to be no meaningful relationship here.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14279922">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">I think it&rsquo;s pretty clear that assessing the correlation coefficients directly proves that there is zero positive relationship between these two assets.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Federal Reserve holds the key</h2>
<p dir="ltr">In truth, I believe this actually says more about gold than Bitcoin. Gold is in a funny place at the moment, trading more off expectations of inflation and interest rate movements rather than current conditions. The correlation between gold and the stock market is therefore higher than what we have typically seen in the past. This is why we are seeing gold often advance when soft CPI numbers are announced, or when dovish Fed comments surface regarding interest rate policy.</p>
<p dir="ltr">If we step back and look at the big picture, it really is not complicated. Bitcoin has gone from $68,00 in November 2021, when money was cheap and risk assets were trading at outrageous valuations, to $15,500 last November, seven months into the swiftest hiking cycle in recent memory and the worst inflation crisis in 50 years. Then, it doubled to $30,000 as inflation numbers fell away and expectations around the length of the hiking cycle softened.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Along with all the fakeouts and reverberation in between, that is a hell of a lot of movement and clearly trading like an extreme-risk asset. Meanwhile, gold has been far less volatile, relatively range-bound between $1,600 and $2,000 for three years now.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Again, while Bitcoin may one day seize the crown of an uncorrelated asset, or a portfolio hedge to inflation, that is clearly not the case today. The below chart is the simplest method of all to show this, plotting Bitcoin&rsquo;s hand-in-hand relationship with the tech-heavy Nasdaq composite since the economy transitioned to this risk-off, tight monetary policy period.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14280066">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">A few months ago, Bitcoin rose during the banking crisis, sparking some to declare it as decoupling from risk assets and the fiat world. As I <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/no-bitcoin-is-still-as-correlated-as-ever-with-the-stock-market-a-deep-dive/"><u>wrote</u></a> back then, this is nothing more than wishful thinking. Rather, it moved off expectations that the Fed would not be able to hike as aggressively in future if banks were going under due to the strain of these higher rates (indeed, soon after, the correlation <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-correlation-with-stocks-rises-again-normal-service-resumed/"><u>rose back up</u></a>).</p>
<p dir="ltr">The latest dip in correlation with gold, falling back down from the ultra-high 0.86ish value it has been for six weeks or so, is similar. There is nothing ambiguous about the situation at the moment &ndash; Bitcoin is trading like a risk-on asset. It may one day claim that coveted title of digital gold, but right now it is nowhere near.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-correlation-with-gold-drops-highlighting-risk-on-nature-remains/">Bitcoin correlation with gold drops, highlighting risk-on nature remains</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>AltSignals price prediction: analyst says investors see AI as an “internet moment&#8221;</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-price-prediction-analyst-says-investors-see-ai-as-an-internet-moment/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 11:22:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Google]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-price-prediction-analyst-says-investors-see-ai-as-an-internet-moment/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Analyst on AI: It&#8217;s transformational and an internet moment that could spark further growth across major tech companies. AltSignals is integrating AI-powered trading signals into its platform. The price of ASI will increase by 51% between the current and the final presale stage. AltSignals is about to enter the next stage of its presale event, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-price-prediction-analyst-says-investors-see-ai-as-an-internet-moment/">AltSignals price prediction: analyst says investors see AI as an “internet moment&#8221;</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Analyst on AI: It&rsquo;s transformational and an internet moment that could spark further growth across major tech companies.</li>
<li dir="ltr">AltSignals is integrating AI-powered trading signals into its platform.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The price of ASI will increase by 51% between the current and the final presale stage.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://token.altsignals.io/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>AltSignals</u></a> is about to enter the next stage of its presale event, so far successful given investors have scooped nearly 80 million ASI tokens. But what do experts say about the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/ai/"><u>AI</u></a> play in mainstream tech space and what are the implications for crypto projects leveraging the narrative?&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/google/"><u>Google</u></a> said on Thursday that it welcomed regulation of the AI industry, with head of Google Cloud Thomas Kurian<a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/06/28/google-has-had-productive-talks-with-eu-on-ai-act-cloud-boss-says.html" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">&nbsp;<u>telling</u></a> CNBC the tech giant&rsquo;s engagements with EU regulators has been productive.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Elsewhere, Dan Ives, the managing director and senior equity researcher at Wedbush Securities, noted AI wasn&rsquo;t just hype but technology that was set to be transformational over the next 20 to 30 years.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Notably, Ives&rsquo; bullish stance is down to the fact that tech behemoths backing the new trend are far more fundamentally resilient than the hype that impacted projects during the internet bubble.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In a CNBC<a href="https://www.cnbc.com/video/2023/06/28/were-in-the-beginning-of-a-new-tech-bull-market-with-ai-says-wedbush-securitiesa-dan-ives.html" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">&nbsp;<u>interview</u></a> aired on June 28, the Wedbush analyst pointed to Nvidia, Meta and Alphabet &ndash; soaring stocks as the companies are all expected to level up on their AI-informed guidance. The industry could see upwards of $1 trillion in inflows, Ives explained.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to him, it&rsquo;s an AI gold rush only paralleled by the 1995 internet and 2007 Apple iPhone breakout.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">AI predictions and what it means for AltSignals?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Experts see regulation and belief in artificial intelligence among top global tech companies as indicative of the power of AI.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In a burgeoning sector such as crypto, it could be massive. Positioned for the expected upward trajectory is trading signals company AltSignals, which is leveraging AI to bring extra benefits to investors within the trading industry.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">AltSignals in a nutshell</h2>
<p dir="ltr">As a project, AltSignals launched in 2017, offering manual trading signals for traders on markets such as forex, stocks and crypto. The company provided these via its proprietary algorithm AltAlgo. The success of the platform has seen it grow to a popular provider of market signals, boasting an expanding community of users.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Yet, AltSignals might be poised for even more growth after incorporating an artificial intelligence layer dubbed ActualizeAI. The AI-powered platform is taking all the signals and putting them into a suite of AI tools that leverage machine learning and natural language processing to improve on accuracy.</p>
<p dir="ltr">ASI is the native token that will power that ecosystem, giving holders membership access among other benefits such as the chance to earn passively from staking and governance.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Is buying AltSignals&rsquo; ASI token worth it?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals is in presale, with over $100k raised in its beta stage. The current stage is 95% sold out and investors have backed the team with $1.03 million out of the targeted $1.08 million. With only 5% of stage 1 to go, investors have a very small window in which to buy ASI at current prices of $0.015.</p>
<p dir="ltr">When the next stage rolls in, the token&rsquo;s value will jump to $0.01875. ASI&rsquo;s value will have jumped by 56% in just a few weeks. In the end, the AltSignals presale is expected to finalise with ASI token price at $0.02274 &ndash; a notable 89% increase from the initial price of $0.012. &nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Indeed, an investor who buys ASI today will still see a 51% upside on the value of their investment.</p>
<p dir="ltr">There&rsquo;s much more information on the AltSignals page that investors can sieve through as they look to invest in this project. If you are interested, you can visit the page <a href="https://token.altsignals.io/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>here</u></a>.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Will AltSignals price reach $5 by 2024?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Crypto analysts suggest the crypto market could rally hard after the SEC approves the first spot Bitcoin ETF in the US. For a timeline, one analyst <a href="https://twitter.com/Rewkang/status/1673833088563171329" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">points</a> to a potential upside over the next two months into the expected SEC deadline.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This could be crucial for AltSignals, which expects ASI to go live on exchanges in Q3, 2023 with listings on Uniswap, CoinGecko and CoinMarketCap. The roadmap then highlights listing on Bybit and Binance in early 2024. Delivering the project&rsquo;s developmental milestones, and combining these with bullish market conditions could catalyse ASI price higher.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In 2023, the main target could be psychologically desired $1, while a push from here in the next twelve months could put bulls on course for $5. These projections are however dependent on market conditions and whether AltSignals&rsquo; AI play delivers. Growing the user base from the current 52,000 or so could be the first step in this direction.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-price-prediction-analyst-says-investors-see-ai-as-an-internet-moment/">AltSignals price prediction: analyst says investors see AI as an “internet moment&#8221;</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum dApps settle on Solana with Neon EVM’s closed beta</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/closed-beta-version-of-neon-evm-launches-on-solanas-mainnet/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 09:49:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/closed-beta-version-of-neon-evm-launches-on-solanas-mainnet/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Neon EVM is a low-friction solution that enables Ethereum dApps to settle transactions on Solana. The EVM helps breach the gap between Ethereum and Solana. Since the Neon EVM beta is closed it will only accept transactions for those on the guest list. What is Neon EVM? Neon EVM is a low-friction solution that enables [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/closed-beta-version-of-neon-evm-launches-on-solanas-mainnet/">Ethereum dApps settle on Solana with Neon EVM’s closed beta</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Neon EVM is a low-friction solution that enables Ethereum dApps to settle transactions on Solana.</li>
<li>The EVM helps breach the gap between Ethereum and Solana.</li>
<li>Since the Neon EVM beta is closed it will only accept transactions for those on the guest list.</li>
</ul>
<h2>What is Neon EVM?</h2>
<p>Neon EVM is a low-friction solution that enables <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/what-is-ethereum/">Ethereum</a> dApps to settle transactions on Solana, eliminating the gap between these two leading blockchains.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Neon EVM positions Ethereum developers to enjoy the best of Solana&rsquo;s network, from low fees to high transaction speeds, and parallel transaction execution capabilities.&nbsp;</p>
<p>While Solana is one of the fastest, organically-growing chains, its incompatibility with EVM has left several hundred million in TVL, millions of users, and an entire ecosystem untouched by EVM multichain dApp developers &mdash; until now.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Neon EVM&rsquo;s pioneering solution is <em>the&nbsp;</em>anticipated innovation in the Solana ecosystem and makes Solana a viable option for multichain builders. Neon EVM brings together the best of both chains while ensuring the finality of settlements on Solana.</p>
<h2>What is Neon EVM closed beta?</h2>
<p>The launch of the closed beta version of Neon EVM, Neon EVM&beta;, to Solana&rsquo;s Mainnet is a significant milestone on the roadmap.</p>
<p>Neon EVM&beta; is a fully-functioning Neon EVM with one major alteration: it supports fee-free transactions.</p>
<p>This means that all transactions are settled to Solana&rsquo;s L1 and require payment in Sol, as per any Solana-settled transaction. However, in beta, the NEON token is not requested by the Proxy Operator responsible for accepting the transaction request and ensuring that it is finalized.</p>
<h2>Why launch in beta?</h2>
<p>The Neon EVM ecosystem includes many more players than just the Neon EVM and the Proxy Operators that accept and settle transaction requests. It includes DAO, oracles, indexers, wallets, multisigs, bridges, explorers, and more. Neon EVM&beta; provides an opportunity for all parties to deploy and test to ensure the seamless integration of their services before the official Solana Mainnet launch.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/05/26/1687776871651-caf251fa-2ab7-45fe-9fec-49c5be1fe00e.png" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="615" height="270"></p>
<p>While Neon EVM could have chosen to do a Shadow Mainnet launch on a fork of the Solana mainchain, launching directly to Mainnet offers significant advantages. Not least of which is that deployed and tested contracts will retain their addresses on Solana Mainnet.</p>
<h2>Why launch in closed beta?</h2>
<p>Launching in closed beta allows the Neon EVM team to onboard and test the services of ecosystem players in controlled phases. The first phase onboarded the infrastructure components, and the second phase accepted dApps and will test the connection of wallets.</p>
<p>Operating in closed beta also controls the budget by keeping the activity limited to an invite-only list. Remember, while the Proxy Operator is not charging a fee, the Solana network still does. It simply is not possible to provide an open beta and predict the cost in SOL for such an initiative (though it is possible to predict that the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/solana/">SOL cost</a> will be less than the equivalent Eth cost would be for an EVM settling to Ethereum!).&nbsp;</p>
<p>When the testing period ends and NEON tokens are available on the market to pay for transactions, Neon EVM will switch back to its normal operation mode. This means that independent Proxy Operators (P2P and Everstake) will resume responsibility for accepting and processing transactions. The Proxy Operator&rsquo;s RPC endpoints will be made available on <u><a href="https://chainlist.org/?chain=245022926&amp;testnets=true&amp;search=Neon+EVM">ChainList</a></u>.</p>
<h2>Want to get involved?</h2>
<p>While Neon EVM is deployed to Solana Mainnet at address <a href="https://solscan.io/account/NeonVMyRX5GbCrsAHnUwx1nYYoJAtskU1bWUo6JGNyG">NeonVMyRX5GbCrsAHnUwx1nYYoJAtskU1bWUo6JGNyG</a>, as this is a closed beta, unless you are on the guest list, it won&rsquo;t accept your transactions yet.&nbsp;</p>
<p>To engage with the community, you can find us on <a href="https://twitter.com/Neon_EVM">Twitter</a> and join Neon EVM&rsquo;s very active <a href="https://discord.gg/neonevm">Discord</a> to meet some of our long-term and loyal community builders. For a high-level overview of the technical architecture and features of Neon EVM, the whitepaper is available at <a href="https://neonevm.org/whitepaper.pdf">NeonEVM.org/whitepaper.pdf</a>. To follow the activity of the network, you can view Neon EVM transactions settled to Solana with the <a href="https://shadow.neonscan.org/">NeonScan</a> dashboard.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/closed-beta-version-of-neon-evm-launches-on-solanas-mainnet/">Ethereum dApps settle on Solana with Neon EVM’s closed beta</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto investors see value proposition in Chancer’s P2P betting solution</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-investors-see-value-proposition-in-chancers-p2p-betting-solution/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-investors-see-value-proposition-in-chancers-p2p-betting-solution/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 09:20:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto adoption]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-investors-see-value-proposition-in-chancers-p2p-betting-solution/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Chancer presale has seen investors buy over 38 million tokens in a few days. The excitement about this project stems from its value proposition, particularly in disrupting the online betting industry. Current presale price for CHANCER token is $0.01, likely a bargain for early investors. The Chancer presale launched this month offering investors an early [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-investors-see-value-proposition-in-chancers-p2p-betting-solution/">Crypto investors see value proposition in Chancer’s P2P betting solution</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Chancer presale has seen investors buy over 38 million tokens in a few days.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The excitement about this project stems from its value proposition, particularly in disrupting the online betting industry.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Current presale price for CHANCER token is $0.01, likely a bargain for early investors.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">The <a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=media&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Chancer presale</u></a> launched this month offering investors an early opportunity to be part of a disruptive betting platform. Is this why the token sale has already seen investors scoop more than 38 million $CHANCER tokens?&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Chancer&rsquo;s value proposition is the game-changer</h2>
<p dir="ltr">As an innovative blockchain-based market, Chancer&rsquo;s value proposition is in its approach to betting. Simply, control is seized from centralised bookmakers and handed to bettors. No central house means custom bets and <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/smart-contracts/">smart contracts</a>-powered payouts, with wagers shared globally to create a real-time social environment.</p>
<p dir="ltr">At the base of it is Chancer&rsquo;s potential to completely change the gambling industry by tapping into the power of Web3. Early backers of this peer-to-peer online betting platform could be investing in the most disruptive project in the predictive markets industry.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Chancer?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer is building the world&rsquo;s first truly decentralised predictions market. It employs <a href="https://coinjournal.net/learn/what-is-blockchain/">blockchain technology</a> to introduce the features of transparency and immutability, a trustless environment that contrasts to the heavily centralised traditional betting industry.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The CHANCER token re-empowers bettors, allowing them to remain in control of their betting experience by offering a platform where they can create their own predictive markets. No bookmaker power to decide which markets to offer and which to restrict.</p>
<p dir="ltr">It means users can participate in all manner of wagers, from the biggest sports events and political contests to that mundane bet against friends and family. And if you are not creating your own custom bet, you can jump onto one from anywhere in the world.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer&rsquo;s P2P platform, which is Certik audited and integrated with Google&rsquo;s WebRTC, makes social betting not just fun but also likely more profitable.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Is CHANCER presale the time to buy?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">CHANCER is central to how Chancer works. The token grants its holders access to the prediction market and it&rsquo;s what makes it possible for participants to create all bets. Payouts are also processed in CHANCER.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Chancer presale is why investors are flocking to the project. Projections are that the betting industry could in a few years be a $150 billion market, with an estimated 11% CAGR to 2030. Adding to this is Chancer&rsquo;s potential to disrupt the whole industry even as an expected crypto boon makes for a great opportunity.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Going by these prospects, it appears investors buying CHANCER today could be early adopters of a project set to grow alongside as well as revolutionise the broader market.</p>
<p dir="ltr">At the current price of $0.01, CHANCER is arguably a massive bargain &ndash; especially given the presale will see the token&rsquo;s value jump more than 100% to $0.021.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The tokens are quickly selling out as can be seen on the presale page<a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=media&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">&nbsp;<u>here</u></a>, and that means interested investors may want to buy now to lock in the early gains as the platform moves through its 12 presale stages.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Will CHANCER price reach $1 in 2024?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer&rsquo;s industry-defining project is still in development, and the roadmap shows the Beta launch of the P2P betting platform is expected in Q3, 2023. Meanwhile, the token will go live on exchanges at the end of the presale, opening it up to more investors and increasing demand.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Availability on major exchanges could inject upside action in CHANCER price at a time the crypto market could be experiencing bullish moves. Product development for Chancer will continue through Q4, with testnet for market making, virtual betting and full node deployment adding to the growth impetus.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Mainnet launch is expected in Q1, 2024. Chancer will also integrate Filecoin data storage, migrate validator nodes and deploy quadratic governance. Certik auditing to verify decentralisation will also be undertaken. Amid these is Chancers tokenomics that outline a deflationary token.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Taken as a whole, the Chancer roadmap points to a project poised to achieve key milestones. Investor confidence could spike due to this and cascade into more demand for the native token, aiding a bullish trajectory that could coincide with an anticipated bull cycle.</p>
<p dir="ltr">If CHANCER price breaks to $0.1 after it goes live, the prediction would be a run to the primary target of $1 later in 2024. However, any investor would know that prevailing market conditions remain key to future CHANCER price performance.</p>
<p>Interested in this project? Find out more on <a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=media&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Chancer.com</a>.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-investors-see-value-proposition-in-chancers-p2p-betting-solution/">Crypto investors see value proposition in Chancer’s P2P betting solution</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-investors-see-value-proposition-in-chancers-p2p-betting-solution/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>DWF Labs Doubles Down on Conflux with $28 Million Invested</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/dwf-labs-doubles-down-on-conflux-with-28-million-invested/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/dwf-labs-doubles-down-on-conflux-with-28-million-invested/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire &#160;]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 06:52:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=144427</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Hong Kong, China, June 28th, 2023, Chainwire DWF Labs, the global digital asset market maker, and multi-stage Web3 investment firm, has further strengthened its commitment to support the growth of Conflux, the tree-graph consensus algorithm Layer-1 blockchain. Conflux has been gaining significant traction since February 2023 on the back of some key partnerships, including the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/dwf-labs-doubles-down-on-conflux-with-28-million-invested/">DWF Labs Doubles Down on Conflux with $28 Million Invested</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Hong Kong, China, June 28th, 2023, Chainwire</strong></p>
<p>DWF Labs, the global digital asset market maker, and multi-stage Web3 investment firm, has further strengthened its commitment to support the growth of Conflux, the tree-graph consensus algorithm Layer-1 blockchain. Conflux has been gaining significant traction since February 2023 on the back of some key partnerships, including the signature collaboration with China Telecom announced on February 15th, with the goal of developing a blockchain SIM (BSIM) card that was first unveiled in May.</p>
<p>DWF Labs recently purchased $18M in CFX token, cementing the long-term relationship between the investment firm and Conflux. This follows DFW Labs buying $10M worth of CFX tokens in March 2023.</p>
<p>More recently, Conflux joined Hong Kong&rsquo;s Web3 Institute, participated in the Singapore Digital Economy Roundtable organized by the Singaporean Government, and led the drafting of IEEE P3217, an international blockchain standard by the Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers. In addition, Conflux announced key partnerships including:</p>
<ul>
<li>Supremacy &ndash; Web3 security platform</li>
<li>dappOS &ndash;&nbsp;an operating protocol that manages crypto infrastructures for users</li>
<li>NuLink &ndash; a privacy-preserving technology that provides APIs for decentralized applications</li>
<li>Smooth Labs &ndash; developing the Layer 2 solution that supports parallel execution</li>
<li>Opside &ndash;&nbsp;a decentralized ZK-RaaS network featuring PoW of ZKP mining</li>
</ul>
<p>DWF Labs has made significant contributions to placing Conflux on the global stage. Since then, Conflux has established ecosystem partnerships with Floki, Worldcoin, Blockbank, Luganodes, AirDAO, Mask, and OpenEden, with a growing list of ongoing partnerships being discussed. Conflux and DWF Labs have also co-hosted multiple events, including those organized in Hong Kong, Tokyo, and Paris.</p>
<p>Fan Long, Conflux Network&rsquo;s Co-Founder, stated: &ldquo;Conflux Network has experienced exponential growth since the start of 2023, pioneering advances in the Chinese NFT market and establishing fresh Web3 access through the BSIM card project with China Telecom. DWF Lab is one of the key supporters of Conflux. This infusion of capital not only strengthens our bond, but also acts as a catalyst for our shared ambition to expand the Conflux ecosystem. Conflux plans to leverage the raised funds to further fuel its ecosystem growth in Asia and Hong Kong, empower burgeoning developer communities, and bring an increasing number of real-world assets onto the Conflux chain.&rdquo;</p>
<blockquote><p>The Managing Partner of DWF Labs, Andrei Grachev stated: &ldquo;We take great pride in our role as supporters of Conflux throughout its remarkable growth trajectory. It exemplifies our commitment to backing projects with immense potential and providing the necessary support to fill in the missing pieces of the Web3 puzzle. Our deep understanding of the crypto market has served as a compass for Conflux, allowing it to fully express its potential on the global stage. We are delighted to have played a part in Conflux&rsquo;s journey towards success.&rdquo;</p></blockquote>
<h3>About Conflux</h3>
<p><a href="https://confluxnetwork.org/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Conflux</a> is a permissionless Layer 1 blockchain connecting decentralized economies across borders and protocols.</p>
<p>Recently migrated to hybrid PoW/PoS consensus, Conflux provides a fast, secure, and scalable blockchain environment with zero congestion, low fees, and improved network security.</p>
<p>As the only regulatory-compliant public blockchain in China, Conflux provides a unique advantage for projects building and expanding into Asia. Conflux has collaborated with global brands and government entities in the region on blockchain and metaverse initiatives, including the city of Shanghai, McDonald&rsquo;s China, and Oreo.</p>
<h3>About DWF Labs</h3>
<p><a href="https://www.dwf-labs.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">DWF Labs</a> is the global digital asset market maker and multi-stage Web3 investment firm, supporting portfolio companies from token listing to market making to OTC trading solutions.</p>
<p>With offices in Singapore, Switzerland, the UAE, Hong Kong, South Korea and BVI, the investment company DWF Labs is an affiliate of Digital Wave Finance (DWF), which consistently ranks among the top 5 trading entities by volume in the cryptocurrency world through its proprietary technology for high-frequency trading.</p>
<p><strong>Contact</strong></p>
<p>Melissa Tirey<br>
conflux@shift6studios.com</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/dwf-labs-doubles-down-on-conflux-with-28-million-invested/">DWF Labs Doubles Down on Conflux with $28 Million Invested</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/dwf-labs-doubles-down-on-conflux-with-28-million-invested/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
