<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 15:26:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Nigeria&#8217;s SEC orders Binance Nigeria Limited to stop operations</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/nigerias-sec-orders-binance-nigeria-limited-to-stop-operations/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 15:26:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Africa]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/nigerias-sec-orders-binance-nigeria-limited-to-stop-operations/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Nigeria&#8217;s SEC said Binance Nigeria Limited is neither registered nor regulated and its operations in Nigeria are illegal. The order against Binance Nigeria Limited comes days after the US SEC sued Binance and its founder CZ. Nigeria&#8217;s SEC had previously said it viewed all crypto assets to be securities by default. According to a Friday [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/nigerias-sec-orders-binance-nigeria-limited-to-stop-operations/">Nigeria&#8217;s SEC orders Binance Nigeria Limited to stop operations</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Nigeria&rsquo;s SEC said Binance Nigeria Limited is neither registered nor regulated and its operations in Nigeria are illegal.</li>
<li>The order against Binance Nigeria Limited comes days after the US SEC sued Binance and its founder CZ.</li>
<li>Nigeria&rsquo;s SEC had previously said it viewed all crypto assets to be securities by default.</li>
</ul>
<p>According to a Friday circular from Nigeria&rsquo;s Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), <a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/binance/">Binance&rsquo;s</a> Nigerian branch has been told to stop all operations immediately.</p>
<p>The circular stated that Binance Nigeria Limited&rsquo;s operations in Nigeria were unlawful because it was neither registered with nor subject to regulation by the Commission. The <a href="https://sec.gov.ng/circular-on-the-activities-of-binance-nigeria-limited/">circular</a> by the SEC states:</p>
<p><em>&ldquo;Binance Nigeria Limited is neither registered nor regulated by the Commission and its operations in Nigeria are therefore illegal. Any member of the investing public dealing with the entity is doing so at his/her own risk.</em></p>
<p><em>As the regulator with the statutory mandate of investor protection, the Commission urges Nigerians to be wary of investing in crypto-assets, and crypto-asset-related financial products and services if the service provider/its platform is not registered or regulated by the Commission. Nigerian investors are hereby warned that investing in crypto-assets is extremely risky and may result in a total loss of their investment.</em></p>
<p><em>By this circular, Binance Nigeria Limited is hereby directed to immediately stop soliciting Nigerian investors in any form whatsoever.&rdquo;</em></p>
<h2>Binance under siege</h2>
<p>Binance Nigeria is the second Binance branch to be accused of operating unlicensed activities. On Monday, the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sec-sues-binance-and-cz-for-breaking-us-securities-rules/">US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) sued Binance</a>, its US affiliate, and its founder Changpeng Zhao violating the securities laws in the country.</p>
<p>The US SEC has gone further to request for the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-sec-is-seeking-court-order-to-freeze-binance-uss-assets/">assets of Binance.US to be frozen</a>. It is currently looking for <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sec-seeks-alternative-ways-to-serve-changpeng-zhao-after-failing-to-get-him/">an alternative way to serve Changpeng Zhao</a> with the court sermon.</p>
<h2>Nigeria&rsquo;s SEC stand on cryptocurrencies</h2>
<p>While this is the first action taken by Nigeria&rsquo;s SEC against a cryptocurrency exchange platform, the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/nigerias-sec-recognises-cryptocurrencies-as-securities/">SEC had previously stated</a> that it considers all crypto assets to be securities by default.</p>
<p>Bloomberg reported in May that Nigeria&rsquo;s SEC was processing registration applications from crypto firms on a trial basis but would not begin doing so formally until it had reached an agreement with the nation&rsquo;s central bank.</p>
<p>Currently, it is <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/central-bank-of-nigeria-bans-crypto-and-sees-angry-backlash/">against the law</a> for banks in Nigeria to provide services to cryptocurrency platforms.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/nigerias-sec-orders-binance-nigeria-limited-to-stop-operations/">Nigeria&#8217;s SEC orders Binance Nigeria Limited to stop operations</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chancer: World&#8217;s first blockchain-based predictive markets app, and a potential game-changer</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-worlds-first-blockchain-based-predictive-markets-app-and-a-potential-game-changer/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Motiur Rahman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 19:44:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technical Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-worlds-first-blockchain-based-predictive-markets-app-and-a-potential-game-changer/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Chancer facilitates P2P predictive markets for betting on conventional and non-conventional markets. Chancer aims to enable user-led predictions amid record betting levels in traditional markets. The token will start presale on June 13,th&#160;2023. Think about this, being able to bet against any event and setting your own rules and odds. This is what the new [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-worlds-first-blockchain-based-predictive-markets-app-and-a-potential-game-changer/">Chancer: World&#8217;s first blockchain-based predictive markets app, and a potential game-changer</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Chancer facilitates P2P predictive markets for betting on conventional and non-conventional markets.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Chancer aims to enable user-led predictions amid record betting levels in traditional markets.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The token will start presale on June 13,th&nbsp;2023.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Think about this, being able to bet against any event and setting your own rules and odds. This is what the new decentralised blockchain platform Chancer is bringing. But that&rsquo;s not the main idea &ndash; Chancer will be an investment opportunity giving its holders a chance to earn in various ways. The token $CHANCER presale happens on June 13th&nbsp;2023 amid growing enthusiasm around the token.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>What is Chancer?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer is a blockchain-based decentralised predictive markets application. Under the main slogan, &ldquo;Chancer: Your Game, Your Rules, Your Odds,&rdquo; the platform will allow people to set their customised P2P betting platforms complete with their own rules.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Users can bet on anything they like, from a live football match to a personal bet, say your best friend will finish the top in the class. Users can also let their friends and others join their market, bringing fun to their betting world.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The platform&rsquo;s token, $CHANCER, will run on the BSC blockchain. The aim is to enable token purchases through a secure chain with minimal transaction fees and high speeds. The team behind the blockchain aims to create a platform that works similarly to a dApp, seamlessly linking to the BSC blockchain. A proof-of-stake consensus mechanism seeks to make Chancer a fully decentralised ecosystem.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Record betting an advantage to decentralised Chancer</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Betting is at all-time highs, thanks to growing technology and more people seeking to grow incomes through various models and have fun. If we take sports betting, for instance, activity levels hit record levels in 2022. The&nbsp;<a href="https://www.americangaming.org/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>American Gaming Association</u></a> reported that gross gaming revenues from sports rose to a record $7.5 billion in 2022, almost a 75% increase from the previous year. In the first quarter of 2023, the AGA reported that commercial gaming revenues hit a quarterly record of more than $16 billion.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Owing to these trends, betting is a big opportunity market. However, betting models have mostly stayed the same as the platforms remain centrally controlled. The need for a betting model that is user-led and peer-controlled is needed. The decentralised model is more transparent and confers benefits to users beyond betting. Chancer follows this model to generate win-win situations for users and investors.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Is Chancer a good investment opportunity?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer isn&rsquo;t only a blockchain-based betting ecosystem. It confers value to its participants by being an investment opportunity. The first benefit to investors is holding the $CHANCER token. This differs from betting platforms, where the winner takes it all.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Holders of $CHANCER can create their own markets and participate in markets created by peers. With this, there is an opportunity to collaborate, engage, and profit from wider Web 3.0 betting. Users benefit from a potential $CHANCER increase in value as more join the network. They can also stake the token for passive income.</p>
<p dir="ltr">There are also market-making rewards for creating Chancer markets through the dApp and live stream features. Users can become platform validators for a chance to earn more and enjoy priorities in platform governance. Other ways to earn include Share2Earn features, where users will get rewarded for promoting the market to increase the participation of members.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The platform will also introduce a &ldquo;Loyalty&rdquo; program. This is a program to reimburse small amounts of transaction charges paid by users. The rebate is an incentive and a strategy to make the platform economically viable for its investors.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The unique ways investors earn and the decentralised model make Chancer a potentially viable investment opportunity. Being the first of its kind, investors may want to experiment with blockchain-based predictions, conferring a chance for the ecosystem to grow and benefit investors.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Chancer presale and listings</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer&rsquo;s presale seeks to raise $15,000,000 over 12 stages of the presale. The token will be listed on Uniswap, Coingecko, and Coinmarketcap in the third quarter. More listings will follow, with the testnet expected in the fourth quarter. The mainnet, with full functionalities, is expected in the first quarter of 2024.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-worlds-first-blockchain-based-predictive-markets-app-and-a-potential-game-changer/">Chancer: World&#8217;s first blockchain-based predictive markets app, and a potential game-changer</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>SEC seeks alternative ways to serve Changpeng Zhao after failing to get him</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/sec-seeks-alternative-ways-to-serve-changpeng-zhao-after-failing-to-get-him/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/sec-seeks-alternative-ways-to-serve-changpeng-zhao-after-failing-to-get-him/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 18:24:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/sec-seeks-alternative-ways-to-serve-changpeng-zhao-after-failing-to-get-him/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>There are rumours that Changpeng Zhao could be in Dubai. There is no known base of operations for the Binance CEO. The SEC is seeking permission from the court to serve CZ lawyers on his behalf. The United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) is asking the US District Court in Washington DC for an [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sec-seeks-alternative-ways-to-serve-changpeng-zhao-after-failing-to-get-him/">SEC seeks alternative ways to serve Changpeng Zhao after failing to get him</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>There are rumours that Changpeng Zhao could be in Dubai.</li>
<li>There is no known base of operations for the Binance CEO.</li>
<li>The SEC is seeking permission from the court to serve CZ lawyers on his behalf.</li>
</ul>
<p>The United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) is asking the US District Court in Washington DC for an &ldquo;alternative service&rdquo; to serve Changpeng Zhao, the CEO of cryptocurrency exchange <a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/binance/">Binance</a>, with a court summons.</p>
<p>The SEC recently filed a <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sec-sues-binance-and-cz-for-breaking-us-securities-rules/">lawsuit against Zhao and Binance</a> over alleged unregistered securities operations.</p>
<h2>The SEC&rsquo;s request to US District Court in Washington DC</h2>
<p>The SEC requested alternative service in a <a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.dcd.256060/gov.uscourts.dcd.256060.26.0_1.pdf">case document</a> that was submitted to the District Court on June 7. The Sec justifies its blatant stance that typical service&mdash;which necessitates the recipient&rsquo;s presence and signature&mdash;might be challenging in this circumstance:</p>
<p>In addition, the SEC requests that the court order Zhao and Binance to deliver a &ldquo;sworn accounting&rdquo; &mdash; a formal disclosure of financial data &mdash; right away.</p>
<p>According to the complaint, the SEC has not been able to determine the full extent of the defendant&rsquo;s assets, the precise location of investor funds, or the condition or location of other assets that might be used to satisfy a monetary judgment against the defendant.</p>
<p>Once more, the SEC lists the logistical issues as a mitigating circumstance. According to the filing, BAM Trading&rsquo;s &ldquo;inability to provide accurate information&rdquo; regarding Zhao&rsquo;s whereabouts or the company&rsquo;s &ldquo;location abroad&rdquo; is the reason for the request for a sworn accounting.</p>
<h2>Changpeng Zhao&rsquo;s physical presence for the summons</h2>
<p>The CEO would probably not be legally required to appear in court simply to respond to the summons, despite the alleged difficulty in serving Zhao. However, the courts typically require some form of service to occur even if the defendant isn&rsquo;t required to appear.</p>
<p>Acknowledging this, Changpeng Zhao&nbsp;<a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1666513302304727059?s=20">tweeted</a> saying:</p>
<p><em>&ldquo;I was told this is just part of the SEC complaint process. Nothing new. Also told I won&rsquo;t have to appear in person. No need to FUD.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p>Although the whereabouts of the Chinese-born Canadian citizen Binance CEO remains unknown, Binance spokesperson Dewy Mustajab on March 28 said that the CEO splits his time between France and Dubai.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sec-seeks-alternative-ways-to-serve-changpeng-zhao-after-failing-to-get-him/">SEC seeks alternative ways to serve Changpeng Zhao after failing to get him</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/sec-seeks-alternative-ways-to-serve-changpeng-zhao-after-failing-to-get-him/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto.com suspends institutional exchange services in the US</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-com-suspends-institutional-exchange-services-in-the-us/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-com-suspends-institutional-exchange-services-in-the-us/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 17:47:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto.com]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-com-suspends-institutional-exchange-services-in-the-us/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto.com cited limited demand for institutional-grade services. The services will be suspended from June 21. Crypto.com&#8217;s retail mobile application and platform remain fully operational in the US. Crypto.com has announced that it will discontinue its institutional exchange services in the United States from June 21, this year. This means that the services will no longer [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-com-suspends-institutional-exchange-services-in-the-us/">Crypto.com suspends institutional exchange services in the US</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Crypto.com cited limited demand for institutional-grade services.</li>
<li>The services will be suspended from June 21.</li>
<li>Crypto.com&rsquo;s retail mobile application and platform remain fully operational in the US.</li>
</ul>
<p>Crypto.com has announced that it will discontinue its institutional exchange services in the United States from June 21, this year. This means that the services will no longer provide institutional clients with services in the United States.</p>
<p>While a majority of crypto players are worried about the ongoing crypto onslaught by the US Securities and Exchanges Commission (SEC), Crypto.com cited the lack of institutional demand as the main driver behind the decision, which was made worse by market testing.</p>
<p>The exchange, however, remains open to a potential re-launch of the suspended institutional exchange services in the US if the market conditions change.</p>
<h2>Retail crypto services still available in the US</h2>
<p>According to a statement from Crypto.com, institutional users of the platform were informed in advance that the service would be suspended. The exchange, however, maintains that its retail mobile application and platform remain fully operational in the US.</p>
<p>In addition, Crypto.com&rsquo;s CFTC-regulated cryptocurrency derivatives trading is still available to American retail users, as well as its UpDown Options product, which enables users to open long or short trading positions on potential future movements of different cryptocurrencies.</p>
<h2>Crypto onslaught by the SEC in the US</h2>
<p>The month of June 2023 has proven to be the most turbulent in the history of cryptocurrency exchanges operating in the US. The Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) started <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-sec-strikes-again-first-binance-now-coinbase/">legal action against both Binance and Coinbase</a> for a variety of allegations including violations of the securities laws.</p>
<p>The SEC&rsquo;s actions have drawn criticism from the larger cryptocurrency community as the SEC appears to be tightening its regulatory clampdown on the sector eight months after <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ftx-collapse-hearing-kevin-oleary-says-binance-caused-the-ftx-implosion/">FTX&rsquo;s demise</a>.</p>
<p>While Crypto.com is yet to be probed by the SEC, the exchange has maintained its expansion throughout the world. The Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS) recently <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-com-completes-its-licensing-process-in-singapore/">granted Crypto.com an official major payment institution (MPI) license</a> for digital payment token (DPT) services, enabling it to provide its services there even as it shutters its US institutional offering.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-com-suspends-institutional-exchange-services-in-the-us/">Crypto.com suspends institutional exchange services in the US</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-com-suspends-institutional-exchange-services-in-the-us/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto price prediction: Render Token, Solana, Polkadot</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-render-token-solana-polkadot/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-render-token-solana-polkadot/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 16:32:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polkadot News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-render-token-solana-polkadot/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrencies remained under pressure this week after the SEC went to war with the industry. The SEC sued Binance and Coinbase, the biggest exchanges in the industry. We explain what to expect with Render Token, Polkadot, and Solana. Cryptocurrencies had a difficult week after the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) went to war with the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-render-token-solana-polkadot/">Crypto price prediction: Render Token, Solana, Polkadot</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Cryptocurrencies remained under pressure this week after the SEC went to war with the industry.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The SEC sued Binance and Coinbase, the biggest exchanges in the industry.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">We explain what to expect with Render Token, Polkadot, and Solana.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Cryptocurrencies had a difficult week after the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) went to war with the biggest companies in the industry. On Monday, the agency filed charges against Binance and its CEO, Changpeng Zhao. Then on the following day, the agency sued Coinbase for offering stacking products. While many coins have rebounded in the past few days, there are regulatory concerns in the industry. This article will look at some of the most popular coins and what to expect. They include: Render Token, Solana, and Polkadot.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Render Token price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/render-token/"><u>Render Network</u></a> is a blockchain platform that provides decentralized GPU services. RNDR, its token, has jumped sharply as investors compare it to Nvidia, a company that is now valued at over $1 trillion. The token has surged by more than 400% this year.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">There are signs that the spectacular rally is fading. On the 4H chart, we see that the token has slipped by over 20% from its highest level this month. This is a signal that it has moved to a bear market. The token has also moved below the 25-day and 50-day exponential moving averages (EMA) and the two are about to form a bearish crossover.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Most importantly, it seems like Render has formed a double-top pattern. Therefore, the token will likely continue falling as sellers target the neckline of this pattern at $1.63.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/05/09/1686328272553-68947f08-9c68-415d-8c3f-a0ff4653ab02.png" style="width: 633px;height: 307.678px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="633" height="307.678"></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Polkadot price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/polkadot"><u>Polkadot</u></a> is a leading blockchain that was established by a co-founder of Ethereum. It is best known for its parachains like Moonbeam, Acala, and Efinity. On the four-hour chart, the coin has been in a downward trend. And most recently, it managed to drop below the key support level at $5.15, &nbsp;the lowest level in May 25 and on May 12.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Polkadot has moved below the 25-day and 50-day exponential moving averages (EMA). The MACD has moved below the neutral point at zero. Therefore, the coin will likely continue falling as sellers target the next support level at $4.50.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/05/09/1686328272030-18b20ee6-cc39-4a61-bb6b-3b94b3707847.png" style="width: 680px;height: 330.933px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="680" height="330.933"></p>
<h3 dir="ltr">How to buy Polkadot</h3>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>


<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=MTQyNjA5&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy DOT with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    CEX.IO</h3>


<p>
    <a href="/visit/cex-crypto?guid=MTQyNjA5&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy DOT with CEX.IO today            </a>
    </p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Solana price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/solana"><u>Solana</u></a>, like other altcoins, has been in a downward trend in the past few months. In this period, it has dropped by almost 30% from the highest point this year. The coin has dropped below the 25-day and 50-day moving averages while the MACD has dropped below the neutral level.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The coin has formed a break-and-retest pattern by retesting the key resistance point at $19.37. Therefore, Solana will likely continue falling since this pattern is usually a bearish sign. If this happens, the next level to watch will be at $15.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/05/09/1686328272314-2377759b-f33c-42eb-a087-73ef867614e3.png" style="width: 640px;height: 311.467px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="640" height="311.467"></p>
<h3 dir="ltr">How to buy Solana</h3>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>


<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=MTQyNjA5&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy SOL with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    CEX.IO</h3>


<p>
    <a href="/visit/cex-crypto?guid=MTQyNjA5&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy SOL with CEX.IO today            </a>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-render-token-solana-polkadot/">Crypto price prediction: Render Token, Solana, Polkadot</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-render-token-solana-polkadot/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>People can set up custom P2P betting markets on Chancer’s new betting platform</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/people-can-set-up-custom-p2p-betting-markets-on-chancers-new-betting-platform/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/people-can-set-up-custom-p2p-betting-markets-on-chancers-new-betting-platform/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 15:35:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/people-can-set-up-custom-p2p-betting-markets-on-chancers-new-betting-platform/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Chancer is using blockchain technology for a social betting platform. The new platform allows users to set up their own P2P betting markets including setting their own odds. Chancer is currently in the development phase with the CHANCER token presale 3 days away. Chancer is a new blockchain-based predictive markets platform that seeks to leverage [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/people-can-set-up-custom-p2p-betting-markets-on-chancers-new-betting-platform/">People can set up custom P2P betting markets on Chancer’s new betting platform</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Chancer is using blockchain technology for a social betting platform.</li>
<li>The new platform allows users to set up their own P2P betting markets including setting their own odds.</li>
<li>Chancer is currently in the development phase with the CHANCER token presale 3 days away.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://chancer.com/">Chancer</a> is a new blockchain-based predictive markets platform that seeks to leverage <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/blockchain/">blockchain technology</a> to develop a social betting platform.</p>
<p>The platform is currently in the development phase with the presale of its native cryptocurrency, the CHANCER, scheduled to start on June 13<sup>th</sup>, 2023. According to the <a href="https://chancer.com/whitepaper.pdf">whitepaper</a>, the presale together with other key development elements is scheduled for completion in Q2, 2023.</p>
<h2>Customized betting markets</h2>
<p>Chancer offers users a decentralized platform that enables them to set up their own unique peer-to-peer (P2P) betting markets without being restricted by what bookmakers offer and their odds. It is crucial to understand that Chancer enables the user to become the house; it is not the house itself.</p>
<p>The platform allows users to not only bet friends but also set their own odds and compete with bets from around the world.</p>
<p>Unlike many betting platforms, Chancer allows betting on any event, including singing contests, friendly wagers between groups of friends (for example, users can wager that their friend will or will not complete a task with specific parameters in place), and even the day that a man will set foot on Mars. This indicates that there are many more things users can do with the platform, which should make it more appealing to users since it is more inclusive and multifunctional.</p>
<p>In addition, any user can set up a betting market, confirm their odds and a set resolution source (so it&rsquo;s transparent how the outcome will be reviewed), and subsequently anyone can participate and take them up on their wager.</p>
<p>The user also has the choice of setting up the bet to only let friends participate in their market, or let anyone in the world join in and back either end.</p>
<p>The bets will be facilitated by the CHANCER token; meaning for anyone to participate on the platform. Interested parties will have the opportunity to buy the token during the presale that opens in three days&rsquo; time.</p>
<h2>Is Chancer a good investment?</h2>
<p>Well, there is a lot that an investor considers before settling on investing in a particular project. And one of the main factors is whether the project is legit or not.</p>
<p>To that extent, the Chancer team have subjected Chancer&rsquo;s specifications, smart contract, and team to an <a href="https://skynet.certik.com/projects/chancer">audit by CertiK</a>, a leading blockchain security firm that provides auditing and consulting services to enhance the security and trustworthiness of blockchain projects. The audit confirms that Chancer&rsquo;s code and roadmap meet the high standards required in Web3.</p>
<p>Seeing that Chancer is Certik-verified, we can now move to the next factor which is the value of the CHANCER token which is built on Binance Smart Chain (BSC).&nbsp;</p>
<p>Going by the presale schedule, the value of CHANCER is projected to rise from $0.010 in the first stage to $0.021 in the last stage. There will be 12 presale stages in total that will raise $15,000,000.</p>
<p>Those interested in the presale will be able to purchase CHANCER tokens only using <a href="https://coinjournal.net/binance-coin/">BNB </a>or BUSD (BEP20) tokens.</p>
<h2>Chancer BETA launch date</h2>
<p>Chancer plans to launch its BETA in Q3, 2023, which is after the conclusion of the presale and listing of CHANCER on Coingecko, Coinmarketcap, Uniswap, and at least two centralized crypto exchanges.</p>
<p>The mainnet launch is scheduled for Q1, 2023 after successful market-making testnet, virtual betting testnet, Initiate WebRTC-Live Streaming testnet, and deployment of Full Validator Nodes testnet launches.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/people-can-set-up-custom-p2p-betting-markets-on-chancers-new-betting-platform/">People can set up custom P2P betting markets on Chancer’s new betting platform</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/people-can-set-up-custom-p2p-betting-markets-on-chancers-new-betting-platform/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto exchange OKX burns $244 million worth of OKB tokens</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-exchange-okx-burns-244-million-worth-of-okb-tokens/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-exchange-okx-burns-244-million-worth-of-okb-tokens/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 08:47:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Events]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto exchange]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-exchange-okx-burns-244-million-worth-of-okb-tokens/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways OKX burned 5.5 million OKB tokens in its 20th OKB repurchase and burning program. The crypto exchange burned $244 million worth of its native token, its highest-ever burning program. OKX burns 5.5 million OKB tokens Cryptocurrency exchange OKX has repurchased and burned 5.5 million of its native OKB token in its latest monthly [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-exchange-okx-burns-244-million-worth-of-okb-tokens/">Crypto exchange OKX burns $244 million worth of OKB tokens</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">OKX burned 5.5 million OKB tokens in its 20th OKB repurchase and burning program.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The crypto exchange burned $244 million worth of its native token, its highest-ever burning program.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr">OKX burns 5.5 million OKB tokens</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Cryptocurrency exchange OKX has repurchased and burned 5.5 million of its native OKB token in its latest monthly program.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/WuBlockchain/status/1667011756072501248" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>According to Wu Blockchain</u></a>, the crypto exchange burned roughly $244 million worth of its native OKB token, the largest value it had repurchased and burned. This&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>latest cryptocurrency news</u></a> implies that 5.5 million OKB tokens were taken from the OKB&rsquo;s total supply.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Wu revealed that this latest development is a record one for the OKX cryptocurrency exchange.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">OKX is not the only major cryptocurrency exchange that burns its native tokens periodically. Binance, the world&rsquo;s largest cryptocurrency exchange by daily trading volume, is known for burning its BNB tokens every quarter.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">OKX describes its native token as a global utility token issued by the OKX Blockchain Foundation. The token allows holders to enjoy benefits, including discounts, exclusive access, and more.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Since its inception in May 2019, OKX has burned 64,042,314.70 tokens. At press time, the price of OKB stands at $44.8, up by less than 1% in the last 24 hours.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Crypto exchanges face the heat</h2>
<p dir="ltr">OKX&rsquo;s latest milestone comes at a time when its rival exchanges, Binance and Coinbase, are facing pressures from the US Securities and Exchange Commission.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Earlier this week, the&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sec-sues-binance-and-cz-for-breaking-us-securities-rules/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>US SEC filed a lawsuit against Binance</u></a>, alleging that the cryptocurrency exchange and its CEO, Changpeng Zhao, violated US securities laws by offering services to high-valued US customers on its platform.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The regulatory agency also wants to freeze the assets on Binance.US, the United States arm of the Binance crypto exchange.</p>
<p>Shortly after that, the SEC also&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/us-sec-sues-binance-and-coinbase-but-bitcoin-remains-above-26k/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>filed a lawsuit against Coinbase</u></a>, alleging that the crypto exchange is operating as an unregistered broker.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-exchange-okx-burns-244-million-worth-of-okb-tokens/">Crypto exchange OKX burns $244 million worth of OKB tokens</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-exchange-okx-burns-244-million-worth-of-okb-tokens/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chancer to launch token presale for its prediction platform</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-to-launch-token-presale-for-its-prediction-platform/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-to-launch-token-presale-for-its-prediction-platform/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 04:06:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-to-launch-token-presale-for-its-prediction-platform/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Chancer, a new company, will launch its token presale on June 13. The company hopes to use blockchain to disrupt the predictions market. Users will be able to create their own blockchain-secured markets. The sports betting industry is going through significant growth around the world. Most of this growth is coming mostly from the United [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-to-launch-token-presale-for-its-prediction-platform/">Chancer to launch token presale for its prediction platform</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Chancer, a new company, will launch its token presale on June 13.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The company hopes to use blockchain to disrupt the predictions market.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Users will be able to create their own blockchain-secured markets.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">The sports betting industry is going through significant growth around the world. Most of this growth is coming mostly from the United States, a country where online betting was banned. Today, American betting companies like Fanduel, DraftKings, and BetMGM among others have become giant enterprises worth billions of dollars.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/blockchain/"><u>blockchain</u></a> industry can disrupt the sports betting industry because of its global nature. Several blockchain companies are seeking to disrupt the industry. Some of the companies seeking to disrupt the sector are SportX and Gnosis. Now,&nbsp;<a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=invezz&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news"><u>Chancer</u></a>, a new company is entering the sector, which analysts believe is ripe for disruption.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Chancer?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer is a new company seeking to change the sports betting industry by introducing new features that are not offered by existing companies. The ecosystem will be secured using the Biance Chain blockchain, which is the market leader in&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/glossary/decentralized-applications-dapps/"><u>dApp</u></a> development.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The most unique feature for Chancer is that, in addition to the available market, users will be able to create their own markets, which other users can place bets on. For example, a user can create a market for an upcoming game.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In addition to sports, users can create a market for current affairs. For example, in an election year, the creator can create a market for the potential winner or loser for the event. While similar betting markets exist, many of them exclude some events, which Chancer&rsquo;s users can take advantage of.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to the developers, the betting market will be facilitated by the $CHANCER token, which will be created using Binance&rsquo;s blockchain. In the future, the token will also be used for governance purposes, where holders will be able to submit and vote on proposals.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer will have several features, including the use of&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/smart-contracts/"><u>smart contracts</u></a><strong>,&nbsp;</strong>open-source code, decentralised nodes, and decentralised data storage. You can read more about Chancer and how it works in its&nbsp;<a href="https://chancer.com/whitepaper.pdf"><u>white paper</u></a>.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Chancer&rsquo;s upcoming token sale</h2>
<p dir="ltr">As part of the developers&rsquo; product launch, they are planning to launch a token sale soon. A token sale is a situation where users contribute funds to a project and are entitled to tokens when they are listed. These users can then exit as soon as they are listed or hold them for a long time. In the past, many people have made a fortune by investing in token presales.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer is planning to raise $15 million in a token sale that will have 12 stages. In each of this stages, the price of the token will be higher. Chancer&rsquo;s token sale will start on June 13th of this year.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Chancer roadmap</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer&rsquo;s developers have already done the preliminary work, including launching the website and commissioning a Certik audit. Other activities set to take place in the second quarter are launching the presale process, releasing the technical roadmap, and announcing partnerships with centralized exchanges.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The third-quarter activities include launching the BETA version of the Chancer platform and launching the validator node program. In Q4, the focus will be on product development testnet. The project will incorporate Filecoi in Q1 of next year and remove centralized entities in the ecosystem.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Will $CHANCER be a good token?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">It is still too early to determine whether Chancer will be a good investment. Besides, the token sale is yet to start. And historically, investing in presales and Initial Coin Offerings (ICOs) tends to be a high-risk and high-reward proposition.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, in this case, my view is that interested investors can allocate some cash to Chancer. As with other crypto projects, the investor should be aware of the risks involved.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-to-launch-token-presale-for-its-prediction-platform/">Chancer to launch token presale for its prediction platform</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-to-launch-token-presale-for-its-prediction-platform/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>No more panic? Crypto resilient after Binance lawsuit, but BNB hits a 6-month low</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/no-more-panic-crypto-resilient-after-binance-lawsuit-but-bnb-hits-a-6-month-low/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/no-more-panic-crypto-resilient-after-binance-lawsuit-but-bnb-hits-a-6-month-low/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Motiur Rahman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 20:03:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technical Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/no-more-panic-crypto-resilient-after-binance-lawsuit-but-bnb-hits-a-6-month-low/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Binance Coin has fallen by double digits after SEC initiates investigations on exchange The rest of the crypto sector remains resilient, with AltSignals having potential $ASI presale demand could fuel the price increase when the token lists on exchanges News that the US Securities and Exchange Commission has sued Binance and later Coinbase could be [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/no-more-panic-crypto-resilient-after-binance-lawsuit-but-bnb-hits-a-6-month-low/">No more panic? Crypto resilient after Binance lawsuit, but BNB hits a 6-month low</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Binance Coin has fallen by double digits after SEC initiates investigations on exchange</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The rest of the crypto sector remains resilient, with AltSignals having potential</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">$ASI presale demand could fuel the price increase when the token lists on exchanges</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">News that the US Securities and Exchange Commission has sued Binance and later Coinbase could be the hottest in crypto now. As an exchange that controls more than 60% of crypto volume, Binance&rsquo;s lawsuit was expected to generate shockwaves. Binance is accused of 13 counts of violations, one being offering unregistered security tokens. Coinbase is charged with operating an unregistered securities exchange, clearing agency, and broker.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>BNB falls to a 6-month low with resilience across the sector</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Binance Coin (BNB) traded at $261 on June 8 on the back of ongoing tussles between the crypto exchange and SEC. The last time the cryptocurrency traded at this level was on January 23, implying a nearly 6-month low.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Despite this significant price drop, the rest of the sector looks resilient. Bitcoin trades at $26,400, Ethereum at $1,840, and XRP at $0.51. Although slightly lower, the price decline has been low compared to the market event triggered by FTX in November 2022.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Elsewhere, DeFi activity has remained steady across various platforms, according to&nbsp;<a href="https://defillama.com/?tvl=true" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>DeFiLlama</u></a>. The total value locked has remained around $45.43 billion. The resilience underlines positive sentiment among investors, unlike previous panic-involving events. The DeFi activity, in conjunction with stable crypto prices, means a potential recovery as circumstances of SEC lawsuits settle.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>AltSignals to benefit from a post-SEC market resurgence</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">It might not be clear when the case of Binance with SEC will conclude. Similar cases like the Ripple entanglements have lasted years. However, a potential clearance of the regulatory hurdle will boost demand for digital assets. AltSignals, a new entrant into the space and currently on&nbsp;<a href="https://token.altsignals.io/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=investment_opportunity" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>presale</u></a>, could benefit from this development.</p>
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals ($ASI) endears as crypto for traders. The token is 87% sold out in presale, with an innovative trading platform being the main attraction. $ASI offers value for investors looking to earn by belonging to a trading community. With a potential renewed focus on tokens not seen as securities under the SEC classification, $ASI could attract investors and unlock a projected 10x return.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Understanding AltSignals and $ASI</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://www.altsignals.io/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>AltSignals</u></a> is a proprietary trading signal platform created in 2017 by a team of experienced UK traders. The signal service covers forex, crypto, and stocks as its main instruments using a technical analysis tool, AltAlgo&trade;.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">A strong demand for AltSignals service has prompted its team to explore a more advanced technical analysis tool using artificial intelligence. The AI platform, dubbed ActualizeAI, will run on the Ethereum network. The platform will use AI to generate more quality trading signals.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Members of ActualizeAI will need to own $ASI as the native token, which they can use to vote on governance. The benefit of belonging to a trading community has fueled the demand for $ASI, explaining the robust presale.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Members can also earn $ASI by participating in trading-related tournaments and contributing to ActualizeAI projects. ActualizeAI members also have exclusive access to other presale opportunities.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>$ASI prediction in 2023</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">2023 is another harsh year for cryptocurrencies, although the market has regained stability after a disastrous 2022. That means the potential for overzealous price increases for any cryptocurrency could be overambitious but realistic.</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, the above can&rsquo;t be said of new and innovative tokens like $ASI. Newly launched tokens have risen by triple digits as the hunt for memes and high-value crypto projects continues in a bear market. As such, the potential for $ASI remains high once it launches on exchanges like Uniswap.</p>
<p dir="ltr">A projected increase of 10x is a realistic target by the end of 2023, considering that the token has the backing of an existing trading community. If $ASI rises by this margin, a price of $0.15 would be the potential minimum for investors.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/no-more-panic-crypto-resilient-after-binance-lawsuit-but-bnb-hits-a-6-month-low/">No more panic? Crypto resilient after Binance lawsuit, but BNB hits a 6-month low</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/no-more-panic-crypto-resilient-after-binance-lawsuit-but-bnb-hits-a-6-month-low/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
