<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 14:11:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Santa delivers as Mirror and Anchor Protocol tokens surge</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/santa-delivers-as-mirror-and-anchor-protocol-tokens-surge/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/santa-delivers-as-mirror-and-anchor-protocol-tokens-surge/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 14:11:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/santa-delivers-as-mirror-and-anchor-protocol-tokens-surge/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Mirror and Anchor Protocol prices went parabolic on Monday. The two tokens were some of the biggest players in Terra. Mirror Protocol (MIR) and Anchor Protocol (ANC) prices surged during the Christmas weekend as demand for the penny cryptos jumped. MIR jumped to a high of $0.245, which was about 171% above the lowest level [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/santa-delivers-as-mirror-and-anchor-protocol-tokens-surge/">Santa delivers as Mirror and Anchor Protocol tokens surge</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Mirror and Anchor Protocol prices went parabolic on Monday.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The two tokens were some of the biggest players in Terra.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Mirror Protocol (MIR) and Anchor Protocol (ANC) prices surged during the Christmas weekend as demand for the penny cryptos jumped. MIR jumped to a high of $0.245, which was about 171% above the lowest level last week. In the same period, Anchor jumped by more than 50%.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Why did Mirror and Anchor Protocols rise?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Mirror and Anchor Protocols were some of the biggest players in Terra&rsquo;s ecosystem. Anchor operated as a crypto bank that provided depositors with interests as high as 20% on their deposits. At its peak, Anchor Protocol had over $20 billion in assets.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Mirror Protocol, on the other hand, operated a platform that enabled people to invest in tokenised assets like stocks, commodities, currencies, and indices. The idea was that people would use the blockchain technology to invest in these financial assets.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">With Mirror Protocol, it was possible for people to invest in these assets on a 24-hour and 7-day basis. It would also lower costs for people to trade and invest, as I wrote&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/anchor-protocol-price-prediction-as-terra-and-ustc-spikes/"><u>here</u></a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">After experiencing remarkable growth in the past few years, Mirror and Anchor Protocol crashed in May 2022 after Terra and Terra USD ecosystems plummeted. This was a notable thing since these platforms were backed by the UST stablecoin.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Anchor and Mirror Protocols ceased operating in May when Terra fell. Still, their tokens have continued trading in the market, giving them a market cap of $12 million and $14 million, respectively.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This performance is likely because some contrarian investors believe that Terra USD will regain its peg in the coming months. This is highly unlikely since the stablecoin was trading at $0.021. Also, their tokens are a reflection of the gap in valuation of crypto tokens. In the past few months, we have seen tokens of bankrupt companies like FTX and Celsius Network rise.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Mirror Protocol price prediction</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2022/11/26/1672063804176-8295436e-9c17-4c02-ae44-bd4716296d52.png" style="width: 607px;height: 301.477px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="607" height="301.477"></p>
<p dir="ltr">The four-hour chart shows that the MIR price surged as Santa delivered. As it rose, it moved above the important resistance point at $0.1836, which was the highest point since November 18. It has jumped above all moving averages.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Relative Strength Index (RSI) and the Stochastic Oscillators have moved above the overbought level. Therefore, I suspect that this rebound is temporary and that the token will resume the bearish trend soon. If this happens, the next key level to watch will be at $0.1373. A move above the resistance point at $0.2200 will invalidate the bearish view. Anchor&rsquo;s MIR will also pull back.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy Mirror Protocol</h2>
<p dir="ltr">
                </p><p>As MIR is such a new asset, it's yet to be listed on major exchanges. You can still purchase MIR using a DEX (decentralised exchange) though, which just means there are a few extra steps. To buy MIR right now, follow these steps:</p>

                                    <h3>1. Buy ETH on a regulated exchange or broker, like <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=OTg4ODQ&amp;component=news-table-1inch" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">eToro &rsaquo;</a></h3>
                    <p>We suggest <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=OTg4ODQ&amp;component=news-table-1inch" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">eToro</a> because it's one of the world's leading multi-asset trading platforms, an exchange and wallet all-in-one with some of the lowest fees in the industry. It's also beginner-friendly, and has more payment methods available to users than any other available service.</p>
                                    <h3>2. Send your ETH to a compatible wallet like Trust Wallet or MetaMask</h3>
                    <p>You'll need to create your wallet, grab your address, and send your coins there.</p>
                                    <h3>3. Connect your wallet to the 1Inch DEX</h3>
                    <p>Head to 1Inch, and 'connect' your wallet to it.</p>
                                    <h3>4. You can now swap your ETH for MIR</h3>
                    <p>Now that you're connected, you'll be able to swap for 100s of coins including MIR.</p>
                

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/santa-delivers-as-mirror-and-anchor-protocol-tokens-surge/">Santa delivers as Mirror and Anchor Protocol tokens surge</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/santa-delivers-as-mirror-and-anchor-protocol-tokens-surge/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>7 of the Top Cryptos to Buy Now: Ultimate Growth in 2023</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/7-of-the-top-cryptos-to-buy-now-ultimate-growth-in-2023/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/7-of-the-top-cryptos-to-buy-now-ultimate-growth-in-2023/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice Davies]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 12:40:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance Coin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/7-of-the-top-cryptos-to-buy-now-ultimate-growth-in-2023/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>While knowing where to put your money in the current bear market can be tricky, many consider a few projects the top cryptos to buy now. As the crypto market trends lower, it might seem counterintuitive to start growing your portfolio now. But, these downturns contain some amazing investment opportunities. This article will explore seven [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/7-of-the-top-cryptos-to-buy-now-ultimate-growth-in-2023/">7 of the Top Cryptos to Buy Now: Ultimate Growth in 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">While knowing where to put your money in the current bear market can be tricky, many consider a few projects the top cryptos to buy now. As the crypto market trends lower, it might seem counterintuitive to start growing your portfolio now. But, these downturns contain some amazing investment opportunities. This article will explore seven promising projects and explain why 2023 could be their best year yet. &nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">1. Metacade (MCADE) &ndash; The top crypto for 2023</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://metacade.co/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade</u></a> is an exciting new project that aims to revolutionize the world of play-to-earn (P2E) gaming. It&rsquo;s a community hub where gamers can connect with like-minded enthusiasts, explore the latest P2E titles, and have their say on the future of Web3 gaming. You&rsquo;ll find everything you need on the platform to get ahead in P2E, like dedicated forums, live chats, reviews, leaderboards, and the hottest&nbsp;<a href="https://academy.binance.com/en/articles/what-is-gamefi-and-how-does-it-work" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>GameFi</u></a> alpha shared by experienced players.</p>
<p dir="ltr">One of Metacade&rsquo;s most significant ambitions is to attract the brightest minds in GameFi onto the platform to share their knowledge with others. That&rsquo;s why it&rsquo;s offering the MCADE token to anyone sharing reviews, tips, or other valuable content with the community. So whether you&rsquo;re a seasoned pro or a P2E noob, you can earn by helping to make Metacade the ultimate place for learning about and earning more from GameFi.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, sharing content is just one of many ways you can earn through Metacade. There are frequent prize draws, tournaments, and opportunities to top up your P2E income by casually testing games using Metacade&rsquo;s native testing environment. Moreover, Metacade&rsquo;s job board, expected in 2024, will host dozens of openings posted by titans of the Web3 and gaming industries, giving users a chance to shape their careers while working on their passion.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In late 2023, Metacade will be giving away its first Metagrant, a funding tool that allows the community to choose which games to build. The process is simple: developers can submit their ideas to a pool of competing projects, and the one that pulls in the most votes receives funding from the Metacade treasury. Not only does this foster a sense of community engagement and ownership, but it creates a grassroots fanbase for developers and allows them the opportunity to receive life-changing financing that might&rsquo;ve been previously unavailable to them.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade&rsquo;s goal is to become the world&rsquo;s first player-owned virtual arcade. To achieve this vision, it has plans to become a <a href="https://www.investopedia.com/tech/what-dao/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>decentralized autonomous organization (DAO)</u></a> once it&rsquo;s fully developed. The DAO will allow Metacade users to propose and vote on changes made to the platform, implemented by leaders selected by the community. In addition, to ensure trust and integrity amongst the community, Metacade will require that all transactions made from the treasury need multiple signatures before being processed.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">With the GameFi industry expected to accelerate at a 100% annual growth rate by 2025 (<a href="https://content-hub-static.crypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/GameFi_Past-Present-and-Future_Overview-with-Comparisons-to-Traditional-Gaming-Industry-2.pdf" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Crypto.com</u></a>), Metacade looks poised for an excellent 2023. Its community-first philosophy and plans to be a one-stop shop for everything P2E set it apart from the crowd, and thousands of investors agree that Metacade could be a top crypto for 2023. Metacade is still in phase 1 of its presale and has sold $1.25m worth of tokens since its launch!&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Part of this flood of investment is likely down to the fact that MCADE looks likely to outperform many top projects in the same period. With all these factors in mind, Metacade is the top crypto to buy right now.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>&gt;&gt;&gt; You can participate in the Metacade pre-sale&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://metacade.co/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong><u>here</u></strong></a><strong>&nbsp;&lt;&lt;&lt;</strong></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">2. Binance Coin (BNB) &ndash; Growing alongside the world&rsquo;s biggest crypto exchange</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://www.binance.com/en" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Binance Coin</u></a> is the native token of the Binance exchange, the world&rsquo;s largest and most popular crypto exchange. It&rsquo;s a multi-purpose utility token used to access exclusive features and benefits on Binance, like discounted trading fees, shopping on Binance Marketplace, and token sales through its Launchpad.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Since its inception in 2017, BNB has consistently remained one of the top-performing cryptocurrencies. From its $0.50 low in November 2017 to its $691.80 top in May 2021, BNB appreciated almost 140,000%! However, in today&rsquo;s bear market, BNB has a long way to go to reach its pre-2021 bull run price.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The continued popularity of BNB is primarily due to the continued success and popularity of the Binance exchange. As the number of people using Binance grows, so does the demand for BNB. Moreover, as one of the most well-trusted and established players in the game (recently supported by <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/proof-of-reserves" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Binance&rsquo;s proof of reserves</u></a>), Binance will likely continue to dominate. For that reason, BNB makes an excellent choice as one of the top cryptos to buy now. &nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">3. Ethereum (ETH) &ndash; Sharding to pave the way for 100,000 TPS</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Ethereum is the world&rsquo;s most popular smart contract platform, enabling the creation of thousands of decentralized apps (dApps), NFT projects, and crypto tokens. Sometimes referred to as &ldquo;the queen of crypto,&rdquo; Ethereum has used its first-mover advantage to dominate the smart contract space. And while many competitors have attempted to knock it from the top spot, they have yet to be able to garner the reputation of Ethereum.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">A recent article from <a href="https://www.banklesstimes.com/cryptocurrency/ethereum-adoption-statistics-data-reveals-surprising-findings/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Bankless Times</u></a> offers some impressive stats about Ethereum. For example, around 24.4% of crypto owners hold ETH globally, while its average daily transaction volume is roughly $16 billion! Additionally, Ethereum awareness is at 19.49% globally, and 2.38% of the global population holds Ethereum.</p>
<p dir="ltr">While Ethereum has received criticism for high transaction fees, slow speeds, and wasteful energy consumption, its recent transition to proof-of-stake should solve these issues. One of the most significant upgrades to Ethereum, anticipated in late 2023, will be sharding. Sharding will enable the Ethereum network to scale significantly, boosting transaction speeds from around 15 transactions per second (TPS) to over 100,000 TPS. This move could vastly expand the use cases for Ethereum and could be the catalyst for a new wave of crypto adoption. That makes Ethereum the third choice for the top cryptos to buy now.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">4. Ripple (XRP) &ndash; SEC vs. Ripple end date in sight?</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://ripple.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Ripple</u></a> is a payment network and digital currency designed to enable fast and cheap international transactions, particularly for financial institutions. Instead of using the traditional SWIFT banking system, which is slow and costly, banks can use Ripple to realize near-instant payments that cost a fraction of a cent.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">This innovation is certainly revolutionary, but Ripple&rsquo;s long-standing case with the SEC has overshadowed its progress. In late 2020, the SEC brought a lawsuit against Ripple Labs, the creators of Ripple, alleging that its sale of XRP constituted an unregistered securities offering. Since then, thousands of Ripple investors have joined the fight against the SEC.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to lawyer and Ripple supporter John Deaton, the case should reach a settlement in March, April, or May. With multiple mitigating factors for Ripple and a seemingly unconvincing case from the SEC, XRP will likely emerge victorious. Moreover, if the decision falls in Ripple&rsquo;s favor, it&rsquo;s expected that XRP will rocket overnight, making Ripple one of the top cryptos to buy for massive growth in 2023.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">5. Chainlink (LINK) &ndash; A vital project with almost no competition</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://chain.link/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Chainlink</u></a> is a decentralized oracle network that aims to provide secure and reliable data to smart contracts. Oracles are third-party services that allow external data, like events, transactions, and APIs, to be accessed by smart contracts, vastly improving the use cases for blockchain technology.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">For example, Chainlink can enable financial services to access real-time price data, allowing complex financial products to become entirely automated. This access has been the case across multiple DeFi projects that require Chainlink to function, like MakerDAO, Aave, and Synthetix. Alternatively, Chainlink can access data generated by smart sensors and meters for use in smart contracts.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This service is vital for the mass adoption of crypto, yet Chainlink faces very little competition. Its closest competitor is BAND Protocol, a project with less than a tenth of the market cap of Chainlink (<a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/band-protocol" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>CoinGecko</u></a>). Alongside many big-name partnerships with companies like Google, Amazon Web Services, and SWIFT, Chainlink&rsquo;s status as the leading provider of decentralized oracles seems unshakeable. That&rsquo;s why it&rsquo;s the fifth top crypto to buy now.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">6. Polkadot (DOT) &ndash; Could DOT scale to 1 million TPS?</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://polkadot.network/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Polkadot</u></a> is an Ethereum rival that aims to solve the interoperability issue across blockchain-enabled networks. Developers created Polkadot to be scalable, flexible, and able to facilitate communication between separate applications and blockchains, like Bitcoin and Ethereum. First, imagine the polka dot pattern; now, imagine connecting lines between all the dots. If each dot is an individual blockchain, then Polkadot is the one connecting the dots.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Unlike other layer 1 solutions, Polkadot was built with decentralization, speed, and security in mind. While other blockchains might excel in one area or another, few have been unable to excel at all three, unlike Polkadot. Much of this success is down to Polkadot&rsquo;s use of parachains, which effectively allow transactions to occur simultaneously rather than consecutively.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">In Q1 of 2023, Polkadot will launch parathreads, which will massively boost its scalability. Not only will block times be cut in half, from 12 seconds to 6 seconds, but transaction speeds should increase by 100 to 1,000 times. This increase in speed will take Polkadot from 1,000 TPS to upwards of 100,000 TPS and potentially even 1 million TPS, making the project a potent contender against Ethereum. These promising figures make DOT one of the top cryptos to buy now. &nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">7. Filecoin (FIL) &ndash; Powering the future of AI?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The last choice as one of the top cryptos for 2023 is&nbsp;<a href="https://filecoin.io/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Filecoin</u></a>. Filecoin is a decentralized storage network that allows users to rent out unused hard drive space to earn FIL tokens. Initially, Filecoin was created as a solution to the centralized storage industry, which is fraught with price gouging, fraud, hacks, and censorship. However, Filecoin is effectively the opposite: the market sets prices, and the decentralized nature of its protocol means that unauthorized access and censorship are virtually impossible.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">With the need for data storage only forecast to increase in the coming years, Filecoin is the perfect solution. It costs a fraction to store data using Filecoin compared to providers like Amazon Web Services or Microsoft Azure and doesn&rsquo;t require building more data centers. Above all else, Filecoin could soon dominate thanks to the rise of AI.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">AI requires massive amounts of data to function. According to <a href="https://twitter.com/sama/status/1599671496636780546" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>OpenAI&rsquo;s CEO, Sam Altman</u></a>, the cost of a single response from ChatGPT is &ldquo;probably single-digits cents,&rdquo; or between 10x to 100x the cost of a regular web search. This cost reflects the fact that computing power (and the number of servers) required to generate AI responses is enormous. Therefore, Filecoin could be used by companies like OpenAI to scale their products without facing exorbitant costs.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">With AI growing faster than previously thought, this necessity for cheap mass storage could come sooner rather than later, perhaps even by the end of 2023. As a result, Filecoin is likely to continue its reign over the decentralized storage market and is one of the top cryptos to buy now</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Metacade (MCADE) is the top crypto to buy now&nbsp;</h2>
<p dir="ltr">How 2023 will fare for the world of cryptocurrency has yet to be determined. However, with the Federal Reserve expected to wind back interest rate hikes in 2023, it could spell the end of the crypto bear market. When that happens, the seven cryptocurrencies on this list will likely rocket, especially given the multiple catalysts mentioned. However, Metacade stands out as the top crypto for 2023.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">With the potential for explosive growth in the GameFi industry, multiple community-based features gamers are sure to love, and a proven track record of attracting investment, Metacade is set for success in 2023. So if you&rsquo;re looking to get in on the ground floor with what could be a leader of P2E gaming, then stop looking. Instead, check out <a href="https://metacade.co/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade</u></a>&lsquo;s presale and discover what you could be missing out on!</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>You can buy the coins mentioned in this article at eToro&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://coinjournal.net/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=OTg4ODE" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong><u>here</u></strong></a><strong>.</strong></p>
<p><strong>You can participate in the Metacade pre-sale&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://metacade.co/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong><u>here</u></strong></a><strong>.</strong></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/7-of-the-top-cryptos-to-buy-now-ultimate-growth-in-2023/">7 of the Top Cryptos to Buy Now: Ultimate Growth in 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/7-of-the-top-cryptos-to-buy-now-ultimate-growth-in-2023/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>ACH soars by 6% as Alchemy Pay integrates its Fiat Onramp solution on Pear</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/ach-soars-by-6-as-alchemy-pay-integrates-its-fiat-onramp-solution-on-pear/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/ach-soars-by-6-as-alchemy-pay-integrates-its-fiat-onramp-solution-on-pear/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 09:45:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/ach-soars-by-6-as-alchemy-pay-integrates-its-fiat-onramp-solution-on-pear/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Alchemy Pay&#8217;s Fiat Onramp solution will be integrated into Pear. ACH is up by more than 6% today, outperforming the broader crypto market. The total crypto market cap remains above $800 billion. Alchemy Pay to integrate with Pear The Alchemy Pay team announced a few hours ago that its Fiat Onramp Solution would be integrated [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ach-soars-by-6-as-alchemy-pay-integrates-its-fiat-onramp-solution-on-pear/">ACH soars by 6% as Alchemy Pay integrates its Fiat Onramp solution on Pear</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Alchemy Pay&rsquo;s Fiat Onramp solution will be integrated into Pear.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">ACH is up by more than 6% today, outperforming the broader crypto market.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The total crypto market cap remains above $800 billion.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr">Alchemy Pay to integrate with Pear</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The Alchemy Pay team announced a few hours ago that its Fiat Onramp Solution would be integrated into Pear, a non-custodial marketplace governed by DAO.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">&#129395; <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/AlchemyPay?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#AlchemyPay</a> Fiat Onramp Solution will be integrated into <a href="https://twitter.com/OfficialPearDAO?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@OfficialPearDAO</a> in the near future! </p>
<p>With this collaboration, PearDAO's users can pay with their preferred fiat payment methods directly to buy <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/cryptocurrencies?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#cryptocurrencies</a> and <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/NFTs?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#NFTs</a>.<a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24ACH&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$ACH</a> <a href="https://t.co/VxMpAFvf5M">pic.twitter.com/VxMpAFvf5M</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Alchemy Pay: Fiat-Crypto Payment Gateway (@AlchemyPay) <a href="https://twitter.com/AlchemyPay/status/1607234747008438272?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 26, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">This <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>latest cryptocurrency news</u></a> means that PearDAO&rsquo;s users can pay with their preferred fiat payment methods directly to buy cryptocurrencies and NFTs.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">ACH, the native token of Alchemy Pay, is now up by more than 6% in the last 24 hours, outperforming the broader market. The total crypto market cap remains at around $810 billion, down by less than 1% so far today.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin, the world&rsquo;s leading cryptocurrency by market cap, is also up by less than 1% today. At press time, the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>price of Bitcoin</u></a> stands at $16,852 and could break past the $17k resistance level soon.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Key levels to watch</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The ACH/USD 4-hour chart is bullish, as Alchemy Pay has been performing well over the past few days. The technical indicators show that ACH could rally higher soon.</p>
<div class="fr-img-space-wrap"><span class="fr-img-caption fr-fic fr-dib fr-draggable fr-fil" style="width: 600px"><span class="fr-img-wrap">
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2022/11/26/1672046958298-a31fcb2e-b0cc-4d09-ad4c-448077f34022.png" style="width: 600px" class="fr-fic fr-dib fr-fil" width="600" height="261"><span class="fr-inner"></span></p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ACHUSD/?exchange=COINBASE"><u>ACH/USD Chart By TradingView</u></a></p>
<p></p></span>
<p></p></span>
<p class="fr-img-space-wrap2">&nbsp;</p>
</div>
<p dir="ltr">The MACD line is above the neutral zone, indicating that the bulls are currently in charge of the ACH market. The 14-day relative strength index of 64 also shows that ACH could enter the overbought region if the rally continues.</p>
<p dir="ltr">At press time, ACH is trading at $0.008435. If the rally continues, ACH could rally toward the $0.009313 resistance level in the near term.</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, it would need the support of the broader cryptocurrency market before it reaches the $0.010385 level it attained earlier this month.&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Where to buy Alchemy Pay now</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    Uphold</h3>

    <p>Uphold is a platform which has over 50 cryptocurrencies to choose from.

It's users can make crypto trades with a bank account, credit card or crypto debit card. It has variable fees and allows users to automate trades.

Users who are on Brave's internet browser can also earn BAT tokens based on their browsing habits.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/uphold-crypto?guid=OTg4Nzk&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=TX&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy ACH with Uphold today            </a>
    </p><h3>
    Swapzone</h3>

    <p>Swapzone is a crypto exchange aggregator that operates as a gateway between the cryptocurrency community and exchange services. Swapzone aims to provide a convenient interface, safe user flow, and crystal-clear data for users to find the best exchange rates among the whole cryptocurrency market.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/swapzone-crypto?guid=OTg4Nzk&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=TX&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy ACH with Swapzone today            </a>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ach-soars-by-6-as-alchemy-pay-integrates-its-fiat-onramp-solution-on-pear/">ACH soars by 6% as Alchemy Pay integrates its Fiat Onramp solution on Pear</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/ach-soars-by-6-as-alchemy-pay-integrates-its-fiat-onramp-solution-on-pear/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>1inch Network releases its Fusion upgrade: will 1inch rally higher?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/1inch-network-releases-its-fusion-upgrade-will-1inch-rally-higher/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/1inch-network-releases-its-fusion-upgrade-will-1inch-rally-higher/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 09:31:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/1inch-network-releases-its-fusion-upgrade-will-1inch-rally-higher/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>1inch Network has announced the release of its Fusion upgrade. The upgrade is set to empower DeFi users to place orders with a specified price and time range. 1INCH is up by less than 1% today but could rally higher soon. 1inch Network&#8217;s Fusion upgrade is now live The 1inch Network team announced earlier today [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/1inch-network-releases-its-fusion-upgrade-will-1inch-rally-higher/">1inch Network releases its Fusion upgrade: will 1inch rally higher?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">1inch Network has announced the release of its Fusion upgrade.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The upgrade is set to empower DeFi users to place orders with a specified price and time range.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">1INCH is up by less than 1% today but could rally higher soon.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>1inch Network&rsquo;s Fusion upgrade is now live</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">The 1inch Network team announced earlier today that its Fusion upgrade had been released. Fusion is a major upgrade centered around the 1inch Swap Engine and is set to empower DeFi users to place orders with a specified price and time range.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">1/ &#128579; Remember we teased some major release about a week ago?</p>
<p>This upgrade is gonna turn the <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/DeFi?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#DeFi</a> game &#128259; upside down.</p>
<p>&#9981;&#65039;&#128683; Meet <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/FusionMode?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#FusionMode</a>, which enables users to place orders without paying network fees!</p>
<p>&#10145;&#65039; Read more: <a href="https://t.co/bniaJKEWnp">https://t.co/bniaJKEWnp</a><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/1inch?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#1inch</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/crypto?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#crypto</a></p>
<p>&mdash; 1inch Network (@1inch) <a href="https://twitter.com/1inch/status/1607015053307379712?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 25, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">This <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>latest cryptocurrency news</u></a> has seen 1INCH outperform the broader cryptocurrency market so far today. At press time, the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/1inch-network/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>price of 1INCH</u></a> stands at $0.4016 per coin, up by less than 1% in the last 24 hours.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The broader cryptocurrency market is underperforming so far today. At press time, the total cryptocurrency market cap stands at $810 billion, down by less than 1% so far today.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin is also up by less than 1% in the last 24 hours but continues to struggle to move past the $17k resistance level.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Key levels to watch</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The 1INCH/USD 4-hour char is bearish as the coin has been underperforming in recent days. The technical indicators show that 1INCH could be ready for a breakout soon.</p>
<div class="fr-img-space-wrap"><span class="fr-img-caption fr-fic fr-dib fr-draggable fr-fil" style="width: 600px"><span class="fr-img-wrap">
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2022/11/26/1672046957894-3e3bf1ee-ce82-4474-936e-7d409cca85b9.png" style="width: 600px" class="fr-fic fr-dib fr-fil" width="600" height="284"><span class="fr-inner"><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/1INCHUSD/?exchange=BITSTAMP"><u>1INCH/USD Chart By TradingView</u></a></span></p>
<p></p></span></span>
<p class="fr-img-space-wrap2">&nbsp;</p>
</div>
<p dir="ltr">The MACD line remains below the neutral zone but continues to move higher. If the bulls gain control soon, the line could cross into the positive region.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The 14-day relative strength index of 32 means that 1INCH is no longer in the oversold region. However, it would need to rally higher before it can enter the overbought zone.</p>
<p dir="ltr">If the bulls pick up pace, 1INCH could surge past the first major resistance level at $0.49 before the end of the day. However, the second major resistance level at $0.63 would be hard for 1INCH to breach in the near term.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Where to buy 1inch Network now</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>

    <p>eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=OTg4Nzg&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=TX&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy 1INCH with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    Binance</h3>

    <p>Binance is one of the largest cryptocurrency exchanges in the world. It is better suited to more experienced investors and it offers a large number of cryptocurrencies to choose from, at over 600.

Binance is also known for having low trading fees and a multiple of trading options that its users can benefit from, such as; peer-to-peer trading, margin trading and spot trading.
</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/binance-crypto?guid=OTg4Nzg&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=TX&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy 1INCH with Binance today            </a>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/1inch-network-releases-its-fusion-upgrade-will-1inch-rally-higher/">1inch Network releases its Fusion upgrade: will 1inch rally higher?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/1inch-network-releases-its-fusion-upgrade-will-1inch-rally-higher/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>This week in crypto: SBF extradited to the United States</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/this-week-in-crypto-sbf-extradited-to-the-united-states/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/this-week-in-crypto-sbf-extradited-to-the-united-states/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 15:57:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/this-week-in-crypto-sbf-extradited-to-the-united-states/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SBF is finally in the United States after signing an agreement earlier this year. The SEC chair said the agency would continue cracking down on cryptocurrency companies. Paxful removes Ether from their trading platform. SBF is now in the United States Sam Bankman-Fried, the former CEO of FTX, is now back in the US after [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/this-week-in-crypto-sbf-extradited-to-the-united-states/">This week in crypto: SBF extradited to the United States</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">SBF is finally in the United States after signing an agreement earlier this year.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The SEC chair said the agency would continue cracking down on cryptocurrency companies.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Paxful removes Ether from their trading platform.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>SBF is now in the United States</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Sam Bankman-Fried, the former CEO of FTX, is now back in the US after he was extradited from the Bahamas earlier this week. He&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sbf-signs-us-extradition-papers-expected-in-the-us-on-wednesday/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>signed US extradition papers</u></a> earlier this week and was moved to the United States on Thursday.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Following the extradition, SBF was issued a $250 million bail which he paid a few hours later. However, he still has a lot to answer for in the United States.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Earlier this week, former Alameda CEO Caroline Ellison and FTX co-founder Gary Wang&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/former-alameda-ceo-caroline-ellison-and-ftx-co-founder-gary-wang-plead-guilty/"><u>pleaded guilty</u></a>, after they were charged with committing fraud that resulted in the collapse of the FTX cryptocurrency exchange.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to the US Attorney for South District of New York (SDNY) Damian Williams, this is likely not the last major development in relation to the FTX investigations.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The US SEC also announced earlier this week that it had charged Wang and Ellison for their roles in a multiyear scheme to defraud FTX equity investors.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>The SEC to continues its crackdown on crypto</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">The SEC chair, Gary Gensler, revealed earlier this week that the agency would continue to clamp down on cryptocurrency companies. He called for the regulation of crypto issuers and exchanges.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">In an interview earlier this week, Gensler said;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;Financial history would tell you that most of these tokens [native tokens of crypto exchanges] will fail. [Insiders] sell the public on an idea while they&rsquo;re potentially fraudulently pumping up the stock. This leads to distorted incentives and puts the public further at risk of the token not being properly registered and having proper disclosures and complying with the various provisions of the securities law about anti-fraud and anti-manipulation.&rdquo;</em></p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Paxful removes ETH from its platform</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Peer-to-peer trading exchange Paxful announced earlier this week that it had&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/paxful-removes-ethereum-eth-from-its-platform/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>removed Ether from its platform</u></a>. The Paxful CEO &nbsp;cited the prevalence of scams among Ethereum-based tokens as one of the major reasons why ETH was removed.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Tezos activates the Lima upgrade</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">The Tezos team announced earlier this week that it had&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tezos-activates-the-12th-upgrade-lima/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>completed the 12th upgrade</u></a> on its blockchain. The upgrade, called Lima, introduces several new features while also reducing the risk of bugs in smart contracts.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Lima marks the fourth protocol upgrade in 2022 as Tezos seeks to improve its blockchain.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Waves planning to launch another stablecoin</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Waves already has the USDN stablecoin, but that might not be enough. The Waves CEO and founder, Sasha Ivanov, promised that he would launch a new stablecoin, one that cannot be deppeged from the US Dollar.</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, the CEO said the new stablecoin would not be launched until the USDN plan resolution is implemented.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Binance.US acquires Voyager assets</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">BAM Trading Services Inc.&rsquo;s bid (operating as Binance.US) was chosen by Voyager Digital LLC, the operating unit of Voyager Digital Ltd., to acquire its assets after reviewing strategic options.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Voyager Digital said it chose Binance.US because it wants to maximise the value returned to clients and creditors as soon as possible. The bid from Binance.US is valued at around $1.022 billion.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to Voyager, the bid consists of the to-be-set fair market value of its crypto portfolio, valued at $1.002 billion at current market prices.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/this-week-in-crypto-sbf-extradited-to-the-united-states/">This week in crypto: SBF extradited to the United States</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/this-week-in-crypto-sbf-extradited-to-the-united-states/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Classic Price Prediction: ETC seems stable whilst Metacade (MCADE) doesn&#8217;t stop rising</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-classic-price-prediction-etc-seems-stable-whilst-metacade-mcade-doesnt-stop-rising/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice Davies]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 15:24:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum Classic News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-classic-price-prediction-etc-seems-stable-whilst-metacade-mcade-doesnt-stop-rising/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Web3 is a constantly expanding industry and crypto price action tends to favour projects that can adapt to its fast-changing environment. ETC is a classic example of a project that has been left behind due to its inability to scale with the rest of the industry, which has resulted in some pessimistic price predictions for [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-classic-price-prediction-etc-seems-stable-whilst-metacade-mcade-doesnt-stop-rising/">Ethereum Classic Price Prediction: ETC seems stable whilst Metacade (MCADE) doesn&#8217;t stop rising</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Web3 is a constantly expanding industry and crypto price action tends to favour projects that can adapt to its fast-changing environment. ETC is a classic example of a project that has been left behind due to its inability to scale with the rest of the industry, which has resulted in some pessimistic price predictions for the Ethereum Classic token.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In contrast, the latest Ethereum blockchain (ETH) continues to grow. There are some key differences between the two Ethereum chains, including ETH being home to fast-growing projects like Metacade.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Ethereum Classic?</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/ethereum-classic/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Ethereum Classic (ETC)</u></a> is a cryptocurrency that was created as a result of a fork in the Ethereum blockchain. Unlike Ethereum (ETH), Ethereum Classic does not support the use of smart contracts. Since ETC is not Turing Complete, developers cannot create decentralised applications (dApps) on the Ethereum Classic blockchain and this has always placed negative pressure on the Ethereum Classic price prediction.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Ethereum Classic is often referred to as &ldquo;Ethereum&rsquo;s original chain&rdquo; because it retains the original Ethereum blockchain. After the Ethereum hard fork in October 2016, Ethereum Classic was kept online by nodes all over the world. This means that crypto users can still make transactions on the Ethereum Classic network, despite Ethereum Mainnet moving in a different direction over the past 6 years.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In recent times, Ethereum Mainnet has made the switch from a Proof of Work consensus mechanism to Proof of Stake. This has reduced the cost of supporting network infrastructure. While ETH is now Proof of Stake, ETC remains a Proof of Work blockchain. The result is that Ethereum Classic is slower and more expensive to run with a block time of 14 seconds and high transaction fees due to its energy-intensive mining system.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Price action lacking in ETC</h3>
<p dir="ltr">The current price of ETC is $25.19. Since&nbsp;<a href="https://www.forbes.com/advisor/au/investing/cryptocurrency/what-is-ethereum-classic/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Ethereum Classic is the oldest Ethereum chain</u></a> and is restricted by its inability to support dApps, it has much lower transaction activity than Ethereum Mainnet. With fewer people buying the token, ETC price is now a fraction as high as ETH, with poor Ethereum Classic price prediction assessments coming from analysts looking at its mid- to long-term prospects.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Despite this, the Ethereum Classic market cap is over $3 billion. However, the chain&rsquo;s lack of functionality within the world of Web3 means it has lower growth potential for the long term. In trying to choose the correct Ethereum Classic price prediction, it&rsquo;ll be important to think about the situation from a development perspective. For developers looking to build exciting digital services using blockchain technology, Ethereum Classic is not an option.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The expected result is that new projects building on ETH will continue to gain value while the Ethereum Classic price prediction shows ETC falling even further in the future. It all boils down to utility.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">A New Project in the ETH Ecosystem Making Major Gains</h2>
<p dir="ltr">While ETC price action leaves much to be desired due to its lack of functionality, one token that continues to impress is&nbsp;<a href="https://metacade.co/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade</u></a>. Built using the latest Ethereum blockchain, this project offers broad utility to crypto holders who are looking to make the most out of the Web3 user experience.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade aims to support the expansion of GameFi as a core sector of blockchain technology. It is a community-driven initiative that rewards crypto natives for providing value to the ecosystem, among a host of other exciting features that are attracting widespread interest.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Metacade?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade is a broad gaming platform that aims to support the expansion of GameFi. Play-to-Earn projects are revolutionising the gaming industry, as players gain financial rewards for the time they spend in-game. This is a core reason why so many are predicting high growth potential for the GameFi sector over the coming years and Metacade is positioning itself as a key player.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Millions Expected to Join the Metaverse</h3>
<p dir="ltr">There are many exciting new&nbsp;<a href="https://www.coin98.net/what-is-gamefi" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>P2E</u></a> projects being developed and the scope of what is possible in the metaverse is constantly being expanded. As blockchain technology becomes increasingly more advanced, and the world becomes increasingly more digital, millions of people are expected to jump into the metaverse to enjoy the hottest new Play-to-Earn games.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Supporting GameFi Developers</h3>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade supports this expansion directly through its Metagrants program. The community will get to decide which new GameFi projects sound the most promising, and vote to use the Metacade treasury to directly fund the development teams. Metacade&rsquo;s aim is to drive growth in Play-to-Earn gaming. For innovative developers that have exciting new ideas, this is an extremely valuable service. The Metacade ecosystem could become a hub of technological progress as a result, pushing the limits and ensuring a fresh supply of awesome titles.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Rewarding Play-to-Earn Gamers</h3>
<p dir="ltr">In addition to supporting the continued development of blockchain-based gaming, Metacade offers some unique features to P2E gamers in its own metaverse scope. Active members of the Metacade community can earn MCADE rewards for their contributions. This includes sharing tips, tricks, and useful knowledge about how to optimise your GameFi playing experience.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The gaming community is at the centre of Metacade&rsquo;s plans for the future. The project aims to connect avid gamers with the best Play-to-Earn opportunities, creating a virtual arcade where users can collaborate and share their insights. Power is given back to the community, as players can share their suggestions with game developers directly and earn MCADE tokens in the process.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">MCADE vs ETC: Which Token Should You Buy?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">While Ethereum Classic continues to hold its price above the $20 mark, investors are favouring projects that support the Web3 ecosystem, giving a relatively negative outlook for Ethereum Classic price prediction. </p>
<p dir="ltr">Ethereum Mainnet, on the other hand, remains the most-used network of decentralised applications, and people are bullish on the long-term future of dApps themselves. ETH stands to fare much better than any Ethereum Classic price prediction currently available, and for good reasons: its upcoming projects.</p>
<p dir="ltr">A prime example of a high-potential project being built on Ethereum is Metacade. Through supporting the expansion of GameFi and offering exclusive benefits to P2E players in an immersive digital world, Metacade is an attractive option for long-term crypto investors.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The MCADE presale is starting out at $0.008 per token. It has high long-term potential, and the price of each token will be increasing as it progresses through presale stages. In contrast, ETC continues to experience slow growth, as the latest Ethereum blockchain offers a vastly improved user experience.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>You can buy ETC on eToro&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://www.etoro.com/markets/etc" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong><u>here</u></strong></a><strong>.</strong></p>
<p><strong>You can participate in the MCADE presale&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://metacade.co/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong><u>here</u></strong></a><strong>.</strong></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-classic-price-prediction-etc-seems-stable-whilst-metacade-mcade-doesnt-stop-rising/">Ethereum Classic Price Prediction: ETC seems stable whilst Metacade (MCADE) doesn&#8217;t stop rising</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Metacade signs terms to list on BitMart</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-signs-terms-to-list-on-bitmart/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 15:18:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-signs-terms-to-list-on-bitmart/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Metacade is expected to list on BitMart after signing the listing terms. Metacade presale is currently in the Beta Sale stage. The Beta round price of the MCADE token is 0.01 USDT for 1 MCADE. After a successful Metacade (MCADE) presale amid the current crypto bear market, Metacade has today announced that it has signed [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-signs-terms-to-list-on-bitmart/">Metacade signs terms to list on BitMart</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul class="decimal_type">
<li>Metacade is expected to list on BitMart after signing the listing terms.</li>
<li>Metacade presale is currently in the Beta Sale stage.</li>
<li>The Beta round price of the MCADE token is 0.01 USDT for 1 MCADE.</li>
</ul>
<p>After a successful <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-presale-for-web3s-first-ever-p2e-crypto-arcade-raises-over-670k-in-under-2-weeks/">Metacade (MCADE) presale</a> amid the current crypto bear market, Metacade has today announced that it has signed the terms to get listed on BitMart, a leading crypto exchange ranked at position 21 by CoinMarketCap with an average daily trading volume of about $447M.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">&#128680;&#128680;&#128680; BREAKING &#128680;&#128680;&#128680;</p>
<p>We are delighted to announce that we have signed terms with one of the leading exchanges in the crypto space, <a href="https://twitter.com/BitMartExchange?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@BitMartExchange</a>! &#9889;&#9889;&#9889;</p>
<p>With over $447m of trading volume in the last 24 hours, they stand 21st in the <a href="https://twitter.com/CoinMarketCap?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@CoinMarketCap</a> exchange rankings! &#128293; <a href="https://t.co/4fxrM0ul6I">pic.twitter.com/4fxrM0ul6I</a></p>
<p>&mdash; METACADE (@Metacade_) <a href="https://twitter.com/Metacade_/status/1606280441190907904?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 23, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>If the listing process is to be completed successfully, BitMart will be among the first cryptocurrency exchanges to allow its customers to trade the decentralized GameFi token that has been making headlines in the past month.</p>
<h2>MCADE token performance so far</h2>
<p>Before delving into the performance of the Metacade (MCADE) token, it is important to mention that Metacade is disrupting the crypto market as we know it by creating a decentralized GameFi hub that will bring everything related to Play-to-Earn (P2E) on one platform. P2E games have been such a hit within the blockchain and crypto world, which is likely the reason behind the great performance of the MCADE token at a time when even the likes of Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH) are struggling.</p>
<p>The MCADE token is currently in the <a href="https://metacade.co/?utm_contentlaunch&amp;utm_term=external&amp;utm_mediumpr=&amp;utm_source=media&amp;utm_campaign=chainwire">Beta presale round</a> and 54% of the available MCADE tokens have already been sold out raising a whopping $1,340,966. One MCADE token is going for 0.01 USDT and the price is expected to rise to 0.012 USDT for one MCADE token in the next stage.</p>
<p>The next phase for Metacade is expected to be highly exciting as gamers and blockchain fanatics collaborate, communicate, and participate in things like dynamic virtual hangouts on the platform.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-signs-terms-to-list-on-bitmart/">Metacade signs terms to list on BitMart</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin versus Ethereum: Which one should you buy when the bull market returns</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-versus-ethereum-which-one-should-you-buy-when-the-bull-market-returns/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-versus-ethereum-which-one-should-you-buy-when-the-bull-market-returns/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Motiur Rahman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 14:47:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-versus-ethereum-which-one-should-you-buy-when-the-bull-market-returns/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin and Ethereum rank #1 and #2, respectively by market cap Bitcoin is a digital version of currency while Ethereum powers smart contracts Both cryptocurrencies are attractive in a bull market Bitcoin and Ethereum rank as the biggest cryptocurrencies. To an investor, deciding which one to buy can be confusing. However, it should be easy [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-versus-ethereum-which-one-should-you-buy-when-the-bull-market-returns/">Bitcoin versus Ethereum: Which one should you buy when the bull market returns</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin and Ethereum rank #1 and #2, respectively by market cap</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin is a digital version of currency while Ethereum powers smart contracts</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Both cryptocurrencies are attractive in a bull market</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin and Ethereum rank as the biggest cryptocurrencies. To an investor, deciding which one to buy can be confusing. However, it should be easy if you understand the role that each plays in the crypto evolution.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Bitcoin (BTC)</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Think of&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/what-is-bitcoin/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Bitcoin</u></a> (BTC/USD) as a digital version of your local currency. The biggest cryptocurrency is, however, different since it is based on a peer-to-peer network. It is decentralised, hence distinct from the conventional currencies, which are controlled by states and national central banks.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As money evolves and digitisation takes over, Bitcoin could become the new form of money. That will see it become a means of payment and a store of value.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Invented in 2009, BTC has immensely grown in value. In 2021, the cryptocurrency tapped an all-time high of above $68,000. That compares to a price of just $500 in 2016 before the cryptocurrency embarked on a sustained surge. Bitcoin now trades above $16,000 after a sustained bear market this year.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Where to buy BTC</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>

    <p>eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=OTgyNDY&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=TX&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy BTC with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    Bitstamp</h3>

    <p>Bitstamp is a leading cryptocurrency exchange which offers trading in fiat currencies or popular cryptocurrencies.

Bitstamp is a fully regulated company which offers users an intuitive interface, a high degree of security for your digital assets, excellent customer support and multiple withdrawal methods.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/bitstamp-crypto?guid=OTgyNDY&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=TX&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy BTC with Bitstamp today            </a>
    </p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Ethereum (ETH)</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Ranked as the second largest cryptocurrency,&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/what-is-ethereum/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Ethereum</u></a> (ETH) is viewed as the epitome of smart contracts. Like Bitcoin, Ethereum is decentralised and acts as a store of value, means of payment, and collateral.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Nonetheless, unlike Bitcoin, which is a dedicated form of digital money, Ethereum aims to power smart contracts, dApps, NFTs, and DeFi. It is also relatively newer compared to Bitcoin since it was created in 2015.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Ethereum price also had its fair share of strengths, reaching nearly $4,800 in 2021. Ethereum traded at less than $10 in 2016 before the start of a sustained climb. It now trades at $1,200 in a bear market. Investors anticipate that a recent move from proof of work consensus to proof of stake could power Ethereum to previous heights when the bull market returns.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Where to buy ETH</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>

    <p>eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=OTgyNDY&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=TX&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy ETH with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    Bitstamp</h3>

    <p>Bitstamp is a leading cryptocurrency exchange which offers trading in fiat currencies or popular cryptocurrencies.

Bitstamp is a fully regulated company which offers users an intuitive interface, a high degree of security for your digital assets, excellent customer support and multiple withdrawal methods.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/bitstamp-crypto?guid=OTgyNDY&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=TX&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy ETH with Bitstamp today            </a>
    </p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Final verdict</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin and Ethereum are very strong&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/cryptocurrencies/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>cryptocurrencies</u></a>. Their price movement is almost similar, making it difficult to choose one over another. The selection of which cryptocurrency to invest in depends on what you like about each. The technical outlook and fundamentals emerging from each can also help when making a decision.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-versus-ethereum-which-one-should-you-buy-when-the-bull-market-returns/">Bitcoin versus Ethereum: Which one should you buy when the bull market returns</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-versus-ethereum-which-one-should-you-buy-when-the-bull-market-returns/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Helium token jumps 36%. Is this a bull trap?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/helium-token-jumps-36-is-this-a-bull-trap/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/helium-token-jumps-36-is-this-a-bull-trap/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Motiur Rahman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 14:27:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/helium-token-jumps-36-is-this-a-bull-trap/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Helium token rose by 36% on Thursday before correcting Helium powers IoT devices through its &#8220;hotspots&#8221; The cryptocurrency remains on a clear downtrend A few&#160;cryptocurrencies embarked on relief rallies on Thursday, although a low-cap coin was among the top gainers. Helium (HNT/USD), a cryptocurrency ranked #91 by market cap, rose by 36% before shedding nearly [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/helium-token-jumps-36-is-this-a-bull-trap/">Helium token jumps 36%. Is this a bull trap?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Helium token rose by 36% on Thursday before correcting</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Helium powers IoT devices through its &ldquo;hotspots&rdquo;</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The cryptocurrency remains on a clear downtrend</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">A few&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/cryptocurrencies/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>cryptocurrencies</u></a> embarked on relief rallies on Thursday, although a low-cap coin was among the top gainers. Helium (HNT/USD), a cryptocurrency ranked #91 by market cap, rose by 36% before shedding nearly half of the gains by Friday. In an exceedingly bearish crypto market, the small-cap token warranted investors&rsquo; attention. What is it?</p>
<p dir="ltr">Helium is a blockchain-powered network that was created in July 2019. It is made to power Internet of Things devices. For instance, it enables wireless devices to communicate and share data through its nodes or &ldquo;hotspots.&rdquo; The network also lets users profitably earn by sharing their broadband. </p>
<p dir="ltr">You would be forgiven for thinking that Helium is less used. Companies that use the IoT technology service of Helium include Abeeway, Agulus, and Airly. The network has been witnessing increasing growth and now connects nearly 1,000k hotspots. In September, Helium announced a migration to Solana to grow its ecosystem. That was after more than 6,000 members voted in favour. The goal of moving to Solana was inspired by the need to cut reliance entirely on its network.</p>
<p dir="ltr">While Helium token price could be earning boosts from the recent changes, the price is unconvincing. Trading at just $2.0, HNT remains on a clear downtrend. The cryptocurrency has lost 96% of value since its $57 all-time high price in November 2021. The cryptocurrency faces resistance at the 50-day MA.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Helium token rejected at the 50-day MA</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2022/11/23/1671805626594-3b76406d-93ac-494c-bda4-368b1cf50f24.png" style="width: 600px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="600" height="321"></p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/HNTUSD/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>HNT/USD Chart by TradingView</u></a></p>
<p dir="ltr">Helium outlook shows the price coming under pressure as it touched the 50-day MA. From the volume indicators, a price spike happened at $1.6, indicating that buyers were very active. The cryptocurrency traded with an intraday 1,500% jump in volumes at the bottom price.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>What next for HNT?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Despite the intraday gains,&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/helium/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>HNT price</u></a> lacks a clear path to recovery as the trend is still bearish. The gains could be a bull trap, especially after getting rejected at the moving averages.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Where to buy HNT</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    Binance</h3>

    <p>Binance is one of the largest cryptocurrency exchanges in the world. It is better suited to more experienced investors and it offers a large number of cryptocurrencies to choose from, at over 600.

Binance is also known for having low trading fees and a multiple of trading options that its users can benefit from, such as; peer-to-peer trading, margin trading and spot trading.
</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/binance-crypto?guid=OTgyNDE&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=TX&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy HNT with Binance today            </a>
    </p><h3>
    Vindax</h3>

    <p>VinDAX Exchange has been live for cryptocurrency trading for global users since March 2019. VinDAX focuses on providing exchange services for digital cryptocurrency transcations with high security level, excellent efficiency and well-optmized trading fee.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/vindax-crypto?guid=OTgyNDE&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=TX&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy HNT with Vindax today            </a>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/helium-token-jumps-36-is-this-a-bull-trap/">Helium token jumps 36%. Is this a bull trap?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/helium-token-jumps-36-is-this-a-bull-trap/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
