<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 11:35:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin consolidation continues ahead of the US inflation report</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-consolidation-continues-ahead-of-the-us-inflation-report/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-consolidation-continues-ahead-of-the-us-inflation-report/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mircea Vasiu]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 11:35:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-consolidation-continues-ahead-of-the-us-inflation-report/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin forms a possible pennant formation ahead of the US inflation report The disinflationary process in the US is set to continue If the dollar takes a hit, Bitcoin may rise above horizontal resistance Summer trading is usually slow and tricky. Even the cryptocurrency market often consolidates levels longer than the norm. It is the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-consolidation-continues-ahead-of-the-us-inflation-report/">Bitcoin consolidation continues ahead of the US inflation report</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitcoin forms a possible pennant formation ahead of the US inflation report</li>
<li>The disinflationary process in the US is set to continue</li>
<li>If the dollar takes a hit, Bitcoin may rise above horizontal resistance</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p>Summer trading is usually slow and tricky. Even the cryptocurrency market often consolidates levels longer than the norm.</p>
<p>It is the case with Bitcoin lately. The good news for cryptocurrency fans is that Bitcoin price holds close to the year&rsquo;s high.</p>
<p>Therefore, one could only ask if this consolidation is a continuation pattern before another leg higher or if sellers put pressure here ahead of the key US inflation report to be released tomorrow.</p>
<p>Like it or not, Bitcoin&rsquo;s performance is linked to the way the US dollar moves. As such, US economic data is critical for the digital asset&rsquo;s performance, especially data directly impacting the Federal Reserve&rsquo;s monetary policy decisions.</p>
<h2>June US CPI is expected to show further declines</h2>
<p>It should be obvious by now that inflation is cooling in the Western Hemisphere. Not all countries have seen similar trends, but the disinflationary process is in full force.</p>
<p>That is why traders expect the June US CPI report, due for release tomorrow, to show that the annual inflation in the United States dropped to 3.1% from 4% previously. If matched by the actual data, the US dollar will take a hit as the bets of further increases from the Fed will decline dramatically.</p>
<p>Hence, Bitcoin should pop above the horizontal resistance seen at $32k.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/11/1689074986789-0e022f43-0f8d-4a18-9196-5f9008361253.jpg" style="width: 1800px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="1800" height="488"></p>
<p><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/?exchange=CRYPTO" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Bitcoin chart by TradingView</a></p>
<h2>A possible pennant keeps Bitcoin hodlers optimistic</h2>
<p>A pennant is a bullish technical analysis pattern. The market typically rallies after a bullish breakout and travels a distance equal to the distance prior to the pennant&rsquo;s formation.</p>
<p>In Bitcoin&rsquo;s case, this is about $6k on top of $31k, so $37k is the logical target.</p>
<p>But that won&rsquo;t happen unless the US inflation report delivers a positive surprise. More precisely, if the inflation cools down more than expected, the Fed is less likely to raise rates, and so the US dollar should weaken.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-consolidation-continues-ahead-of-the-us-inflation-report/">Bitcoin consolidation continues ahead of the US inflation report</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-consolidation-continues-ahead-of-the-us-inflation-report/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Zuckerberg’s Threads hits 100 million users- What&#8217;s in it for Chancer?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/zuckerbergs-threads-hits-100-million-users-whats-in-it-for-chancer/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/zuckerbergs-threads-hits-100-million-users-whats-in-it-for-chancer/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 11:07:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Twitter]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/zuckerbergs-threads-hits-100-million-users-whats-in-it-for-chancer/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Twitter rival Threads has raced to more than 100 million users days after its launch. Chancer is a predictive markets app built on the blockchain and which seeks to disrupt the betting market. The $CHANCER presale is gaining upside momentum amid investor exuberance on project&#8217;s potential. Chancer&#8217;s presale is gathering fresh momentum, with over 67 [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/zuckerbergs-threads-hits-100-million-users-whats-in-it-for-chancer/">Zuckerberg’s Threads hits 100 million users- What&#8217;s in it for Chancer?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Twitter rival Threads has raced to more than 100 million users days after its launch.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Chancer is a predictive markets app built on the blockchain and which seeks to disrupt the betting market.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The $CHANCER presale is gaining upside momentum amid investor exuberance on project&rsquo;s potential.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Chancer&rsquo;s presale</a> is gathering fresh momentum, with over 67 million tokens sold and nearly $680k raised so far. This comes as the investor community gets to learn about the potential impact of this blockchain-based predictive markets platform in the global betting industry.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The project is also attracting interest at a time when what would end up as an epic battle in the social media space takes shape.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What&rsquo;s Threads?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Mark Zuckerberg, the CEO &amp; founder of Meta Platforms (formerly Facebook), recently announced the launch of Threads, a new social media platform touted as the biggest threat to Twitter. Days after the launch, which saw over 30 million sign ups in hours, Threads has hit more than 100 million users.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The rivalry between this Instagram sister app and the Elon Musk-owned platform might just be at the beginning of what could turn into a titanic battle. Already, Musk has labelled Threads a copycat and his lawyers have threatened legal action over allegations that Meta snapped former Twitter employees to gain insider information that it used to create Threads.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Threads has Twitter-like features such as liking posts, commenting, retweeting (reposting), and sharing. There are no direct messages or hashtags. The app however supports 500 characters per thread (more than Twitter), and videos of up to 5 minutes.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Twitter vs. Threads: &nbsp;Who&rsquo;s your money on?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Statistics <a href="https://www.statista.com/statistics/303681/twitter-users-worldwide/">show</a> Twitter&rsquo;s users number less than 370 million, which means Threads could possibly overtake it. It is notable that Twitter had to wait five years to reach 100 million users &ndash; something Threads did in four days.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Predictions on the possibility of Threads overtaking Twitter or not are part of the social conversation now. Also not surprising is the fact that some people might have placed wagers on one or the other outcome.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">While the Musk vs. Zuckerberg &ldquo;caged match&rdquo; type of battle has zero chance of happening, if it ever does, blockchain-based Chancer app could be where most wagers happen due to its completely different approach to betting.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Chancer?</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Chancer</a> is a new predictive markets platform that looks to tap into the power of blockchain technology to revolutionise the betting industry. While a few crypto projects offer prediction markets products, Chancer is taking a new approach to the industry &ndash; one that is tailored towards removing control from traditional bookmakers.</p>
<p dir="ltr">It seeks to replace the centralised approach of legacy betting companies with a decentralised peer-to-peer (P2P) model. The goal, according to the Chancer whitepaper, is to put users in control of the markets (odds, rules, payouts).</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bettors placing wager on any market can play by their own rules and leverage the utility of the native $CHANCER token to benefit from passive income opportunities. Token holders also have a chance to earn passively by staking tokens to bolster network security.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Chancer presale gains fresh momentum</h2>
<p dir="ltr">$CHANCER is a Binance Smart Chain token currently in presale. There&rsquo;s fresh momentum for the token sale as investors poured over $200k in two days to push overall fundraising proceeds to over $676k.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">As CoinJournal <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-introduces-a-unique-betting-platform-for-cryptocurrency-enthusiasts/">highlighted</a> in June, Chancer&rsquo;s unique approach could be very attractive to investors.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Investors who participate in the presale are helping Chancer raise funds to achieve its mission of democratising the betting industry. And it&rsquo;s likely that investing now while prices of the native token are still low could come with significant future returns.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The platform targets $15 million across 12 presale stages. </p>
<h2 dir="ltr">A look at the Chancer roadmap</h2>
<p dir="ltr">As well as the <a href="https://chancer.com/whitepaper.pdf" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">whitepaper</a> that outlines the technology behind the project and how it works, many people eyeing investments in its token also look at the roadmap. In most cases, a clear roadmap with strategic milestones is critical to a project&rsquo;s overall success.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer&rsquo;s roadmap includes the token launch on exchanges in the third quarter of 2023 before further development of the P2P platform in the next quarter. Testnets for the product will then pave the way for the mainnet launch expected in Q1, 2024.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The platform will also integrate Filecoin for file storage and launch its quadratic governance system as it works on achieving true decentralisation.</p>
<p dir="ltr">If you are looking for more details about Chancer before you invest, a good place to start would be <a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">here</a>.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/zuckerbergs-threads-hits-100-million-users-whats-in-it-for-chancer/">Zuckerberg’s Threads hits 100 million users- What&#8217;s in it for Chancer?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/zuckerbergs-threads-hits-100-million-users-whats-in-it-for-chancer/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Blockchain Game Pikamoon Raises $3.6m, Final ICO Phase Selling Out Fast</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-blockchain-game-pikamoon-raises-3-6m-final-ico-phase-selling-out-fast/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-blockchain-game-pikamoon-raises-3-6m-final-ico-phase-selling-out-fast/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire &#160;]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 10:12:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=145603</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Dubai, United Arab Emirates, July 11th, 2023, Chainwire Pikamoon, an emerging Ethereum blockchain game, has raised $3.6 million in its ongoing ICO to bring more value to the Ethereum ecosystem and revolutionise the blockchain gaming space. Pikamoon would launch the world&#8217;s most immersive metaverse game and a first-of-its-kind earning model that allows players to withdraw [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-blockchain-game-pikamoon-raises-3-6m-final-ico-phase-selling-out-fast/">Ethereum Blockchain Game Pikamoon Raises $3.6m, Final ICO Phase Selling Out Fast</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Dubai, United Arab Emirates, July 11th, 2023, Chainwire</strong></p>
<p class="ql-align-justify"><a href="https://pikamoon.io/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Pikamoon,</a> an emerging Ethereum blockchain game, has raised $3.6 million in its ongoing ICO to bring more value to the Ethereum ecosystem and revolutionise the blockchain gaming space. Pikamoon would launch the world&rsquo;s most immersive metaverse game and a first-of-its-kind earning model that allows players to withdraw their in-game rewards directly to their wallet or bank account without the need for a third party.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Pikamoon focuses on becoming the most realistic metaverse game where players can get a 360-degree experience of the growing virtual space through unparalleled gameplay, stunning visuals, and innovative DeFi features. Drawing inspiration from legendary games like Fortnite, Pokemon, and FIFA, the Ethereum game has leaped forward and is prepared to blend NFTs, video gaming, and metaverse entertainment perfectly.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">The Pikamoon game is built on Unity, the world&rsquo;s most advanced game development technology, to create the stunning visuals and architecture needed to give players a truly immersive experience.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Additionally, Pikamoon is built across two blockchains: Ethereum and MultiversX (formerly Elrond). While Ethereum provides scalability, MultiversX complements it by providing efficiency and ensuring the game is environmentally friendly by reducing carbon emissions generated by transactions. This dual blockchain feature ensures that the Pikamoon ecosystem can cater to legions of gamers without any lag.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify"><img decoding="async" src="https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot_2023-07-11_at_113639_1689064806IU4w0Bn5ye.jpg"></p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Gaming enthusiasts and smart investors are convinced Pikamoon is the future of gaming, and this is evident in how fast phase one and phase two of the ICO sold out. In the first phase, one PIKA sold for $0.0002, which increased to $0.0004 in the second phase, and now in the third and last phase, one PIKA is selling for $0.0006 and selling out faster.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Notable partners of this Ethereum-based game include future-thinking Web3 brands such as Ethereum, Transak, Cryptonews.com, Kevuru Games, and MultiversX. This line-up of industry leaders further reinforces the credibility of the project, reaffirming the fact that the team is committed to building the best of the best gaming projects.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Pikamoon offers investors the opportunity to enter what is strategically seen as a huge market of the Metaverse and gaming on the Ethereum blockchain. A core feature of the PIKA token is its deflationary nature. Whenever a sell or transfer transaction occurs in the Pikamoon ecosystem, 0.5% of the tokens involved in the transaction are burned forever, translating into more profits for long-term investors.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">The much-talked-about presale, which is still on, uses Ethereum as its base currency, becoming the new favorite of the Ethereum community. This seamless integration with Ethereum not only simplifies the investment process for eager investors but also strengthens the overall Ethereum ecosystem.</p>
<p><iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/CqoH9AZiZVA?showinfo=0"></iframe></p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">
</p><h3 class="ql-align-justify">About Pikamoon</h3>
<p class="ql-align-justify"><a href="https://pikamoon.io/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Pikamoon</a> makes metaverse gameplay exciting and rewarding for players of all age groups. The Pikamoon&rsquo;s metaverse, the Pikaverse, offers players endless opportunities to explore, battle, trade, and earn a living within the game. It operates on two blockchains, Ethereum and MultiversX, ensuring smooth and glitch-free gameplay for every player. Similarly, Pikamoon&rsquo;s unique earning model allows players to easily monetize gameplay, solidifying its place as one of the best metaverse games on the market.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify"><strong>Find out more about Pikamoon (PIKA)</strong></p>
<ul>
<li class="ql-align-justify"><a href="https://pikamoon.io/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Website</a></li>
<li class="ql-align-justify"><a href="https://pikamoon.io/buy" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Where to purchase PIKA</a></li>
<li class="ql-align-justify"><a href="https://twitter.com/Pikamooncoin" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Twitter</a></li>
<li class="ql-align-justify"><a href="https://t.me/pikamoonofficial" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Telegram</a></li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Contact</strong></p>
<p>Founder<br>
Nick Evans<br>
Pikamoon<br>
info@pikamooncrypto.com</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-blockchain-game-pikamoon-raises-3-6m-final-ico-phase-selling-out-fast/">Ethereum Blockchain Game Pikamoon Raises $3.6m, Final ICO Phase Selling Out Fast</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-blockchain-game-pikamoon-raises-3-6m-final-ico-phase-selling-out-fast/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Netflix flips VFX play with AI-powered green screen</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/netflix-flips-vfx-play-with-ai-powered-green-screen/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/netflix-flips-vfx-play-with-ai-powered-green-screen/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 08:18:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/netflix-flips-vfx-play-with-ai-powered-green-screen/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>AltSignals&#8217; presale has raced to 50% sold out in stage 2 already. The ActualizeAI layer will tap into Artificial Intelligence to boost accuracy of trading signals. Meanwhile, Netflix is seeing the use of AI in green screen technology as a game-changer. Artificial Intelligence (AI) application across various industries and sectors continues to gather speed even [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/netflix-flips-vfx-play-with-ai-powered-green-screen/">Netflix flips VFX play with AI-powered green screen</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">AltSignals&rsquo; presale has raced to 50% sold out in stage 2 already.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The ActualizeAI layer will tap into Artificial Intelligence to boost accuracy of trading signals.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Meanwhile, Netflix is seeing the use of AI in green screen technology as a game-changer.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Artificial Intelligence (AI) application across various industries and sectors continues to gather speed even as regulators push for rules to streamline growth.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Google, Microsoft and Meta lead the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/ai/">AI</a> gold rush, but other companies like Nvidia and Netflix are quietly tapping into the technology to revolutionise their own industries. TechCrunch <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2023/07/10/netflixs-ai-assisted-green-screen-bathes-actors-in-eye-searing-magenta/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>reports</u></a> that in Netflix&rsquo;s case, the new AI-enabled technology could be a game-changer for VFX artists.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In the crypto space, one AI-powered application that could potentially disrupt the trading industry is <a href="https://token.altsignals.io/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>AltSignals</u></a>. The project is edging closer to the launch of its own AI-powered layer, and is currently seeing huge interest with its token sale already 50% sold out.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Netflix reveals AI-powered green screen</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The film and television industry have seen a fair share of revolutionary features from streaming giant Netflix. The company just added to that list with the debut of its Magenta Green Screen (MGS) &ndash; an application powered by artificial intelligence to change the visual effects space.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Researchers at the company say MGS makes VFX more realistic compared to legacy green screens. This is because an algorithm refined via machine learning gives colours near ground truth than models using simple algorithms.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Among the game-changing capabilities this new technology brings to the film and television industry is the ability for VFX artists to work with intricate details that have been extremely challenging. Observers say the use of generative AI provides for a major flip in filming, and Netflix is betting big on the possibilities that MGS could offer.</p>
<p dir="ltr">It&rsquo;s such capabilities that have so excited the trading community when it comes to AltSignals. And if big companies like Netflix see the future in AI-powered systems, investing in the <a href="https://token.altsignals.io/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>AltSignals presale</u></a> could offer an opportunity investors might want to take. Here&rsquo;s a bit more about this project.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What&rsquo;s AltSignals?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals is an online trading platform that offers access to trading signals for its user community. The signals cover most markets, including cryptocurrency, stocks, forex and CFDs and are currently powered by a proprietary algorithm called AltAlgo.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Traders leverage signals offered by the trading tool to enter or exit trades, with an average success rate of around 64%.</p>
<p dir="ltr">An improvement on this score has seen the AltSignals team look to artificial intelligence. The project is developing an AI-powered layer that will leverage machine learning and natural language processing to increase win rates to an average of 80%.</p>
<p dir="ltr">ActualizeAI is that new platform that will be powered by a native utility token ASI.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to details in their whitepaper, the project says tapping into AI will see ActualizeAI analyse data from virtually every corner of the market, including news, sentiment and price indicators. Optimising this data for best buy or sell prices is expected to add to the overall profitability of trades.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Strong AI-narrative sees AltSignals presale register huge interest&nbsp;</h2>
<p dir="ltr">AlltSignals&rsquo; presale began with the ASI token priced at $0.012. The price has since increased in two subsequent stages, with ASI available at $0.015 in the first stage before rising to $0.01875. The AI-related token will eventually rise to $0.02274 in the last stage of the presale, giving early buyers significant returns.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The trading community is largely optimistic of ActualiseAI&rsquo;s capabilities and features as shown by how fast the presale has progressed.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Investors are also see ASI as a potentially interesting token to hold, particularly around the broader benefits that could come with its utility, including ecosystem governance, staking and participating in tournaments.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What&rsquo;s the AltSignals price outlook? ASI to $1 in 2024?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Price predictions for AltSignals&rsquo; native token suggest a rally to new highs when it goes live on exchanges later in the quarter. Key short term price targets would be at $0.5 and $1. Exchange listings and ActualizeAI launch could possibly combine with positive market conditions to push ASI higher.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The reason for such a bullish view for AltSignals is that it&rsquo;s already a trusted platform. The number of users has quickly grown into one of largest trading communities and the numbers could explode when the presale ends.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Amid this outlook, investors might still want to focus on what happens with the AI-powered signals layer. Success could be a huge booster for ASI price.</p>
<p>Read more on AltSignals <a href="https://token.altsignals.io/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>here</u></a>.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/netflix-flips-vfx-play-with-ai-powered-green-screen/">Netflix flips VFX play with AI-powered green screen</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/netflix-flips-vfx-play-with-ai-powered-green-screen/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Presale of the new AI-powered Shiba Memu project attracting huge investor attention</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/presale-of-the-new-ai-powered-shiba-memu-project-attracting-huge-investor-attention/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 05:03:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOGE]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/presale-of-the-new-ai-powered-shiba-menu-project-attracting-huge-investor-attention/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Shiba Memu is a new Shiba-themed AI-powered cryptocurrency project. It is currently conducting a presale for its native token Shiba Memu (SHMU). One SHMU is currently going for $0.012250, however, it is only a matter of hours before that price increases to $0.012475. Shiba Memu, a new cryptocurrency project taking advantage of the meme coin [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/presale-of-the-new-ai-powered-shiba-memu-project-attracting-huge-investor-attention/">Presale of the new AI-powered Shiba Memu project attracting huge investor attention</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul class="decimal_type">
<li>Shiba Memu is a new Shiba-themed AI-powered cryptocurrency project.</li>
<li>It is currently conducting a presale for its native token Shiba Memu (SHMU).</li>
<li>One SHMU is currently going for $0.012250, however, it is only a matter of hours before that price increases to $0.012475.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news">Shiba Memu</a>, a new cryptocurrency project taking advantage of the meme coin and artificial intelligence hype has launched its token presale, which has attracted quite a huge number of investors within the first few days.</p>
<p>The Shiba Memu presale has already raised in excess of $294,961 and the price of SHMU tokens is expected to rise in the next 2 hours.</p>
<h2>What is Shiba Memu?</h2>
<p>Shiba Memu is a ground-breaking cryptocurrency token that combines <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/blockchain/">blockchain</a> and AI to produce an unstoppable, fully independent marketing powerhouse. It is a brand-new and ground-breaking meme token.</p>
<p>Shiba Memu will develop its own marketing strategies, write its own PR, and advertise itself in pertinent forums and social networks, in contrast to other meme tokens that depend heavily on human teams&rsquo; marketing efforts to gain traction.</p>
<p>Shiba Memu&rsquo;s native token SHMU is a distinctive and alluring investment because of its self-sufficient marketing abilities, which are supported by AI technology.</p>
<h2>How Shiba Memu works</h2>
<p>The Shiba Memu platform uses blockchain and AI technologies to generate content including press releases, social content, and marketing materials. The platform&rsquo;s AI continually analyzes data and then self-publishes the generated content across relevant forums and social platforms.</p>
<p>The Shiba Memu interactive AI dashboard responds to user inquiries and channels data from every newly developed insight into conversations it holds with real people across forums and social channels.</p>
<p>Besides blockchain technology, Shiba Memu uses AI-powered Natural Language Processing (NLP), Sentiment Analysis, Image and Video Recognition, Predictive Analytics, and Personalization.</p>
<p>Shiba Memu pegs its success on its self-sufficient marketing and promotion solutions that make it a low-maintenance crypto project. It is powered by a cross-chain token called SHMU token, which operates on both <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/what-is-ethereum/">Ethereum</a> and Binance Smart Chain (BSC).</p>
<p>85% (850 million) of the total SHMU tokens in circulation supply are currently up for grabs in the ongoing token presale that will see 350 million tokens sold on BSC and 500 million tokens sold on Ethereum.</p>
<h2>Why invest in Shiba Memu?</h2>
<p>The meme token has witnessed parabolic growth in recent years just like the artificial intelligence (AI) market that has seen a lot of hype since the launch of ChatGPT. According to Coinmarketcap, the meme token market grew by over $20 billion in two years between 2020 and 2022.</p>
<p>The success of meme tokens like <a href="https://coinjournal.net/shiba-inu/what-is-shiba-inu/">Shiba Inu (SHIB)</a> and <a href="https://coinjournal.net/dogecoin/what-is-dogecoin/">Dogecoin (DOGE)</a> has prompted the development of an array of meme tokens most of which hit the ground running. For instance, the PEPE and KEKE meme coins which were recently launched are now among the most trending cryptocurrencies after witnessing a huge surge in trading volumes.</p>
<p>Going by the recent trends, the demand for meme tokens is only expected to grow even further in the years ahead, offering a great market opportunity for Shiba Memu (SHMU) meme token. The self-sufficient, AI-powered marketing capabilities make SHMU a compelling, highly attractive opportunity for investors.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/presale-of-the-new-ai-powered-shiba-memu-project-attracting-huge-investor-attention/">Presale of the new AI-powered Shiba Memu project attracting huge investor attention</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin could hit $120,000 by the end of 2024: Standard Chartered</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-price-forecast-2024-standard-chartered-analyst/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wajeeh Khan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 20:52:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Standard Chartered]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=145549</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Standard Chartered analyst sees another 60% upside in Bitcoin this year. Geoff Kendrick explained his bullish view on BTC in a research note today. Bitcoin is already up a whopping 85% since the start of the year 2023. The massive rally in Bitcoin since the start of this year is just a drop in the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-price-forecast-2024-standard-chartered-analyst/">Bitcoin could hit $120,000 by the end of 2024: Standard Chartered</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Standard Chartered analyst sees another 60% upside in Bitcoin this year.</li>
<li>Geoff Kendrick explained his bullish view on BTC in a research note today.</li>
<li>Bitcoin is already up a whopping 85% since the start of the year 2023.</li>
</ul>
<p>The massive rally in <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> since the start of this year is just a drop in the bucket compared to where it&rsquo;s headed, as per a Standard Chartered analyst.</p>
<h2>BTC could climb another 60% this year</h2>
<p>On Monday, Geoff Kendrick said the world&rsquo;s largest cryptocurrency could climb further to $50,000 by the end of 2023 which suggests another 60% upside from here.</p>
<p>The analyst is convinced that a continued increase in the price of BTC will make it rewarding for miners to stock huge amounts of it. Reduced net supply, in return, will help the cryptocurrency reach for the skies, he added.</p>
<blockquote><p>If BTC rises [as] we expect by end-2023, share of newly mined being sold should fall to 20%-30%. That&rsquo;s a net annual reduction in selling of BTC 250,000.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Bitcoin supply is set to halve next year</h2>
<p>Note that the total supply of Bitcoin is scheduled to halve in April or May of 2024.</p>
<p>The Standard Chartered analyst sees several other factors helping unlock significant upside in BTC next year. One of them is the recent <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-05-02/bitcoin-climbs-as-us-bank-failure-bolsters-crypto-narrative" target="_blank" rel="noopener">banking crisis</a>. Earlier this year, he had forecast Bitcoin at $100,000 by the end of 2024. In a note today, though, Kendrick said:</p>
<blockquote><p>We now think this estimate is too conservative, and we, therefore, see a 20% upside to our end-2024 target.</p></blockquote>
<p>That essentially means Bitcoin could hit $120,000 next year. The cryptocurrency is expected to benefit if the Securities and Exchange Commission greenlights a Spot Bitcoin ETF that many asset managers, including <a href="https://decrypt.co/147177/blackrock-spot-bitcoin-etf-filing-sec-coinbase-surveillance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BlackRock</a>, have recently filed for.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-price-forecast-2024-standard-chartered-analyst/">Bitcoin could hit $120,000 by the end of 2024: Standard Chartered</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Former SEC Chair says Bitcoin ETF approval &#8216;hard to resist&#8217;</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/former-sec-chair-says-bitcoin-etf-approval-hard-to-resist/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/former-sec-chair-says-bitcoin-etf-approval-hard-to-resist/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 20:25:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Policy and Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US regulation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/former-sec-chair-says-bitcoin-etf-approval-hard-to-resist/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Jay Clayton shared his opinion during an interview with CNBC on Monday. The former SEC chair says if applicants demonstrate efficacy and have surveillance, it would be hard for the SEC to deny a spot Bitcoin ETF. BlackRock, Fidelity and others have market surveillance agreements with Coinbase. The US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/former-sec-chair-says-bitcoin-etf-approval-hard-to-resist/">Former SEC Chair says Bitcoin ETF approval &#8216;hard to resist&#8217;</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Jay Clayton shared his opinion during an interview with CNBC on Monday.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The former SEC chair says if applicants demonstrate efficacy and have surveillance, it would be hard for the SEC to deny a spot Bitcoin ETF.</li>
<li dir="ltr">BlackRock, Fidelity and others have market surveillance agreements with Coinbase.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">The US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has so far denied all the applications for a spot <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/bitcoin-etf/">Bitcoin ETF</a> to come before it.</p>
<p dir="ltr">But now might be the time the regulator gives a seal of approval to the product, former SEC Chair Jay Clayton said on Monday.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>If they&rsquo;re right that the spot market has similar efficacy to the futures market, it would be hard to resist approving a bitcoin ETF</em>,&rdquo; Clayton <a href="https://twitter.com/SquawkCNBC/status/1678381857367289856" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">told</a> CNBC&rsquo;s Squawk Box.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">"I was very skeptical with trading in the <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#bitcoin</a> market when I was SEC Chair," says Jay Clayton. "But if you can demonstrate that the spot market has similar efficacy to the futures market, it would be hard to resist approving a <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#bitcoin</a> ETF." <a href="https://t.co/mig05ZUwIL">pic.twitter.com/mig05ZUwIL</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Squawk Box (@SquawkCNBC) <a href="https://twitter.com/SquawkCNBC/status/1678381857367289856?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 10, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">SEC&rsquo;s approval of futures ETFs</h2>
<p dir="ltr">This is the argument that applicants have put forth, particularly with BlackRock, Fidelity and others taking steps to comply with requirements previously cited as reasons for SEC&rsquo;s disapproval.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Notably, proposals by the Cboe and Nasdaq have included market surveillance agreements &ndash; the so-called surveillance sharing agreement (SSA) with major cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Noting this, and the fact that the SEC has approved futures-based ETFs on this basis, Clayton added:</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>When the SEC approved a futures-based ETF, they said &lsquo;let&rsquo;s look at the futures market, we see the surveillance, we see the protections in that market for the investor, that are sufficient. We don&rsquo;t see them in the spot market, so we&rsquo;re going to make that distinction&rsquo;. I think what the institutions are arguing is that those distinctions have gone away and that the spot product is now less drag, more efficient for the investor</em>.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">With no delta in regulation and efficacy, the SEC will have to approve a first spot Bitcoin ETF for the US market. As highlighted earlier, Clayton believes it would be &ldquo;hard&rdquo; for SEC to &ldquo;resist&rdquo; a spot ETF any further if applicants prove efficacy.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As CoinJournal <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/secs-spot-bitcoin-etf-approval-fairly-high-bernstein/">reported</a> last week, analysts at $650 billion asset manager Bernstein noted that chances of a spot Bitcoin ETF approval are &ldquo;fairly high.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The crypto market has been largely optimistic of an approval ever since BlackRock filed its proposal in mid-June. The optimism was reflected in the price of Bitcoin rallying after the news to reach a new year-to-date high above $31k last month.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/former-sec-chair-says-bitcoin-etf-approval-hard-to-resist/">Former SEC Chair says Bitcoin ETF approval &#8216;hard to resist&#8217;</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/former-sec-chair-says-bitcoin-etf-approval-hard-to-resist/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Raoul Pal shares massive price prediction for Solana</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/raoul-pal-shares-massive-price-prediction-for-solana/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/raoul-pal-shares-massive-price-prediction-for-solana/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 18:54:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/raoul-pal-shares-massive-price-prediction-for-solana/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Raoul Pal, CEO of Real Vision is super bullish on Solana (SOL). According to Pal, SOL could rally 20x from current levels if it mirrors Ethereum&#8217;s 47x move from its 2018 low. He also says Bitcoin price could triple from its all-time high level amid a supply crunch in 2023. Raoul Pal, the founder &#38; [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/raoul-pal-shares-massive-price-prediction-for-solana/">Raoul Pal shares massive price prediction for Solana</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Raoul Pal, CEO of Real Vision is super bullish on Solana (SOL).</li>
<li dir="ltr">According to Pal, SOL could rally 20x from current levels if it mirrors Ethereum&rsquo;s 47x move from its 2018 low.</li>
<li dir="ltr">He also says Bitcoin price could triple from its all-time high level amid a supply crunch in 2023.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Raoul Pal, the founder &amp; CEO of Real Vision suggests&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/solana/"><u>Solana (SOL)</u></a> could embark on a massive price move. If the &ldquo;dream scenario&rdquo; for the world&rsquo;s 10th&nbsp;largest cryptocurrency by market cap occurs, SOL could outperform both&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/"><u>Bitcoin (BTC)</u></a> and Ethereum (ETH).</p>
<p dir="ltr">Pal shared his massively bullish outlook for Solana during a recent&nbsp;<a href="https://youtu.be/fINxauWFYtA" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>interview</u></a> in which he shared &nbsp;views on varied topics. These &nbsp;include AI and its impact on jobs, BlackRock&rsquo;s ETF filing and CEO Larry Fink&rsquo;s remarks about BTC.</p>
<p dir="ltr">He also aired his thoughts on the Ethereum/Bitcoin flippening debate, central bank digital currencies (CBCDs), global economy and government money printing before briefly offering his&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/solana/price-prediction/"><u>price prediction Solana</u></a>. The macro guru also shared predictions for Bitcoin and Ethereum.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Solana price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr">On what he thought of the price performance of BTC, ETH and SOL in the next bull cycle, Pal shared a highly bullish projection for Ethereum&rsquo;s &ldquo;competitor.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Currently, Solana trades around $21, about 1.4% down in the past 24 hours.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, the cryptocurrency is more than 10% in the green over the past seven days and 43% in the past 30 days. While it&rsquo;s also down 43% from its value a year ago, Pal noted that the bottom might have come when prices fell to around $9 in December 2022.</p>
<p dir="ltr">With this outlook, Pal suggests SOL could do what ETH achieved after bottoming in 2018 &ndash; roaring to its all-time high above $4,800 during the last bull market. The macro guru says that if Solana takes on this projection, the potential gains could be staggering.</p>
<p dir="ltr">He compared the 47x that ETH saw after the 2018 low to what Solana could do. He opined:</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>Look&hellip; there&rsquo;s a possibility &ndash; a dream scenario &ndash; that Solana does what ETH did from the 2018 low which was a 47x. The Solana low was nine bucks, so you could do the maths [and] the numbers are potentially very interesting</em>.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">While Solana&rsquo;s price might not do the 47x or so that Ethereum price managed since its bottom in 2018, Pal predicts a &ldquo;20 something x&rdquo; move. According to him, this is a reasonable outlook for a protocol that&rsquo;s battle-tested and is seeing a huge spike in network and ecosystem activity.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Should Pal&rsquo;s bullish outlook for SOL price hold, it would mean an eventual burst to prices above $400 for the cryptocurrency. In the last bull market, Solana rose to the all-time high at $260.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitcoin and Ethereum price predictions</h2>
<p dir="ltr">For BTC and ETH, Pal agreed with projections of a 3x and 5x respectively &ndash; suggesting Bitcoin could more than triple its value during the next bull cycle. However, that is from the all-time highs that was $69,000 in November 2021.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Trippling from that ATH would mean a 6x from current prices, he opined. But that would depend on severa factors that could dictate market direction.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>It&rsquo;s very difficult to predict where it actually goes, but what we can say is [that] it&rsquo;s reasonable that Bitcoin from all-time highs doubles or triples. That&rsquo;s not asking a lot. That will be the worst bull market in Bitcoin&rsquo;s history.</em>&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to him, a potential supply crunch in 2023 is what could squeeze Bitcoin to a new all-time high.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/raoul-pal-shares-massive-price-prediction-for-solana/">Raoul Pal shares massive price prediction for Solana</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/raoul-pal-shares-massive-price-prediction-for-solana/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is the Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC) stock a good buy now?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/is-the-grayscale-bitcoin-trust-gbtc-stock-a-good-buy-now/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/is-the-grayscale-bitcoin-trust-gbtc-stock-a-good-buy-now/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 16:08:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/is-the-grayscale-bitcoin-trust-gbtc-stock-a-good-buy-now/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Grayscale Bitcoin Trust has jumped by over 168% from December lows. The trust is hoping for Bitcoin to have a bullish breakout above the YTD high. The Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC) stock price has moved sideways in the past few days as Bitcoin remained stuck at $30,000. GBTC was trading at $20, the highest [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/is-the-grayscale-bitcoin-trust-gbtc-stock-a-good-buy-now/">Is the Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC) stock a good buy now?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The Grayscale Bitcoin Trust has jumped by over 168% from December lows.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The trust is hoping for Bitcoin to have a bullish breakout above the YTD high.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">The Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC) stock price has moved sideways in the past few days as Bitcoin remained stuck at $30,000. GBTC was trading at $20, the highest level since June last year. It has jumped by more than 168% from the lowest level in December.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitcoin consolidation continues</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The Grayscale Bitcoin Trust is the biggest fund in the cryptocurrency industry. It has over $18.9 billion of assets under management (AUM). Over the years, the fund has jumped by more than 19,200% since its inception.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Grayscale Bitcoin Trust stores its assets in an offline cold wallet with Coinbase Custody Trust. Most companies that have filed for Bitcoin ETFs have also selected&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/coinbase/"><u>Coinbase</u></a> as the custodian of the funds.</p>
<p dir="ltr">GBTC creators have filed to convert the GBTC fund into an exchange-traded fund (ETF). Indeed, the company has sued the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) in a case that could change the industry.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">A ruling in favor of the company will open the possibility for other companies like Blackrock and Invesco to launch their spot ETFs.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">GBTC is widely known for its massive discount to its assets, The market price per share stands at $19.81 compared to its holdings per share of $22. This discount has been narrowing in the past few weeks.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The next key important catalyst for the GBTC stock price will be&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/"><u>Bitcoin</u></a>&rsquo;s price action. Bitcoin has remained stuck slightly above the key support level at $30,000. Therefore, if Bitcoin rebounds, there is a likelihood that the Grayscale Bitcoin Trust will continue rising as well.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">GBTC stock price forecast</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/10/1689005283450-3bc36ee2-b4f5-4838-bec2-08be5178c44d.png" style="width: 579px;height: 281.78px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="579" height="281.78"></p>
<p dir="ltr">The daily chart shows that the GBTC share price has been in a strong bullish trend in the past few days. It has managed to move above the important resistance point at $18.53, the highest level on April 10th.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Grayscale Bitcoin Trust stock price has moved above the 50-day and 100-day exponential moving averages (EMA). Further, the Relative Strength Index (RSI) has moved slightly below the overbought level to 69. GBTC&rsquo;s volume has moved downwards.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, there is a likelihood that the GBTC price will continue rising as buyers target the next key resistance level at $25. A drop below the support at $18.53 will invalidate the bullish view.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/is-the-grayscale-bitcoin-trust-gbtc-stock-a-good-buy-now/">Is the Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC) stock a good buy now?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/is-the-grayscale-bitcoin-trust-gbtc-stock-a-good-buy-now/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
