<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 21:16:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Venmo to enable crypto transfers for its customers in May</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/venmo-to-enable-crypto-transfers-for-its-customers-in-may/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/venmo-to-enable-crypto-transfers-for-its-customers-in-may/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 21:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto payments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/venmo-to-enable-crypto-transfers-for-its-customers-in-may/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Venmo will roll out a new crypto transfer feature in May, allowing customers to send crypto to other Venmo accounts. Customers will also be able to buy tokens and send them to PayPal, external wallets and exchanges. Users will also be able to use a unique wallet address QR code to receive crypto from other [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/venmo-to-enable-crypto-transfers-for-its-customers-in-may/">Venmo to enable crypto transfers for its customers in May</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Venmo will roll out a new crypto transfer feature in May, allowing customers to send crypto to other Venmo accounts.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Customers will also be able to buy tokens and send them to PayPal, external wallets and exchanges.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Users will also be able to use a unique wallet address QR code to receive crypto from other people.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Mobile payments app Venmo has announced that its customers will from May 2023 be able to buy crypto using their account and transfer these to family and friends on Venmo.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Venmo, whose parent company is <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/paypal/">PayPal</a>, revealed this as it outlined a new feature on Friday.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Making it easy for customers to move crypto</h2>
<p dir="ltr">According to a <a href="https://newsroom.paypal-corp.com/2023-04-28-Introducing-Crypto-Transfers-for-Venmo-Customers" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">press release</a> Venmo published on 28 April, the new functionality is part of the company&rsquo;s effort to make it easier for customers to manage and move crypto.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Dropping in to announce a new feature of ours: crypto transfers&#9889;Get started now. <a href="https://t.co/R9QtUENfae">https://t.co/R9QtUENfae</a> <a href="https://t.co/UoeEAWVhlz">pic.twitter.com/UoeEAWVhlz</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Venmo (@Venmo) <a href="https://twitter.com/Venmo/status/1652000306811613196?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">April 28, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">Other than being able to send crypto to other Venmo users, customers will also be able to send cryptocurrencies to PayPal accounts, external wallets and exchanges within the digital asset ecosystem. Any Venmo customer can navigate to the Receive page to access a unique digital asset address QR code. Customers can share this QR code with others when looking to receive funds.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to details shared in the news release, the crypto transfers feature will be available to Venmo users beginning May 2023.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Venmo introduced crypto purchases for its customers in April 2021, and is a popular mobile app for those looking to <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/buy/venmo/">buy Bitcoin</a>. The platform added support for crypto price alerts in November 2021, allowing for push notifications for price alerts of Bitcoin, Ethereum, Bitcoin Cash and Litecoin.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/venmo-to-enable-crypto-transfers-for-its-customers-in-may/">Venmo to enable crypto transfers for its customers in May</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/venmo-to-enable-crypto-transfers-for-its-customers-in-may/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto price prediction: OMG Network, Serum, Injective Protocol</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-omg-network-serum-injective-protocol/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-omg-network-serum-injective-protocol/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 19:57:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OMG Network News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-omg-network-serum-injective-protocol/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Market intelligence platform Santiment says wide price performance ranges have left crypto assets split between extremely overbought and underbought categories.&#160; The price outlook for OMG Network (OMG), Serum (SRM) and Vidt DAO (VIDT) suggests they are most underbought. Meanwhile, Render (RNDR), Injective Protocol (INJ) and Bella Protocol (BEL) are extremely overbought. Cryptocurrency prices have been [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-omg-network-serum-injective-protocol/">Crypto price prediction: OMG Network, Serum, Injective Protocol</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Market intelligence platform Santiment says wide price performance ranges have left crypto assets split between extremely overbought and underbought categories.&nbsp;</li>
<li dir="ltr">The price outlook for OMG Network (OMG), Serum (SRM) and Vidt DAO (VIDT) suggests they are most underbought.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Meanwhile, Render (RNDR), Injective Protocol (INJ) and Bella Protocol (BEL) are extremely overbought.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/price/">Cryptocurrency prices</a> have been quite volatile in April, with a number of coins seeing massive gains before toppling to pre-rally levels amid extensive selling. But the outlook of some tokens suggests they are trending in extremely overbought territory, while a few remain greatly underbought.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Render (RNDR), Injective Protocol (INJ) and Bella Protocol (BEL) are all heavily overbought. <a href="https://coinjournal.net/omg-network/">OMG Network (OMG)</a>, <a href="https://coinjournal.net/serum/">Serum (SRM)</a> and Vidt DAO (VIDT) fall in the latter category.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Crypto price predictions for OMG, SRM and INJ</h2>
<p dir="ltr">While Bitcoin (BTC) price is back above $29,000 on Friday and is trending with positive sentiment as bulls target a good start to the historically slow May, analysts say ending April above the key support of $28,200 is the critical move.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Meanwhile, trading patterns for some altcoins suggest this might be a good buying moment &ndash; with market intelligence platform Santiment highlighting <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/omg/">OMG</a>, SRM and VIDT &nbsp;as some of the most underbought tokens.</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, with the global crypto market cap shrinking to $1.25 trillion from recent highs, some altcoins that rallied hard are massively overbought. These tokens, including RNDR, INJ, and BEL could be quite risky, Santiment explained on Friday.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>Prices have been more scattered and non-correlated to one another here in April than in previous months. And our MVRV model confirms average trading returns appear as historically good times to buy for some ($OMG, $SRM, $VIDT), and quite risky for others ($BEL, $INJ, $RNDR)</em>.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">&#128202; Prices have been more scattered and non-correlated to one another here in April than in previous months. And our MVRV model confirms average trading returns appear as historically good times to buy for some ( <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24OMG&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$OMG</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24SRM&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$SRM</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24VIDT&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$VIDT</a>), and quite risky for others ( <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24BEL&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$BEL</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24INJ&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$INJ</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24RNDR&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$RNDR</a>). <a href="https://t.co/g6z1IAfySz">pic.twitter.com/g6z1IAfySz</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Santiment (@santimentfeed) <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1652021186719797248?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">April 28, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">The MVRV (market-value-to-realized-value) model gives the ratio of a token&rsquo;s market capitalization against its realized capitalization.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As a comparison of the two metrics, that is market cap and realized cap, the MVRV ratio is often used to highlight the price of an asset versus its deemed fair value. Being above or below this &ldquo;fair value&rdquo; price helps traders assess the potential profitability of the token.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-omg-network-serum-injective-protocol/">Crypto price prediction: OMG Network, Serum, Injective Protocol</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-omg-network-serum-injective-protocol/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitfarms stock still has another 80% upside from here, analyst says</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitfarms-stock-price-forecast-h-c-wainwright/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wajeeh Khan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 19:13:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=138059</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>H.C. Wainwright analyst sees upside in Bitfarms to $2.0 a share. He explained his constructive view in a research note on Friday. Bitfarms stock has already nearly tripled since the start of 2023. Shares of Bitfarms Ltd have already nearly tripled since the start of the year but an H.C. Wainwright analyst is convinced that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitfarms-stock-price-forecast-h-c-wainwright/">Bitfarms stock still has another 80% upside from here, analyst says</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>H.C. Wainwright analyst sees upside in Bitfarms to $2.0 a share.</li>
<li>He explained his constructive view in a research note on Friday.</li>
<li>Bitfarms stock has already nearly tripled since the start of 2023.</li>
</ul>
<p>Shares of Bitfarms Ltd have already nearly tripled since the start of the year but an H.C. Wainwright analyst is convinced that rally is far from over just yet.</p>
<h2>Bitfarms stock could climb to $2.0</h2>
<p>On Friday, Kevin Dede reiterated his &ldquo;buy&rdquo; rating on the bitcoin miner and said its shares could climb to $2.0 &ndash; up another 80% from here.</p>
<p>The bullish call on Bitfarms stock arrives only hours after the company expanded operations in <a href="https://decrypt.co/138268/bitcoin-miner-bitfarms-hits-new-hashrate-high-argentine-expansion" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Argentina</a> that increased its fleet hash to 5 EH/s.</p>
<p>Estimates Dede has for 2023 are based on a hash rate of about 5.7 EH/s &ndash; a level he&rsquo;s confident the miner will hit in its September quarter.</p>
<blockquote><p>This fleet expansion also came without further shareholder dilution &ndash; an added prize not universally shared across the spectrum of publicly traded bitcoin miners.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Bitfarms Ltd is generating cash</h2>
<p>The H.C. Wainwright analyst remains constructive on Bitfarms Ltd also because it did not slip into negative EBITDA even in the <a href="https://bitfarms.com/media/news/detail/182/bitfarms-reports-fourth-quarter-and-full-year-2022-results" target="_blank" rel="noopener">fourth quarter</a> when thing went haywire for the crypto space at large.</p>
<p>Other reasons cited for the constructive view on Bitfarms stock include its gross mining margin that declined sharply (year-over-year) in 2022 but still stood at a healthy 33% nonetheless. Dede said in his <a href="https://hcwco.bluematrix.com/sellside/EmailDocViewer?encrypt=79331a69-55b5-4219-b70c-27c84b787bb9&amp;mime=pdf&amp;co=Hcwco&amp;id=jayson.derrick@investoogroup.com&amp;source=mail" target="_blank" rel="noopener">research note</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>We understand potential upside in Argentina. With greater financial flexibility via stronger balance sheet, Bitfarms has options to consider additional business development opportunities.</p></blockquote>
<p>Expansion in Quebec, Paraguay, and Washington State will help the share price as well, he concluded.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitfarms-stock-price-forecast-h-c-wainwright/">Bitfarms stock still has another 80% upside from here, analyst says</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mastercard partners Solana and Polygon on new crypto standards system</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/mastercard-partners-solana-and-polygon-on-new-crypto-standards-system/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/mastercard-partners-solana-and-polygon-on-new-crypto-standards-system/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 18:29:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Avalanche News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/mastercard-partners-solana-and-polygon-on-new-crypto-standards-system/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Mastercard is looking to help bring defined standards to the blockchain and Web3 ecosystems. The company is partnering blockchain platforms Polygon, Solana, Aptos Labs, and Ava Labs, on the common standards program it calls Mastercard Crypto Credential. Mastercard will also work with wallet providers Uphold, Bit2Me, Lirium, and Mercado Bitcoin on the program. Mastercard is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/mastercard-partners-solana-and-polygon-on-new-crypto-standards-system/">Mastercard partners Solana and Polygon on new crypto standards system</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Mastercard is looking to help bring defined standards to the blockchain and Web3 ecosystems.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The company is partnering blockchain platforms Polygon, Solana, Aptos Labs, and Ava Labs, on the common standards program it calls Mastercard Crypto Credential.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Mastercard will also work with wallet providers Uphold, Bit2Me, Lirium, and Mercado Bitcoin on the program.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Mastercard is partnering with several blockchain platforms in a bid to develop a new set of crypto standards aimed to boost the industry&rsquo;s overall trust score.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In an<a href="https://www.mastercard.com/news/perspectives/2023/bringing-more-trust-to-blockchain-transactions/">&nbsp;<u>announcement</u></a> at Consensus 2023 on Friday, the payments firms said it was teaming up with <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/polygon/">Polygon</a>, Aptos Labs, Solana Foundation and Ava Labs, to develop the Crypto Credential.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">At <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Consensus23?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Consensus23</a>, we announced how we are instilling trust in the blockchain ecosystem through Mastercard Crypto Credential. With crypto wallet providers <a href="https://twitter.com/Bit2Me_Global?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@Bit2Me_Global</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/LiriumAG?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@LiriumAG</a> , <a href="https://twitter.com/MercadoBitcoin?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@MercadoBitcoin</a>  and <a href="https://twitter.com/UpholdInc?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@UpholdInc</a>  and public blockchain network organizations <a href="https://twitter.com/AptosLabs?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@AptosLabs</a>,&hellip; <a href="https://t.co/P33mtDVAas">pic.twitter.com/P33mtDVAas</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Mastercard News (@MastercardNews) <a href="https://twitter.com/MastercardNews/status/1652003395052380160?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">April 28, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">According to the company, the Mastercard Crypto Credential is an effort targeted at incorporating the best of common standards into the crypto infrastructure and broader space providers to help instill trust in crypto from consumers, businesses and governments.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Raj Dhamodharan, the head of crypto at Mastercard noted in a statement that building trust is a crucial step for the blockchain ecosystem as it looks towards mainstream adoption. Crypto Credential, he noted, is one way of pushing for &ldquo;<em>trusted, compliant, and verifiable</em>&rdquo; blockchain interactions.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>With Mastercard Crypto Credential, we can help ensure that those interested in interacting across Web3 environments are meeting defined standards for the types of activities they&rsquo;d like to pursue. Mastercard Crypto Credential will not only define verification standards and levels, but also provide necessary enabling technology to help bring more use cases to life</em>&rdquo; he added.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Standards for verification in NFTs</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The common standards being advocated for will also help with instilling trust in <a href="https://coinjournal.net/learn/what-are-nfts-and-how-do-they-work/">NFTs</a>, with the partners collaborating towards enhancing verification in NFTs. Mastercard will also work with blockchain firms around verification in ticketing and other payments solutions.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Solana, Polygon, Aptos Labs and Ava Labs are set to aid in having the new crypto standards available to and applied by developers within their ecosystems.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Other than that, crypto wallet providers Lirium, Uphold, Mercado Bitcoin and Bit2Me will look to tap into the standards for their cross border transfers. The platforms will initially focus on crypto payments and remittances within the United States, Latin America and the Caribbean corridors.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/mastercard-partners-solana-and-polygon-on-new-crypto-standards-system/">Mastercard partners Solana and Polygon on new crypto standards system</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/mastercard-partners-solana-and-polygon-on-new-crypto-standards-system/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Newscrypto Coin price prediction: NWC looking at potential 100% rally</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/newscrypto-coin-price-prediction-nwc-looking-at-potential-100-rally/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/newscrypto-coin-price-prediction-nwc-looking-at-potential-100-rally/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 17:06:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/newscrypto-coin-price-prediction-nwc-looking-at-potential-100-rally/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Newscrypto Coin (NWC) price has seen a slight decline today, trading near $0.12 after giving up gains from highs of $0.18 &#160;on 14 April 2023. Crypto analyst says the token could break higher and rally 100% or more over coming months. NWC reached its all-time high of $2.22 in May 2021. Newscrypto Coin (NWC) traded [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/newscrypto-coin-price-prediction-nwc-looking-at-potential-100-rally/">Newscrypto Coin price prediction: NWC looking at potential 100% rally</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Newscrypto Coin (NWC) price has seen a slight decline today, trading near $0.12 after giving up gains from highs of $0.18 &nbsp;on 14 April 2023.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Crypto analyst says the token could break higher and rally 100% or more over coming months.</li>
<li dir="ltr">NWC reached its all-time high of $2.22 in May 2021.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Newscrypto Coin (NWC) traded at around $0.12 on Friday morning, with a 24-hour price return of about -2% at the time of writing.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The daily trading volume was around $1.4 million in 24 hours, representing an increase of about 8% as selling pressure pushed the price of the altcoin down. The Newscrypto Coin, whose market cap currently stands at $18.5 million, traded at lows of $0.05 in early April.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Newscrypto Coin price prediction: analysts highlights NWC breakout</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Newscrypto Coin (NWC), which reached its highest price of $2.22 on 3 May, 2021, had been one of the best performers in the last month as it rose to $0.18 on 14 April 2023.</p>
<p dir="ltr">But while the token&rsquo;s value remains over 128% up in the past month, the latest dip in <a href="https://coinjournal.net/price/">prices</a> across the markets has seen it pare some of the gains over the past week to just +8%. NWC price is down nearly 28% in the past two weeks.</p>
<p dir="ltr">So what&rsquo;s the Newscrypto Coin price prediction over the short term?</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to popular crypto analyst Rekt Capital, NWC tokens can trade higher if a breakout happens above a downtrending channel that is potentially forming on the monthly chart.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>First signs of a Downtrending Channel forming</em>,&rdquo; he tweeted. &ldquo;<em>A breakout could see NWC rally +100% to major resistance (red) over time</em>.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The potential catalyst for a new uptrend for Newscrypto Coin is the fact that a significant amount of the total supply of NWC tokens will remain locked until 2028.</p>
<p dir="ltr">At current prices, Newscrypto Coin price is over 776% up since its all-time lows of $0.01 reached in mid-November 2019. Bulls could add to these gains if a breakout pushes the price to $0.35 as per Rekt Capital&rsquo;s prediction.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24NWC&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$NWC</a> / USDT &ndash; <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/NWC?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#NWC</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/NewsCrypto?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#NewsCrypto</a></p>
<p>First signs of a Downtrending Channel forming</p>
<p>A breakout could see NWC rally +100% to major resistance (red) over time</p>
<p>NWC tokens are locked in the team wallet until 2028 which may act as a catalyst for an eventual uptrend<a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/BTC?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#BTC</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Crypto?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Crypto</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Bitcoin</a> <a href="https://t.co/3V6j2ptF2G">pic.twitter.com/3V6j2ptF2G</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Rekt Capital (@rektcapital) <a href="https://twitter.com/rektcapital/status/1651943948892381184?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">April 28, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">The analyst suggests in the above chart that the primary support level for NWC/USD could be near $0.05.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/newscrypto-coin-price-prediction-nwc-looking-at-potential-100-rally/">Newscrypto Coin price prediction: NWC looking at potential 100% rally</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/newscrypto-coin-price-prediction-nwc-looking-at-potential-100-rally/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ojamu Announces “Alphie” Launch &#8211; its latest AI-driven Smart Tool for the Blockchain Industry integrated with ChatGPT</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/ojamu-announces-alphie-launch-its-latest-ai-driven-smart-tool-for-the-blockchain-industry-integrated-with-chatgpt/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/ojamu-announces-alphie-launch-its-latest-ai-driven-smart-tool-for-the-blockchain-industry-integrated-with-chatgpt/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire &#160;]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 16:51:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=138053</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Singapore, Singapore, April 28th, 2023, Chainwire &#8220;Alphie&#8221; bot currently specializes in the hot ZK &#38; Optimistic Rollup sectors, with more to come Ojamu, the AI &#38; Blockchain-powered intelligence platform geared towards providing insights into the blockchain &#38; Web3 economy, announced its latest product today, with the launch of its ChatGPT integrated bot &#8220;Alphie&#8221;, available in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ojamu-announces-alphie-launch-its-latest-ai-driven-smart-tool-for-the-blockchain-industry-integrated-with-chatgpt/">Ojamu Announces “Alphie” Launch &#8211; its latest AI-driven Smart Tool for the Blockchain Industry integrated with ChatGPT</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Singapore, Singapore, April 28th, 2023, Chainwire</strong></p>
<p class="ql-align-center">&ldquo;Alphie&rdquo; bot currently specializes in the hot ZK &amp; Optimistic Rollup sectors, with more to come</p>
<p><a href="https://www.ojamuai.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Ojamu</a>, the AI &amp; Blockchain-powered intelligence platform geared towards providing insights into the blockchain &amp; Web3 economy, announced its latest product today, with the launch of its ChatGPT integrated bot &ldquo;<a href="http://chat.ojamuai.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Alphie</a>&rdquo;, available in both mobile and desktop versions.</p>
<p>Alphie is an advanced, AI-driven &lsquo;Alpha Finder&rsquo;, providing valuable insights and in-depth analysis in the most cutting-edge areas of the cryptocurrency industry.</p>
<blockquote><p>Ojamu CEO and Founder Hal Bame commented, &ldquo;The bot&rsquo;s name comes from &lsquo;Alpha&rsquo;, which in many industries is seen as &lsquo;hard-to-find&rsquo; or essential information. Alphie initially focuses on the incredibly popular and fast-moving ZK/Optimistic Rollup space, with leading chains such as Polygon &amp; Arbitrum incredibly acitve, helping users understand complex concepts and terminologies that might otherwise be difficult to grasp and find necessary information on, as well as associated projects.&rdquo;</p></blockquote>
<p><img decoding="async" src="https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/111png_1682697024JUfgnKl2YX.jpg"></p>
<p>Alphie&rsquo;s capability goes beyond &lsquo;lookups&rsquo;. For example, it can break down whitepapers into more digestible information, in order to accelerate users&rsquo; research and help them to make better-informed decisions, find specifics on various technologies and understand how those projects differentiate from others.</p>
<p>Key groups within the crypto/blockchain ecosystem will benefit from Alphie:</p>
<p>&#9679;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<strong><u>Traders</u></strong> gain insights on project fundamentals, technology, and team credentials to make informed decisions and improve trading outcomes.</p>
<p>&#9679;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<strong><u>Investors</u></strong> can make better investment choices based on solid evaluation of projects&rsquo; long-term potential by analyzing tokenomics, use cases, and market trends.</p>
<p>&#9679;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<strong><u>Developers</u></strong> can easily assess complex emerging technologies like ZK/Optimistic Rollup scaling solutions to decide which is best suited to integrate into their projects.</p>
<p>&#9679;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<strong><u>Crypto enthusiasts</u></strong> can expand their knowledge of the ZK/Optimistic Rollup space and stay up-to-date with the latest trends and developments thanks to Alphie&rsquo;s ability to simply explain complex concepts.</p>
<p>Alphie leverages ChatGPT AI technology and fine-tuning AI smart toolsets, as well as Ojamu&rsquo;s own proprietary AI and data methodology, in order to provide as complete and up-to-date information as possible.</p>
<p>Alphie demystifies ZK/Optimistic Rollups and other advanced blockchain technologies, making it easier for users to comprehend their advantages, limitations, and potential use cases. The bot can provide a comprehensive understanding of these two technologies, their underlying principles, benefits, and drawbacks. It can explain how these Layer 2 scaling solutions work, how they differ from each other, and how they can help address the transaction throughput challenges faced by various blockchain networks. Alphie can also delve into the potential risks and trade-offs associated with implementing these technologies, such as security and data availability concerns.</p>
<p>Ojamu&rsquo;s future product plans include expanding Alphie&rsquo;s coverage to encompass all crypto categories and provide more advanced research and insights based on further technical and fundamental analysis. GPT-4 research and integration are already underway for enhanced AI performance and datasets, as well as improved natural language understanding capabilities, ensuring that Alphie remains at the cutting edge of AI-driven chatbot technology.</p>
<p>For more information, visit: <a href="http://www.ojamuai.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">www.ojamuai.com</a></p>
<h3><span style="font-weight: normal">About Ojamu</span></h3>
<p>Alphie is the second product offering in Ojamu&rsquo;s suite of AI-driven smart toolsets and is the first of its B2C product offerings. Ojamu is continually is looking to enhance and expand the Alphie suite of products, increasing its offerings both within the crypto/blockchain space and beyond.</p>
<p>Ojamu&rsquo;s first product, The Ojamu Intelligence Platform (OIP) continues development and focuses on the B2B space, providing brands the actionable intelligence that they need to succeed in the Web 3.0 economy.</p>
<ul>
<li><a href="http://ojamu.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Web</a></li>
<li><a href="https://t.me/OjamuChat" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Telegram</a></li>
<li><a href="https://twitter.com/ojamuglobal" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Twitter</a></li>
<li><a href="https://ojamu.medium.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Medium</a></li>
</ul>
<h5>Contacts</h5>
<p><strong>Transform Group</strong>, <strong>Ojamu.&nbsp;</strong><strong>ojamu@transformgroup.com</strong>,&nbsp;<strong>press@ojamu.com</strong></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ojamu-announces-alphie-launch-its-latest-ai-driven-smart-tool-for-the-blockchain-industry-integrated-with-chatgpt/">Ojamu Announces “Alphie” Launch &#8211; its latest AI-driven Smart Tool for the Blockchain Industry integrated with ChatGPT</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/ojamu-announces-alphie-launch-its-latest-ai-driven-smart-tool-for-the-blockchain-industry-integrated-with-chatgpt/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Robinhood to allow customers buy crypto directly from within dApps and wallets</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/robinhood-to-allow-customers-buy-crypto-directly-from-within-dapps-and-wallets/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 15:13:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brokers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robinhood]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/robinhood-to-allow-customers-buy-crypto-directly-from-within-dapps-and-wallets/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Robinhood has announced Robinhood Connect, a new feature that offers seamless crypto integration for dApps and wallets. Self-custody wallet Giddy is among the first mobile wallets to integrate the new on-ramp feature. Customers can directly and instantly buy or transfer crypto from within the dApps and also fund their Web3 wallets. Robinhood, a leading online [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/robinhood-to-allow-customers-buy-crypto-directly-from-within-dapps-and-wallets/">Robinhood to allow customers buy crypto directly from within dApps and wallets</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Robinhood has announced Robinhood Connect, a new feature that offers seamless crypto integration for dApps and wallets.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Self-custody wallet Giddy is among the first mobile wallets to integrate the new on-ramp feature.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Customers can directly and instantly buy or transfer crypto from within the dApps and also fund their Web3 wallets.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/robinhood/">Robinhood</a>, a leading online brokerage for stocks and crypto investing, has <a href="https://blog.robinhood.com/news/2023/4/27/introducing-robinhood-connect-simplifying-access-to-web-3" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">launched</a> Robinhood Connect, a new product that will allow customers to easily buy and transfer cryptocurrencies as well as fund their Web3 wallets.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In this case, anyone with a Robinhood balance can now <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/buy/">buy Bitcoin</a> or other tokens instantly and transfer to their <a href="https://coinjournal.net/wallets/">wallet</a> using the new on-ramp.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Robinhood&rsquo;s new on-ramp to Web3</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Robinhood Connect is a new low-cost, on-ramp that will see customers add funds to their wallets from decentralised applications or third party wallets, all without having to leave the dApps or first connect to their Robinhood Crypto account.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>Crypto and Web3 have the potential to change the future of the financial system for the better, but we recognize there are still significant hurdles preventing broader adoption</em>,&rdquo; Johann Kerbrat, the general manager of Robinhood Crypto, said during the product&rsquo;s launch at Consensus 2023.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Kerbrat added that Robinhood Connect demonstrates the brokerage platform&rsquo;s strong commitment to crypto adoption, with the new product set to boost crypto&rsquo;s accessibility and usability.</p>
<p dir="ltr">With developers able to tap into seamless integration for Connect, embedding the feature will be easy. Developers can make this feature directly available to users from within dApps, according to the announcement. This means that projects will be able to allow their customers to buy tokens via the brokerage platform and send them to self-custody wallets.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Robinhood announced on Thursday that <a href="https://giddy.co/what-is-giddy/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Giddy</a>, a self-custody, recoverable smart wallet app powered by Polygon, was among the first mobile wallets to integrate Robinhood Connect. The program will also be rolled out to other platforms over the next few months.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">We&rsquo;re proud to announce that Giddy is one of the first mobile wallets to integrate Robinhood Connect from <a href="https://twitter.com/RobinhoodApp?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@RobinhoodApp</a> &#128640; <a href="https://t.co/TbHgA9WPXt">pic.twitter.com/TbHgA9WPXt</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Giddy (@giddydefi) <a href="https://twitter.com/giddydefi/status/1651646762640105474?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">April 27, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Robinhood seeing new growth momentum</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Founded in 2013, Robinhood has seen massive growth across its crypto products since diving into the space in 2018. While the crypto winter saw its crypto trading revenue fall by over 24% at the end of 2022, the online brokerage remains a popular app for traders.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The collapse of crypto exchange FTX in 2022, and a recent <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/robinhood-is-under-investigation-by-the-us-sec-for-its-crypto-activities/">investigation</a> by the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), has cast Robinhood negatively in recent months. Despite this, the platform continues to take major steps to position itself as a leading destination for crypto trading.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Integration with top crypto platforms and introduction of multiple customer-focused programs are among these steps.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Currently, the platform supports crypto trading and investing for 18 cryptocurrencies, including Bitcoin, Ethereum, Litecoin and Bitcoin Cash. The online brokerage also supports buying and selling of the top meme coins Dogecoin and Shiba Inu.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/robinhood-to-allow-customers-buy-crypto-directly-from-within-dapps-and-wallets/">Robinhood to allow customers buy crypto directly from within dApps and wallets</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Findora launches its Triple Masking ZK SDK to boost privacy and auditability for dApps</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/findora-launches-its-triple-masking-zk-sdk-to-boost-privacy-and-auditability-for-dapps/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 15:07:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/findora-launches-its-triple-masking-zk-sdk-to-boost-privacy-and-auditability-for-dapps/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways Findora has launched its Triple Masking ZK SDK solution. The solution empowers developers to integrate ZK privacy features into their dApps.&#160; With Findora Triple Masking ZK SDK, developers can ensure their users enjoy privacy and convenience.&#160; Findora&#8217;s Triple Masking ZK SDK Findora, an innovative Layer-1 blockchain, has announced the launch of the Findora [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/findora-launches-its-triple-masking-zk-sdk-to-boost-privacy-and-auditability-for-dapps/">Findora launches its Triple Masking ZK SDK to boost privacy and auditability for dApps</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Findora has launched its Triple Masking ZK SDK solution.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The solution empowers developers to integrate ZK privacy features into their dApps.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">With Findora Triple Masking ZK SDK, developers can ensure their users enjoy privacy and convenience.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr">Findora&rsquo;s Triple Masking ZK SDK</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Findora, an innovative Layer-1 blockchain, has announced the launch of the Findora Triple Masking SDK, a universal privacy-preserving solution set for Web3.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In a press release shared with Coinjournal, the team said the Findora Triple Masking SDK gives developers a simple way to integrate zero-knowledge proofs into their decentralised applications.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Thanks to the launch of this product, users can conduct private transactions that remain auditable, with multiple options for what information is masked or remains transparent. The Findora Triple Masking SDK provides simple, plug-and-play privacy for every Web3 dApp, the team added.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">While commenting on this&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/"><u>latest cryptocurrency news</u></a>, &nbsp;Sam Harrison, CEO of Discreet Labs, said;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;Triple Masking fulfills a promise that blockchain technology made years ago: your financial status, your financial future, is no longer in the hands of some unknown, so-called &ldquo;trusted&rdquo; third party. It&rsquo;s in your hands. This SDK simplifies the developer experience of implementing complicated zk-proofs, which in turn enables more decentralized applications to offer the benefits of these zk-proofs to their users.&rdquo;&nbsp;</em></p>
<p dir="ltr">He added that he is excited to see the choices developers can offer their users that would ensure that they enjoy both convenience and privacy.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Findora empowers dApps to be ZK-enabled&nbsp;</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The Findora team added that the Masking SDK is a privacy-focused asset transfer solution supported on the Findora Network that provides full-privacy protection and anonymity for transactions rather than simple pseudonymity.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The solution makes it possible for developers to make their dApps ZK-enabled, with optional transaction privacy at three levels. Users will have the option to mask the wallet addresses of the sender and receiver, the type of assets involved, and the amount sent.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Furthermore, transactions carried out using the Findora &nbsp;Triple Masking ZK SDK will remain auditable to ensure compliance with regulatory entities.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Harrison added that;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;Triple Masking is more than simply encrypting information. We are also offering the ability to trace assets in a way that complies with existing regulations and analysis tools. This way, Triple Masking solves both the privacy AND compliance requirements of a professional institution.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p dir="ltr">The Findora team said its compatibility with the secp256k1 curve would enable common EVM wallets, such as MetaMask, to sign a transaction.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Findora is a public blockchain with programmable privacy. Findora utilises the latest breakthroughs in zero-knowledge proofs and multi-party computation, to allow users transactional privacy with selective auditability.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/findora-launches-its-triple-masking-zk-sdk-to-boost-privacy-and-auditability-for-dapps/">Findora launches its Triple Masking ZK SDK to boost privacy and auditability for dApps</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>CFTC wins a record $3.4B penalty payment in a Bitcoin-related fraud case</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/cftc-wins-a-record-3-4b-penalty-payment-in-a-bitcoin-related-fraud-case/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/cftc-wins-a-record-3-4b-penalty-payment-in-a-bitcoin-related-fraud-case/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 12:29:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CFTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/cftc-wins-a-record-3-4b-penalty-payment-in-a-bitcoin-related-fraud-case/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This is the largest fraud case involving Bitcoin that CFTC has cracked so far. The case involved the CEO of Mirror Trading International Proprietary Limited (MTI). Half of the $3.4B will go toward providing restitution to victims of MTI&#8217;s fraudulent activities. A Texas court has ordered Johannes Steynberg, the CEO of Mirror Trading International Proprietary [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/cftc-wins-a-record-3-4b-penalty-payment-in-a-bitcoin-related-fraud-case/">CFTC wins a record $3.4B penalty payment in a Bitcoin-related fraud case</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul class="decimal_type">
<li>This is the largest fraud case involving Bitcoin that CFTC has cracked so far.</li>
<li>The case involved the CEO of Mirror Trading International Proprietary Limited (MTI).</li>
<li>Half of the $3.4B will go toward providing restitution to victims of MTI&rsquo;s fraudulent activities.</li>
</ul>
<p>A <a href="https://www.cftc.gov/PressRoom/PressReleases/8696-23">Texas court has ordered</a> Johannes Steynberg, the CEO of Mirror Trading International Proprietary Limited (MTI) to pay a $3.4 billion penalty in connection with a large-scale fraud case involving <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/what-is-bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a>.</p>
<p>According to the CFTC allegations, Steynberg engaged in an international fraudulent multilevel marketing scheme (MLM) to ask for bitcoins from the public for an unregistered commodity pool operated by the South Africa-based company MTI.</p>
<p>Steynberg who was controlling MTI and the company falsely claimed to trade off-exchange retail forex through a proprietary &ldquo;bot&rdquo; or software program between May 2018 and approximately March 2021.</p>
<p>The final judgment read:</p>
<p><em>&ldquo;Either directly or indirectly, the defendants misappropriated all of the Bitcoin they accepted from pool participants.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p>According to the CFTC Steynberg, individually and as the principal and agent of MTI, accepted at least 29,421 bitcoins, valued at over $1.7 billion at the time. The bitcoin was obtained from at least 23,000 individuals in the US and other countries around the world. The individuals were tricked to participate in the commodity pool although MTI was not registered as a commodity pool operator (CPO), as required by the law.</p>
<h2>Steynberg arrest</h2>
<p>Steynberg was arrested in December 2021 and has been held in Brazil on an Interpol arrest warrant since then.</p>
<p>Besides the recent charges against him by the CFTC, Steynberg is also permanently banned from registering with the CFTC or trading in any CFTC-regulated markets.</p>
<h2>Restituting MTI&rsquo;s victims</h2>
<p>Half of the $3.4 billion penalty will go towards providing restitution to the victims of MTI&rsquo;s fraudulent activities. The other half is a civil penalty, which is the highest civil penalty to be ordered in any CFTC case.</p>
<p>The CFTC has however conceded that &ldquo;orders requiring payment of funds to victims may not result in the recovery of any money lost because wrongdoers may not have sufficient funds or assets.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/cftc-wins-a-record-3-4b-penalty-payment-in-a-bitcoin-related-fraud-case/">CFTC wins a record $3.4B penalty payment in a Bitcoin-related fraud case</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/cftc-wins-a-record-3-4b-penalty-payment-in-a-bitcoin-related-fraud-case/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
