<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 16:52:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Blockchain technology is ‘trying to address very large TAMs’: Roger Bayston</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/blockchain-very-large-tams-roger-bayston/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wajeeh Khan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 16:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Interview]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital assets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=143585</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Roger Bayston expects crypto investors to eventually be rewarded. He&#8217;s bullish on blockchain as it sits at the heart of a digital economy. Bayston is the Head of Digital Assets at Franklin Templeton. Roger Bayston remains constructive on crypto even though the U.S. SEC has recently sued both Binance and Coinbase for violating securities laws. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/blockchain-very-large-tams-roger-bayston/">Blockchain technology is ‘trying to address very large TAMs’: Roger Bayston</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Roger Bayston expects crypto investors to eventually be rewarded.</li>
<li>He&rsquo;s bullish on blockchain as it sits at the heart of a digital economy.</li>
<li>Bayston is the Head of Digital Assets at Franklin Templeton.</li>
</ul>
<p>Roger Bayston remains constructive on crypto even though the U.S. SEC has recently sued both <a href="https://www.sec.gov/news/press-release/2023-101" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a> and <a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/economy/2023/6/6/us-sec-sues-coinbase-for-breaking-market-rules" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase</a> for violating securities laws.</p>
<h2>Roger Bayston&rsquo;s view on cryptocurrencies</h2>
<p>The Head of Digital Assets at Franklin Templeton Investments is convinced that crypto investors will eventually be rewarded for their patience through the current volatility and uncertainty.</p>
<blockquote><p>As regulatory environment becomes clear, there&rsquo;ll be continued innovation in these software protocol development platforms &hellip; don&rsquo;t expect it to end just at Bitcoin and Ethereum.</p></blockquote>
<p>Franklin Templeton is behind two blockchain investment funds and a consumer app that enables browsing tokenised securities and cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>It has also launched the OnChain U.S. Government Money Market &ndash; a registered mutual fund on two blockchains (Polygon and Stellar).</p>
<h2>Blockchain is central to digital economy</h2>
<p>Bayston is bullish primarily because he sees big future for the digital and data-driven economy &ndash; and the blockchain technology sits right at the heart of it.</p>
<p>Over time, he&rsquo;s confident that it will transform capital markets as well as asset management. Speaking with CNBC this morning, the Franklin Templeton expert also said:</p>
<blockquote><p>These protocols are trying to address very large TAMs where there&rsquo;s application for these public databases that help reduce friction of one database not being the exact copy of another.</p></blockquote>
<p>Also on Monday, top crypto analyst &ndash; Rekt Capital said BTC is positioned for further downside ahead (<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-signals-potential-breakdown-top-analyst-says-about-btc-price/">read more</a>).</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/blockchain-very-large-tams-roger-bayston/">Blockchain technology is ‘trying to address very large TAMs’: Roger Bayston</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Do Kwon sentenced to 4 months in prison in Montenegro</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/do-kwon-sentenced-to-4-months-in-prison-in-montenegro/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/do-kwon-sentenced-to-4-months-in-prison-in-montenegro/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 16:20:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/do-kwon-sentenced-to-4-months-in-prison-in-montenegro/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Do Kwon was arrested in March as he tried to board a flight to Dubai. The Terraform Labs CEO is wanted in South Korea and in the US on charges related to the collapse of TerraUSD and Terra LUNA. Kwon was sentenced together with Han Chang-joon, the former CEO of South Korea-based payments app Chai. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/do-kwon-sentenced-to-4-months-in-prison-in-montenegro/">Do Kwon sentenced to 4 months in prison in Montenegro</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Do Kwon was arrested in March as he tried to board a flight to Dubai.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The Terraform Labs CEO is wanted in South Korea and in the US on charges related to the collapse of TerraUSD and Terra LUNA.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Kwon was sentenced together with Han Chang-joon, the former CEO of South Korea-based payments app Chai.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">In the latest <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/">cryptocurrency related news</a>, a Montenegrin court has sentenced Terra co-founder Do Kwon to a four-month jail term after he was found guilty of using a forged passport.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Kwon was arrested in March</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Kwon, who fled to Montengro amid an effort by <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/south-korea/">South Korea</a> and the US to nab him over the collapse of Terra LUNA and TerraUSD, allegedly tried to flee the country on fake documents.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/do-kwon-sentenced-to-four-months-for-passport-fraud-in-montenegro-6fb924fa" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">reports</a>, the Terraform Labs CEO was sentenced alongside Han Chang-joon, the former CEO of Chai, a South Korea-based payments app.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Kwon and Chang-joon were arrested in March while attempting to flee to Dubai, with prosecutors charging them for possessing forged passports bearing details of Costa Rica and Belgium. The two had pleaded not guilty.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Prior to the sentence, Kwon&rsquo;s $400,000 bail had reportedly been quashed by a higher court. The former crypto mogul, whose crypto platform collapsed in May last year and saw over $40 billion in crypto value wiped out in days, already faced a mandatory six-month extension to his detention and now faces a four-month stint in a Montenegro prison.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As well as being wanted in South Korea, Kwon faces extradition to the US where he been indicted on multiple charges, including fraud.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/do-kwon-sentenced-to-4-months-in-prison-in-montenegro/">Do Kwon sentenced to 4 months in prison in Montenegro</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/do-kwon-sentenced-to-4-months-in-prison-in-montenegro/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Report: 33 straight days of net withdrawals from crypto exchanges</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/report-33-straight-days-of-net-withdrawals-from-crypto-exchanges/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/report-33-straight-days-of-net-withdrawals-from-crypto-exchanges/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dan Ashmore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 16:05:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[On-Chain data]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/report-33-straight-days-of-net-withdrawals-from-crypto-exchanges/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key Takeaways Regulators are clamping down hard on the US crypto industry, with recent lawsuits announced against Binance and Coinbase Bitcoin&#8217;s correlation with stocks is at a 5-year low, with the latter soaring but Bitcoin&#8217;s price suppressed by concerns around future of industry in US Exchanges have seen net outflows for 33 days in a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/report-33-straight-days-of-net-withdrawals-from-crypto-exchanges/">Report: 33 straight days of net withdrawals from crypto exchanges</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2 dir="ltr">Key Takeaways</h2>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Regulators are clamping down hard on the US crypto industry, with recent lawsuits announced against Binance and Coinbase</li>
<li dir="ltr">Bitcoin&rsquo;s correlation with stocks is at a 5-year low, with the latter soaring but Bitcoin&rsquo;s price suppressed by concerns around future of industry in US</li>
<li dir="ltr">Exchanges have seen net outflows for 33 days in a row, but size of withdrawals are not particularly notable</li>
<li dir="ltr">Binance is seeing the largest withdrawals, 7.3% of its balance heading for the exit doors</li>
<li dir="ltr">Allegations against Binance go beyond securities violations which most centralised companies are facing</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p dir="ltr">Binance&rsquo;s war with the SEC goes on. As does Coinbase&rsquo;s. As does, well, the entire cryptocurrency space, which suddenly faces a regulatory threat that feels existential for the crypto industry in the US.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The market has responded, unsurprisingly, by selling. Bitcoin dipped below $25,000 for the first time in three months last week, before bouncing back to where it currently trades at $26,500.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">More notable, however, was that this came amid a time when the stock market is soaring. As I detailed in depth <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-correlation-with-stocks-at-5-year-low-as-regulatory-crackdown-takes-toll/"><u>last week</u></a>, the correlation between stocks and Bitcoin is now at a 5-year low. This is similar to the dip in correlation we saw in November when FTX collapsed while the stock market surged off softer-than-expected inflation numbers.&nbsp;</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/05/15/1686836790790-e6ad26c9-1132-4a69-b507-7ea8eb63f579.png" style="width: 600px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="600" height="427">In such a way, while Bitcoin&rsquo;s price decline seems minor on the face of things, it is underperforming relatively as the rest of the market is red hot. </p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitcoin on exchanges</h2>
<p dir="ltr">But beyond price, how are markets reacting? Are people again concerned about storing their assets with these centralised exchanges?</p>
<p dir="ltr">Well, looking at the total amount of Bitcoin sitting in these exchanges, there has been net outflows for 33 days in a row. That is the longest streak since November 2022 amid the FTX scandal.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14182964">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">The scale of withdrawals is not the same, however. Back in November, the last time we saw a consistent stream of net withdrawals, FTX was exposed as insolvent (and fraudulent) with $8 billion of customer assets gone. Fear was extreme and the entire market panicked, concerned that other exchanges could follow. Bitcoin <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/a-net-flow-of-200000-bitcoins-leaves-exchanges-following-ftx-collapse-as-trust-broken/"><u>ran for the exit doors</u></a>, much of it sent straight to cold storage (or sold for cash).&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">While the current developments are concerning for crypto in their own way, there appears to be no fear that customer assets are in danger. This is not a repeat of FTX, and the market reaction is also significantly more muted.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Indeed, if we look at the total balance of Bitcoin across exchanges, we can see that the recent dip does not stand out in the context of the steep downtrend we have seen since the start of 2020.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14183006">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<h2 dir="ltr">Is Binance different?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">But what about Binance? Accusations levelled at the world&rsquo;s biggest crypto exchange are certainly more sordid than merely securities violations. Binance and CEO Changpeng Zhao have been accused of trading against customers, manipulating trade volume, failing to implement adequate money laundering procedures, encouraging US customers and VIPs to circumvent location-based restrictions, and commingling customer funds.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">It is the latter accusation which is the headline one and throws up painful memories of FTX. While I have been critical of Binance for operating in an incredibly opaque manner (they have always refused to reveal their liabilities), there has been no evidence to date that customer funds have been misappropriated as they were in the FTX case. Again, this really has little in common with the FTX situation.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">On Saturday, a US court even approved an agreement between Binance and the SEC that would dismiss a temporary restraining order to freeze all Binance.US assets.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;We are pleased to inform you that the Court did not grant the SEC&rsquo;s request for a TRO and freeze of assets on our platform which was clearly unjustified by both the facts and the law,&rdquo; Binance.US said on Twitter.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This appears to have assuaged the doomsday scenario, whatever chance there was of that to begin with. In looking at the flows on Binance specifically, however, it has seen more outflows than any other major exchange. 7.3% of its Bitcoin balance was withdrawn in the two weeks since the lawsuit was announced on June 5th. &nbsp;That equates to 52,000 Bitcoin, or about 0.3% of the total circulating supply.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14183172">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">For context, when Binance came under fire for its lack of transparency around reserves after FTX collapsed, 13.3% of its Bitcoin balance was withdrawn in a similar two-week period &ndash; evidently bigger as seen on the above chart, nearly double the flows of what have been seen thus far amid this SEC case.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">What does this all mean? Not very much, really. Binance has long operated in the shadows, and as I wrote <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/opinion-binance-sued-by-sec-an-inevitable-but-ominous-day-for-crypto/"><u>here</u></a> upon the SEC&rsquo;s case being announced, it was a day that had long been coming. But there should not be a sudden uptick in concern around the safety of customer funds, and that is reflected in the relatively small flow of funds out of the platform.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Nonetheless, the allegations against Binance are far more than merely selling unregistered securities, which is the main sticking point across the industry (and what Coinbase is being sued for). It is for this reason that funds have moved out of Binance at a faster pace than other exchanges, even if the size of these is no reason for alarm.</p>
<p dir="ltr">All in all, the reaction is not surprising. Nor were the news of these lawsuits, really.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/report-33-straight-days-of-net-withdrawals-from-crypto-exchanges/">Report: 33 straight days of net withdrawals from crypto exchanges</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/report-33-straight-days-of-net-withdrawals-from-crypto-exchanges/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin signals potential breakdown, top analyst says about BTC price</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-signals-potential-breakdown-top-analyst-says-about-btc-price/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-signals-potential-breakdown-top-analyst-says-about-btc-price/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 15:22:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-signals-potential-breakdown-top-analyst-says-about-btc-price/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin (BTC) is positioned for further downside as a new Weekly Close below the 200-week moving average signals. BTC rejecting from above $26k would welcome bears to the party as double-confirmation of the breakdown. According to crypto analyst Rekt Capital, the 200-week MA is a robust resistance zone.&#160; As Bitcoin bulls face rejection from above [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-signals-potential-breakdown-top-analyst-says-about-btc-price/">Bitcoin signals potential breakdown, top analyst says about BTC price</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Bitcoin (BTC) is positioned for further downside as a new Weekly Close below the 200-week moving average signals.</li>
<li dir="ltr">BTC rejecting from above $26k would welcome bears to the party as double-confirmation of the breakdown.</li>
<li dir="ltr">According to crypto analyst Rekt Capital, the 200-week MA is a robust resistance zone.&nbsp;</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">As <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> bulls face rejection from above $26k, a top analyst has pointed out the benchmark cryptocurrency&rsquo;s price faces fresh downside pressure.</p>
<p dir="ltr">BTC price is currently 2.4% up in the past week, but has failed to break past key resistance around $26,600. The breakdown to lows of $24,800 last week amid negative regulatory headlines appears to have only emboldened bears further.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitcoin positioned for downside</h2>
<p dir="ltr">According to crypto analyst Rekt Capital, the technical outlook for BTC suggests more weakness is likely. This is after a new weekly close below the 200-week moving average, which signals a &ldquo;double confirmation of [a] breakdown,&rdquo; the analyst noted.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Last week, Bitcoin price recovered from lows of $24.8k after the market reacted sharply to the SEC&rsquo;s lawsuits against crypto exchanges Binance and Coinbase. Commenting after the upside, Rekt Capital<a href="https://twitter.com/rektcapital/status/1670490269878239232" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"> <u>suggested</u></a> that Bitcoin had &ldquo;<em>run straight into the 200-week MA</em>&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">He noted that if bears managed to turn this zone into new resistance, there was likelihood BTC could see a &ldquo;two-step breakdown confirmation.&rdquo; Such a price scenario was likely to result in further downside pressure.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>T</em><em>echnically, BTC is positioned for downside. Why? Because it has produced another, new Weekly Close below the 200-week MA. As a result, $BTC has shown double-confirmation of breakdown from the 200-week MA. Continued rejection here could send price lower</em>,&rdquo; he<a href="https://twitter.com/rektcapital/status/1670789716138917889" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"> <u>tweeted</u></a> on Monday, pointing to last week&rsquo;s prediction.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Here&rsquo;s a<a href="https://twitter.com/rektcapital/status/1670789716138917889/photo/1" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">&nbsp;<u>chart</u></a> the analyst shared, showing Bitcoin&rsquo;s rejection at both a downtrend line and the 200-week MA.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/05/19/1687187774157-4bd37017-6c19-433a-a25a-201ad7129418.jpg" style="width: 800px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="800" height="434"></p>
<p dir="ltr">If Bitcoin gives up the $26k level again, a run to June lows could open up room for more losses. However, as BitMEX founder and former CEO Arthur Hayes pointed out last week, its likely crypto will hit the pain of an extended sideways action before a new trigger sets up an &ldquo;autumn rally.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">As CoinJournal <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/arthur-hayes-says-the-chinese-trader-will-drive-cryptos-next-bull-market/">reported</a>, the BitMEX founder believes the trigger will be retail trading, and a big possibility is this next bull market is led by the Chinese trader. BlackRock filing for a spot Bitcoin ETF could also be a significant tailwind in coming months.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-signals-potential-breakdown-top-analyst-says-about-btc-price/">Bitcoin signals potential breakdown, top analyst says about BTC price</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-signals-potential-breakdown-top-analyst-says-about-btc-price/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum proposal seeks to increase validator limit from 32 ETH to 2,048 ETH</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-proposal-seeks-to-increase-validator-limit-from-32-eth-to-2048-eth/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-proposal-seeks-to-increase-validator-limit-from-32-eth-to-2048-eth/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 14:26:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-proposal-seeks-to-increase-validator-limit-from-32-eth-to-2048-eth/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum Foundation researcher Michael Neuder outlined the proposal during a core developer meeting. The proposal seeks to raise the validator stake limit from 32 ETH to 2,048 ETH, an increase that would be 64x. Core developers are considering the proposal. Ethereum Foundation researcher Michael Neuder has proposed that Ethereum&#8217;s validator balance cap be increased from [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-proposal-seeks-to-increase-validator-limit-from-32-eth-to-2048-eth/">Ethereum proposal seeks to increase validator limit from 32 ETH to 2,048 ETH</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Ethereum Foundation researcher Michael Neuder outlined the proposal during a core developer meeting.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The proposal seeks to raise the validator stake limit from 32 ETH to 2,048 ETH, an increase that would be 64x.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Core developers are considering the proposal.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Ethereum Foundation researcher Michael Neuder has<a href="https://ethresear.ch/t/increase-the-max-effective-balance-a-modest-proposal/15801" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"> <u>proposed</u></a> that Ethereum&rsquo;s validator balance cap be increased from the current 32 ETH.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The proposal is under consideration by core developers and if approved could see those looking to be validators on the world&rsquo;s largest proof-of-stake network required to have 2,048 ETH, a balance that would be 64 times higher than the current limit.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Raise ETH limit and auto-compounding of rewards</h2>
<p dir="ltr">According to Neuder, while the 32 ETH limit works towards more decentralisation of the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/ethereum/">Ethereum</a> network, increasing it not only helps lower the size of the validator set, but will also ultimately bring more efficiency to the leading altcoin.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Large validators, such exchanges and institutions will find it easy to manage their operations given the reduction such an increase from 32 ETH to 2,048 ETH would occasion.</p>
<p dir="ltr">With the 32 ETH limit, entities that run as validators had to increase the number of validator nodes they operate for them to have sufficient stake. But with more people eyeing the staking rewards, the number of Ethereum validators has remained high even after the Shapella upgrade.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Currently, Ethereum has over 700,000 validators, and a further 90,000 are looking to join the set.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Also part of the proposal is the idea of having staking rewards auto-compounded. This means instead of requiring any ETH above the current cap moved to another account, the rewards could be compounded to have validators earn higher staking income.</p>
<p dir="ltr">While core Ethereum developers debated the likely pitfalls of implementing such a change, the agreement was for continued discussions. Notably, the proposal seeks to increase the limit, but the minimum stake will remain 32 ETH.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-proposal-seeks-to-increase-validator-limit-from-32-eth-to-2048-eth/">Ethereum proposal seeks to increase validator limit from 32 ETH to 2,048 ETH</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-proposal-seeks-to-increase-validator-limit-from-32-eth-to-2048-eth/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP/USD price prediction: bullish triangle favors a move to $0.8</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/xrp-usd-price-prediction-bullish-triangle-favors-a-move-to-0-8/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/xrp-usd-price-prediction-bullish-triangle-favors-a-move-to-0-8/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mircea Vasiu]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 13:55:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/xrp-usd-price-prediction-bullish-triangle-favors-a-move-to-0-8/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>XRP/USD keeps failing at the $0.55 area As long as the market holds the higher lows series, the bias remains bullish A bullish triangle&#8217;s measured move points to $0.8 The cryptocurrency market is in consolidation following the strong rally since the start of the year. For example, Ripple (XRP) rallied against the US dollar in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/xrp-usd-price-prediction-bullish-triangle-favors-a-move-to-0-8/">XRP/USD price prediction: bullish triangle favors a move to $0.8</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul class="decimal_type">
<li>XRP/USD keeps failing at the $0.55 area</li>
<li>As long as the market holds the higher lows series, the bias remains bullish</li>
<li>A bullish triangle&rsquo;s measured move points to $0.8</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p>The cryptocurrency market is in consolidation following the strong rally since the start of the year. For example, Ripple (XRP) rallied against the US dollar in the first four months of the year as it jumped from $0.3 to almost $0.6 following the overall bullish cryptocurrency market trend.</p>
<p>But then, a consolidation followed. Since trading close to the $0.6 level, XRP/USD failed to make a new high for the year. In fact, it was constantly rejected by horizontal resistance.</p>
<p>However, this rejection, while bearish short term, also tells something different. As long as the price action keeps the series of higher lows intact, it builds energy before another try at the resistance level.</p>
<p>In other words, the bias remains bullish for the XRP/USD if the price is above $0.4. If the level holds, XRP/USD may be close to finishing a bullish reversal triangle with a measured move pointing to much higher levels.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/05/19/1687182225052-e9251ea1-b854-47ef-968e-5b7d79d288ff.jpg" style="width: 1800px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="1800" height="488"></p>
<p><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XRPUSD/?exchange=CRYPTO" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">XRPUSD chart by TradingView</a></p>
<h2>Ripple finds support at $0.3</h2>
<p>The cryptocurrency market&rsquo;s bearish trend ended in the last part of 2022. In the case of XRP/USD, one can see a double bottom pattern at the $0.3 level &ndash; a bullish reversal pattern.</p>
<p>But that is not the only bullish sign. The fact that the market formed a series of higher highs while failing at horizontal resistance tells us that it is building energy to break higher.</p>
<p>More precisely, the price action resembles a bullish triangle. On a close above $0.6, the market should keep advancing toward the $0.8 area because such a triangle has a measured move equal to the length of its longest segment.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/xrp-usd-price-prediction-bullish-triangle-favors-a-move-to-0-8/">XRP/USD price prediction: bullish triangle favors a move to $0.8</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/xrp-usd-price-prediction-bullish-triangle-favors-a-move-to-0-8/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sui Blockchain awards blockchain security firm CertiK $500K CertiK for flagging a threat</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/sui-blockchain-awards-blockchain-security-firm-certik-500k-certik-for-flagging-a-threat/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 13:05:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/sui-blockchain-awards-blockchain-security-firm-certik-500k-certik-for-flagging-a-threat/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Sui awarded CertiK for identifying a vulnerability dubbed &#8220;HamsterWheel&#8221; on Sui Blockchain. The &#8220;HamsterWheel&#8221; vulnerability traps nodes in an endless loop similar to hamsters jogging on a wheel. HamsterWheel attack demonstrates the evolving sophistication of threats to blockchain networks. Sui Blockchain has awarded the blockchain security company CertiK a $500,000 bounty for identifying a threat [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sui-blockchain-awards-blockchain-security-firm-certik-500k-certik-for-flagging-a-threat/">Sui Blockchain awards blockchain security firm CertiK $500K CertiK for flagging a threat</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Sui awarded CertiK for identifying a vulnerability dubbed &ldquo;HamsterWheel&rdquo; on Sui Blockchain.</li>
<li>The &ldquo;HamsterWheel&rdquo; vulnerability traps nodes in an endless loop similar to hamsters jogging on a wheel.</li>
<li>HamsterWheel attack demonstrates the evolving sophistication of threats to blockchain networks.</li>
</ul>
<p>Sui Blockchain has awarded the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/blockchain/">blockchain</a> security company CertiK a $500,000 bounty for identifying a threat that could have brought down the entire Sui layer-1 blockchain.</p>
<p>The identified vulnerability is called &ldquo;HamsterWheel&rdquo; and the CertiK team explained that the vulnerability was distinct from more conventional attacks that aim to crash nodes and bring down blockchains.</p>
<h2>HamsterWheel attack details</h2>
<p>Similar to hamsters running on a wheel, the HamsterWheel attack traps nodes and allows them to carry out operations without processing new transactions. The attack has the power to paralyze networks and render them unusable.</p>
<p>Certick identified the HamsterWheel vulnerability before <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sui-iou-price-spikes-ahead-of-airdrop-mainnet-launch/">Sui&rsquo;s mainnet launch</a> at the beginning of May 2023. Sui then went ahead and implemented fixes in response to the security threat to guard against the potential harm that an attack could cause to the blockchain.</p>
<p>Sui gave CertiK a $500,000 bounty as a thank-you for their efforts; emphasizing the value of bug bounty programs and preventative security measures.</p>
<h2>Blockchain security</h2>
<p>According to CertiK&rsquo;s chief security officer Kang Li, threats to blockchain networks are constantly changing. Li stated that &ldquo;the HamsterWheel attack&rsquo;s discovery demonstrates the evolving sophistication of threats to blockchain networks.&rdquo;</p>
<p>CerticK&rsquo;s announcement states that additional technical information will be released and made accessible soon. Additionally, once all mitigations have been implemented and thoroughly tested, complete reports will be made public.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sui-blockchain-awards-blockchain-security-firm-certik-500k-certik-for-flagging-a-threat/">Sui Blockchain awards blockchain security firm CertiK $500K CertiK for flagging a threat</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>BNB price prediction as Binance outflows continues</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bnb-price-prediction-as-binance-outflows-continues/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/bnb-price-prediction-as-binance-outflows-continues/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 13:03:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance Coin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bnb-price-prediction-as-binance-outflows-continues/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>BNB crypto price has been in a strong bearish trend in the past few weeks. Binance is facing significant regulatory concerns. The company exited the Netherlands and is facing a crackdown in the US and the UK. Binance Coin price crawled back slightly during the weekend as investors attempted to buy the dip. The BNB [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bnb-price-prediction-as-binance-outflows-continues/">BNB price prediction as Binance outflows continues</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">BNB crypto price has been in a strong bearish trend in the past few weeks.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Binance is facing significant regulatory concerns.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The company exited the Netherlands and is facing a crackdown in the US and the UK.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/binance-coin/"><u>Binance Coin</u></a> price crawled back slightly during the weekend as investors attempted to buy the dip. The BNB token rose to a high of $245, which was higher than this month&rsquo;s low of $221. It remains sharply below the year-to-date high of $351.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Binance outflows continue</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Binance Coin is one of the leading cryptocurrencies in the world with a market cap of over $37 billion. It is a leading coin that powers the BNB ecosystem, which is a platform that powers the&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/learn/what-is-defi/"><u>decentralized finance</u></a><strong>&nbsp;</strong>(DeFi), metaverse, and the&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/glossary/non-fungible-token-nft/"><u>non-fungible token</u></a> (NFT).</p>
<p dir="ltr">BNB coin is known for its association with Binance, the biggest&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/"><u>crypto exchange</u></a><strong>&nbsp;</strong>in the world. Binance has made several headlines in the past two weeks. It is facing a major investigation by the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Most recently, Binance announced that it was exiting the Dutch market. The company has announced that it is not accepting new customers from the country. The statement added:</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;No further purchases, trades or deposits will be possible. We encourage users to take appropriate action by withdrawing assets from their Binance accounts.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Binance is also facing investigations in France, the second-biggest economy in Europe. Most importantly, the firm decided to cancel it registration in the UK, where it is also facing significant regulatory concerns.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">As a result, data shows that the company&rsquo;s assets have dropped in the past few weeks. According to DeFi Llama, Binance has lost over $80 million in assets in the past 24 hours. It has lost over $4.4 billion in the past 30 days.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Further, the BNB Chain has seen its DeFi total value locked (TVL) drop by more than 23% in the past 30 days. It now has a TVL of over $5.17 billion, making it the third-biggest chain in the world after Ethereum and Tron.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Binance Coin price prediction</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/05/19/1687179755953-57e7638d-1b5a-43f3-8899-120d2bef9cb6.png" style="width: 693px;height: 337.26px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="693" height="337.26"></p>
<p dir="ltr">The daily chart shows that the BNB price has been in a bearish trend in the past few days. As it dropped, the coin dropped below the important support levels at $298.4 and $265.6, respectively. The two were the lowest levels on April 3rd and March 10 of this year.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Binance Coin has dropped below the 25-day and 50-day moving averages. It has also formed what looks like a bearish pennant pattern. Therefore, the BNB price will likely have a bearish breakout as sellers target the next support at $200.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy Binance Coin</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>


<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=MTQzNTY2&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy BNB with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    CEX.IO</h3>


<p>
    <a href="/visit/cex-crypto?guid=MTQzNTY2&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy BNB with CEX.IO today            </a>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bnb-price-prediction-as-binance-outflows-continues/">BNB price prediction as Binance outflows continues</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/bnb-price-prediction-as-binance-outflows-continues/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin holders with 100 BTC or less scooped 254% of mined supply last month: Glassnode</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-holders-with-100-btc-or-less-scooped-254-of-mined-supply-last-month-glassnode/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-holders-with-100-btc-or-less-scooped-254-of-mined-supply-last-month-glassnode/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 11:49:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-holders-with-100-btc-or-less-scooped-254-of-mined-supply-last-month-glassnode/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s price struggles aside, last month saw more entities with less than 100 BTC buy 2.54X of all coins mined. Glassnode data shows these entities added 2,286 BTC per day. Shrimps increased their BTC holdings by 117% last month, while crabs added 80% and fish bought 57% of mined bitcoin. It appears Bitcoin (BTC)&#160;wallet addresses [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-holders-with-100-btc-or-less-scooped-254-of-mined-supply-last-month-glassnode/">Bitcoin holders with 100 BTC or less scooped 254% of mined supply last month: Glassnode</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Bitcoin&rsquo;s price struggles aside, last month saw more entities with less than 100 BTC buy 2.54X of all coins mined.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Glassnode data shows these entities added 2,286 BTC per day.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Shrimps increased their BTC holdings by 117% last month, while crabs added 80% and fish bought 57% of mined bitcoin.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">It appears <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">Bitcoin (BTC)</a>&nbsp;wallet addresses with under 100 BTC have used the recent dump in the flagship cryptocurrency&rsquo;s value to add to their positions.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to on-chain data <a href="https://insights.glassnode.com/bitcoin-supply-distribution-revisited/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">shared</a> by Glassnode, the cohorts from shrimps (less than 1 BTC) to fish (less than 100 BTC), purchased 2.54x of daily mined supply over the past month. With the current daily mined coins at approximately 900, these entities scooped 2,286 BTC per day.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Shrimps and crabs increase total BTC holdings 117% and 80% respectively</h2>
<p dir="ltr">As can be seen in the chart below, the monthly absorption rates for shrimps, crabs and fish was 117%, 80% and 57% respectively. That&rsquo;s a massive 254% in terms of the share of mined coins &ndash; shrimps, crabs and octopus and fish added to their total holdings last month. With Bitcoin price around $26,300, that&rsquo;s more than $60 million worth BTC per day.</p>
<div class="fr-img-space-wrap"><span class="fr-img-caption fr-fic fr-dib fr-draggable" style="width: 800px"><span class="fr-img-wrap">
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/05/19/1687174927802-24abfd0d-dbdf-4bdb-a2b4-42abcb4fcb7e.jpg" style="width: 800px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="800" height="353"><span class="fr-inner">Bitcoin monthly distribution rates for shrimps, crabs, octopus and fish. Source: <a href="https://twitter.com/glassnode/status/1670744450887213060" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Glassnode</a></span></p>
<p></p></span></span>
<p class="fr-img-space-wrap2">Shrimps now hold 1.26 million BTC, or 6.6% of the total circulating supply, up from roughly 4.86% a year ago. Crabs account for 2.03 million BTC, which is 10.5% of circulating supply. The cohort&rsquo;s total holdings have increased from 8.7% from a year ago.</p>
</div>
<p dir="ltr">Meanwhile, the supply held by whale entities continued to decline and stood at 34.4% as of June 2023. This is a decline of 45% since Bitcoin&rsquo;s first halving in 2012, when whales accounted for 62.7% of total BTC supply.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Whales currently hold approximately 6.64 million BTC, down from a peak of 7.8 million BTC in 2016.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-holders-with-100-btc-or-less-scooped-254-of-mined-supply-last-month-glassnode/">Bitcoin holders with 100 BTC or less scooped 254% of mined supply last month: Glassnode</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-holders-with-100-btc-or-less-scooped-254-of-mined-supply-last-month-glassnode/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
