<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 09:22:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Mark Cuban, John Reed Stark Debate on Right Crypto Regulation Approach</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/mark-cuban-john-reed-stark-crypto/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/mark-cuban-john-reed-stark-crypto/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 09:22:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[japan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[john reed stark]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mark cuban]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[securities and exchange commission]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261673</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/mark-cuban-john-reed-stark-crypto/">Mark Cuban, John Reed Stark Debate on Right Crypto Regulation Approach</a></p>
<p>Cuban argued that the failure of the SEC to set “clear regulations” was what caused investors to lose their money in the FTX collapse.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/mark-cuban-john-reed-stark-crypto/">Mark Cuban, John Reed Stark Debate on Right Crypto Regulation Approach</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/mark-cuban-john-reed-stark-crypto/">Mark Cuban, John Reed Stark Debate on Right Crypto Regulation Approach</a></p>
<p>Billionaire businessman Mark Cuban has been seen having a public debate with former SEC official John Reed Stark. The debate which took place on Twitter, bordered on the role of regulators, such as the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>), on the collapse of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a> and the likes.</p>
<h2>Crypto Regulation: Mark Cuban Urges SEC to Take a Cue from Japan</h2>
<p>Stark had earlier suggested that cryptocurrencies, stablecoins, and even CBDCs do not have any real use. And that, even worse, the industry operates without regulation. This, according to Stark, was always a recipe for disaster as there couldn&#8217;t be any proper consumer protection.</p>
<p>Cuban then argued that the failure of the SEC to set “clear regulations” was what caused investors to lose their money in the FTX collapse.</p>
<p>To buttress his claim, Cuban noted how Japanese regulators have shown the world the right way to regulate. He <a href="https://twitter.com/mcuban/status/1676258204924407808?t=4tRnb8jpnea5sussXcbXRQ&amp;s=19" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">wrote</a> in part:</p>
<blockquote><p>“When FTX crashed, NO ONE IN FTX JAPAN LOST MONEY.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Furthermore, Cuban claims that things could have ended better for investors if the USA/SEC had followed Japan&#8217;s example by setting clear regulations. That is regulations that will ensure the separation of customer and business funds and clear wallet requirements.</p>
<p>According to the businessman, the SEC took the wrong approach by litigating to regulate, and that has ultimately cost billions.</p>
<h2>Stark Replies</h2>
<p>Meanwhile, Stark has also fired back. The ex-SEC employee says Cuban might be overreaching by blaming the SEC for the collapses of FTX, BlockFi, Celsius, Terra, and others.</p>
<p>Admittedly, Stark believes the regulator may have made some mistakes in its approach. However, he also insists that the regulator did save investors “millions, perhaps even billions” in crypto losses.</p>
<p>Stark also points to the fact that the crypto industry is undecided in its quest for regulatory clarity.  He says that the industry has a tradition of crying foul whenever rules are proposed, often resorting to lawsuits to fight the rules.</p>
<p>For example, Stark mentioned how the recent cases of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-sues-binance-securities-rules/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a> and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-sec-coinbase-unregistered-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase</a>. He says the SEC made it clear many months ago that they were not in compliance. However, after recently charging them, the crypto industry began wailing again.</p>
<p>Overall, Cuban has suggested what he feels is the “best way” to prevent the insecurities of cryptocurrency. The entrepreneur says that can only be achieved by implementing “bright line investor protection regulations”.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitget-dual-coin-crypto-loan-service/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/mark-cuban-john-reed-stark-crypto/">Mark Cuban, John Reed Stark Debate on Right Crypto Regulation Approach</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/mark-cuban-john-reed-stark-crypto/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitget Launches Dual-Coin Crypto Loan Service</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitget-dual-coin-crypto-loan-service/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitget-dual-coin-crypto-loan-service/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mercy Tukiya Mutanya]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 09:15:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitget]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockfi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[celsius network]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[genesis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261689</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitget-dual-coin-crypto-loan-service/">Bitget Launches Dual-Coin Crypto Loan Service</a></p>
<p>The announcement comes at a time when crypto loans are increasing in popularity owing, in large part, to the overall growth of the digital lending market.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitget-dual-coin-crypto-loan-service/">Bitget Launches Dual-Coin Crypto Loan Service</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitget-dual-coin-crypto-loan-service/">Bitget Launches Dual-Coin Crypto Loan Service</a></p>
<p>Crypto derivatives platform Bitget has announced the launch of a new product called “Crypto Loans” targeted at users not satisfied with traditional lending institutions. The new product will enable users to stake one coin as collateral to enable them to borrow the corresponding amount in another coin in what is known as a dual-coin approach.</p>
<p>According to Bitget, the borrowing process has been simplified and designed to emulate the process used by traditional lending institutions. This is in a bid to facilitate user onboarding. First, users will have to stake their collateral following which the requested loan amount will automatically be released. Loans will have varying interest rates, with the amount one can borrow depending on the market value of the staked collateral.</p>
<p>Bitget’s Managing Director <a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2023/07/04/2699197/0/en/Bitget-Launches-Crypto-Loans-To-Meet-The-Growing-Demand-For-Lending-Services.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Gracy Chen noted</a> that beyond providing credit, the Crypto Loans service will also help users expand their crypto investment portfolio.</p>
<p>&#8220;Bitget&#8217;s new product highlights the flexibility of collateralized currency usage, enhancing capital utilization. Users now have the opportunity to stake less-demanded coins, enabling them to obtain loans in more liquid assets for investment purposes,” Chen states. “Our platform&#8217;s flexible borrowing and repayment mechanism is designed to cater to the needs of all users, accommodating their requests and ensuring convenience.”</p>
<p>The announcement comes at a time when crypto loans are increasing in popularity owing, in large part, to the overall growth of the digital lending market. According to a <a href="https://www.gminsights.com/industry-analysis/digital-lending-platform-market" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report by Global Markets Insight</a>, the digital lending sector passed the $8.5 billion mark in 2022 and is expected a Compound Annual Growth Rate (CAGR) of 20.5% from 2023 to 2032. The industry’s value is projected to reach $60 billion in 2032. This growth, along with the increased mainstream adoption of technologies such as blockchain and artificial intelligence, is expected to continue to aid the growth of the crypto loans industry.</p>
<p>While several crypto lenders have experienced setbacks in recent years – with crypto lenders such as Celsius, BlockFi, and Genesis filing for bankruptcy – Bitget emphasizes that their loan disbursement process is modeled after existing processes used by lenders in traditional finance. The firm also states that it has taken steps to account for its holdings and ensure that user collateral is secure.</p>
<p>In late March, the platform partnered with decentralized data firm Space and Time to create a decentralized data warehouse. This tamperproof audit trail was created to provide users with an increased level of transparency in Bitget operations. The exchange, like many others following the collapse of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a>, also released its proof of reserves in the form of a dedicated section on its website.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-ceo-rate-limit-tweets/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitget-dual-coin-crypto-loan-service/">Bitget Launches Dual-Coin Crypto Loan Service</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitget-dual-coin-crypto-loan-service/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Twitter CEO Defends Elon Musk’s Rate Limit on Tweets</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-ceo-rate-limit-tweets/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-ceo-rate-limit-tweets/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 09:11:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[linda yaccarino]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[twitter]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261684</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-ceo-rate-limit-tweets/">Twitter CEO Defends Elon Musk’s Rate Limit on Tweets</a></p>
<p>In a recent blog post, Twitter provided an explanation for the imposition of rate limits, highlighting the need to take “extreme measures” to combat the presence of spam and bots on the platform.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-ceo-rate-limit-tweets/">Twitter CEO Defends Elon Musk’s Rate Limit on Tweets</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-ceo-rate-limit-tweets/">Twitter CEO Defends Elon Musk’s Rate Limit on Tweets</a></p>
<p>The new CEO of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/twitter/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Twitter Inc</a>, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/linda-yaccarino/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Linda Yaccarino</a> has come out in defense of<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/elon-musk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"> Elon Musk</a>&#8216;s decision to impose limits on the number of views user’s tweets receive.</p>
<p>In a <a href="https://twitter.com/TwitterBusiness/status/1676278441774292992" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Twitter post</a>, Yaccarino wrote that she is committed to upholding the platform&#8217;s mission and taking significant steps to enhance its functionality and impact. She highlighted that Twitter needs to make big moves to strengthen the platform as the outfit&#8217;s purpose goes beyond being a mere social media platform.</p>
<p>By supporting the imposition of limits on tweet views, the CEO is advocating for a more responsible and thoughtful approach to social media use, where the potential harm caused by misinformation and unchecked influence is mitigated.</p>
<h2>Concerns Raised by Industry Experts</h2>
<p>Last week Elon Musk imposed limits on the number of posts that can be viewed by users. Initially, the limit was set at 600 posts per day for unverified users and 6000 posts for verified users. However, the limit was later increased to 1000 posts per day for unverified accounts and 10,000 tweets for verified accounts.</p>
<p>The controversial measure, which has been met with mixed reactions aims to address “extreme levels of data scraping” and “system manipulation”, as stated by Musk. However, Twitter users have taken to the platform to share screenshots demonstrating their inability to view tweets, including those from corporate advertisers.</p>
<p>This limitation has raised concerns among marketing professionals who believe it could potentially undermine the efforts of Yaccarino to attract advertisers. In an earlier Coinspeaker <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-daily-tweet-views-ceo-efforts/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">report</a>, Jasmine Enberg, a principal analyst at Insider Intelligence, voiced concerns about the potential impact of limiting user views on Twitter&#8217;s advertising business.</p>
<p>Enberg has expressed worry that such a move could have a “catastrophic” effect and make it even more challenging for Twitter to attract advertisers back to the platform, which is already a difficult task.</p>
<h2>Twitter Raises Defense</h2>
<p>In a recent <a href="https://business.twitter.com/en/blog/update-on-twitters-limited-usage.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">blog post</a>, Twitter provided an explanation for the imposition of rate limits, highlighting the need to take “extreme measures” to combat the presence of spam and bots on the platform.</p>
<p>The company highlighted that the rate limits were implemented as a means to address two primary concerns: the scraping of public Twitter data for the development of AI models, and the manipulation of users and conversations on the platform.</p>
<p>In the same blog post, Twitter clarified that the rate limit restrictions had been imposed on only a small percentage of users at present, and added that the company would provide updates once their work is complete.</p>
<p>Regarding advertising, Twitter assured that the effects of the rate limit restrictions have been minimal. This statement is aimed at addressing potential concerns among advertisers who may have worried about the impact on their advertising campaigns and the reach of their content.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/voyager-134m-outflows-celsius/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-ceo-rate-limit-tweets/">Twitter CEO Defends Elon Musk’s Rate Limit on Tweets</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-ceo-rate-limit-tweets/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Voyager Digital Records $134M in Outflows while Celsius Network Remains Dormant</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/voyager-134m-outflows-celsius/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/voyager-134m-outflows-celsius/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 09:06:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[celsius network]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gemini]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[usdc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[voyager digital]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261676</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/voyager-134m-outflows-celsius/">Voyager Digital Records $134M in Outflows while Celsius Network Remains Dormant</a></p>
<p>Voyager and Celsius are forging ahead with their bankruptcy plans but only Voyager seems to be making any crypto transfers.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/voyager-134m-outflows-celsius/">Voyager Digital Records $134M in Outflows while Celsius Network Remains Dormant</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/voyager-134m-outflows-celsius/">Voyager Digital Records $134M in Outflows while Celsius Network Remains Dormant</a></p>
<p>Crypto lending firms Voyager Digital and Celsius Network have both received approvals to begin moving their crypto portfolios around. Both bankrupt lenders are still trying to resolve their bankruptcies in court and have been involved in court action since filing for bankruptcy last year. However, activity on the Celsius front has been stagnant, while Voyager is active.</p>
<p>According to a <a href="https://cases.stretto.com/public/x191/11749/PLEADINGS/1174906302380000000027.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">filing</a> on June 30, the Bankruptcy Court in the Southern District of New York authorized Celsius to exchange its remaining crypto for Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a>) or Ether (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ETH</a>). The firm had admitted to meeting with the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) over its recent decision to <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-binance-matic-sol-lawsuit/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">classify some cryptocurrencies</a> as securities. According to the Commission, MATIC, BNB, ADA, ALGO, and SOL, among others, are securities.</p>
<p>Following these talks, the court allowed Celsius to “maximize the value of [its] Altcoins” and sell them for ETH or BTC. Data from crypto intelligence platform Arkham Intelligence stated that Celsius held nearly $600 million at the time, including $187.04 million in altcoins.</p>
<p>Despite the approval, Celsius has yet to make any moves as of Tuesday. The lender’s last activity was moving $11.3 million worth of MATIC (17.3 million tokens) to a Polygon staking contract for rewards. Before then, Celsius had sent $7.1 million USDC to FalconX.</p>
<p>Celsius filed a bankruptcy exit plan following an agreement with crypto consortium Fahrenheit. After launching an auction last October and receiving multiple bids, Fahrenheit <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fahrenheit-consortium-celsius-network/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">beat</a> NovaWulf Digital Management to emerge the winner. The offer includes a $300 million cash payment and $700 million worth of Fahrenheit tokens. However, Celsius later filed an update that limits user recovery and is now <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/celsius-creditor-bankruptcy-exit/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">getting heavy pushback</a> from customers.</p>
<h2>Voyager Moves Crypto Around as Celsius Holds Off</h2>
<p>While the Celsius Network seems to be delaying any sales or transfer transactions, Voyager has recorded heavy activity. Nearly one year after suspending all operations, Voyager authorized user withdrawals from June 23. According to Arkham Intelligence, Voyager held nearly $413 million in multiple assets the day before withdrawals officially began. Withdrawals will only be possible for 30 days.</p>
<p>Last week, crypto exchange and custodian Gemini <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gemini-withdrawals-voyager-customers/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">announced</a> support for users looking to withdraw funds from its platform. Customers can only transfer assets supported by Gemini as attempts to do otherwise or transfer supported assets on unsupported networks, may result in loss.</p>
<p>Since officially starting withdrawals, Voyager has recorded consistent outflows, reducing its $413 million by 25% to $307.5 million. Calculated at current market prices, the total value of all crypto withdrawn is $134 million. The top three outflows are BTC, USDC, and ETH, respectively.</p>
<p>Last week, Voyager <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/voyager-digital-1-1m-legal-fees/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">received</a> a $1.1 million bill from its legal advisor, Kirkland &amp; Ellis, for April. The company charged Voyager for work done, at a blended hourly rate of $1,313.18. On the other hand, Voyager Creditors <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/voyager-creditors-5-1m-bill/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">got</a> a $5.1 million bill for services rendered from March to May. Law firm McDermott Will &amp; Emery has now billed the group of creditors more than $16 million.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/britains-house-lords-crypto-bill/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/voyager-134m-outflows-celsius/">Voyager Digital Records $134M in Outflows while Celsius Network Remains Dormant</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/voyager-134m-outflows-celsius/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Britain’s House of Lords Passes Bill to Seize and Freeze Crypto Used for Crime</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/britains-house-lords-crypto-bill/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/britains-house-lords-crypto-bill/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 08:46:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[house of lords]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261667</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/britains-house-lords-crypto-bill/">Britain&#8217;s House of Lords Passes Bill to Seize and Freeze Crypto Used for Crime</a></p>
<p>Having passed through UK's upper chamber, the new bill is close to law. The bill seeks to allow authorities to seize cryptocurrencies used for criminal activities. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/britains-house-lords-crypto-bill/">Britain&#8217;s House of Lords Passes Bill to Seize and Freeze Crypto Used for Crime</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/britains-house-lords-crypto-bill/">Britain&#8217;s House of Lords Passes Bill to Seize and Freeze Crypto Used for Crime</a></p>
<p>On Tuesday, July 4, the UK&#8217;s Economic Crime and Corporate Transparency Bill, entered its final stages thereby becoming law, after being passed by the House of Lords. Basically, this bill seeks to empower British agencies to seize and freeze cryptocurrencies used for criminal activities such as money laundering or terror financing.</p>
<p>Additionally, the bill has introduced an amendment to ensure that courts can also ask the authorities to take action on crypto used for crime. In order to identify cryptocurrencies linked to criminal activities, Britain has introduced crypto tactical advisers and police departments nationwide.</p>
<p>In March 2023, the British government said that they would be combating the criminal use of crypto under the three-year economic agenda.</p>
<p>The new bill has passed through the UK&#8217;s upper chamber, bringing it closer to becoming a law. There are a few more steps remaining: a review by the lower chamber called the House of Commons, agreement on any further changes by both chambers and approval by King Charles III.</p>
<p>Over the past months, UK lawmakers included various additions to the bill. In November, they introduced provisions that allow public authorities to seize digital assets associated with terrorism and take control of properties that can help identify cryptocurrencies linked to criminal activities.</p>
<p>Britain first introduced the UK&#8217;s Economic Crime and Corporate Transparency Bill back in September 2022. Back then, Graeme Biggar, director general of the National Crime Agency, <a href="https://www.finextra.com/newsarticle/41004/uk-government-launches-fraud-and-money-laundering-crackdown" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Domestic and international criminals have for years laundered the proceeds of their crime and corruption by abusing UK company structures, and are increasingly using cryptocurrencies. These reforms – long awaited and much welcomed – will help us crack down on both.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>The Purpose of the Bill Passed by the House of Lords</h2>
<p>In a statement released in September, the government mentioned that the Economic Crime and Corporate Transparency Bill will enhance the UK&#8217;s reputation as a favorable place for lawful businesses to flourish while also eliminating illicit money from the country. The reforms will require everyone registering a company in the UK to confirm their identity, addressing the misuse of companies for criminal purposes or by corrupt foreign officials.</p>
<p>The United Kingdom has initiated several <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-law-commission-digital-assets/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">measures</a> to legitimize the use of digital assets. Recently, the UK Law Commission submitted a proposal to the government to provide a comprehensive legal foundation for cryptocurrencies. Last month, the UK government also <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-passes-legislation-crypto-brexit/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">passed legislation</a> to promote the safe adoption of cryptocurrencies.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-ethereum-supply-goldman-sachs/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/britains-house-lords-crypto-bill/">Britain&#8217;s House of Lords Passes Bill to Seize and Freeze Crypto Used for Crime</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/britains-house-lords-crypto-bill/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Goldman Sachs Report: Bitcoin and Ethereum Supply on Exchanges Drops Sharply in June</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-ethereum-supply-goldman-sachs/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-ethereum-supply-goldman-sachs/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 08:22:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[goldman sachs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261671</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-ethereum-supply-goldman-sachs/">Goldman Sachs Report: Bitcoin and Ethereum Supply on Exchanges Drops Sharply in June</a></p>
<p>Goldman Sachs reported that the total monthly Bitcoin inflows from miners to centralized exchanges almost doubled from May to $99 million in June. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-ethereum-supply-goldman-sachs/">Goldman Sachs Report: Bitcoin and Ethereum Supply on Exchanges Drops Sharply in June</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-ethereum-supply-goldman-sachs/">Goldman Sachs Report: Bitcoin and Ethereum Supply on Exchanges Drops Sharply in June</a></p>
<p>A new report from Goldman Sachs Group Inc (NYSE: GS) shows that Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a>) and Ethereum (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ETH</a>) supply on centralized exchanges (CEXes) significantly reduced in June as holders migrated to self-custody services. The migration majorly caused by the ongoing crypto regulatory crackdown and increased fear of theft through hacks saw Bitcoin and Ether supply on CEX drop to levels not seen YTD. According to the report, Bitcoin supply <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/07/04/bitcoin-ether-supply-on-exchanges-fell-in-june-goldman-sachs/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">dropped</a> 4 percent, nearing the level of December 2022, while Ether supply declined 5.8 percent in June to levels not seen since May 2018.</p>
<p>As for Ethereum, most holders preferred to stake and earn passive returns while storing securely instead of just holding on centralized exchanges. Moreover, increased risks of hacks and rug pull on centralized crypto firms has the old slang ‘not your keys, not your coins’ at work.</p>
<p>Interestingly, crypto investors continued to hold and add more coins in recent months despite the prices showcasing overbought features. Investors remain highly bullish on Bitcoin and Ethereum in the long term, especially with increased institutional crypto demand.</p>
<p>In June, the Bitcoin market led the altcoins in gains following an ETF frenzy from key institutional investors. Although the SEC has remained adamant in approving the first Bitcoin ETF in the United States, the underlying crypto demand by institutional investors is undeniable.</p>
<p>As Bitcoin price rallied towards $31k last month, on-chain data analyzed by Goldman Sachs shows miners increased their profit taking, perhaps fueled by the fear of a possible correction. Specifically, Goldman Sachs reported that the total monthly Bitcoin inflows from miners to centralized exchanges almost doubled from May to $99 million in June.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin and Ethereum Market Outlook</h2>
<p>The top two digital assets by market capitalization continued to record increased on-chain activities in June. Heightened DeFi development on Ethereum and the uprising use of Bitcoin ordinal dubbed BRC-20 standard were identified as the root cause of increased activity. For instance, the Binance exchange was at one time forced to halt withdrawals following heightened network congestion that resulted in a sharp uptick in transaction fees.</p>
<p>The report by <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/goldman-sachs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Goldman Sachs</a> further highlighted that the monthly address activity for Bitcoin and Ethereum increased by approximately 15.5 percent and 37.5 percent respectively in June. The increase in on-chain activity was also underpinned by the fact that the daily average new address count for Bitcoin and Ethereum gained by approximately 9.8 percent and 48.2 percent monthly.</p>
<p>Worth noting, the Goldman report highlighted that the average daily Ether burnt on the beacon chain in June dropped by approximately 65.1 percent while the average daily fees dropped by about 63.3 percent.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-global-tech-semiconductor/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-ethereum-supply-goldman-sachs/">Goldman Sachs Report: Bitcoin and Ethereum Supply on Exchanges Drops Sharply in June</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-ethereum-supply-goldman-sachs/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>China Seeks Global Tech Control via Issuing Stern Restrictions on Exporting Semiconductor-Making Materials</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-global-tech-semiconductor/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-global-tech-semiconductor/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 15:37:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Transportation News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nvda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nvda stock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nvidia]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261647</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-global-tech-semiconductor/">China Seeks Global Tech Control via Issuing Stern Restrictions on Exporting Semiconductor-Making Materials</a></p>
<p>China manufactures nearly 80 percent of global gallium and germanium products used in making chips that are critical in AI developments.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-global-tech-semiconductor/">China Seeks Global Tech Control via Issuing Stern Restrictions on Exporting Semiconductor-Making Materials</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-global-tech-semiconductor/">China Seeks Global Tech Control via Issuing Stern Restrictions on Exporting Semiconductor-Making Materials</a></p>
<p>The Xi Jinping-led government has once again pushed the People&#8217;s Republic of China to arise against the enemy’s gunfire after being left with few moves to play. Notably, the government of China has issued a stern warning against the exportation of gallium and germanium products, which are mostly used in the manufacture of semiconductor chips. On July 3, the Chinese Ministry of Commerce issued a joint statement with the General Administration of Customs requiring all gallium and germanium metal exports to have a government license.</p>
<p>Citing national security interests, the Chinese government <a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/china-to-tighten-control-on-exports-of-ai-chip-making-materials" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">noted</a> that there will be no excess exportation of gallium and germanium starting from August 1. Reportedly, the government has put in place punitive actions against persons caught going against the issued orders.</p>
<p>Some of the metal products highlighted in the recent export restrictions include gallium antimonide, gallium arsenide, gallium metal, gallium nitride, gallium oxide, gallium phosphide, gallium selenide, and indium gallium arsenide.</p>
<p>Others are germanium products including germanium dioxide, germanium epitaxial growth substrate, germanium ingot, germanium metal, germanium tetrachloride, and zinc germanium phosphide.</p>
<h2>China Checkmates US Sanctions on AI Chips</h2>
<p>Undeniably, the Chinese government has outwitted the United States government in taking control of futuristic technologies by restricting the exportation of key materials. Moreover, a 2023 report from the European Commission and the European Association of Critical Raw Materials Alliance (CRMA), shows that the Republic of China is home to over 80 percent of global gallium supply. The Chinese tech experts are now working on scaling the production of their modern semiconductor chips to remain a major global hub for tech companies in the future.</p>
<p>Notably, Chinese tech companies have suffered a low supply of American emerging technologies since the Trump administration began issuing sanctions. The situation has over the years worsened after the Biden administration issued similar sanctions and pushed its allies including Japan to cut China off the semiconductor supply.</p>
<p>Since the Artificial Intelligence (AI) boom, related stocks and products have skyrocketed amid heavy speculations. For instance, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/nvidia/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Nvidia Corp.</a> (NASDAQ: NVDA) saw its market capitalization rally towards $1 trillion earlier this year following the demand vs supply choke. According to the latest stock market data, NVDA shares have rallied about 19 percent YTD to trade around $424 on Tuesday. Interestingly, nearly 50 Wall Street analysts expect the NVDA stock market to rally further in the coming future with an average rating of Buy.</p>
<p>The response from the White House on the matter is expected to escalate or calm down the situation after Chinese officials earlier requested nations to work together on technology for humanity’s future. Nonetheless, the ongoing war between Russia and Ukraine has complicated the relationship between the West and China.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-subscribers-tweetdeck/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-global-tech-semiconductor/">China Seeks Global Tech Control via Issuing Stern Restrictions on Exporting Semiconductor-Making Materials</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-global-tech-semiconductor/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Twitter Subscribers to Gain Exclusive Access to TweetDeck</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-subscribers-tweetdeck/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-subscribers-tweetdeck/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 15:34:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluesky]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jack dorsey]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mastodon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Meta]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TweetDeck]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[twitter]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261640</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-subscribers-tweetdeck/">Twitter Subscribers to Gain Exclusive Access to TweetDeck</a></p>
<p>The competition in the social media industry is heating up, and Twitter is finding itself in the midst of a dynamic landscape with various rivals vying for user attention and engagement.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-subscribers-tweetdeck/">Twitter Subscribers to Gain Exclusive Access to TweetDeck</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-subscribers-tweetdeck/">Twitter Subscribers to Gain Exclusive Access to TweetDeck</a></p>
<p>In a recent announcement, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/twitter/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Twitter Inc</a> confirmed that a change is forthcoming regarding the accessibility of TweetDeck. According to recent <a href="https://www.nottinghampost.com/news/uk-world-news/twitter-says-tweetdeck-soon-only-8572133" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reports</a>, starting in 30 days, TweetDeck will only be accessible to users who have obtained verified status on the platform.</p>
<p>TweetDeck has long been regarded as a helpful resource for social media enthusiasts, professionals, and corporations. Its unique features, such as the ability to handle various feeds and searches, have made it a go-to platform for people looking for a more simplified way to manage their Twitter activities.</p>
<h2>The Release of TweetDeck 2.0</h2>
<p>Notably, TweetDeck 2.0 introduces numerous major features and changes to the popular social media management application.</p>
<p>While users can expect new features such as video docking and enhanced Tweet composer functionality, one significant adjustment is the temporary disabling of TweetDeck Teams. However, Twitter has reassured users that TweetDeck Teams will be reintroduced in the coming weeks.</p>
<p>This announcement comes just days after <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/elon-musk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Elon Musk</a>, Twitter’s Chairman made another significant change by <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-daily-tweet-views-ceo-efforts/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">limiting</a> unverified users to reading only 1000 posts per day. Since assuming ownership of the company, Musk has maintained an active and vocal presence, implementing various changes aimed at improving user experience and tackling longstanding issues plaguing the platform.</p>
<p>Twitter&#8217;s recent updates and changes continue to make waves in the social media landscape. In a recent development, verified users on Twitter, who have either subscribed to Twitter Blue or are considered “notable,” have seen an increase in their daily post limit.</p>
<p>Initially set at 6,000 posts, verified users can now read up to 10,000 posts per day, allowing for a more extensive engagement with the platform. As of now, all users, regardless of their Twitter Blue status, are able to access the new version of TweetDeck. This means that there is no immediate restriction on accessing TweetDeck for verified or unverified users.</p>
<h2>Competition Heats Up for Twitter</h2>
<p>The competition in the social media industry is heating up, and Twitter is finding itself in the midst of a dynamic landscape with various rivals vying for user attention and engagement.</p>
<p>One of the significant competitors that Twitter faces is Facebook from <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/meta/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Meta Platforms Inc</a> (NASDAQ: META), which has a massive user base and an established ecosystem of platforms and services.</p>
<p>Facebook&#8217;s recent <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-twitter-app-july-6/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">launch</a> of a rival app dubbed Threads adds another layer of competition to the mix. With its extensive resources and user reach, Facebook has the potential to pose a significant challenge to Twitter&#8217;s market position.</p>
<p>Other microblogging platforms have also emerged as formidable contenders in the social media space. Following Musk&#8217;s announcement, Bluesky, a platform backed by Jack Dorsey, the co-founder and former CEO of Twitter, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bluesky-record-traffic-twitter/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">experienced a surge</a> in traffic. Users flocked to Bluesky, leading to “record-high traffic” on the same day the announcement was made.</p>
<p>Another platform that <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-mastodon-user-base/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">witnessed</a> a significant increase in traffic is Mastodon, a decentralized social network. Eugen Rochko, CEO of Mastodon revealed that the platform experienced a surge in its active user base by at least 110,000 on Sunday, July 2.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-g7-inflation-oecd-data/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-subscribers-tweetdeck/">Twitter Subscribers to Gain Exclusive Access to TweetDeck</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-subscribers-tweetdeck/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>OECD Data: UK Is Only G7 Country where Inflation Is Still Rising</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-g7-inflation-oecd-data/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-g7-inflation-oecd-data/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 15:21:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bank of america]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[boe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[g7]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[imf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[oecb]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261632</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-g7-inflation-oecd-data/">OECD Data: UK Is Only G7 Country where Inflation Is Still Rising</a></p>
<p>Inflation in the UK is still on the rise despite continuous hikes in interest rates and inflation reductions in other G7 countries.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-g7-inflation-oecd-data/">OECD Data: UK Is Only G7 Country where Inflation Is Still Rising</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-g7-inflation-oecd-data/">OECD Data: UK Is Only G7 Country where Inflation Is Still Rising</a></p>
<p>Inflation in the United Kingdom (UK) is still rising despite continuous efforts from the country’s central bank. <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/07/04/uk-is-now-the-only-major-economy-where-inflation-is-still-rising.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Data</a> from the Organization for Economic Cooperation and Development (OECD) states that inflation in all other G7 countries is falling.</p>
<p>According to the OECD, G7 inflation dropped from 5.6% in April to 4.6% in May. The organization noted that this reduction, the lowest in more than 6 months, was true of G7 countries outside the UK. The OECD said there are noted reductions in inflation in Japan, Canada, Germany, the US, France, and Italy.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the OECD said inflation dropped in all observed nations in May, from April, excluding the UK, Norway, and the Netherlands. In the UK, consumer prices rose 7.8% between April and May, and 7.9% compared to last year.</p>
<h2>Bank of England Still Fighting UK Inflation</h2>
<p>The Bank of England (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/bank-of-england/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BoE</a>) recently <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-raises-interest-13th-time/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">announced</a> an interest rate hike by 50 basis points. The announcement came after the Monetary Policy Committee voted 7-2 in favor, marking the 13th consecutive hike.</p>
<p>The BoE increased rates in response to inflation as the annual consumer price index climbed 8.7% in May, higher than the 8.4% economists had predicted. Core inflation, excluding alcohol, tobacco, and food, also climbed to 7.1% from the 6.8% recorded in April. Back in March, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-inflation-double-digit-march-2023/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">UK inflation was at 10.1%</a> according to the Office for National Statistics, higher than the 9.8% expected by a Reuters poll of economists. UK inflation hit <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-inflation-soars-highest-41-years/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">11.1% in November</a>, the highest level in 41 years.</p>
<p>Speaking on the hike, BoE governor Andrew Bailey said the increase was necessary. Bailey admitted that although the economy is improving, hiking interest rates is important as inflation is “still too high and we’ve got to deal with it.” Bailey warned that any delay in increasing these rates could worsen the economy in the near future.</p>
<p>Despite the poor figures, the International Monetary Fund (IMF) has a bullish outlook on the UK’s inflation. According to the IMF, the UK will likely escape a recession in 2023 and see positive growth this year. However, the IMF warns that although it expects growth, this outlook is “subdued”. Essentially, the Fund does not expect large growth margins. The IMF had previously <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/imf-global-growth-forecast-us-eurozone-gdp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">predicted</a> that growth in the UK would contract by 0.3%</p>
<h2>More Hikes Coming?</h2>
<p>A Reuters <a href="https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/bank-england-hikes-rates-5-surprise-move-tackle-stubborn-inflation-2023-06-22/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a> states that markets predict a 50% chance that the rate would peak at 6.25% this year. The recent hike had pushed rates to 5%.</p>
<p>Generally, the UK’s economy has suffered a few setbacks that may have worsened inflation over time. In addition to Brexit and COVID-19, the country has experienced quite an increase in gas prices because of Russia’s war against Ukraine. Although many countries have suffered their fair share of problems caused by the same factors, the UK is still struggling.</p>
<p>Bailey said while the BoE is not expecting a recession, the rate hike was “absolutely imperative”, and the bank will continue to do whatever is required to reduce inflation.</p>
<p>A BoE forecast puts growth in the UK for 2023 at 0.25%.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/telescope-gpt-web3-grading-tool/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-g7-inflation-oecd-data/">OECD Data: UK Is Only G7 Country where Inflation Is Still Rising</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-g7-inflation-oecd-data/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Telescope Labs Unveils GPT 4-Backed Advanced Tool for Analyzing and Grading Web3 Games</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/telescope-gpt-web3-grading-tool/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/telescope-gpt-web3-grading-tool/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 13:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gaming News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[telescope labs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261409</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/telescope-gpt-web3-grading-tool/">Telescope Labs Unveils GPT 4-Backed Advanced Tool for Analyzing and Grading Web3 Games</a></p>
<p>Apart from setting the bar with the first-of-its-kind solution, Telescope Labs boasts the plugin's integration with artificial intelligence for advanced real-time analysis. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/telescope-gpt-web3-grading-tool/">Telescope Labs Unveils GPT 4-Backed Advanced Tool for Analyzing and Grading Web3 Games</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/telescope-gpt-web3-grading-tool/">Telescope Labs Unveils GPT 4-Backed Advanced Tool for Analyzing and Grading Web3 Games</a></p>
<p>Launched in 2022, data analytics startup Telescope Labs has launched an advanced tool for analyzing and grading web3 games. The company provides support for web3 gaming outfits and uses predictive models and machine learning to cater to users. According to an official announcement on July 4th, the newly-unveiled plugin is powered by OpenAI&#8217;s GPT-4. The tool is a unique solution that utilizes <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/technology/artificial-intelligence-news/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">AI</a> to access thousands of web3 games.</p>
<h2>Telescope Labs Rolls Out AI Tool for Analyzing and Grading Web3 Games</h2>
<p>Telescope Labs deploying the advanced reasoning abilities of GPT-4 means that the new tool for analyzing and grading web3 grams goes beyond the traditional analysis tools. It will help its users conduct daily analyses and compare the growth performance of multiple games. In addition, the Telescope Labs web3 game analytics powered by GPT-4 can be used to predict future trends.</p>
<p>Following the launch, users of the Telescope Labs tool can use it for grading and analyzing over 2,000 web3 games. Also, there are 37 distinct Key Performance Indicators (KPIs) available to them to make smarter choices. The KPIs have been optimized for web3 and are accessible to all users.</p>
<p>The CEO and co-founder of Telescope Labs, Semih Gilan, is excited about the announcement of the grading tool. He added that &#8220;the plugin&#8217;s blend of voluminous and varied data, sophisticated reasoning, user-friendliness, and real-time responsiveness is a game-changer for web3 gaming and blockchain.&#8221;</p>
<p>Notably, the plugin is the first-of-its-kind solution, and this means that Telescope Labs has set a standard for future developments. Already, OpenAI disrupted the markets with its ChatGPT before releasing GPT-4 months ago. Since its release on March 14th, 2023, the latest version of OpenAI&#8217;s multimodal larger language model has caught the attention of many companies like Telescope Labs. With Telescope Labs launching a GPT-4-backed web3 games grading tool, there will be a higher understanding of web3 gaming and blockchain game analysis.</p>
<h2>Telescope Labs Sets Bar for Future Developments</h2>
<p>Telescope Labs spoke about the push behind the development of the grading tool. The data analytics startup said the plugin is responding to the blockchain gaming industry&#8217;s call for advanced analysis tools. It added that blockchain gaming community members have been demanding user-friendly data analysis tools. Hence, the unveiling of the plugin.</p>
<p>Apart from setting the bar with the first-of-its-kind solution, Telescope Labs boasts the plugin&#8217;s integration with artificial intelligence for advanced real-time analysis. It also said the tool is easy to use and sets the benchmark regarding data access.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-ordinals-luminex-brc-69/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/telescope-gpt-web3-grading-tool/">Telescope Labs Unveils GPT 4-Backed Advanced Tool for Analyzing and Grading Web3 Games</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/telescope-gpt-web3-grading-tool/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4110 metric#misses=41 metric#hit-ratio=99.0 metric#bytes=1067422 metric#prefetches=202 metric#store-reads=20 metric#store-writes=2 metric#store-hits=209 metric#store-misses=2 metric#sql-queries=34 metric#ms-total=357.13 metric#ms-cache=21.34 metric#ms-cache-avg=1.0160 metric#ms-cache-ratio=6.0 -->