<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>CoinGape</title>
	<atom:link href="https://coingape.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coingape.com/</link>
	<description>CoinGape - 24*7 Crypto Updates</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 05:25:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/14183030/cropped-CoinGape_logo-32x32.png</url>
	<title>CoinGape</title>
	<link>https://coingape.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Litecoin and dYdX See Large Whale Transactions, These Altcoins Are on Traders&#8217; Radar</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/litecoin-and-dydx-see-large-whale-transactions-these-altcoins-are-on-traders-radar/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 05:25:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin price analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=136758</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The altcoin market has been showing good strength recently with Ethereum and other top-ten altcoins taking the lead. But over the last two-three months, one altcoin that&#8217;s been consistently doing well is Litecoin (LTC). During the last 90 days, LTC has gained more than 80% while grabbing the attention of investors. As per the on-chain <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/litecoin-and-dydx-see-large-whale-transactions-these-altcoins-are-on-traders-radar/" title="Litecoin and dYdX See Large Whale Transactions, These Altcoins Are on Traders&#8217; Radar"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/litecoin-and-dydx-see-large-whale-transactions-these-altcoins-are-on-traders-radar/">Litecoin and dYdX See Large Whale Transactions, These Altcoins Are on Traders&#8217; Radar</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/03182142/altcoin.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p>The altcoin market has been showing good strength recently with Ethereum and other top-ten altcoins taking the lead. But over the last two-three months, one altcoin that&#8217;s been consistently doing well is Litecoin (LTC).</p>
<p>During the last 90 days, LTC has gained more than 80% while grabbing the attention of investors. As per the on-chain data, large whale addresses holding LTC have exploded in activity. On-chain data provider Santiment reported:</p>
<blockquote><p>Litecoin&#8217;s large whale transactions have exploded with activity, indicating a resurgence of transactions that are valued at $1 million or more. On the tail end of the last two similarly sized whale spikes, prices jumped +37% and +33% at their peaks.</p></blockquote>
<figure id="attachment_136759" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-136759" style="width: 2913px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-136759" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/26103154/Litecoin-Whale-Transactions.jpeg" alt="" width="2913" height="1816" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-136759" class="wp-caption-text">Courtesy: <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1618453883029970945" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Santiment</a></figcaption></figure>
<p>Market analysts believe that LTC will continue to be on investors&#8217; radars this year as the major <a href="https://coingape.com/litecoin-price-prediction-when-to-expect-ltc-rally-ahead-of-halving-event/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">halving event</a> is approaching in the second half of 2023. This could serve as a major catalyst for the LTC to all even more. Some analysts are expecting Litecoin&#8217;s (LTC) price to rally all the way to $150 and around.</p>
<h3>dYdX Also Joins Litecoin In Party</h3>
<p>Over the last 24-hours, dYdX has jumped by a staggering 30% as the dYdX Foundation <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://dydx.foundation/blog/lock-up-extension" target="_blank" rel="noopener">said</a> that they would be delaying the unlocking of its 150 million tokens from the next month of February to later December this year. As a result, there&#8217;s been huge whale participation in dYdX as of now.</p>
<p>As of press time, dYdX is trading at a price of $1.99. The Santiment <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1618292489051594752" target="_blank" rel="noopener">report</a> notes:</p>
<blockquote><p>DYDX <span class="css-901oao css-16my406 r-poiln3 r-bcqeeo r-qvutc0">has been a bright spot and is +22% on the day in an otherwise quiet </span><span class="r-18u37iz">#altcoin</span><span class="css-901oao css-16my406 r-poiln3 r-bcqeeo r-qvutc0"> market. There are already 986 active addresses on the </span><span class="r-18u37iz">#DYDX</span><span class="css-901oao css-16my406 r-poiln3 r-bcqeeo r-qvutc0"> network, indicating a big utility increase. Additionally, there are already 10 $1M+ whale transactions today.</span></p></blockquote>
<figure id="attachment_136760" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-136760" style="width: 2773px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-136760" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/26104823/DYDX-Price-Rally.jpeg" alt="" width="2773" height="1768" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-136760" class="wp-caption-text">Courtesy: Santiment</figcaption></figure>
<p>Along with Litecoin and dYdX, several other small and mid-cap altcoins have seen strong rallies this year. Some of the altcoins that have jumped 20% in the last 24 hours include LCX, SONM, Aptos, Nervos, Concordium, etc.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f973.png" alt="🥳" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Altcoins?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Altcoins</a> are on another impressive run, with several notable assets up 20% or more. After a 5-day <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/crypto?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#crypto</a> dip, prices are seeing little resistance. Social spikes &amp; <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/FOMO?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#FOMO</a> may cause a top, or traders will scoff at this run (allowing rallies to continue). <a href="https://t.co/Fv5R7Ke87Z">https://t.co/Fv5R7Ke87Z</a> <a href="https://t.co/Ez1WW5vPsf">pic.twitter.com/Ez1WW5vPsf</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Santiment (@santimentfeed) <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1618372704612257799?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 25, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/litecoin-and-dydx-see-large-whale-transactions-these-altcoins-are-on-traders-radar/">Litecoin and dYdX See Large Whale Transactions, These Altcoins Are on Traders&#8217; Radar</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/03182142/altcoin.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mango Labs Decides to Sue Trade Over Token Manipulation in Mango Markets</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/mango-labs-decides-to-sue-trade-over-token-manipulation-in-mango-markets/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 04:16:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi Hacks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mango Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MNGO token]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=136757</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Mango Labs, the parent organization behind Solana-based DeFi platform Mango Markets has decided to sue the trader who manipulated the price of the MNGO token back in October 2022 and allegedly raked up more than $114 million in profits. In its Federal lawsuit filed on Wednesday, January 25, Mango Labs said that the hacker &#8211; <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/mango-labs-decides-to-sue-trade-over-token-manipulation-in-mango-markets/" title="Mango Labs Decides to Sue Trade Over Token Manipulation in Mango Markets"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/mango-labs-decides-to-sue-trade-over-token-manipulation-in-mango-markets/">Mango Labs Decides to Sue Trade Over Token Manipulation in Mango Markets</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="640" height="377" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/12081542/Solana-Mango-DeFi.png" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p>Mango Labs, the parent organization behind Solana-based DeFi platform Mango Markets has decided to sue the trader who <a href="https://coingape.com/solana-based-defi-platform-hacked-in-a-100-million-exploit-heres-the-details/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">manipulated the price of the MNGO token</a> back in October 2022 and allegedly raked up more than $114 million in profits.</p>
<p>In its Federal lawsuit filed on Wednesday, January 25, Mango Labs said that the hacker &#8211; Avraham Eisenberg &#8211; had agreed to return $67 million of the ill-gotten funds. But Mango Labs now wants the rest of the money as well.</p>
<p>In a separate filing previously, the US Securities Commission and the U.S. CFTC had sued Eisenberg for perpetrating the crime. As both agencies accused him of manipulating the MNGO token, the trader faces parallel criminal charges. Last month in December 2022, Eisenberg was arrested in Puerto Rico, however, it&#8217;s not confirmed whether he&#8217;s been moved to New York, <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/mango-labs-sues-trader-to-recover-allegedly-stolen-tokens-1.1875005" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reports</a> Bloomberg.</p>
<h3>The Mango Markets Hack</h3>
<p>Last month in October 2022, Avraham Eisenberg used two separate accounts on the Mago Markets Defi platform to manipulate the price of the MNGO tokens through perpetual swaps. These are basically futures trades that allow users to keep their positions open.</p>
<p>As per details, Eisenberg managed to push the price of the swaps up by 1300% in just 20 minutes and cash out. Amid this, the price of MNGO tokens dropped to just 2 cents with Mango Markets forced to suspend operations the day after the incident.</p>
<p>Interestingly, Eisenberg went out all on Twitter bragging that the team operated a &#8220;highly profitable trading strategy&#8221; while allegedly referring to the Mango scheme. Eisenberg also posted that he believed that his actions were legal.</p>
<p>Mango Markets has further accused Eisenberg of attacking the crypto lending platform Aave. The company <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/mango-labs-sues-trader-to-recover-allegedly-stolen-tokens-1.1875005" target="_blank" rel="noopener">said</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Since the attack, defendant has continued to plot to attack Mango Markets further, in public, and has used the converted funds to attack other cryptocurrency protocols as well&#8221;.</p></blockquote>
<p>The case is currently going on in the US District Court, Southern District of New York (Manhattan). Besides, Eisenberg hasn&#8217;t got a lawyer for himself yet. The last year of 2022 witnessed some of the biggest hacks in the DeFi space. The DeFi market lost $4 billion alone in hacks.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/mango-labs-decides-to-sue-trade-over-token-manipulation-in-mango-markets/">Mango Labs Decides to Sue Trade Over Token Manipulation in Mango Markets</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/12081542/Solana-Mango-DeFi.png" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Lawsuit: Here&#8217;s The Latest Update On SEC Vs. Ripple Case</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/xrp-lawsuit-new-update-on-ripple-vs-sec-court-case/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pratik Bhuyan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 20:38:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ripple (XRP)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple vs SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=136750</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SEC Vs Ripple News: Although the legal dispute between the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and cryptocurrency firm Ripple has continued for a third year, a resolution may be close at hand. Following the submission of both parties&#8217; final documents on the XRP lawsuit, Ripple and the SEC, together with other interested parties&#8211;have since <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/xrp-lawsuit-new-update-on-ripple-vs-sec-court-case/" title="XRP Lawsuit: Here&#8217;s The Latest Update On SEC Vs. Ripple Case"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/xrp-lawsuit-new-update-on-ripple-vs-sec-court-case/">XRP Lawsuit: Here&#8217;s The Latest Update On SEC Vs. Ripple Case</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="783" height="391" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/26014535/images-61.jpeg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="XRP lawsuit|sec vs. ripple" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p><strong>SEC Vs Ripple News:</strong> Although the legal dispute between the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/">cryptocurrency</a> firm <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/ripple-xrp/">Ripple</a> has continued for a third year, a resolution may be close at hand. Following the submission of both parties&#8217; final documents on the <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/xrp-lawsuit/">XRP lawsuit</a>, Ripple and the SEC, together with other interested parties&#8211;have since showcased summary briefings that are likely to influence the final outcome of the case.</p>
<h2>XRP Lawsuit&#8217;s New Update</h2>
<p>However, before the final briefings, defense counsel James Filan disclosed that the <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/united-states/page/16/">United States</a>-based crypto firm had submitted a motion in opposition to a filing that was made by Investment Banker Declarant trying to conceal certain facts from being made public. The data contains, among other things, his name, job title, and company name. The declarant claims he should be shielded from liability since he voluntarily filed the declaration in support of the SEC&#8217;s summary judgment motion.</p>
<p>According to latest <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/FilanLaw/status/1618313473599115264" rel="nofollow">reports</a>, the “Investment Banker Declarant (IBD)” has filed a response to Ripple’s opposition to the motion. The official release states that none of the defendants&#8217; reasons are strong enough to outweigh the substantial privacy and safety concerns of Investment Banker Declarant in allowing the specifically targeted redactions. First and foremost, the Defendants&#8217; principal defense that IBD, an employee of an SEC-regulated entity, provided his declaration to the SEC &#8220;voluntarily&#8221; provides no legitimate justification for refusing leave to redact.</p>
<p><strong><em>Read More: </em></strong><a href="https://coingape.com/best-telegram-crypto-channels-list/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><em>Check Out The Top Crypto Telegram Channels Of 2023</em></a></p>
<p>The IBD, who is employed by a broker-dealer that is registered with the <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/sec/">SEC</a>, was unable to refuse a request for a declaration from the SEC, which serves as his company&#8217;s main regulatory body. The SEC&#8217;s other option, had Investment Banker Declarant declined to give a statement, was to compel his testimony to verify the document in question. It goes without saying that there cannot be a truly voluntary &#8220;decision&#8221; when a witness&#8217;s two options are to make a declaration or testify. Even if there were, voluntariness is not taken into account when analyzing redactions, and the defendants provide no evidence to the contrary. If anything, historical precedent clearly shows that where there are compelling grounds to redact, especially when it comes to the safety and privacy of other individuals involved in the dispute, those concerns take precedence over all other factors.</p>
<h2>The SEC Vs. Ripple Saga</h2>
<p>Furthermore, the report states, the court has already acknowledged that the risks to witnesses, in this case, are significant to warrant the redaction of any identifying information that may have been included in the documents. As a publicly-named witness in this high-profile matter, Investment Banker Declarant and his co-workers would face similar risks. In conclusion, the firm representing the IBD in the ongoing <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/ripple-vs-sec/">SEC Vs. Ripple case</a> &#8212; alleged that the Defendants&#8217; arguments if followed to their logical conclusion, would make any future government inquiries more difficult. The participation of individuals who may desire or need to maintain their anonymity is extremely important to investigators.</p>
<blockquote><p>If that confidentiality cannot be assured, cooperation will not be forthcoming.</p></blockquote>
<p>With all the hype and discussion surrounding the XRP lawsuit, the case development is anticipated to have a substantial effect on the price of XRP; which has received some bullish signals as a result of the situation. <span id="inputElements~dce916a38741450f" class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-inherit css-1uk1gs8">As things stand, the price of <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/xrp/">XRP token</a> is currently exchanging hands at $0.41.</span><span id="inputElements~821cca2d8e5ecb60" class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-inherit css-1uk1gs8"> This represents a decrease of 2.47% on the day, in contrast to a gain of 6.11% during the week as per CoinGape’s <a href="https://coingape.com/markets">crypto market</a> tracker.</span></p>
<p><em><strong>Also Read: </strong><a title="Revealed: Top 5 Cryptos With Highest Development Activity" href="https://coingape.com/top-5-cryptos-with-highest-development-activity/" rel="bookmark">Top 5 Cryptos With Highest Development Activity</a></em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/xrp-lawsuit-new-update-on-ripple-vs-sec-court-case/">XRP Lawsuit: Here&#8217;s The Latest Update On SEC Vs. Ripple Case</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/26014535/images-61.jpeg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Best Cryptocurrency To Buy Today, 5 Contenders With 50x Gain Potential!</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/best-cryptocurrency-to-buy-today-5-contenders-with-50x-gain-potential-10019/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Coingape Staff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 20:20:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Defi]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=136715</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the year 2022, cryptocurrencies were the most wounded asset class of all. The total market capitalization plunged more than 63% over the year. But, right now, the cryptocurrency market is slowly moving toward a bullish trend and if you are looking for the best cryptocurrency to buy today, you are at the right place. <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/best-cryptocurrency-to-buy-today-5-contenders-with-50x-gain-potential-10019/" title="Best Cryptocurrency To Buy Today, 5 Contenders With 50x Gain Potential!"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/best-cryptocurrency-to-buy-today-5-contenders-with-50x-gain-potential-10019/">Best Cryptocurrency To Buy Today, 5 Contenders With 50x Gain Potential!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/25175006/50x-Gain-Potential-1.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p>In the year 2022, <a rel='nofollow'  href="http://cryptocurrencies" rel="nofollow">cryptocurrencies</a> were the most wounded asset class of all. The total market capitalization plunged more than 63% over the year. But, right now, the <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/cryptocurrency-market/">cryptocurrency market</a> is slowly moving toward a bullish trend and if you are looking for the <strong>best cryptocurrency to buy today</strong>, you are at the right place.</p>
<h2>Best Cryptocurrency to buy today</h2>
<p>These are the top 5 cryptocurrencies based on their performance over the past 24 hours that may have 50x growth potential.</p>
<h4>CANTO</h4>
<p>Canto is a layer-1 blockchain built to deliver on the promise of <a href="https://coingape.com/5-best-defi-tokens-to-watch-out-this-week/">DeFi</a>. Driven by a loosely organized collective of chain-native builders, this cryptocurrency provides a new commons powered by free public infrastructure. At present, Canto is trading $0.299422 (up by 40%) with a 24-hour trading volume of $458,408.</p>
<figure id="attachment_136716" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-136716" style="width: 1177px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-136716" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/25174622/CANTO.png" alt="" width="1177" height="633" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-136716" class="wp-caption-text">Source &#8211; CoinMarketCap</figcaption></figure>
<p>Read more: <a href="https://coingape.com/upcoming-coinbase-listings-in-2023/">3 Upcoming Coinbase Listings in February 2023; Here’s a List</a></p>
<h4>Audius</h4>
<p>Audius is a decentralized music streaming protocol that will soon be listed on one of the biggest cryptocurrency exchanges, <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/coinbase/">Coinbase</a>. After the official Twitter announcement, Audius&#8217;s price have been rising constantly. Currently, the coin is hovering around $0.2661 (Up by 21%) with a 24 hours trading volume of $478,235,061.</p>
<figure id="attachment_136717" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-136717" style="width: 1173px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-136717" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/25174702/Audius-.png" alt="" width="1173" height="628" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-136717" class="wp-caption-text">Source &#8211; CoinMarketCap</figcaption></figure>
<h4>Aptos</h4>
<p>Aptos is a Layer 1 Proof-of-Stake <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/blockchain/">blockchain</a> that can achieve a theoretical transaction throughput of over 150,000 transactions per second through parallel execution. Aptos is currently trading around $13.79 with a one-day trading volume of $1,201,765,810. Moreover, the token has surged 89.76% in a week.</p>
<figure id="attachment_136718" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-136718" style="width: 1175px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img decoding="async" class="wp-image-136718 size-full" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/25174726/Aptos.png" alt="" width="1175" height="652" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-136718" class="wp-caption-text">Source &#8211; CoinMarketCap</figcaption></figure>
<h4>Threshold</h4>
<p>Yet another coin that is witnessing a price surge after being announced to be listed on Coinbase. The current price of the Threshold token is $0.05 with a one-day trading volume of $1,143,026,406. It has risen by 129.97% during the past seven days.</p>
<figure id="attachment_136719" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-136719" style="width: 1173px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-136719" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/25174756/Threshold.png" alt="" width="1173" height="637" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-136719" class="wp-caption-text">Source &#8211; CoinMarketCap</figcaption></figure>
<h4>eCash</h4>
<p>The rebranded version of Bitcoin Cash ABC, eCash has been performing better than many cryptocurrencies. At the time of writing, XEC is trading around $0.00003349 with a one-day trading volume of $38,884,029. It has increased by nearly 1.68% in the past 24 hours. eCash has seen a surprising surge of 9.18% in a week.</p>
<figure id="attachment_136720" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-136720" style="width: 1163px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-136720" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/25174820/ecash.png" alt="" width="1163" height="643" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-136720" class="wp-caption-text">Source &#8211; CoinMarketCap</figcaption></figure>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/budget-2023-india-date-time-when-and-where-we-can-watch-live-streaming-budget-speech-10015/">Budget 2023 India Date &amp; Time: When and Where We Can Watch Live Streaming Budget Speech</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/best-cryptocurrency-to-buy-today-5-contenders-with-50x-gain-potential-10019/">Best Cryptocurrency To Buy Today, 5 Contenders With 50x Gain Potential!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/25175006/50x-Gain-Potential-1.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Traders Should Beware Of This Bull Trap If They Are Buying Apecoin</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/markets/traders-should-beware-of-this-bull-trap-if-they-are-buying-apecoin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brian Bollinger]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 19:39:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[APE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apecoin price analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?post_type=markets&#038;p=136753</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Over the past two months, the Ape price showcased a sustained recovery in the daily chart. This bullish rally was led by a rising parallel channel pattern and doubled the Ape Coin&#8217;s market value from its November 2022 low. However, in theory, this pattern is known as a bearish continuation pattern, intensifying the selling pressure <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/markets/traders-should-beware-of-this-bull-trap-if-they-are-buying-apecoin/" title="Traders Should Beware Of This Bull Trap If They Are Buying Apecoin"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/markets/traders-should-beware-of-this-bull-trap-if-they-are-buying-apecoin/">Traders Should Beware Of This Bull Trap If They Are Buying Apecoin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="716" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/28222535/APECOIN-explained.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="apes apecoin" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Over the past two months, the Ape price showcased a sustained recovery in the daily chart. This bullish rally was led by a <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/parallel-channel-pattern/">rising parallel channel pattern</a> and doubled the Ape Coin&#8217;s market value from its November 2022 low. However, in theory, this pattern is known as a bearish continuation pattern, intensifying the selling pressure upon the breakdown of the support trendline. Having said that, the buyers gave an upside breakout from the patterns trendline but is still struggling to offer a follow-up rally.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Key points: </span></h2>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The multiple rejection candles at $6 indicate the sellers continue to defend this level</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">A bullish crossover between the 50-and-100-day EMA could encourage the resumption of a bullish recovery</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The intraday trading volume in Apecoin is $173. Million, indicating a 26% gain</span></li>
</ul>
<p><img decoding="async" class="alignnone" src="https://s3.tradingview.com/snapshots/l/l7SCOpeX.png" alt="Apecoin" width="1946" height="1104" />Source: tradingview</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In a strong bullish scenario, an upside breakout from the patterns resistance trendline will undermine this bearish thesis and increase the buying pressure. There, on January 21st, <a href="https://coingape.com/price/apecoin/">Apecoin price</a> gave a high momentum breakout from the pattern&#8217;s resistance trendline, offering an entry opportunity for sidelined traders. This breakout was supposed to trigger a significant rally, but instead, the coin price is moving sideways, struggling to breach $6.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The coin currently trades at the $5.84 mark and shows several higher price rejection candles at $6 in the last five days. These rejection candles signal the exhausted bullish moment and the ability of buyers to sustain higher prices.</span></p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/defi-lending-platforms/">Top 10 DeFi Lending Platforms In 2023</a></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Thus, if the selling pressure persists, the coin price will likely break the rising trendline and validate the prior breakout as a fakeout or <a href="https://coingape.com/education/what-is-bull-trap-in-crypto/">bull trap.</a> This breakdown will encourage longer corrections and may plunge the price back to $4.47.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Conversely, the traders looking for a long entry opportunity should wait for a daily candle closing above $6.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Technical Indicator</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><strong>RSI</strong>: despite a rising price action, the <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/rsi-relative-strength-index/">RSI slope</a> showing a downfall indicates a bearish divergence. This divergence with price action showcase and additional confirmation for coming correction.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><strong>EMAs</strong>: the recently reclaimed 200-day EMA  moving the $5.2 mark increases the support power of this level.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Apecoin Intraday Price Levels</span></h2>
<ul>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">Spot price: $5.8</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">Trend: Bullish</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">Volatility: High</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">Resistance level- $6 and $7.64</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">Support level- $5.2 and $3.8</span></li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/markets/traders-should-beware-of-this-bull-trap-if-they-are-buying-apecoin/">Traders Should Beware Of This Bull Trap If They Are Buying Apecoin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/28222535/APECOIN-explained.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Top Reasons Why Crypto Market Is Falling Today</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/top-reasons-why-crypto-market-is-falling-today/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pratik Bhuyan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 16:51:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=136742</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The price of Bitcoin (BTC), along with the overall cryptocurrency market, is undergoing a correction as traders are left apprehensive by the plummeting U.S. stock market; with Microsoft falling over by 4% in the opening hours of trading. Overnight, the value of cryptocurrencies started to experience a downward trend, with Ethereum (ETH) being the most <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/top-reasons-why-crypto-market-is-falling-today/" title="Top Reasons Why Crypto Market Is Falling Today"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/top-reasons-why-crypto-market-is-falling-today/">Top Reasons Why Crypto Market Is Falling Today</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="960" height="540" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/25210608/0x0.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="crypto market" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p>The <a href="https://coingape.com/price/bitcoin/">price of Bitcoin (BTC)</a>, along with the overall cryptocurrency market, is undergoing a correction as traders are left apprehensive by the plummeting U.S. stock market; with Microsoft falling over by 4% in the opening hours of trading. Overnight, the value of cryptocurrencies started to experience a downward trend, with <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/ethereum/">Ethereum (ETH)</a> being the most negatively affected crypto asset in the top five currencies by <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/market-capitalization/">market cap</a>.</p>
<h2>Stocks Pull Crypto Market Down</h2>
<p>According to market data obtained at the time of writing, the overall <a href="https://coingape.com/markets">crypto market</a> decreased by 2.66%, bringing its value to $1.02 trillion. In addition, the total volume of trades executed fell by 0.82%, reaching almost $56.31 billion. Since the mid of December, there has been an increase in the degree to which <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/bitcoin/">Bitcoin&#8217;s</a> price and that of equities have correlated with one another. Today&#8217;s drop in <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/cryptocurrency-5/">cryptocurrency</a> prices follows a downward trend in equity markets as well. The last time correlations were this high was during the pre-FTX collapse era. Prominent crypto analysts too have voiced the same opinion and are finding this dip as an opportunity to re-enter the market.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">S&amp;P coming down, <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Bitcoin</a> comes down. </p>
<p>Easy play. </p>
<p>Waiting for my long fills to be hit.</p>
<p>&mdash; Michaël van de Poppe (@CryptoMichNL) <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoMichNL/status/1618262455528075265?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 25, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2>Crypto Stocks &amp; FOMC Meeting</h2>
<p>With all major indexes, such as the <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/sp500/">S&amp;P500</a> and Dow Jones falling over by 2% in the opening hours, Microsoft posted a fall of 4% while Amazon dipped roughly by 3% to $93 per share. Crypto-focused stocks were hit hard as well, with Silvergate dropping by 4.6% to $13. Although, the crypto-friendly bank saw its stock price surge early this week, today&#8217;s loss has given back majority of the gains it had made. Crypto giant <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/coinbase/">Coinbase</a> also witnessed a decline of 6.4% to $50, and <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/jack-dorsey/">Jack Dorsey&#8217;s</a> Block dropped by approximately 5.9% to $76. MicroStrategy&#8217;s stock price dropped by 4.5% shortly after the opening bell.</p>
<p><strong><em>Read More: </em></strong><a href="https://coingape.com/best-telegram-crypto-channels-list/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><em>Check Out The Top Crypto Telegram Channels Of 2023</em></a></p>
<p>Market participants are also divided on the upcoming <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/fomc/">FOMC</a> meeting scheduled to be held on the 1st of February. In a speech on January 20, Gov. Christopher Waller at the Council on Foreign Relations stated that he currently favors a 25 basis point increase at the next meeting. Other <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/federal-reserve-system/">Federal Reserve</a> officials have also made similar comments.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-136747" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/25215456/Screenshot-2023-01-25-215435.png" alt="" width="902" height="657" /></p>
<p><span id="inputElements~dce916a38741450f" class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-inherit css-1uk1gs8">As things stand, cryptocurrencies are taking a hit due to the falling prices in the traditional markets. Popular <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/meme-cryptocurrency/">memecoins</a> like <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/dogecoin/">Dogecoin</a> and <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/shiba-inu-shib/#:~:text=Shiba%20Inu%20is%20also%20called,group%20or%20individual%20called%20Ryoshi.">Shiba Inu</a>, both witnessed significant losses, with the former falling 5.1% and the latter falling by 6.2%. Other significant <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/altcoins/">altcoins</a>, including BNB, XRP and Cardano, also experienced price drops of over 4%. Whereas, crypto&#8217;s flagship asset&#8211;Bitcoin&#8211;witnessed a significant decline and is currently exchanging hands at $22,593.</span><span id="inputElements~821cca2d8e5ecb60" class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-inherit css-1uk1gs8"> This represents a decrease of 1.5% on the day, in contrast to a gain of 7% during the week as per CoinGape’s crypto market tracker.</span></p>
<p><em><strong>Also Read: </strong><a title="Coinbase Reveals 3 New Tokens To Get Listed Soon" href="https://coingape.com/coinbase-new-tokens-listing-roadmap/" rel="bookmark">Coinbase Reveals 3 New Tokens To Get Listed Soon</a></em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/top-reasons-why-crypto-market-is-falling-today/">Top Reasons Why Crypto Market Is Falling Today</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/25210608/0x0.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Prediction: $30k Or $15k, What&#8217;s Next For BTC Price?</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/markets/bitcoin-price-prediction-30k-or-15k-whats-next-for-btc-price/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brian Bollinger]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 16:42:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price prediction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?post_type=markets&#038;p=136746</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin Price Prediction: The Bitcoin price struggling to offer a follow-up rally of $22500 breakout suggests the exhausted bullish momentum. Moreover, the multiple higher-price rejections daily candles showcased a higher possibility of a minor pullback. Here&#8217;s how long this correction phase could extend, and should you buy it? Key points: A potential pullback in Bitcoin <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/markets/bitcoin-price-prediction-30k-or-15k-whats-next-for-btc-price/" title="Bitcoin Price Prediction: $30k Or $15k, What&#8217;s Next For BTC Price?"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/markets/bitcoin-price-prediction-30k-or-15k-whats-next-for-btc-price/">Bitcoin Price Prediction: $30k Or $15k, What&#8217;s Next For BTC Price?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="676" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/09111809/Bitcoin1.jpeg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Bitcoin Price" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Bitcoin Price Prediction: The <a href="https://coingape.com/price/bitcoin/">Bitcoin price</a> struggling to offer a follow-up rally of $22500 breakout suggests the exhausted bullish momentum. Moreover, the multiple higher-price rejections daily candles showcased a higher possibility of a minor pullback. Here&#8217;s how long this correction phase could extend, and should you buy it?</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Key points:</span></h2>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">A potential pullback in Bitcoin price could assist traders in recuperating the bullish momentum. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">A bullish crossover between the 50-and-100 EMA encourages additional buyers in the market.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The intraday trading volume in Bitcoin is $26.2 Billion, indicating a 2% gain</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><img decoding="async" class="alignnone" src="https://s3.tradingview.com/snapshots/z/zror2F5H.png" alt="Bitcoin Price Prediction" width="1946" height="1104" />Source-</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Tradingview</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Over the past two months, the Bitcoin price showcased a simple structure of a <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/rounding-bottom-pattern/">rounding bottom pattern</a>. This is one of the famous bullish patterns which is often spotted at market bottoms and displays a sign of sustained recovery in the market.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The U-shaped recovery visible in the daily chart has surged the BTC price to 36.7% higher since the beginning of 2023. On January 20th, the BTC price provided a massive breakout from the pattern&#8217;s neckline resistance of $21600 and local resistance of $22500.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This breakout should have accelerated the bullish momentum and extended the ongoing recovery, but instead, the Bitcoin price went sideways and hovered above the $22500 support. Over the past five days, the Bitcoin price showed several higher price rejections at the $23000 mark, indicating the birds are struggling to sustain breached levels.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">These rejection candles suggest profit booking from short-term traders, hinting at a higher possibility of price correction. Anyhow a minor consolidation or pullback could benefit Bitcoin price to neutralize the excessive buying since January 1st.</span></p>
<blockquote><p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/crypto-discord-groups-servers/">Top Crypto Discord Servers/Groups Worth Joining In 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This potential pullback could tumble the BTC price 4.5% down to retest the $21600 support.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">However, under the influence of the rounding bottom pattern, the post-correction rally could rise 25% higher to hit the $28150 resistance. Thus, if the buying pressure persists, the buyers could surpass this pattern to chase $30000. mark.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On a contrary note, the possible correction and daily candle closing below $21600 could weaken the bullish thesis.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Technical indicator</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><strong>RSI</strong>&#8211; The <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/rsi-relative-strength-index/">daily RSI slope</a> falling from the oversold region indicates the prices are in process of stabilizing the bullish trend.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><strong>EMAs</strong>:  the 20 and 200-day EMAs nearing a police crossover at the $21600 mark increase the support power of this level.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Bitcoin</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> Price Intraday Levels</span></h2>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Spot rate: $22851</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Trend: Bearish</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Volatility: High</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Resistance levels- $25000 and $28000</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Support levels- $22500 and $21500</span></li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/markets/bitcoin-price-prediction-30k-or-15k-whats-next-for-btc-price/">Bitcoin Price Prediction: $30k Or $15k, What&#8217;s Next For BTC Price?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/09111809/Bitcoin1.jpeg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Massive LUNC Tokens Burn By Terra Classic Validators</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/massive-lunc-tokens-burn-by-terra-classic-validators/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Varinder Singh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 15:12:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LUNC price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terra]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terra Classic]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=136738</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Terra Classic community has burned over 20 million LUNC tokens in a week amid the push to increase the burn rate. Validators and projects running on the Terra Classic network commit to burn millions of LUNC tokens after crypto exchange Binance temporarily suspended its LUNC burn mechanism until March. Terra Classic Validators Lead the Burns <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/massive-lunc-tokens-burn-by-terra-classic-validators/" title="Massive LUNC Tokens Burn By Terra Classic Validators"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/massive-lunc-tokens-burn-by-terra-classic-validators/">Massive LUNC Tokens Burn By Terra Classic Validators</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1280" height="720" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/23210244/lunc-1-1-e1671875694694.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Terra Classic (LUNC)" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" srcset="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/23210244/lunc-1-1-e1671875694694.jpg 1280w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/23210244/lunc-1-1-e1671875694694-300x169.jpg 300w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/23210244/lunc-1-1-e1671875694694-768x432.jpg 768w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/23210244/lunc-1-1-e1671875694694-1224x689.jpg 1224w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/23210244/lunc-1-1-e1671875694694-678x381.jpg 678w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/23210244/lunc-1-1-e1671875694694-150x84.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1280px) 100vw, 1280px" /><p>The Terra Classic community has burned over 20 million LUNC tokens in a week amid the push to increase the burn rate. Validators and projects running on the Terra Classic network commit to burn millions of LUNC tokens after <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/crypto-exchange-2" target="_blank" rel="noopener">crypto exchange</a> Binance temporarily <a href="https://coingape.com/breaking-binance-suspends-terra-classic-lunc-burn-lunc-price-falls/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">suspended its LUNC burn</a> mechanism until March.</p>
<h2>Terra Classic Validators Lead the Burns for Community</h2>
<p>CoinGape has been tracking the weekly burns by the Terra Classic community, believing in the revival of the Terra Classic as per the roadmap suggested by core developer Edward Kim. Also, the community plans to burn billions of LUNC tokens in 2023.</p>
<p>While the week still has a few days left, the community has already burned over 20 million LUNC tokens in the last 4 days. The LUNC burns have increased by almost 4 million week-over-week in January, indicating a move in the right direction.</p>
<p>The highest burn of the week came from <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/HappyCatKripto/status/1617988930489712640" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">validator</a> HappyCattyCrypto, which burned over 9 million LUNC tokens. It is followed by 7.2 million LUNC tokens burn by Cremation Coin, which aims to burn millions of tokens every week.</p>
<p>Validators LUNC DAO committed sent over 1.62 million LUNC tokens to the burn address. LUNC DAO is the fifth-largest contributor to the LUNC burn, with almost 435.79 million LUNC burned in total. The remaining burns came from members of the Terra Classic community including Yanis, a top contributor who sent 1 million tokens to the burn address.</p>
<p>Last week, the community burned over <a href="https://coingape.com/another-massive-lunc-tokens-burn-by-terra-classic-community/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">16 million LUNC tokens</a>, which was also a 4 million increase as compared to the earlier week’s <a href="https://coingape.com/terra-classic-community-burns-over-12-million-lunc-price-jumps/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">12 million LUNC tokens</a>.</p>
<h2>LUNC Community Approves Crucial Proposal</h2>
<p><a href="https://coingape.com/lunc-news-terra-classic-community-passes-proposal-to-bring-back-binance-burns/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Proposal 11310 by Terra Classic</a> core developer Edward Kim was unanimously passed by the Terra Classic community. The proposal aims to upgrade the <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/blockchain/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">blockchain</a> from v1.0.4 to v1.0.5 and introduces codes to make future upgrades possible.</p>
<p>It will also enable the Joint L1 Task Force to make necessary changes to bring back burn Binance LUNC burn mechanism. Binance may stop its LUNC burn mechanism if the Terra Classic community fails to make these changes.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, the LUNC price trades at $0.0001697, down over 5% in the last 24 hours.</p>
<p><strong>Also Read</strong>: <a href="https://coingape.com/will-crypto-miners-sell-their-btc-holdings-as-bitcoin-price-recovers" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Will Crypto Miners Sell Their BTC Holdings As Bitcoin Price Recovers?</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/massive-lunc-tokens-burn-by-terra-classic-validators/">Massive LUNC Tokens Burn By Terra Classic Validators</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/23210244/lunc-1-1-e1671875694694-1224x689.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Just In: DCG Owned Crypto Exchange Luno Lays Off 35% Of Employees</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/dcg-owned-crypto-exchange-luno-lays-off-35-of-employees/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Anvesh Reddy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 15:08:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DCG]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=136743</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Luno Layoff News: In yet another sign of continuing market contagion that began with the Genesis bankruptcy, a crypto exchange belonging to the Digital Currency Group (DCG) announced layoffs. The exchanges cited market turbulence for the decision to layoff around 35% of the company&#8217;s global headcount. This comes within a week after Consensys, the company <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/dcg-owned-crypto-exchange-luno-lays-off-35-of-employees/" title="Just In: DCG Owned Crypto Exchange Luno Lays Off 35% Of Employees"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/dcg-owned-crypto-exchange-luno-lays-off-35-of-employees/">Just In: DCG Owned Crypto Exchange Luno Lays Off 35% Of Employees</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="900" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/18212631/95521410.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="luno layoff" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p><strong>Luno Layoff News</strong>: In yet another sign of continuing market contagion that began with the Genesis bankruptcy, a crypto exchange belonging to the <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/dcg/">Digital Currency Group (DCG)</a> announced layoffs. The exchanges cited market turbulence for the decision to layoff around 35% of the company&#8217;s global headcount. This comes within a week after Consensys, the company behind <a href="https://coingape.com/metamask-creator-consensys-layoffs-workforce-due-reason/">MetaMask, announced reducing its staff count</a> due to market slowdown. However, in a relief to the crypto market that went through a bad year in 2022, the current rally is giving positive momentum.</p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/bitcoin-drops-for-the-second-consecutive-day-in-2023-is-the-party-over/?utm_source=24hrsupdateall">Bitcoin Drops for the Second Consecutive Day in 2023, Is The Party Over?</a></p>
<h2>DCG&#8217;s Luno Cuts Staff</h2>
<p>According to a <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/01/25/dcg-owned-crypto-exchange-luno-axes-35percent-of-staff.html" rel="nofollow">CNBC report</a>, the company&#8217;s move will affect more than 300 employees. Last week, crypto lender <a href="https://coingape.com/crypto-lender-genesis-filed-for-bankruptcy-amid-troubles/">Genesis Global filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy</a> protection, as it fell prey to the FTX led contagion. Luno&#8217;s latest move comes as yet another setback to the DCG, which is facing the heat due to the liquidity crisis. The crypto exchange, with around 900 employees, is based in London. The company&#8217;s CEO, Marcus Swanepoel, said,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;2022 has been an incredibly tough year for the broader tech industry and in particular the crypto market. Luno unfortunately hasn’t been immune to this turbulence, which has affected our overall growth and revenue numbers.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/will-crypto-miners-sell-their-btc-holdings-as-bitcoin-price-recovers/?utm_source=priceanalysisbar">Will Crypto Miners Sell Their BTC Holdings As Bitcoin Price Recovers?</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/dcg-owned-crypto-exchange-luno-lays-off-35-of-employees/">Just In: DCG Owned Crypto Exchange Luno Lays Off 35% Of Employees</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/18212631/95521410.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Top 5 Altcoins That May Skyrocket In 2023</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/markets/top-5-altcoins-that-may-skyrocket-in-2023/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brian Bollinger]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 14:51:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Aave Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano price analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polkadot Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP price analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?post_type=markets&#038;p=136740</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Top 5 Altcoins That May Skyrocket In 2023: The recent growth in the majority of cryptocurrencies since January 1st has created a sense of recovery sentiment in the crypto market. Thus, amid this recovery, we are picking up the top crypto coins which are following the famous bullish pattern called the falling wedge. Under the <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/markets/top-5-altcoins-that-may-skyrocket-in-2023/" title="Top 5 Altcoins That May Skyrocket In 2023"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/markets/top-5-altcoins-that-may-skyrocket-in-2023/">Top 5 Altcoins That May Skyrocket In 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="630" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/27023300/ALTCOINS1.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Atlcoins doge" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Top 5 Altcoins That May Skyrocket In 2023: The recent growth in the majority of cryptocurrencies since January 1st has created a sense of recovery sentiment in the crypto market. Thus, amid this recovery, we are picking up the top crypto coins which are following the famous bullish pattern called the <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/wedge-pattern/">falling wedge.</a> Under the influence of this pattern, the selected coins could witness massive gains in 2023.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">About The Falling Wedge Pattern</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This pattern displays itself when an asset price is wobbling between two converging trend lines. With these trendline extending downwards, this pattern often showcases an established downtrend and provide a discount opportunity to market participants. Furthermore, the most common outcome of the pattern is a bullish breakout from the resistance trendline, triggering a fresh recovery rally. This breakout signals a switch in market sentiment from selling in rallies to buying on dips. In addition, the lower high formation during this pattern also acts as a potential target upon breakout.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ethereum(ETH)</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><img decoding="async" src="https://s3.tradingview.com/snapshots/s/s0KrhsGx.png" alt="TradingView Chart" />Source- Tradingview</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">With the recent recovery, the <a href="https://coingape.com/price/ethereum/">Ethereum coin price</a> shows a strong green candle in the monthly time frame chart, This bullish candle breaks the long-coming trendline of the wedge pattern hinting at an early sign of trend reversal.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The ETH price currently trades at the $1558 mark and is discounted 68.12% from the all-time high of $4891. Thus, with sustained buying, the coin price should chase the potential targets of $2140, $3630, and $4680.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ripple(XRP)</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><img decoding="async" src="https://s3.tradingview.com/snapshots/8/8hwxMyaP.png" alt="TradingView Chart" />Source- Tradingview</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The <a href="https://coingape.com/price/xrp-price/">Ripple(XRP) coin price</a> has been wobbling within the wedge pattern for nearly two years. Amid the new year recovery, the price shows a breakout attempt from the pattern trendline, which could ring a recovery opportunity for XRP holders.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The coin price currently trades at the $0.4 mark and is 89.37% down from All time high of $3.84. Thus, a monthly candle closing above the downsloping will accelerate the bullish momentum and offer an entry opportunity for sidelined buyers. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Under the influence of a wedge pattern, the potential target for XRP price could be $0.56, $0.936, $1.36, or $1.9.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Cardano(ADA)</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><img decoding="async" src="https://s3.tradingview.com/snapshots/b/bMheaVvO.png" alt="TradingView Chart" />Source- Tradingview </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In response to the falling wedge pattern, the <a href="https://coingape.com/price/cardano/">Cardano coin price</a> showcased a steady downtrend for the past seven months, On January 12th, the Cardano coin price offered a bullish breakout from the long coming trendline, offering an entry opportunity for sidelined traders. So far, the post-retest rally has surged the coin price 12% higher to currently trade at the $0.36 mark.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Furthermore, if the buying pressure persists, the coin price could rise to the $0.43, $0.58, or $0.67 mark.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Polkadot(DOT)</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><img decoding="async" src="https://s3.tradingview.com/snapshots/m/M8scu27T.png" alt="TradingView Chart" />Source- Tradingview </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The <a href="https://coingape.com/price/polkadot/">Polkadot coin price</a> currently exchanges hands at $6.27 and is discounted 88.6% from an all-time high of $55.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On January 14th, the prices provided a massive breakout from the pattern resistance trendline and pushed the post-retest to rally 17% higher to hit the local resistance of $6.7.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Anyhow, in response to the wedge pattern breakout, the prices could extend the bull run to $7.3, $9.6, or $11.8.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Aave(AAVE)</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><img decoding="async" src="https://s3.tradingview.com/snapshots/r/RKfdO9eM.png" alt="TradingView Chart" />Source- Tradingview </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The <a href="https://coingape.com/price/aave/">AAVE price</a> monthly chart showcases one of the textbook examples of a falling pattern. The coin price has been resonating within this pattern for nearly two years and has tumbled its market value by 87.77%.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The recent recovery in the crypto market bolstered coin buyers to breach the pattern’s resistance trendline, suggesting an upcoming recovery in AAVE price.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This altcoin currently trades at the $81 mark and provides potential targets of $114, $250, $425, or $584.</span></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/markets/top-5-altcoins-that-may-skyrocket-in-2023/">Top 5 Altcoins That May Skyrocket In 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/27023300/ALTCOINS1.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Breaking: Bithumb&#8217;s Owner Faces Arrest Over These Charges</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/bithumb-exchange-owner-faces-arrest/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pratik Bhuyan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 14:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bithumb]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=136713</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bithumb, a cryptocurrency exchange with headquarters in South Korea, has recently attracted the attention of the tax and regulatory authorities. And, as per latest reports, prosecutors have asked for an arrest warrant to be issued for 41-year-old Mr. Kang Jong-hyeon, who is reported to be the real owner of the crypto exchange. The investigation into <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/bithumb-exchange-owner-faces-arrest/" title="Breaking: Bithumb&#8217;s Owner Faces Arrest Over These Charges"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/bithumb-exchange-owner-faces-arrest/">Breaking: Bithumb&#8217;s Owner Faces Arrest Over These Charges</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="720" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/25182911/5079.png" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Bithumb owner arrest" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p><a href="https://coingape.com/tag/bithumb/">Bithumb</a>, a cryptocurrency exchange with headquarters in South Korea, has recently attracted the attention of the tax and regulatory authorities. And, as per latest <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://news.einfomax.co.kr/news/articleView.html?idxno=4251784" rel="nofollow">reports</a>, prosecutors have asked for an arrest warrant to be issued for 41-year-old Mr. Kang Jong-hyeon, who is reported to be the real owner of the crypto exchange. The investigation into allegations of embezzlement by the core executives of the exchange is being conducted by the prosecution.</p>
<h2>Bithumb Owner Faces Arrest</h2>
<p>According to members of the legal community, on the 25th, the Seoul Southern District Prosecutor&#8217;s Office of Financial Investigation handed down sentences to Kang and two executives of Bithumb affiliates on charges of misappropriation of funds and breach of trust under the Act of Aggravated Punishment of Specific Economic Crimes as well as fraudulent illegal transactions under the Capital Markets Act.</p>
<p><em><strong>Read More:</strong> <a title="Is Bitcoin (BTC) Price Heading For $46K After This Massive Breakout?" href="https://coingape.com/bitcoin-btc-price-heading-for-46k-massive-breakout/" rel="bookmark">Is Bitcoin (BTC) Price Heading For $46K After This Massive Breakout?</a></em></p>
<p>Kang is the older brother of Kang Ji-yeon, who serves as the CEO of two firms affiliated with Bithumb called Inbiogen and Bucket Studio. It is believed that Kang played a significant part in the scheme to artificially inflate the share prices of Bithumb affiliate companies (Inbiogen and Bucket Studio) by issuing convertible bonds. The conditions under which Kang stole corporate money or manipulated stock prices were seized by the prosecutors, and in October of last year, the prosecutors seized and searched one after another of Bithumb&#8217;s affiliates such as Vident, Inbiogen, and Bucket Studio.</p>
<h2>Bithumb&#8217;s Growing Concerns</h2>
<p>With a stake worth 34.2% in Bithumb Holdings, Vidente is the single largest shareholder in the company. Inbiogen, on the other hand, holds the majority stake in Vident, while Bucket Studio appears to be the majority stake in Inbiogen. According to a prior report that was <a href="https://coingape.com/breaking-bithumb-exchange-faces-second-investigation-in-a-row/">published</a> on CoinGape, near the close of the year before, the body of the Vice President of Vidente was found outside the front yard of his home. The method of death was determined to be &#8220;suspected suicide&#8221; by the police after an investigation.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-136739" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/25193012/Screenshot-2023-01-25-192813.png" alt="" width="1595" height="562" /></p>
<p>Bithumb has also seen a significant drop in trading volume in recent months following the legal turmoil. Once, the second-largest <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/crypto-exchange-2/">crypto exchange</a> in South Korea, Bithumb has gradually been replaced by the likes of Coinone, Korbit, and Upbit. Recently, investigators also raised concerns about the irregularities found on taxes filed by Bithumb Korea, Bithumb Holdings, and its affiliates.</p>
<p><em><strong>Also Read: </strong><a title="Revealed: Top 5 Cryptos With Highest Development Activity" href="https://coingape.com/top-5-cryptos-with-highest-development-activity/" rel="bookmark">Revealed: Top 5 Cryptos With Highest Development Activity</a></em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/bithumb-exchange-owner-faces-arrest/">Breaking: Bithumb&#8217;s Owner Faces Arrest Over These Charges</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/25182911/5079.png" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>How This Ontario Man Lost Everything In Crypto Scam?</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/web-stories/how-this-ontario-man-lost-everything-in-crypto-scam/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Divya Sinha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 13:33:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?post_type=web-story&#038;p=136732</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[		<div class="wp-block-web-stories-embed alignnone">
			<a href="https://coingape.com/web-stories/how-this-ontario-man-lost-everything-in-crypto-scam/">
									<img
						src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/26161535/Poster-Image-99.jpg"
						width="360"
						height="600"
						alt="How This Ontario Man Lost Everything In Crypto Scam?"
																			sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"
												loading="lazy"
						decoding="async"
					/>
								</a>
		</div>
		]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[		<div class="wp-block-web-stories-embed alignnone">
			<a href="https://coingape.com/web-stories/how-this-ontario-man-lost-everything-in-crypto-scam/">
									<img
						src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/26161535/Poster-Image-99.jpg"
						width="360"
						height="600"
						alt="How This Ontario Man Lost Everything In Crypto Scam?"
																			sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"
												loading="lazy"
						decoding="async"
					/>
								</a>
		</div>
		]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/26161535/Poster-Image-99.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Shadow Fork Goes Live: Here Are 7 Things You Can&#8217;t Miss</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/ethereum-shadow-fork-goes-live-here-are-7-things-you-need-to-know-10018/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Coingape Staff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 13:30:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=136694</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum Shadow fork Goes Live: Users of the world’s second-largest blockchain, Ethereum, are one step closer to accessing the $26 billion worth of ETH. On Monday, developers of Ethereum said they have deployed the first mainnet shadow fork in preparation for the Shanghai upgrade in March. Here are the 7 Things to Know about Ethereum <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/ethereum-shadow-fork-goes-live-here-are-7-things-you-need-to-know-10018/" title="Ethereum Shadow Fork Goes Live: Here Are 7 Things You Can&#8217;t Miss"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/ethereum-shadow-fork-goes-live-here-are-7-things-you-need-to-know-10018/">Ethereum Shadow Fork Goes Live: Here Are 7 Things You Can&#8217;t Miss</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/25154904/Ethereum-Shadow-fork.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p><strong>Ethereum Shadow fork Goes Live:</strong> Users of the world’s second-largest <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/blockchain/">blockchain</a>, Ethereum, are one step closer to accessing the $26 billion worth of ETH. On Monday, developers of <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/ethereum/">Ethereum</a> said they have deployed the first mainnet shadow fork in preparation for the <a href="https://coingape.com/shanghai-upgrade-will-enable-stake-withdrawals-but-theres-a-catch/">Shanghai upgrade</a> in March.</p>
<h2>Here are the 7 Things to Know about Ethereum Shadow Fork</h2>
<p>1. According to <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/vdWijden?ref_src=twsrc%5Egoogle%7Ctwcamp%5Eserp%7Ctwgr%5Eauthor" rel="nofollow">Marius Van Der Wijden</a>, a software developer at the Ethereum Foundation, there were a few minor glitches on Geth clients — software used by nodes to operate the blockchain — but the team managed to resolve them and the shadow fork was applied successfully.</p>
<p>2. Ethereum shadow fork is a copy of the blockchain used to run tests before creating the public testnet. It will allow developers to test the waters before the upcoming Shanghai upgrade. The public testnet for Shanghai will go live in the coming days.</p>
<p>3. The Shanghai upgrade will be the first major update since Ethereum’s historic merge in September. The <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/ethereum-merge/">Ethereum merge</a> introduced the ability for users to deposit ETH with the network to become validators and help authenticate on-chain transactions.</p>
<p>4. There is some concern within the crypto industry that once the Shanghai upgrade goes live there will be increased sell pressure on the token from the sudden availability of 16 million unlocked Ether.</p>
<p><strong>Read More</strong>: <a href="https://coingape.com/blog/5-ethereum-stocks-to-indirectly-reap-the-benefits-of-ethers-surge/">5 Ethereum stocks to Indirectly Reap the Benefits of Ether’s Surge</a></p>
<p>5. <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/vitalik-buterin/">Vitalik Buterin</a>, Ethereum’s founder and current CEO, proposed the implementation of a feature he named “Stealth Addresses.” In an article, while highlighting the difficulty of ensuring privacy in the ecosystem, Buterin stated: “Fixing this state of affairs is a serious topic.”</p>
<p>6. Impact of Ethereum shadow fork: the argument against that is that 16 million Ether represents only 13.2% of the total circulating supply of the cryptocurrency. This upgrade will allow the around 16 million staked into the network to be unlocked, according to Etherscan.</p>
<p>7. Some Ethereum Devs Opposed the Rushed Upgrade: While most people are looking forward to the launch of Shanghai, a handful of Ethereum developers remain opposed to it. They believe that the unstaking of ETH is acceding to public demands and not so much about the long-term health of Ethereum.</p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/top-7-ethereum-ecosystem-tokens-you-can-add-portfolio-next-week-10001/">Top 7 Ethereum Ecosystem Tokens to Add in Your Portfolio Next Week</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/ethereum-shadow-fork-goes-live-here-are-7-things-you-need-to-know-10018/">Ethereum Shadow Fork Goes Live: Here Are 7 Things You Can&#8217;t Miss</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/25154904/Ethereum-Shadow-fork.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>5 Reasons Why Bitcoin (BTC) Price Risks Falling Below $21,500</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/just-in-reasons-why-bitcoin-btc-price-rally-is-likely-over/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Varinder Singh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 13:13:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European central bank]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[U.S. Federal Reserve]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=136474</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin price witnessed a marvelous 40% rally in January as traders expect a turnaround of events. The BTC price hit a high of $23,282 last week, marking a 5-month high despite the FTX contagion that continues to impact the market sentiment. Bitcoin price currently trades at $22.8K, trading sideways in the last two days. The <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/just-in-reasons-why-bitcoin-btc-price-rally-is-likely-over/" title="5 Reasons Why Bitcoin (BTC) Price Risks Falling Below $21,500"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/just-in-reasons-why-bitcoin-btc-price-rally-is-likely-over/">5 Reasons Why Bitcoin (BTC) Price Risks Falling Below $21,500</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/20175759/bitcoin4.jpeg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Reasons Why Bitcoin (BTC) Price Rally Is Likely Over" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p>Bitcoin price witnessed a marvelous 40% rally in January as traders expect a turnaround of events. The BTC price hit a high of $23,282 last week, marking a 5-month high despite the <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/ftx" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a> contagion that continues to impact the market sentiment.</p>
<p>Bitcoin price currently trades at $22.8K, trading sideways in the last two days. The 24-hour low and high for Bitcoin are $22,387 and $23,056, respectively. While analysts expect Bitcoin price to hit $25k this month, the rally may not happen.</p>
<p><strong>Also Read</strong>: <a href="https://coingape.com/bitcoin-btc-price-to-hit-25k-or-21k-whats-next/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin (BTC) Price To Hit $25K or $21K, What’s Next?</a></p>
<h2>5 Reasons Why Bitcoin (BTC) Price Hitting $25K Is Unlikely</h2>
<p>Here are the reasons why the Bitcoin rally is likely over and the BTC price may not hit $25k this month.</p>
<h3>1. European Central Bank Monetary Tightening</h3>
<p>The European Central Bank plans to deliver 50 bps interest rate hikes in the next two meetings in February and March. ECB President Christine Lagarde asserts the need for further tightening and revising rate hike targets to bring down inflation.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the European Parliament&#8217;s Economic Affairs Committee votes on a draft law seeking banks offering crypto services to hold more capital to manage risks from crypto assets.</p>
<h3>2. US Federal Reserve FOMC Meeting</h3>
<p>The U.S. <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/federal-reserve-system/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Federal Reserve</a> to announce a rate hike in the next FOMC meeting on February 1. While the <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/consumer-price-index-cpi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CPI</a> and jobs data signal a smaller rate hike, economists expect another 50 bps rate hike. Invests may have to wait a little longer for the Fed pivot.</p>
<p>As per <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://www.cmegroup.com/markets/interest-rates/cme-fedwatch-tool.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">CME FedWatch Tool</a>, the probability of a 25 bps rate hike is 97.2%. The reading has decreased from the last day as investors await the fourth-quarter GDP data due on Thursday.</p>
<p>Bitcoin price stabilizes below $23k ahead of the ECB and U.S. Fed rate hike decision. Thus, traders are unlikely to take any decision before these events.</p>
<h3>3. US Dollar Index Volatility</h3>
<p>The U.S. dollar index (<a rel='nofollow'  href="https://www.marketwatch.com/investing/index/dxy" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">DXY</a>) will continue to show volatility ahead of the importance week. The DXY currently moves below 102 and is likely to jump higher ahead of the rate hike decision by the U.S. Federal Reserve.</p>
<p>A rise in DXY will make the Bitcoin price to dive lower and bring a correction in the broader crypto market. Moreover, the recent policy decision by Japan and European Union have weakened the US dollar and the Fed will most likely thwart it.</p>
<h3>4. The Bitcoin Fear and Greed Index Plunges</h3>
<p><a href="https://coingape.com/blog/what-is-crypto-fear-and-greed-index-how-does-it-work/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin Fear and Greed Index</a> is neutral at 50. The index has dropped in the last few days as traders anticipate a decline in Bitcoin price due to possibilities of profit-taking and &#8220;sell the news&#8221; strategy.</p>
<p>While the BTC price is in an early <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/bull-market/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">bull market</a>, traders are unlikely to trade in the current market conditions.</p>
<h3>5. Bitcoin Technical Indicators Signal Strong Resistance</h3>
<p>Bitcoin price is trading above the 200-day moving average (DMA). Analysts expect a move to 200-WMA, which is near $25k.</p>
<p>In the daily timeframe, Bollinger Bands breakout to subdue in the coming days and Bitcoin price can fall below $21,500. Moreover, the RSI is moving in the overbought zone and is likely to fall lower. Other indicators also signal a decline in Bitcoin price.</p>
<figure id="attachment_136736" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-136736" style="width: 733px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img decoding="async" class=" wp-image-136736" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/25185715/BTCUSDT_2023-01-25_18-56-43.png" alt="Bitcoin price" width="733" height="446" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-136736" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Price in Daily Timeframe. Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p><strong>Also Read</strong>: <a href="https://coingape.com/5-on-chain-indicators-signals-bitcoin-entering-bull-market-cycle/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Here&#8217;s When Bitcoin Bull Market Cycle Starts</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/just-in-reasons-why-bitcoin-btc-price-rally-is-likely-over/">5 Reasons Why Bitcoin (BTC) Price Risks Falling Below $21,500</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/20175759/bitcoin4.jpeg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Tops BSC Whales’ This List; Is XRP Price Pump On The Way?</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/xrp-news-xrp-tops-bsc-whales-this-list-is-price-pump-on-the-way/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ashish Kumar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 13:08:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Xrp price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP vs SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=136702</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>XRP News: XRP, Ripple’s native token price took a hit on Wednesday after riding over a good upward momentum in reaction to the recent updates coming out of the XRP lawsuit. However, the crypto whales have used this price drop in order to add more. Whales buy XRP price dip As per the data provided <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/xrp-news-xrp-tops-bsc-whales-this-list-is-price-pump-on-the-way/" title="XRP Tops BSC Whales’ This List; Is XRP Price Pump On The Way?"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/xrp-news-xrp-tops-bsc-whales-this-list-is-price-pump-on-the-way/">XRP Tops BSC Whales’ This List; Is XRP Price Pump On The Way?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/08175304/22_20220906_140233_0013.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="XRP lawsuit price news" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p><strong>XRP News:</strong> XRP, Ripple’s native token price took a hit on Wednesday after riding over a good upward momentum in reaction to the recent updates coming out of <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/ripple-xrp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">the XRP lawsuit.</a> However, the crypto whales have used this price drop in order to add more.</p>
<h2>Whales buy XRP price dip</h2>
<p>As per the data provided by the WhaleAlert, Crypto whales have moved more than 128 million XRP (approx worth $53 million) in multiple transactions over the past 24 hours. The single biggest transaction recorded has been of dumping 35 million XRP (approx worth $15 million) on the Bitstamp crypto exchange.</p>
<p>However, the whale addresses have dumped more than 68 million XRP (approx worth $28 million) over the past day. <a href="https://coingape.com/price/xrp-price/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">XRP price</a> have dropped by 4% in the same period of time. While its 24 hour trading has also declined by 25% to stand at $1.19 billion. <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/ripple-xrp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>Read More XRP News Here&#8230;</strong></a></p>
<p>Several crypto whales have utilized this price dip opportunity in order to add more XRP. As per the data, whales have accumulated around 60.2 million XRP tokens (approx worth $25 million) in the last 24 hours. The <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/whale_alert/status/1618027256802168832" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">biggest accumulation transaction recorded</a> by the tracker has been of adding 30.2 million XRP (approx worth $13 million).</p>
<h2>What&#8217;s BSC whales&#8217; doing?</h2>
<p>WhaleStats reported that Ripple’s native token emerged as the most traded token among the top 100 BSC whales. XRP dislodged Cake token in order to gain the top spot. As we dig in, data shows that the top 100 whales are holding more than $28.6 million worth of XRP which makes 2.5% of their total holdings.</p>
<p>XRP price surged by a whopping 16% in the last 24 hours. It is trading at an average price of $0.406, at the press time.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/xrp-news-xrp-tops-bsc-whales-this-list-is-price-pump-on-the-way/">XRP Tops BSC Whales’ This List; Is XRP Price Pump On The Way?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/08175304/22_20220906_140233_0013.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is ChatGPT A Google Killer?</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/is-chatgpt-a-google-killer/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Coingape Staff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 13:02:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ChatGPT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[google]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=136700</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Google is much more than just a search engine these days, it has evolved into how most people access the internet. But as artificial intelligence takes over the world, the most widely used search engine appears to be worried. Not just people are concerned about AI; Google has allegedly issued a &#8220;red code&#8221; regarding an <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/is-chatgpt-a-google-killer/" title="Is ChatGPT A Google Killer?"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/is-chatgpt-a-google-killer/">Is ChatGPT A Google Killer?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="627" height="418" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/25171459/ChatGPT-is-a-Google-Killer.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="ChatGPT" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p>Google is much more than just a search engine these days, it has evolved into how most people access the internet. But as artificial intelligence takes over the world, the most widely used search engine appears to be worried. Not just people are concerned about <strong><a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/artificial-intelligence/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">AI</a></strong>; Google has allegedly issued a &#8220;red code&#8221; regarding an <strong><a href="https://coingape.com/blog/what-is-chatgpt-3-why-it-has-become-so-popular/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">AI chatbot</a></strong>.</p>
<h2><b>ChatGPT could revolutionize search</b></h2>
<p><strong><a href="https://coingape.com/blog/is-chatgpt-the-new-google-how-crypto-traders-may-benefit-from-it/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ChatGPT</a></strong> and other language models may have an impact on search engines by making information more easily accessible in a way that feels more natural to users. This might make it simpler for individuals to locate the data they require, particularly if they are unfamiliar with the particular terminology or syntax necessary for conventional search queries.</p>
<p>ChatGPT may also improve search results by making them more precise and pertinent. However, by comprehending the purpose and context of a user&#8217;s query. This may be particularly helpful for more intricate or nuanced queries, for which it may be difficult for traditional search algorithms to comprehend the user&#8217;s requirements.</p>
<p><strong>Also Read:<a href="https://coingape.com/blog/chatgpt-alternative-5-best-chatgpt-ai-alternatives-cant-miss-in-2023/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"> ChatGPT Alternative: 5 Best ChatGPT AI Alternatives Can’t Miss In 2023</a></strong></p>
<h3><b>Web3 is the internet&#8217;s next evolution</b></h3>
<p>The core principles of <strong><a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/web-3-0/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Web3</a></strong> are privacy, decentralization, and zero trust. Blockchain technologies will be crucial to achieving many of the goals of the upcoming internet. With AI, <strong><a href="https://coingape.com/top-5-indian-web3-companies-to-look-out-for-in-2023/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Web3 projects</a></strong> can be more effective and functional at scale.</p>
<p>Web3 is still in its infancy, and difficulties prevent its widespread adoption. Between users who are knowledgeable about <strong><a href="https://coingape.com/what-is-web3-and-why-should-you-care/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Web3 and the rest of us</a></strong>, there is a communication gap. However, early <strong><a href="https://coingape.com/decentralization-will-build-a-better-internet-for-all/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Web1 and Web2</a></strong> also experienced this. Before users fully adopt Web3, if at all, it is likely to happen in fits and starts.</p>
<h2><b>ChatGPT may replace Google</b></h2>
<p>ChatGPT still has limitations as they are in the early stages of development. They might be unable to comprehend all questions or always give precise answers. It&#8217;s important to take into account any ethical ramifications of using language models to produce search results, such as the potential for the dissemination of inaccurate or biased information.</p>
<p>Even though ChatGPT and other language models do not directly compete with <strong><a href="https://coingape.com/tag/google/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Google</a></strong> Search, they have the potential to alter how users access and interact with information online. It will be crucial to carefully weigh the advantages and disadvantages of utilizing these technologies in search and other applications as they develop.</p>
<p><strong>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/education/the-sandbox-game-discover-sand-metaverse-play-and-earn-nft-rewards/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">The Sandbox Game: Discover SAND Metaverse; Play and Earn NFT Rewards</a></strong></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/is-chatgpt-a-google-killer/">Is ChatGPT A Google Killer?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/25171459/ChatGPT-is-a-Google-Killer.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dormant Whale Moves Over 2 Billion Dogecoin (DOGE), Price Dump Coming?</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/dormant-whale-moves-over-2-billion-dogecoin-doge-price-dump-coming/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Varinder Singh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 13:01:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto whale]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogecoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=136714</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Dogecoin witnessed a 30% rally in January amid the recovery in the crypto market. However, a market-wide selloff in the last two days has also led to a slight pullback in DOGE price. Moreover, whales have been selling meme coin DOGE due to decreased interest among traders, with Shiba Inu attracting the most attention amid <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/dormant-whale-moves-over-2-billion-dogecoin-doge-price-dump-coming/" title="Dormant Whale Moves Over 2 Billion Dogecoin (DOGE), Price Dump Coming?"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/dormant-whale-moves-over-2-billion-dogecoin-doge-price-dump-coming/">Dormant Whale Moves Over 2 Billion Dogecoin (DOGE), Price Dump Coming?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="675" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/23115041/Dogecoin-1.jpeg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Dormant Whale Moves Over 2 Billion Dogecoin (DOGE), Price Dump Coming?" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p>Dogecoin witnessed a 30% rally in January amid the recovery in the crypto market. However, a market-wide selloff in the last two days has also led to a slight pullback in DOGE price. Moreover, <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/whale-accumulation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">whales</a> have been selling meme coin DOGE due to decreased interest among traders, with Shiba Inu attracting the most attention amid the <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/shibarium" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Shibarium</a> Beta release.</p>
<h2>Dogecoin Whale Moves Billions in DOGE to Binance</h2>
<p>According to Whale Alert, a whale <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/whale_alert/status/1618206876390359040" target="_blank" rel="noopener">transferred</a> 1,400,000,004 Dogecoin (DOGE) tokens worth $117.53 million to crypto exchange Binance on January 25.</p>
<p>Within five minutes, the whale transfers 985,000,236 DOGE tokens worth $82.66 million from Binance to its wallet.</p>
<p>On-chain data revealed that the whale purchased 1,400,000,000 DOGE tokens on May 23 last year. Since then, the wallet has been dormant. The whale suddenly became active after 7 months and traded DOGE tokens on the day of Tesla&#8217;s quarterly earnings.</p>
<p>While whales have become active after the recent sharp market recovery, a lack of interest from Dogecoin fan <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/elon-musk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Elon Musk</a> in integrating the meme coin into Twitter has caused selloffs by whales. Moreover, dormant whale transactions generally indicate an upcoming fall in prices.</p>
<p>Traders expected a market-wide fall in crypto prices as there was <a href="https://coingape.com/bitcoin-btc-price-to-hit-25k-or-21k-whats-next/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">no significant pullback in Bitcoin</a> and <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/ethereum" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a> prices.</p>
<p>Dogecoin (DOGE) price fell over 5% in the last 24 hours, with the price currently trading at $0.08457. The 24-hour low and high are $0.08245 and $0.08919, respectively. Furthermore, the trading volume has declined by 10% in the last 24 hours, indicating a decrease in interest among traders.</p>
<p><strong>Also Read</strong>: <a href="https://coingape.com/lunc-news-terra-classic-community-passes-proposal-to-bring-back-binance-burns" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Terra Classic Community Passes Proposal To Bring Back Binance Burns</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/dormant-whale-moves-over-2-billion-dogecoin-doge-price-dump-coming/">Dormant Whale Moves Over 2 Billion Dogecoin (DOGE), Price Dump Coming?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/23115041/Dogecoin-1.jpeg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dogecoin (DOGE) Ready For Rally Ahead Of Tesla Quarterly Earnings?</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/dogecoin-doge-rally-tesla-quarterly-earnings/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Anvesh Reddy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 12:48:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin (DOGE)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elon Musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Meme Coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=136712</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Dogecoin (DOGE) News: Dogecoin whales are accumulating the memecoin as it takes a trajectory of fluctuation ahead of the Tesla Q4 earnings release. It may be recalled that during the second quarter earnings call, Elon Musk said Tesla did not sell any of the DOGE holdings. The automaker is owning Dogecoin with the sale of <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/dogecoin-doge-rally-tesla-quarterly-earnings/" title="Dogecoin (DOGE) Ready For Rally Ahead Of Tesla Quarterly Earnings?"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/dogecoin-doge-rally-tesla-quarterly-earnings/">Dogecoin (DOGE) Ready For Rally Ahead Of Tesla Quarterly Earnings?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="630" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/27124033/musk-et-dogecoin.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Dogecoin (DOGE) Tesla" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p><strong>Dogecoin (DOGE) News</strong>: Dogecoin whales are accumulating the <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/meme-cryptocurrency/">memecoin</a> as it takes a trajectory of fluctuation ahead of the Tesla Q4 earnings release. It may be recalled that during the second quarter earnings call, Elon Musk said Tesla did not sell any of the DOGE holdings. The automaker is owning Dogecoin with the sale of Tesla merchandise as it accepts payments in DOGE. Meanwhile, it remains to be seen how the cryptocurrency will react to the earnings report.</p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/dogecoin-whales-scoops-over-500m-doge-price-to-rally-over-0-1-again/">Dogecoin Whales Scoops Over 500M DOGE, Price To Rally Over $0.1 Again?</a></p>
<h2>Tesla Quarterly Earnings</h2>
<p>The fourth quarter earnings are set to be released in context of three consecutive instances where the company missed targets. Also, the electric carmaker announced price cuts for Chinese customers in October 2022. Even if Tesla goes on to announce positive momentum in terms of car sales, it remains to be seen if the figures would trigger TSLA share price rise. In this context, the DOGE price could also be up for significant reaction to the earnings report.</p>
<p>As of writing, the DOGE price stands at $0.08485, down 4.65% in the last 24 hours, according to <a href="https://coingape.com/price/dogecoin/">CoinGape price tracker</a>. The meme cryptocurrency is currently ranked 9th based on total market cap at $11.20 billion. In addition to this, <a href="https://coingape.com/markets/heres-the-dogecoin-price-analysis-guide-for-the-coming-week/">technical indicators</a> are also pointing towards a potential price rise. A breakout from the $0.09 resistance range could well mean a DOGE price rise as much as 22%. Whether the Tesla earnings could lead to the breakout remains to be seen.</p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/bitcoin-drops-for-the-second-consecutive-day-in-2023-is-the-party-over/?utm_source=24hrsupdateall">Bitcoin Drops for the Second Consecutive Day in 2023, Is The Party Over?</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/dogecoin-doge-rally-tesla-quarterly-earnings/">Dogecoin (DOGE) Ready For Rally Ahead Of Tesla Quarterly Earnings?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/27124033/musk-et-dogecoin.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>&#8220;Musk&#8217;s Twitter Can Access Any Account Using GodMode&#8221; Whistleblower</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/web-stories/musks-twitter-can-access-any-account-using-godmode-whistleblower/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Javed]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 11:58:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?post_type=web-story&#038;p=136705</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[		<div class="wp-block-web-stories-embed alignnone">
			<a href="https://coingape.com/web-stories/musks-twitter-can-access-any-account-using-godmode-whistleblower/">
									<img
						src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/05152803/Poster-Image-2023-01-05T152754.877.jpg"
						width="360"
						height="600"
						alt="&#8220;Musk&#8217;s Twitter Can Access Any Account Using GodMode&#8221; Whistleblower"
																			sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"
												loading="lazy"
						decoding="async"
					/>
								</a>
		</div>
		]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[		<div class="wp-block-web-stories-embed alignnone">
			<a href="https://coingape.com/web-stories/musks-twitter-can-access-any-account-using-godmode-whistleblower/">
									<img
						src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/05152803/Poster-Image-2023-01-05T152754.877.jpg"
						width="360"
						height="600"
						alt="&#8220;Musk&#8217;s Twitter Can Access Any Account Using GodMode&#8221; Whistleblower"
																			sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"
												loading="lazy"
						decoding="async"
					/>
								</a>
		</div>
		]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/05152803/Poster-Image-2023-01-05T152754.877.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Will Crypto Miners Sell Their BTC Holdings As Bitcoin Price Recovers?</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/will-crypto-miners-sell-their-btc-holdings-as-bitcoin-price-recovers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Varinder Singh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 11:37:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Miners]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ki Young Ju]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=136693</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto miners are back on track after facing challenges including debt and high-energy prices for almost a year as Bitcoin price skyrockets almost 40% in January. Crypto mining firms are turned on their machines back to bring a necessary lifeline to their cash-strapped businesses. As a result, crypto mining stocks have on average jumped 100% this <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/will-crypto-miners-sell-their-btc-holdings-as-bitcoin-price-recovers/" title="Will Crypto Miners Sell Their BTC Holdings As Bitcoin Price Recovers?"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/will-crypto-miners-sell-their-btc-holdings-as-bitcoin-price-recovers/">Will Crypto Miners Sell Their BTC Holdings As Bitcoin Price Recovers?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="814" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/17180842/Bitcoin-mining-6-e1653307843986.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Will Crypto Miners Sell Their Bitcoin Holdings As BTC Price Recovers?" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p>Crypto miners are back on track after facing challenges including debt and high-energy prices for almost a year as Bitcoin price skyrockets almost 40% in January. <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/crypto-mining/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Crypto mining</a> firms are turned on their machines back to bring a necessary lifeline to their cash-strapped businesses. As a result, crypto mining stocks have on average jumped 100% this month.</p>
<h2>Crypto Miners Seek Financial Recovery</h2>
<p>Risks of crypto miner capitulation declined significantly amid the market recovery in January. Bitcoin price rallied over $23,500, recording a nearly 40% recovery from lows.</p>
<p>According to data from Hashrate Index, the average <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/hash-rate/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">hashrate</a> or the computing power directed towards mining bitcoin rose to a record 280 exahash on January 20 when Bitcoin price jumped over $23,500.</p>
<p>The rise in hashrate indicates an uptick in crypto mining activity. Thus, it signals a recovery in the crypto mining industry after facing challenges including debt and high-energy prices for almost a year.</p>
<p>On-chain data shows an increase in transactions and the creation of new blocks in the <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/blockchain/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">blockchain</a>. Several crypto mining firms took the opportunity of the bear market to purchase mining rigs for low prices or buy new energy-efficient mining machines at discounts. However, one of the largest miners <a href="https://coingape.com/breaking-core-scientific-filing-for-chapter-11-bankruptcy-in-texas-today/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Core Scientific failed</a> to withstand the pressure and filed for bankruptcy on December 21.</p>
<p>&#8220;The sentiment among miners is better than in a long time. For many bankruptcy threatened players, the sudden increase in the bitcoin price is a lifeline,&#8221; said Jaran Mellerud, an analyst at Hashrate Index.</p>
<p>Share prices of listed companies including Marathon Digital Holdings, which soared 171% this month, and Hut 8, which climbed 150%. Other such as HIVE Blockchain Technologies, Riot Platforms, and Bitfarms soared 122%, 80%, and 197%, respectively.</p>
<p><strong>Also Read</strong>: <a href="https://coingape.com/top-crypto-mining-stocks-to-buy-in-2023/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Top Crypto Mining Stocks To Buy In 2023</a></p>
<h2>Tech Giants To Rescue Crypto Miners?</h2>
<p>Despite running mining rigs at full capacity, mining companies are still experiencing financial troubles due to reasons such as high-energy prices, taxes, and regulatory pressure.</p>
<p>CryptoQuant CEO Ki Young Ju hopes that TradeFi or tech giants acquire U.S. crypto mining firms at a discount this year.</p>
<p><strong>Also Read</strong>: <a href="https://coingape.com/popular-analysts-predicts-further-fall-in-ethereum-price-to-this-level" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Popular Analyst Predicts Further Fall In Ethereum Price To This Level</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/will-crypto-miners-sell-their-btc-holdings-as-bitcoin-price-recovers/">Will Crypto Miners Sell Their BTC Holdings As Bitcoin Price Recovers?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/17180842/Bitcoin-mining-6-e1653307843986.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
