<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 16:16:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>JPMorgan Warns of Potential Economic Downturn for UK, Says Interest Rates Could Surge to 7%</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-uk-interest-rates/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-uk-interest-rates/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 16:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bank of england]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[boe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[inflation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[interest rate]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jpmorgan chase]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261994</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-uk-interest-rates/">JPMorgan Warns of Potential Economic Downturn for UK, Says Interest Rates Could Surge to 7%</a></p>
<p>The potential increase in interest rates would have wide-ranging implications for the UK economy.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-uk-interest-rates/">JPMorgan Warns of Potential Economic Downturn for UK, Says Interest Rates Could Surge to 7%</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-uk-interest-rates/">JPMorgan Warns of Potential Economic Downturn for UK, Says Interest Rates Could Surge to 7%</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/jpmorgan-chase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">JPMorgan Chase &amp; Co</a> (NYSE: JPM), a renowned global financial institution, has <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/07/06/boe-could-hike-interest-rates-to-7percent-in-some-scenarios-jpmorgan.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">issued</a> a warning of a potential economic downturn for the United Kingdom (UK). While the bank expects interest rates to peak at 5.75% by November, it warns that rates could climb even higher under certain scenarios, reaching as much as 7%.</p>
<p>The proposed move by the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/bank-of-england/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bank of England</a> (BoE) to hike interest rates reflects its commitment to maintaining price stability and addressing the potential threats posed by rising inflationary pressures. Alongside its counterpart in other developed countries, the BOE has been hiking interest rates as its major tool to fight headline inflation.</p>
<p>In December, the Bank of England hiked interest rates by 50 basis points to 3.5% and experts believe the bank will raise interest rates again when it meets next. JPMorgan Economist Allan Monks suggests that the BoE may need to raise rates above current forecasts to ensure that real interest rates turn positive and interrupt the wage-price spiral.</p>
<h2>Rising Costs and Financial Strain</h2>
<p>Inflation is a complex economic phenomenon characterized by a long-term rise in the general price level of goods and services within an economy. In the UK, official May figures showed a strong annual price increase of 8.7%, exceeding experts’ expectations and notably exceeding the BoE target of 2%.</p>
<p>Consequently, British consumers are facing increasing financial difficulty as necessary items such as food, energy, and mortgages continue to rise.</p>
<p>These escalating costs place a huge strain on consumers’ budgets, limiting their capacity to maintain their desired living standards. These rising expenses have ramifications for household budgets and discretionary spending.</p>
<h2>Challenges Ahead of the BoE</h2>
<p>During an interview with BBC, BoE Governor Andrew Bailey <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-inflation-first-time-august-2022/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">acknowledged</a> the challenges faced by individuals amidst rising inflation. Bailey recognized that people were being forced to make tough choices about their purchases due to the current economic environment. He, however, emphasized that the BoE is committed to bringing inflation back to the desired level.</p>
<p>It is worth noting that the potential increase in interest rates would have wide-ranging implications for the UK economy. On the one hand, such a step could assist to keep inflation under control by decreasing consumer spending and borrowing. Higher interest rates frequently lead to lower consumer borrowing and investment, which can help to alleviate pricing pressures.</p>
<p>However, an interest rate hike of this magnitude may also introduce challenges. It has the potential to raise borrowing costs for both enterprises and individuals, potentially depressing economic activity. Higher interest rates may also have an impact on housing markets, as mortgage rates can rise, impacting both homeowners and potential purchasers.</p>
<p>Ultimately, the BoE faces the challenging task of finding the delicate balance between addressing inflationary pressures and maintaining sustainable economic growth. While the proposed interest rate increase might help combat inflation, experts advocate cautious implementation to avoid stifling economic recovery.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uae-leading-bitcoin-mining-hub/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-uk-interest-rates/">JPMorgan Warns of Potential Economic Downturn for UK, Says Interest Rates Could Surge to 7%</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-uk-interest-rates/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>UAE Emerges as Leading Bitcoin Mining Hub in Middle East</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/uae-leading-bitcoin-mining-hub/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/uae-leading-bitcoin-mining-hub/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 13:51:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261968</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uae-leading-bitcoin-mining-hub/">UAE Emerges as Leading Bitcoin Mining Hub in Middle East</a></p>
<p>The UAE recently opened the biggest nuclear power plant in the Arab world, with a total capacity of 4 gigawatts, and is gearing up for expansion later this year.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uae-leading-bitcoin-mining-hub/">UAE Emerges as Leading Bitcoin Mining Hub in Middle East</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uae-leading-bitcoin-mining-hub/">UAE Emerges as Leading Bitcoin Mining Hub in Middle East</a></p>
<p>The United Arab Emirates (UAE) is establishing itself as a key destination for <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> (BTC) mining in the Middle East. With its pro-Web3 ecosystem, abundant energy resources, tax advantages, and business-friendly environment, the country offers an appealing choice for miners seeking growth and profitability.</p>
<p>In a lengthy Twitter <a href="https://twitter.com/JMellerud/status/1676652814401937447?t=fD6gI66UYksw9XEuT_TPdA&amp;s=19" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">thread</a> on July 5, Jaran Mellerud, a business development associate at Luxor and crypto mining expert, gave insight on the latest developments in the UAE mining sector. According to him, the partnership between Zero Two, a blockchain infrastructure provider and a subsidiary of Abu Dhabi&#8217;s sovereign wealth fund, and the US-based mining firm Marathon Digital in May 2023 began the country&#8217;s journey into the global mining scheme.</p>
<p>Both companies partnered to launch two mining sites in Abu Dhabi. These facilities, equipped with a combined capacity of 250 megawatts (MW), will be powered by excess energy from Abu Dhabi grids, ensuring sustainability and efficiency. Earlier in 2021, Zero Two partnered with the local mining firm Phoenix Technology to strengthen its presence in the country.</p>
<h2>UAE Combined Mining Capacity Estimated to Reach 400MW</h2>
<p>As a significant player in the energy market, the UAE has proactively shifted its focus from traditional fossil fuels to renewable energy sources. Solar and nuclear power have emerged as key pillars in the country&#8217;s energy transition. The surplus of energy generated from these sustainable sources presents an opportunity for Bitcoin miners to tap into clean energy and contribute to the country&#8217;s green initiatives.</p>
<p>The West Asian country recently opened the biggest nuclear power plant in the Arab world, with a total capacity of 4 gigawatts, and is gearing up for expansion later this year. The expansion aims to increase the influx of nuclear energy demand for flexibility.</p>
<p>Mellerud revealed in the tweets that the UAE&#8217;s Bitcoin mining capacity is estimated to be around 400 MW, accounting for approximately 4% of the global hash rate. While countries like the United States, China, Russia, and Kazakhstan dominate the hash rate leaderboard, the UAE&#8217;s abundant resources and favorable environment position it as a rising contender in the global mining landscape.</p>
<p>He further noted that the country&#8217;s mining capacity could surpass 600 MW by the end of this year as the semi-governmental projects expand.</p>
<h2>Tax Advantages and Regulatory Environment</h2>
<p>Mellerud said one significant advantage for Bitcoin miners in the UAE is the country&#8217;s zero tax policy and lack of regulation regarding mining activities. Miners can register their operations in one of the UAE&#8217;s more than 30 free trade zones, enabling them to avoid corporate tax, value-added tax (VAT), and import duties.</p>
<p>This tax haven status provides a competitive edge for miners in the global mining industry, allowing them to optimize their financials and enhance profitability.</p>
<p>Aside from the 0% tax on Bitcoin mining activities, the country also has zero taxation on crypto gains, unlike other nations such as India, which imposed a 30% tax on all digital assets earnings.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-shares-dip-bullish-start/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uae-leading-bitcoin-mining-hub/">UAE Emerges as Leading Bitcoin Mining Hub in Middle East</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/uae-leading-bitcoin-mining-hub/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase Shares Dip despite Bullish Start to This Week</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-shares-dip-bullish-start/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-shares-dip-bullish-start/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 13:47:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wall Street]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blackrock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261954</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-shares-dip-bullish-start/">Coinbase Shares Dip despite Bullish Start to This Week</a></p>
<p>At the beginning of the week, Coinbase generated significant buzz with its announcement of potential collaborations with several asset managers.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-shares-dip-bullish-start/">Coinbase Shares Dip despite Bullish Start to This Week</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-shares-dip-bullish-start/">Coinbase Shares Dip despite Bullish Start to This Week</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase Global Inc</a> (NASDAQ: COIN), one of the world&#8217;s leading crypto exchanges, experienced a decline in its shares on Wednesday, dropping nearly 2% despite an initially optimistic start to the week.</p>
<p>According to a Bloomberg <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-07-05/coinbase-downgraded-as-analyst-says-crypto-limbo-dims-revenue-outlook" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a>, the company experienced a decline in its shares and closed at almost 2% lower at $78.35 per share. The drop was primarily attributed to a recent downgrade by analysts at Piper Sandler. Remarkably, this setback comes despite Coinbase Exchange&#8217;s significant year-to-date appreciation, with the stock notably surging by 133% since the beginning of the year.</p>
<h2>Coinbase Shares Receive Analyst Downgrade</h2>
<p>Coinbase Exchange&#8217;s journey has been marked by regulatory hurdles, particularly with the recent US Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) lawsuit.</p>
<p>While the company has managed to mitigate some of its losses following the lawsuit announcement, concerns, and uncertainty lingers. The legal action by the SEC has created an environment of ambiguity for Coinbase, impacting analysts&#8217; ability to forecast future revenues with confidence.</p>
<p>In a recent note to investors, Piper Sandler analyst Patrick Moley downgraded his recommendation on Coinbase shares from overweight to neutral. Moley&#8217;s revised stance comes as he expects the exchange&#8217;s second-quarter trading volumes and monthly active user totals to hit their lowest levels in over two years.</p>
<p>Notably, Piper Sandler is not the first to express concern about the regulatory constraints surrounding Coinbase. Last week, broker firm Berenberg also warned that the stock&#8217;s sharp surge in June could be short-lived after investors flocked in following the application for a spot Bitcoin <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-bitcoin-exchange-traded-fund-etf/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Exchange-Traded Fund</a> (ETF) by investment giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/blackrock/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BlackRock Inc</a> (NYSE: BLK).</p>
<p>At the beginning of the week, Coinbase generated significant buzz with its <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/blackrock-coinbase-spot-bitcoin-etf/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">announcement</a> of potential collaborations with several asset managers. The proposed partnerships aimed to introduce spot Bitcoin ETFs to the market, providing investors with a regulated and accessible way to invest in the premier digital currency.</p>
<h2>Legal Proceedings and Implications</h2>
<p>The SEC&#8217;s lawsuit against Coinbase revolves around the exchange&#8217;s trading of unregistered securities and the merging of functions that are traditionally separated within securities markets. The regulatory body is scrutinizing Coinbase&#8217;s operations and seeking to enforce compliance with securities regulations in a bid to protect investors.</p>
<p>According to an earlier <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-coinbase-case-july-13/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">report</a>, the long-awaited court hearing between crypto exchange Coinbase and SEC has been scheduled to hold on the 13th of July. Coinbase&#8217;s defense strategy, which involved submitting its initial response ahead of the August 7th deadline, prompted the rescheduling of the court date from August to July.</p>
<p>The rescheduled court date indicates the progress of the Coinbase-SEC legal battle and the increasing momentum toward a trial, if necessary. The legal clash between the exchange and the regulatory authority carries significant implications for the crypto industry, as the outcome could potentially shape future regulations and standards.</p>
<p>The court proceedings will shed light on the alleged unregistered securities trading and the merging of functions within Coinbase&#8217;s operations, as mentioned in the SEC&#8217;s lawsuit. The case will determine the extent to which crypto exchanges must comply with existing securities regulations.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-hits-new-2023-high/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-shares-dip-bullish-start/">Coinbase Shares Dip despite Bullish Start to This Week</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-shares-dip-bullish-start/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Hits New 2023 High Not Seen in 13 Months</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-hits-new-2023-high/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-hits-new-2023-high/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 12:58:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blackrock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cboe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261952</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-hits-new-2023-high/">Bitcoin Hits New 2023 High Not Seen in 13 Months</a></p>
<p>The price of Bitcoin could continue its way upwards as the SEC mulls spot ETF applications, leading to a new 2023 high for the king coin.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-hits-new-2023-high/">Bitcoin Hits New 2023 High Not Seen in 13 Months</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-hits-new-2023-high/">Bitcoin Hits New 2023 High Not Seen in 13 Months</a></p>
<p>Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a>), the largest cryptocurrency by market cap, has hit a new high not seen in 13 months. On Thursday, Bitcoin climbed over 3% and hit $31,500, its highest point of 2023 so far. However, BTC has fallen as of press time and is trading around $31,200 on a 2.45% 24-hour increase.</p>
<p>The price of Bitcoin has been relatively healthy in recent times following multiple applications for spot Bitcoin ETFs. At the moment, the general sentiment is that the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) could approve an application this year. Many believe that the application for iShare Bitcoin Trust ETF by <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/blackrock/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BlackRock</a> (NYSE: BLK) would likely cinch the regulator’s approval.</p>
<p>Rachel Lin, the CEO of decentralized derivatives protocol SynFutures, is optimistic about Bitcoin’s chance of upward movement. Highlighting the king coin’s resilience in the $30,000 to $31,000 support range, Lin <a href="https://www.barrons.com/articles/bitcoin-ethereum-price-crypto-markets-today-9b8174de" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Bitcoin’s current trend indicates an encouraging uptrend phase, now trading at the $31,000 resistance level. Price projections for Bitcoin point towards an upward trajectory if the price can remain above the current level, potentially breaching the immediate $32,400 resistance.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>However, Lin adds that a correction all the way to $27,500 could happen if BTC falls below $29,500.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin’s New 2023 High Spurred by ETF Hopefuls</h2>
<p>The SEC has received a few spot Bitcoin ETF applications over the last few weeks. So far, WisdomTree, Invesco, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/fidelity-investments/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Fidelity Investments</a>, ARK Invest, Valkyrie, Bitwise, and BlackRock have all submitted filings. While the application is BlackRock’s first, others like ARK Invest, WisdomTree, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/grayscale/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Grayscale Investments</a>, and Vaneck have had their applications previously rejected.</p>
<p>To date, the SEC has rejected all spot Bitcoin ETF applications ever submitted since Gemini founders Tyler and Cameron Winklevoss submitted the first one in 2013. The SEC turns down these applications each time, stating that they contain inadequate measures to prevent market manipulation and fraud. These rejections are now the basis of a <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/grayscale-lawsuit-sec-bitcoin-spot-etf-bid-rejection/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">lawsuit</a> between <a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2022/06/30/2471737/0/en/Grayscale-Investments-Initiates-Lawsuit-Against-the-SEC.html">Grayscale and the SEC</a> after the Commission rejected its application. Grayscale CEO Michael Sonnenshein said he “vehemently disagrees” with the rejection.</p>
<p>Bitcoin’s new 2023 high and projected uptrend stems from the increase in spot ETF applications and the sentiment suggesting an approval, likely for BlackRock. Recently, Bloomberg senior ETF analyst Eric Balchunas gave BlackRock a <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fidelity-spot-bitcoin-etf-blackrock/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">50% chance of approval</a> for a few reasons, including Grayscale’s chance of a win. Bloomberg’s Intelligence analyst Elliott Stein had estimated that Grayscale has a 70% chance of winning its lawsuit against the SEC after an oral argument in court that won judges to Grayscale’s side.</p>
<p>Another reason for BlackRock’s possible win is an amendment of its iShares application. The asset management giant recently added a surveillance-sharing agreement (SSA) to address the SEC’s market manipulation concerns. The agreement will involve other players and require information sharing for transparency and fraud prevention. Not long after, the Cboe BZX Exchange <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cboe-ark-bitcoin-etf/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">imitated</a> BlackRock and also amended its ARK 21Shares to include an SSA.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/metaverse-strategy-european-governance/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-hits-new-2023-high/">Bitcoin Hits New 2023 High Not Seen in 13 Months</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-hits-new-2023-high/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Leaked Metaverse Strategy of European Union Includes Regulatory Sandbox &amp; Governance Structure</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/metaverse-strategy-european-governance/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/metaverse-strategy-european-governance/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 12:55:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Virtual Reality & Augmented Reality News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[european law commission]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nft]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261959</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/metaverse-strategy-european-governance/">Leaked Metaverse Strategy of European Union Includes Regulatory Sandbox &#038; Governance Structure</a></p>
<p>The European Commission said that it seeks to explore the potential of digital cooperation models, which includes the decentralized autonomous organizations (DAOs) underpinning different financial applications. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/metaverse-strategy-european-governance/">Leaked Metaverse Strategy of European Union Includes Regulatory Sandbox &#038; Governance Structure</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/metaverse-strategy-european-governance/">Leaked Metaverse Strategy of European Union Includes Regulatory Sandbox &#038; Governance Structure</a></p>
<p>A recently leaked paper from the European Commission highlights how Metaverse would require a new kind of global governance in order to continue to stay open and lawful.</p>
<p>Popular crypto publication <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/07/06/eus-leaked-metaverse-strategy-proposes-regulatory-sandbox-new-global-governance/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">CoinDesk</a> had access to the draft document that proposes relaxing regulations to boost innovation. Furthermore, the draft document notes that it wants to address the legal barriers to new forms of digital cooperation such as the decentralized autonomous organizations (DAOs).</p>
<p>Citing the benefits of education, healthcare, and culture, a version of the draft document talks about “Virtual worlds bring unprecedented opportunities in many societal areas. This technological shift also involves new forms of global governance.”</p>
<p>The document emphasizes the importance of international collaboration on various subjects like technological standards, identity management, censorship, and surveillance. It highlights the need to shape the future of the internet as an open and secure space that aligns with EU values and regulations.</p>
<p>Referring to the global bodies addressing today&#8217;s online world such as the Internet Corporation for Assigned Names and Numbers (ICANN), the document notes: “The Commission will support the creation of a technical multi-stakeholder governance process to address essential aspects of virtual worlds and Web4 that are beyond the remit of existing internet governance institutions.&#8221;</p>
<h2>European Law Commission and Crypto</h2>
<p>The European Law Commission has been seriously working around building frameworks and structures for the crypto industry. A week back, the UK Law Commission <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-commission-proposals-digital-euro/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">proposed</a> the government develop laws governing cryptocurrencies and ensure that the UK becomes a global hub for digital assets and non-fungible tokens (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NFTs</a>).</p>
<p>By the end of 2023, the Commission said that it seeks to explore the potential of digital cooperation models. This typically includes the decentralized autonomous organizations (DAOs) that underpin novel financial applications. As a result, they would carry out a study to “identify legal, administrative, and economic barriers that prevent their uptake.”</p>
<p>According to the document, in the early part of next year, the promotion of &#8220;regulatory sandboxes&#8221; will be initiated to test short-term projects under a more relaxed regulatory framework. The paper also highlights concerns about the dominance of large &#8220;gatekeeper&#8221; companies that may hinder competition from smaller rivals, as well as the threat of counterfeit goods that can undermine brand integrity.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/circle-asia-japanese-stablecoin-issuance/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/metaverse-strategy-european-governance/">Leaked Metaverse Strategy of European Union Includes Regulatory Sandbox &#038; Governance Structure</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/metaverse-strategy-european-governance/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Circle Explores Expansion in Asia, Eyes Japanese Market for Stablecoin Issuance</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/circle-asia-japanese-stablecoin-issuance/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/circle-asia-japanese-stablecoin-issuance/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Temitope Olatunji]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 11:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[circle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jeremy allaire]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[progmat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[usd coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[usdc]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261914</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/circle-asia-japanese-stablecoin-issuance/">Circle Explores Expansion in Asia, Eyes Japanese Market for Stablecoin Issuance</a></p>
<p>Even though Circle already offers USD Coin (USDC), its co-founder and CEO Jeremy Allaire believes that introducing a Yen-linked stablecoin would provide new opportunities.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/circle-asia-japanese-stablecoin-issuance/">Circle Explores Expansion in Asia, Eyes Japanese Market for Stablecoin Issuance</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/circle-asia-japanese-stablecoin-issuance/">Circle Explores Expansion in Asia, Eyes Japanese Market for Stablecoin Issuance</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/circle/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Circle</a>, the company that issues <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/usd-coin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">USDC (USD coin)</a>, a stablecoin linked to the United States dollar, is now interested in strengthening its presence in Asia. The company&#8217;s co-founder and CEO <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/jeremy-allaire/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Jeremy Allaire</a> is considering issuing stablecoins in Japan after visiting the country in June.</p>
<p>Allaire&#8217;s interest in Japan is coming after Japan implemented stablecoin legislation that allows and governs the use of stablecoin in the country and beyond. He believes that if stablecoins gain widespread adoption for international and cross-border trades, then Japan could be a major market for digital assets, especially because the new stablecoin regulation is already putting Japan ahead of many countries.</p>
<p>In an interview with Japan Posts English, Allaire <a href="https://japan.postsen.com/local/79001/Stablecoin-US-Circle-Starts-Considering-Issuance-in-Japan-CEO-Interview--CoinDesk-JAPAN--CoinDesk-Japan.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">stated</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“As a global company, we want to grow in large markets around the world. USDC is already used in 190 countries. Japan has a long history of cross-border trade, foreign currency transactions, and global commerce. If stablecoins become more widely used for such purposes, we believe that Japan will become an extremely large market.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Japan is the first country among major economies in the world to have a structured and clear law that governs the use of stablecoins. According to the law, the stablecoins in the country have to be pegged to the Japanese Yen or another major currency that serves as a reserve asset and must guarantee redemption to the holders at face value. The law also allows only trusted and licensed agents to issue the stablecoin. The entities include banks licensed in the country and registered money transfer agents.</p>
<p>Although the company will have to comply with the tough rules stated in the Japanese Act, Allaire is interested in the partnership. He sees the move by the Japanese government as an important one which opens the door for his company to partner toward the goal of a digital financial system.</p>
<h2>Circle Has Continued to Expand Its Stablecoin Services to Many Regions</h2>
<p>Circle is a regulated digital asset and money transfer company in the United States. The company was recently registered and regulated in Singapore as a money transfer company that can issue digital currencies and transfer money across borders. It is also working on getting authorization in Europe as a digital asset provider. Its interest in the Japanese market is obviously part of a larger move to spread its services to many countries around the world.</p>
<p>Even though the company has USDC, the CEO believes that a Yen-linked stablecoin would provide new opportunities. The company seeks to continue to grow and provide the necessary financial infrastructure to facilitate the growth of the digital financial system.</p>
<p>Some other financial institutions in the country are also expressing interest in using stablecoins. One is <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/mufg-bank/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Mitsubishi UFJ Trust</a>, which announced its desire to launch its own stablecoin platform, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/mufg-stablecoin-progmat-blockchain/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Progmat</a>, where interested organizations can mint their stablecoins. Although MUFJ didn&#8217;t announce the plan to create its own stablecoin, the move will facilitate other institutions&#8217; easy creation of stablecoin.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/mastercard-ai-fraud-detection-tool-banks/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/circle-asia-japanese-stablecoin-issuance/">Circle Explores Expansion in Asia, Eyes Japanese Market for Stablecoin Issuance</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/circle-asia-japanese-stablecoin-issuance/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mastercard Implements AI Fraud Detection Tool in Nine UK Banks to Prevent APP Scams</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/mastercard-ai-fraud-detection-tool-banks/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/mastercard-ai-fraud-detection-tool-banks/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 11:31:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FinTech News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mastercard]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tsb]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261928</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/mastercard-ai-fraud-detection-tool-banks/">Mastercard Implements AI Fraud Detection Tool in Nine UK Banks to Prevent APP Scams</a></p>
<p>TSB, one of the nine banks, said the Mastercard AI tool has increased its APP fraud detection ability by 20%.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/mastercard-ai-fraud-detection-tool-banks/">Mastercard Implements AI Fraud Detection Tool in Nine UK Banks to Prevent APP Scams</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/mastercard-ai-fraud-detection-tool-banks/">Mastercard Implements AI Fraud Detection Tool in Nine UK Banks to Prevent APP Scams</a></p>
<p>American multinational financial services corporation <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/mastercard/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Mastercard Inc</a> (NYSE: MA) has created a new AI tool that helps detect fraudulent transactions and has shipped the tool off to a few banks.</p>
<p>Mastercard calls its AI tool the Consumer Fraud Risk system and has already installed it in nine UK banks in the UK. Some include Bank of Scotland Plc, Lloyds Banking Group Plc, and Natwest Group Plc.</p>
<p>According to a Bloomberg <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-07-05/mastercard-s-ai-tool-helps-nine-british-banks-tackle-scams/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a>, Mastercard trained its AI tool using years of transaction data. This training allows the tool to predict customer attempts to move funds that may be flagged for authorized push payment (APP) scams. These scams fraudulently convince a person to transfer money to an account feigning legitimacy. Fraudsters may create accounts and pretend they belong to a business, known friend, or family member.</p>
<p>According to Mastercard’s president of cyber and intelligence, many APP (authorized push payments) scams are difficult to tackle because they involve transfers legitimately completed by the account owners. Bhalla says Mastercard considers this a “huge problem” because since the transfers are legit, they pass security checks deployed to detect other fraudulent schemes like unauthorized payments.</p>
<h2>How the Mastercard AI Tool Works</h2>
<p>Mastercard’s AI tool scouts all attempted transfers by customers. The Consumer Fraud Risk system designates each attempt with a risk score from 0 to 999 in less than a second. Aided by its own analysis and the AI tool, a bank can block a potential transaction in time.</p>
<p>Mastercard created the tool using extensive work with banks. For five years, the payment processor has collaborated with banks to study how fraudsters move funds between banks. These scammers use this method to complicate or conceal fraudulent activity. Using this information, Mastercard noticed certain patterns and several accounts that may increase the risk of fraudulent behavior and used these data to train the AI tool.</p>
<p>The Bloomberg report states that TSB Banking Group Plc is the first institution to install the system. Since the implementation four months ago, the bank’s ability to detect this type of fraud has increased by 20%. TSB predicts that banks in the UK can save £100 million every year upon full industry adoption of Mastercard’s AI tool. According to the bank’s head of fraud Paul Davis, “it’s a good example of the power of sharing data. It’s the first time we’ve been able to see both sides of the payment &#8211; sending and receiving.”</p>
<h2>Banking Fraud Stats</h2>
<p>Online fraud prevention platform Seon highlighted the cost of fraud in a <a href="https://seon.io/resources/global-banking-fraud-index/#h-costs-of-fraud" target="_blank" rel="noopener">June publication</a>. According to Seon, there was a 4.2% increase in the overall cost of fraud per dollar for all US retail services, including banks. The report puts specific fraud losses from bank payments at nearly $1.6 billion. In addition, Seon states that every $1 of fraud costs $4.23.</p>
<p>Another <a href="https://blog.gitnux.com/bank-fraud-statistics/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a> states that APP fraud in the UK hit £479 million in 2020, with online banking fraud climbing 64% in 2019. The report also mentions that 47% of all UK bank fraud cases happened through remote banking channels. It adds that the average loss to the victim at £600 per case.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/blackrock-ceo-larry-fink-bitcoin/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/mastercard-ai-fraud-detection-tool-banks/">Mastercard Implements AI Fraud Detection Tool in Nine UK Banks to Prevent APP Scams</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/mastercard-ai-fraud-detection-tool-banks/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>BlackRock CEO Larry Fink Says Bitcoin Has Potential to Revolutionize Finance</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/blackrock-ceo-larry-fink-bitcoin/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/blackrock-ceo-larry-fink-bitcoin/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mercy Tukiya Mutanya]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 11:14:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funds & ETFs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blackrock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[larry fink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261909</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/blackrock-ceo-larry-fink-bitcoin/">BlackRock CEO Larry Fink Says Bitcoin Has Potential to Revolutionize Finance</a></p>
<p>Fink believes that a spot Bitcoin ETF has the potential to be as revolutionary for the financial sector in general as traditional ETFs were for the mutual fund industry.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/blackrock-ceo-larry-fink-bitcoin/">BlackRock CEO Larry Fink Says Bitcoin Has Potential to Revolutionize Finance</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/blackrock-ceo-larry-fink-bitcoin/">BlackRock CEO Larry Fink Says Bitcoin Has Potential to Revolutionize Finance</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/blackrock/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BlackRock</a> CEO Larry Fink on Wednesday, July 5, stated that crypto, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> in particular, has the potential to revolutionize the financial system. This was during an <a href="https://www.foxbusiness.com/media/blackrock-fink-wont-mention-esg-anymore-been-weaponized-left-right" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">interview</a> with Fox Business to discuss the asset manager’s recent spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) filing with the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>).</p>
<p>Fink was previously in opposition of the cryptocurrency, decrying its potential for use in “illicit activities”. That stance has recently shifted, with the CEO calling Bitcoin an “international asset” and revealing that BlackRock intends to make it cheaper and more convenient to invest in the top cryptocurrency. Fink hopes that regulators will view the recent ETF filings as a way to “democratize crypto”.</p>
<p>The asset management firm, which reported over $9 trillion in assets under management in the first quarter of 2023, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-2023-high-blackrock-etf/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">filed for a spot Bitcoin ETF </a>on June 16 through its iShares unit. The filing prompted a host of other firms to present their own applications for a similar product with the regulator. The flurry of activity resulted in green charts for the cryptocurrency which surged by over 12% in June and is currently up over 85% year-to-date according to <a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/investing/cryptocurrency/btcusd" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">MarketWatch data</a>. The asset manager also tagged Coinbase Global Inc. for market surveillance.</p>
<p>“We do believe that if we can create more tokenization of assets and securities – that’s what Bitcoin is – it could revolutionize finance,” he said during the interview, adding: “Instead of investing in gold as a hedge against inflation, a hedge against the onerous problems of any one country, or the devaluation of your currency whatever country you’re in – let’s be clear, Bitcoin is an international asset, it’s not based on any one currency and so it can represent an asset that people can play as an alternative.”</p>
<p>Fink believes that a spot Bitcoin ETF has the potential to be as revolutionary for the financial sector in general as traditional ETFs were for the mutual fund industry. It remains unclear when the SEC will announce its decision on the filing.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/unhappy-staff-binance-coinbase-gemini/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/blackrock-ceo-larry-fink-bitcoin/">BlackRock CEO Larry Fink Says Bitcoin Has Potential to Revolutionize Finance</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/blackrock-ceo-larry-fink-bitcoin/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Unhappy Staff: Binance, Coinbase, and Gemini Rank Low in Job Satisfaction</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/unhappy-staff-binance-coinbase-gemini/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/unhappy-staff-binance-coinbase-gemini/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 10:59:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[animoca brands]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitmain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brian armstrong]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gemini]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[moonpay]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ripple]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261917</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/unhappy-staff-binance-coinbase-gemini/">Unhappy Staff: Binance, Coinbase, and Gemini Rank Low in Job Satisfaction</a></p>
<p>Companies like Circle, Ripple, and the non-fungible tokens (NFTs) marketplace OpenSea have happier employees.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/unhappy-staff-binance-coinbase-gemini/">Unhappy Staff: Binance, Coinbase, and Gemini Rank Low in Job Satisfaction</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/unhappy-staff-binance-coinbase-gemini/">Unhappy Staff: Binance, Coinbase, and Gemini Rank Low in Job Satisfaction</a></p>
<p>Employee happiness is a crucial aspect of any industry, and the cryptocurrency space is no exception. However, recent data derived from Glassdoor indicates that staff satisfaction at popular crypto exchanges such as <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/gemini/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Gemini</a>, Binance, and Coinbase is relatively low.</p>
<p>The tech recruitment firm TrueUp <a href="https://www.trueup.io/crypto/trends#layoffs" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">collected</a> data from Glassdoor to assess employee happiness and growth in 27 prominent crypto firms. The results were presented in a quadrant chart, which revealed that bankrupt crypto lender Celsius, digital assets trading platform Amber Group, and virtual asset service provider Gemini had the least happy employees based on reviews from 80, 139, and 42 individuals, respectively. Binance and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase</a> were also positioned on the left side of the chart, indicating lower employee satisfaction, with a total of 1,257 <a href="https://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Gemini-Reviews-E1400858.htm" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reviews</a>.</p>
<p>It is important to note that Glassdoor does not provide a specific happiness metric. Instead, it evaluates employee sentiment through indicators such as the likelihood of recommending the company, approval of the CEO, and overall outlook. These metrics offer valuable insights into employee satisfaction within the crypto industry and serve as a basis for further analysis.</p>
<p>In the past year, Coinbase CEO <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/brian-armstrong/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Brian Armstrong</a> responded strongly to employees expressing dissatisfaction, suggesting they should consider quitting. The response came after a group of staff filed a petition calling for the removal of certain executives, including chief operating officer Emilie Choi, chief product officer Surojit Chatterjee, and chief people officer LJ Brock, citing unrealistic demands from the executives as the reason for their request.</p>
<p>&#8216;We, the employees at Coinbase, believe that the executive team has recently been making decisions that are not in the best interests of the company, its employees, and its shareholders,&#8221; the petition read.</p>
<h2>Circle, Ripple, and OpenSea: Higher Staff Satisfaction</h2>
<p>However, not all companies in the digital asset sector face employee dissatisfaction. According to the TrueUp data, companies like Circle, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ripple-labs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ripple</a>, and the non-fungible tokens (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NFTs</a>) marketplace OpenSea have happier employees. Other virtual asset service providers, such as Chainalysis, Fireblocks, Ava Labs, and Immutable, also rank in the same category.</p>
<p>When it comes to growth, companies like <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a>, Coinbase, Blockchain.com, Bitpanda, and Gemini have experienced significant expansion over the years. These crypto service providers have established themselves as key players in the emerging economy, attracting users and investors from around the world. The TrueUp data also identified Animoca Brands, MoonPay, and Bitmain as crypto firms that have experienced rapid growth.</p>
<h2>Binance Responds to the Data Claim</h2>
<p>In response to the data, Binance emphasized its commitment to hiring individuals who excel in high-performance environments and are dedicated to delivering for users. The company&#8217;s spokesperson <a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/binance-coinbase-gemini-staff-among-least-happy-glassdoor" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">told</a> Cointelegraph that not all employees may align with their &#8220;hardcore&#8221; values, which could contribute to negative reviews stating that Binance sees feedback as an opportunity for growth and continuously strives to enhance the employee experience.</p>
<p>&#8220;It also means that sometimes, we have some who are not able to thrive in this unique, brutally fast environment, and we have to accept some negative reviews as a result,&#8221; the Binance spokesperson explained.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/celsius-ex-ceo-cftc-lawsuit/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/unhappy-staff-binance-coinbase-gemini/">Unhappy Staff: Binance, Coinbase, and Gemini Rank Low in Job Satisfaction</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/unhappy-staff-binance-coinbase-gemini/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Celsius Ex-CEO Risk to Face CFTC Lawsuit</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/celsius-ex-ceo-cftc-lawsuit/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/celsius-ex-ceo-cftc-lawsuit/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 10:53:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alex mashinsky]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[celsius]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[celsius bankruptcy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[celsius network]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cftc]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261853</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/celsius-ex-ceo-cftc-lawsuit/">Celsius Ex-CEO Risk to Face CFTC Lawsuit</a></p>
<p>CFTC investigators claim that they have reasons to believe that the bankrupt lender and its former CEO violated the rules of the agency.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/celsius-ex-ceo-cftc-lawsuit/">Celsius Ex-CEO Risk to Face CFTC Lawsuit</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/celsius-ex-ceo-cftc-lawsuit/">Celsius Ex-CEO Risk to Face CFTC Lawsuit</a></p>
<p>It appears that yet another trouble may be lurking around the corner for failed crypto lender Celsius Network and its former CEO Alex Mashinsky. According to a recent Bloomberg <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-07-05/cftc-probe-concludes-crypto-lender-celsius-ex-ceo-mashinsky-broke-rules?sref=3REHEaVI#xj4y7vzkg" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a>, the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/cftc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CFTC</a>) might already be building a case against the firm and Mashinsky. The report also claims that the case may even surface as early as this July, per inside sources.</p>
<h2>Celsius CEO Allegedly Misled Investors</h2>
<p>Bloomberg reports that CFTC investigators claim that they have reasons to believe that the bankrupt lender and its former CEO violated the rules of the agency. That is, in terms of misleading investors. So, if a majority of the CFTC’s commissioners can agree to pursue a case, then there will be a case.</p>
<p>The new submission by CFTC is similar to the report of former prosecutor Shoba Pillay. After Celsius <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/celsius-files-chapter-11-bankruptcy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">filed</a> for US bankruptcy last July, US Bankruptcy Judge Martin Glenn, who is overseeing the bankruptcy proceedings, appointed Pillay as an independent examiner.</p>
<p>Her duty was to find out if there was any truth to Celsius customers&#8217; claims that the firm was indeed a Ponzi scheme. She was also tasked with reporting on Celsius&#8217; handling of cryptocurrency deposits.</p>
<p>However, the examiner&#8217;s report wasn&#8217;t exactly conclusive at the time. Pillay determined that there were times when Celsius truly operated like a Ponzi scheme. She said Celsius did not exactly disclose to its customers, the risks it took with their crypto assets. The report read in part:</p>
<blockquote><p>“How Celsius ran its business differed significantly from what Celsius told its customers.”</p></blockquote>
<p>As of publication, the CFTC is yet to make an official statement regarding the potential case, whereas efforts to reach Celsius’ press have also proved abortive.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, it might also be worth noting that the Securities and Exchange Commission and federal prosecutors in Manhattan are also looking into Celsius. That is according to bankruptcy <a title="bankruptcy court filing" href="https://cases.stretto.com/public/x191/11827/PLEADINGS/1182710062280000000010.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener">filings</a>.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/samsungs-profits-low-chip-sales/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/celsius-ex-ceo-cftc-lawsuit/">Celsius Ex-CEO Risk to Face CFTC Lawsuit</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/celsius-ex-ceo-cftc-lawsuit/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4190 metric#misses=41 metric#hit-ratio=99.0 metric#bytes=1059334 metric#prefetches=199 metric#store-reads=19 metric#store-writes=2 metric#store-hits=205 metric#store-misses=2 metric#sql-queries=34 metric#ms-total=114.99 metric#ms-cache=5.60 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.2800 metric#ms-cache-ratio=4.9 -->