<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 17:59:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Pro: the recent rally in Bitcoin may not be ‘sustainable’</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/recent-rally-in-bitcoin-not-sustainable/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wajeeh Khan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 17:59:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Interview]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=101255</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Katie Stockton expects a pullback in Bitcoin price ahead. She explained her &#8220;neutral&#8221; view on CNBC&#8217;s &#8220;Squawk Box&#8221;. Bitcoin has climbed roughly 40% since the start of 2023. Bitcoin has now surpassed the key $23,000 level but Katie Stockton of Fairlead Strategies continues to recommend caution as the recent rally could reverse just as easily. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/recent-rally-in-bitcoin-not-sustainable/">Pro: the recent rally in Bitcoin may not be ‘sustainable’</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Katie Stockton expects a pullback in Bitcoin price ahead.</li>
<li>She explained her &ldquo;neutral&rdquo; view on CNBC&rsquo;s &ldquo;Squawk Box&rdquo;.</li>
<li>Bitcoin has climbed roughly 40% since the start of 2023.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> has now surpassed the key $23,000 level but Katie Stockton of Fairlead Strategies continues to recommend caution as the recent rally could reverse just as easily.</p>
<h2>Stockton defends her stance on CNBC</h2>
<p>Year-to-date, the first ever decentralised cryptocurrency has gained about 40% &ndash; a strength she says is an opportunity for investors to pull out.</p>
<p>Reiterating her &ldquo;neutral&rdquo; stance on Bitcoin, Stockton said this week on CNBC&rsquo;s <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/video/2023/01/24/katie-stockton-our-longer-term-indicators-for-bitcoin-still-point-lower.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">&ldquo;Squawk Box&rdquo;</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>When you see such strong, steep rallies, they&rsquo;re more characteristic of countertrend moves. At one point, we had 14 consecutive up days this month for BTC. So, we&rsquo;re sceptical to its sustainability and see it as countertrend.</p></blockquote>
<p>The upcoming week is a crucial one for Bitcoin because of the Fed&rsquo;s announcement. The <a href="https://www.cmegroup.com/markets/interest-rates/cme-fedwatch-tool.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CME FedWatch Tool</a> currently signals a more than 98% probability of a 25 basis points hike this time.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin has broken above its 200-day MA</h2>
<p>Also on Sunday, a top trader and analyst, <a href="https://coingape.com/legendary-trader-peter-brandt-predicts-next-move-as-bitcoin-price-hits-23-5k/?utm_source=24hrsupdateall" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Peter Brandt</a> warned of a near-term pullback in BTC. Others, including Michael van de Poppe and Credible Crypto have a similar opinion as well.</p>
<p>Interestingly, Bitcoin is now trading meaningfully above its 200-day Moving Average. Still, Katie Stockton said:</p>
<blockquote><p>This has happened before and it proved to be a false breakout. So, we&rsquo;re not convinced we have a breakout here. But it&rsquo;s an incremental positive. We hope this manifests in our longer-term indicators which still very much point lower.</p></blockquote>
<p>She&rsquo;s not particularly constructive either on the benchmark S&amp;P index that&rsquo;s up more than 6.0% for the year at writing.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/recent-rally-in-bitcoin-not-sustainable/">Pro: the recent rally in Bitcoin may not be ‘sustainable’</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto casino Stake partners with Alfa Romeo F1 Team</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-casino-stake-seals-multi-year-sponsorship-deal-with-alfa-romeo-f1-team/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 16:29:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sport]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-casino-stake-seals-multi-year-sponsorship-deal-with-alfa-romeo-f1-team/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The partnership sees Stake become a co-title sponsor for the 2023 F1 season and beyond. The Alfa Romeo F1 Team will take on a new identity as Alfa Romeo F1 Team Stake. Stake co-founder Bijan Tehrani said the crypto casino will use the partnership to bring more people to the digital space. Stake.com, a leading [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-casino-stake-seals-multi-year-sponsorship-deal-with-alfa-romeo-f1-team/">Crypto casino Stake partners with Alfa Romeo F1 Team</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">The partnership sees Stake become a co-title sponsor for the 2023 F1 season and beyond.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The Alfa Romeo F1 Team will take on a new identity as Alfa Romeo F1 Team Stake.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Stake co-founder Bijan Tehrani said the crypto casino will use the partnership to bring more people to the digital space.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Stake.com, a leading <a href="https://coinjournal.net/casinos/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">online casino</a> and betting platform, has <a href="https://twitter.com/Stake/status/1618886458772979714" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">sealed</a> a multi-million dollar sponsorship deal with the Alfa Romeo F1 Team.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to a <a href="https://www.sauber-group.com/motorsport/f1-news/record-breaking-title-partnership-sees-launch-of-alfa-romeo-f1-team-stake-for-2023-and-beyond/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">press release</a> from the Formula One team, Stake has agreed to be the official co-title partner in a multi-year partnership that will help Stake increase its fan base across the world. The partnership will increase the crypto gambling platform&rsquo;s brand recognition as it makes entry into a new market with diverse users.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Stake in ground-breaking partnership</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Ahead of the 2023 Formula One season, the partnership will see Alfa Romeo&rsquo;s team identity changed to Alfa Romeo F1 Team Stake. Meanwhile, Stake will use the partnership to bring more people to the digital space, the platform&rsquo;s co-founder Bijan Tehrani said in a statement.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>We could not be more thrilled to join a legendary F1 team that shares with us the same ambitions of growth and success</em>,&rdquo; he noted.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The two companies will work together to expand the online casino&rsquo;s opportunities, with fan engagement programs initiated alongside the Formula One calendar. The firms hope to make race weekends even more engaging and eventful for fans, with brand recognition enhanced via visibility on the Alfa Romeo F1 Team Stake.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The crypto gambling platform, founded in 2017, will also benefit from the Alfa Romeo F1 Team Stake&rsquo;s partnership with live streaming platform Kick.com. The community-driven platform will further increase Stake&rsquo;s visibility to a global audience.</p>
<p dir="ltr">With this deal, Stake&rsquo;s portfolio now includes some of the best in the global sports and entertainment industry, including music, soccer and mixed martial arts. Two of the biggest names in the world of sports and entertainment who have deals with Stake are Canadian superstar Drake and Argentinian footballer legend Sergio Aguero.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-casino-stake-seals-multi-year-sponsorship-deal-with-alfa-romeo-f1-team/">Crypto casino Stake partners with Alfa Romeo F1 Team</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Floki Inu price soars on DAO proposal to burn 4.97 trillion FLOKI</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/floki-inu-price-soars-on-dao-proposal-to-burn-4-97-trillion-floki/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/floki-inu-price-soars-on-dao-proposal-to-burn-4-97-trillion-floki/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 14:53:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/floki-inu-price-soars-on-dao-proposal-to-burn-4-97-trillion-floki/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Floki Inu will burn 4.97 trillion FLOKI tokens worth over $55 million if the DAO vote passes. The meme coin project is also looking to cut transaction tax from 3% to 0.3% and permanently disable the cross-chain bridge. The price of FLOKI rose 25% early Saturday to hit its highest level since August. Floki Inu [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/floki-inu-price-soars-on-dao-proposal-to-burn-4-97-trillion-floki/">Floki Inu price soars on DAO proposal to burn 4.97 trillion FLOKI</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Floki Inu will burn 4.97 trillion FLOKI tokens worth over $55 million if the DAO vote passes.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The meme coin project is also looking to cut transaction tax from 3% to 0.3% and permanently disable the cross-chain bridge.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The price of FLOKI rose 25% early Saturday to hit its highest level since August.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Floki Inu (<a href="https://coinjournal.net/floki/">FLOKI</a>) holders are voting on a major governance <a href="https://snapshot.org/#/floki-inu.eth/proposal/0x7beecbefc3808d9cfbac864de875b43f02c26322e7792883cddc8eb29108b183" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">proposal</a> that could see the meme cryptocurrency burn millions worth of the nativ FLOKI tokens, permanently removing them from circulation.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Floki to burn 4.97 trillion FLOKI and cut tax to 0.3%</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Here&rsquo;s the DAO proposal announcement as posted by the official Floki Inu Twitter account.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Floki?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Floki</a>'s latest DAO proposal is live!</p>
<p>If this proposal passes:</p>
<p>&ndash; 4.97 trillion <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24FLOKI&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$FLOKI</a> tokens (worth ~$54,670,000) in the Floki bridge will be burnt.<br>&ndash; The <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Floki?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Floki</a> buy/sell transaction tax would be reduced to 0.3%.</p>
<p>Read the full proposal and vote here:<a href="https://t.co/nmx4cxJ6v1">https://t.co/nmx4cxJ6v1</a></p>
<p>&mdash; FLOKI (@RealFlokiInu) <a href="https://twitter.com/RealFlokiInu/status/1618723728564817922?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 26, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">Notably, Floki Inu&rsquo;s maximum supply is 10 trillion tokens, but more than half of it is currently held in a cross-chain bridge created when the mainnet launched on the BNB Chain.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The developer team highlights the security threats posed by this scenario, noting in the proposal that cross-chain bridge exploits have seen over $2.5 billion lost in the past two years.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>In Floki&rsquo;s case, an exploit on our main cross-chain bridge would have a catastrophic impact on the project since this bridge currently holds 55.7% of what should be FLOKI&rsquo;s total circulating supply</em>,&rdquo; the developers noted.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to the proposal introduced Friday, the goal is to also cut the 3% tax on FLOKI transactions to 0.3%. This will enhance FLOKI&rsquo;s utility and the Floki Inu ecosystem as one of the top platforms for decentralised finance (DeFi).</p>
<p dir="ltr">If the DAO vote on the two issues passes, 4.97 trillion FLOKI worth over $55 million will be burnt. The team will also permanently disable the cross-chain bridge. As of 9:00 am ET on 28 January 2023, roughly 99.97% of the votes were in support of the proposal.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Voting will end at 9:16 PM UTC (4:16 pm ET) on Saturday, 28th January.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">FLOKI price jumps 25% on token burn proposal</h2>
<p dir="ltr">As token burns reduce supply of a given token, the expectation is that the price of that token will go up amid the basic principles of scarcity. The outlook is no different for Floki Inu.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">There is <a href="https://twitter.com/FlokiJim/status/1619257570539208705" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">excitement</a> about what the future could hold for the FLOKI token, even as the meme coin continues to see upside momentum in 2023.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The <a href="https://coinjournal.net/floki/">price of the Floki</a> Inu utility token surged early Saturday to hit $0.00001715, its highest level since August. &nbsp;According to data from CoinGecko, FLOKI is currently more than 25% up in the past 24 hours, changing hands around $0.00001643.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Weekly gains are nearly 50% while the token&rsquo;s value has risen by 96% in the past 30 days.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/floki-inu-price-soars-on-dao-proposal-to-burn-4-97-trillion-floki/">Floki Inu price soars on DAO proposal to burn 4.97 trillion FLOKI</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/floki-inu-price-soars-on-dao-proposal-to-burn-4-97-trillion-floki/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hackers steal $750K after fake NFT link on Azuki’s Twitter account</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/hackers-steal-750k-after-fake-nft-link-on-azukis-twitter-account/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/hackers-steal-750k-after-fake-nft-link-on-azukis-twitter-account/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 11:13:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Twitter]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/hackers-steal-750k-after-fake-nft-link-on-azukis-twitter-account/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Azuki team managed to reclaim the Twitter account shortly after the attack. Data shows the hacker was able to steal over $750,000 from one wallet, while several others were drained of ETH, USDC and NFTs. The Azuki NFT collection brand has previously been used to lure unsuspecting users via other compromised Twitter accounts. Hackers [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/hackers-steal-750k-after-fake-nft-link-on-azukis-twitter-account/">Hackers steal $750K after fake NFT link on Azuki’s Twitter account</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">The Azuki team managed to reclaim the Twitter account shortly after the attack.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Data shows the hacker was able to steal over $750,000 from one wallet, while several others were drained of ETH, USDC and NFTs.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The Azuki NFT collection brand has previously been used to lure unsuspecting users via other compromised Twitter accounts.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Hackers stole thousands of dollars&rsquo; worth of digital assets and NFTs after compromising the Twitter account of anime-inspired <a href="https://coinjournal.net/glossary/non-fungible-token-nft/">non-fungible token</a> collection Azuki.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The incident, which happened on Friday, 27 January, saw the malicious actor(s) post a fake link regarding a land mint in Azuki&rsquo;s The Garden metaverse.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">1/ The <a href="https://twitter.com/AzukiOfficial?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@AzukiOfficial</a> Twitter was compromised today. A series of malicious tweets were posted during the morning of Friday, Jan 27th (Pacific Time). </p>
<p>The team has regained control of the <a href="https://twitter.com/AzukiOfficial?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@AzukiOfficial</a> Twitter. </p>
<p>Details below &#128071;</p>
<p>&mdash; Azuki (@AzukiOfficial) <a href="https://twitter.com/AzukiOfficial/status/1619114813766139906?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 27, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Hacker drained over $750,000 from one wallet</h2>
<p dir="ltr">According to on-chain data from <a href="https://etherscan.io/tx/0x69895dac473853f296938e4cd58ff01a272cb25f47090cdb8a3c46477894bea9" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Etherscan</a>, the result of the attack was the loss of over $752,000 from one wallet. Blockchain data also shows the attackers drained 751,321.805231 USD Coin (USDC), or $752,073 from the unsuspecting Azuki fan to the attacker&rsquo;s <a href="https://coinjournal.net/wallets/">wallet</a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Users who clicked on the malicious link also helped the hackers steal 11 NFTs, 3.9 Ether (ETH), and over 6.7k USDC.</p>
<p dir="ltr">While Azuki quickly reclaimed control of the Twitter account, users have been asked to be vigilant. The team has <a href="https://twitter.com/AzukiOfficial/status/1619114816811188228" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">advised</a> that the community ensures the announcements they respond to are those &ldquo;simultaneously&rdquo; posted on multiple Azuki channels, including Twitter, Discord and the Azuki website.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Notably, the Azuki name and NFT brand has previously been used to propagate a similar Twitter account attack. The Twitter account of India University Grant Commission was compromised in April last year, with the hackers using it to promote a fake Azuki NFTs airdrop.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/hackers-steal-750k-after-fake-nft-link-on-azukis-twitter-account/">Hackers steal $750K after fake NFT link on Azuki’s Twitter account</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/hackers-steal-750k-after-fake-nft-link-on-azukis-twitter-account/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>DOJ says Bankman-Fried attempted to influence witness</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/doj-says-bankman-fried-attempted-to-influence-witness/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 09:29:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/doj-says-bankman-fried-attempted-to-influence-witness/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>US prosecutors argue that Sam Bankman-Fried tried to influence Ryne Miller, the General Counsel of FTX US. The former FTX CEO allegedly contacted Miller through encrypted instant messaging platform Signal and via email. The prosecution seeks to have SBF banned from using Signal or other apps and not to contact any former employees of FTX [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/doj-says-bankman-fried-attempted-to-influence-witness/">DOJ says Bankman-Fried attempted to influence witness</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">US prosecutors argue that Sam Bankman-Fried tried to influence Ryne Miller, the General Counsel of FTX US.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The former FTX CEO allegedly contacted Miller through encrypted instant messaging platform Signal and via email.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The prosecution seeks to have SBF banned from using Signal or other apps and not to contact any former employees of FTX and Alameda.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">The US Department of Justice (DOJ) has asked for a communications ban on Sam Bankman-Fried over allegations that the former FTX CEO had contacted a witness in an attempt to influence their testimony.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In a <a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.nysd.590940/gov.uscourts.nysd.590940.50.0.pdf" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">court documen</a>t federal prosecutors filed on Friday, the DOJ has applied to have the bail conditions against Bankman-Fried be modified to ensure he doesn&rsquo;t contact any prospective witnesses.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Specifically, the prosecution requested US District Court Judge Lweis Kaplan to impose conditions restricting Bankman-Fried&rsquo;s communication.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">SBF tried to &ldquo;influence&rdquo; witness testimony, says DOJ</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The DOJ claims that Bankman-Fried tried to influence Ryne Miller, the General Counsel of FTX US, through communication sent on 15 January, 2023.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Miller is designated as potentially Witness-1, and according to the government, SBF emailed Miller and also contacted him via Signal with a message that suggests he sought to influence the witness&rsquo;s testimony.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Part of the message sent to the witness reads: &ldquo;<em>I would really love to reconnect and see if there&rsquo;s a way for us to have a constructive relationship, use each other as resources when possible, or at least vet things with each other.</em>&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">In the document, submitted by United States Attorney Southern District of New York Damian Williams, the prosecution argues:</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>The defendant&rsquo;s request to &ldquo;vet things with each other&rdquo; is suggestive of an effort to influence Witness-1&rsquo;s potential testimony, and the appeal for a &ldquo;constructive relationship&rdquo; likewise implies that Witness-1 should align with the defendant. This is particularly concerning given that the defendant is aware that Witness-1 has information that would tend to inculpate the defendant</em>,&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Prosecutors also allege that Bankman-Fried has contacted other FTX employees, who might be witnesses in the trial.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to the filing, SBF should be barred from contacting current or former employees of FTX and Alameda, unless with counsel. And while he can communicate with immediate family members, federal prosecutors want the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ftx-was-run-as-a-personal-fiefdom-of-bankman-fried-says-company-lawyers/">ex-FTX honcho</a> banned from using encrypted messaging apps &ndash; including Signal.</p>
<p dir="ltr">It&rsquo;s alleged the defendant can use Signal or similar encrypted messaging apps in a way that helps then elude pretrial oversight. Being able to evade bail restrictions can also see the defendant succeed in obstructing justice, the DOJ added.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bankman-Fried is facing multiple charges related to the collapse of the FTX crypto exchange. He is out on a $250 million bail awaiting trial.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/doj-says-bankman-fried-attempted-to-influence-witness/">DOJ says Bankman-Fried attempted to influence witness</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is Silvergate stock a &#8216;buy&#8217; after it suspended preferred stock dividend?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/sell-silvergate-stock-suspends-preferred-stock-dividend/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wajeeh Khan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 00:58:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=101245</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Silvergate Capital Corp suspends dividend on its preferred stock. Wedbush Securities analyst reiterates his neutral&#160;rating on &#8220;SI&#8221;. Silvergate stock is currently down over 85% since mid-August. Silvergate Capital Corp ended 5.0% down on Friday after the crypto bank suspended dividend on its preferred stock. Silvergate is trying to preserve capital The embattled digital currency services [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sell-silvergate-stock-suspends-preferred-stock-dividend/">Is Silvergate stock a &#8216;buy&#8217; after it suspended preferred stock dividend?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Silvergate Capital Corp suspends dividend on its preferred stock.</li>
<li>Wedbush Securities analyst reiterates his neutral&nbsp;rating on &ldquo;SI&rdquo;.</li>
<li>Silvergate stock is currently down over 85% since mid-August.</li>
</ul>
<p>Silvergate Capital Corp ended 5.0% down on Friday after the crypto bank suspended dividend on its preferred stock.</p>
<h2>Silvergate is trying to preserve capital</h2>
<p>The embattled digital currency services company is cutting back on the payout to preserve capital. Its <a href="https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20230126006026/en/Silvergate-Suspends-Series-A-Preferred-Stock-Dividend" target="_blank" rel="noopener">press release</a> reads:</p>
<blockquote><p>This decision reflects the Company&rsquo;s focus on maintaining a highly liquid balance sheet with a strong capital position. Company continues to maintain a cash position in excess of its digital asset customer related deposits.</p></blockquote>
<p>The California-based company also confirmed that its Board will re-evaluate the quarterly payment once market conditions improve.</p>
<p>Silvergate stock has lost over 85% since mid-August, related partially to the FTX collapse. Consequently, billionaire investor <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ark-fund-unloads-silvergate-stake-131252888.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Cathie Wood</a> almost entirely pulled out of it at the start of the new year.</p>
<h2>Is Silvergate stock a buy?</h2>
<p>According to a Wedbush Securities analyst, suspending Series A preferred stock dividend will make things more difficult for this financial infrastructure solutions firm in the long run.</p>
<p>Reiterating his &ldquo;neutral&rdquo; rating on the Silvergate stock on Friday, David Chiaverini said:</p>
<blockquote><p>We believe this move could raise Silvergate&rsquo;s cost of capital down the road when Silvergate attempts to tap the capital markets for a future capital raise. Any new fixed income or preferred issuance will require a higher coupon.</p></blockquote>
<p>His $13 price objective on the stock suggests it lacks any upside whatsoever. Earlier in January, Silvergate Capital Corp said average deposits from digital asset customers tanked 39% to $7.3 billion in its fourth quarter as <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/silvergate-plunges-after-crypto-meltdown-triggered-deposit-run/">Coin Journal reported here.</a></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sell-silvergate-stock-suspends-preferred-stock-dividend/">Is Silvergate stock a &#8216;buy&#8217; after it suspended preferred stock dividend?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Moody&#8217;s is building a scoring system for stablecoins: report</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/moodys-is-building-a-scoring-system-for-stablecoins-report/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/moodys-is-building-a-scoring-system-for-stablecoins-report/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 18:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/moodys-is-building-a-scoring-system-for-stablecoins-report/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Moody&#8217;s wants to build a scoring system for stablecoins as the market grows amid increased regulatory attention. The system will provide an rating system for the top stablecoins based on quality of their reserve attestations. The leading stablecoins by market cap today are Tether (USDT), USD Coin (USD) and Binance USD (BUSD). Moody&#8217;s Corporation, a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/moodys-is-building-a-scoring-system-for-stablecoins-report/">Moody&#8217;s is building a scoring system for stablecoins: report</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Moody&rsquo;s wants to build a scoring system for stablecoins as the market grows amid increased regulatory attention.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The system will provide an rating system for the top stablecoins based on quality of their reserve attestations.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The leading stablecoins by market cap today are Tether (USDT), USD Coin (USD) and Binance USD (BUSD).</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Moody&rsquo;s Corporation, a leading global credit-ratings company, is reportedly developing a scoring system for the stablecoin industry.</p>
<p dir="ltr">A <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-01-26/credit-rater-moody-preps-crypto-stablecoins-scoring-system" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">report</a> by Bloomberg that cited sources familiar with the development, noted that Moody&rsquo;s solution will not be an official credit rating. However, the integrated risk assessment giant is looking to deliver a platform that offers a scoring system based on a comprehensive analysis of the world&rsquo;s largest <a href="https://coinjournal.net/glossary/stablecoin/">stablecoins</a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Moody&rsquo;s already has a footprint in the crypto space, with major digital asset companies such as Coinbase getting credit ratings from the US-based provider. The credit rater also has a research unit that offers access to analytic reports touching on various issues in the crypto industry.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to the report, the new system will offer access to ratings for up to 20 stablecoins, with the company utilizing the latest technology to score the asset-backed tokens. Among the most important metrics to consider will be the reserves and quality of attestations for each of the stablecoins.</p>
<p dir="ltr">People familiar with the project say its development is still in the early stages.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Moody&rsquo;s to score major stablecoins</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Stablecoins allow holders to participate in the crypto market, including in value transfer without being overly exposed to potentially high volatility characteristic of cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin, Ethereum and so on. &nbsp;But they are not without risks, particularly liquidity and manipulation.</p>
<p dir="ltr">It&rsquo;s these issues that have seen stablecoins increasingly fall into regulatory spotlight, especially around reserves as they must maintain a 1:1 backing to the issued tokens.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Various issuers have attestation reports to ascertain indeed every stablecoin token is backed. But regulators want to see the sector streamlined to better protect investors. As <em>CoinJournal</em> <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/stablecoin-legislation-may-come-this-year-bitwise-exec-says/">recently reported</a>, Bitwise Chief Compliance Officer Kathrine Dowling believes US stablecoin regulation will be ready before the end of 2023.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">The top stablecoins today</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The US dollar-pegged Tether (USDT) is the largest stablecoin with over $67.3 billion worth of tokens in circulation. USD Coin (USDC), another dollar backed stablecoin, follows with $43.2 billion coins in circulation. Meanwhile, Binance USD (BUSD) is the third largest with just over $15.4 billion worth of the tokens circulating.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/categories/stablecoins" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">data</a> from CoinGecko, the stablecoin market capitalization currently stands at over $137 billion. More than $68 billion was traded in the past 24 hours as of 13:20 pm ET on 27 January, 2023.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/moodys-is-building-a-scoring-system-for-stablecoins-report/">Moody&#8217;s is building a scoring system for stablecoins: report</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/moodys-is-building-a-scoring-system-for-stablecoins-report/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Institutional investors are increasingly bullish on Ethereum: report</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/institutional-investors-are-increasingly-bullish-on-ethereum-report/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/institutional-investors-are-increasingly-bullish-on-ethereum-report/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 17:17:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Institutional investors]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/institutional-investors-are-increasingly-bullish-on-ethereum-report/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>60% of respondents are convinced Ethereum will a better investment in 2023.&#160; Bitcoin is also seen as one with huge potential, while other coins attracting institutional investors are Polkadot, Cardano and XRP. Speculative interest and exposure to distributed ledger technology are main reasons for increased interest. Ethereum is the second largest cryptocurrency by market cap, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/institutional-investors-are-increasingly-bullish-on-ethereum-report/">Institutional investors are increasingly bullish on Ethereum: report</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">60% of respondents are convinced Ethereum will a better investment in 2023.&nbsp;</li>
<li dir="ltr">Bitcoin is also seen as one with huge potential, while other coins attracting institutional investors are Polkadot, Cardano and XRP.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Speculative interest and exposure to distributed ledger technology are main reasons for increased interest.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/">Ethereum</a> is the second largest cryptocurrency by market cap, with its market worth nearly $190 billion.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">While it remains behind <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a>, whose market cap as of 27 January 2023 stood at over $482 billion, institutional investors are reportedly more bullish on the cryptocurrency&rsquo;s prospects in 2023 than was the case going into the third quarter last year.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">60% of institutional investors are bullish on Ethereum</h2>
<p dir="ltr">According to the latest survey results <a href="https://a.storyblok.com/f/155294/x/f076ec53c8/coinshares-quarterly-digital-asset-investor-survey-jan-23-pdf.pdf" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">published</a> by digital assets manager CoinShares, bullish sentiment around the top altcoin by institutional investors has increased by 20% since the last survey in October 2022.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The asset manager&rsquo;s report states that 60% of respondents from major wealth majors, family offices, hedge funds and financial advisors, believe Ethereum has a better growth outlook in 2023. In October, when CoinShares published its previous Digital Asset Quarterly Fund Manager Survey, 40% of respondents had indicated a bullish outlook for the leading smart contracts platform.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Comparatively, 30% of the survey participants were bullish on Bitcoin &ndash; down from 40% in the previous report. But while most of the big money is betting on ETH, CoinShares highlighted that a growing number of investors are invested in both assets.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Other digital assets that institutional investors are eyeing in 2023 are Polkadot, Cardano, XRP, Solana and Polygon.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Why are institutional investors adding crypto to portfolios?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">According to CoinShares, the main reasons behind increased interest and investment in digital assets are speculation and the need to gain exposure to opportunities across the distributed ledger technology ecosystem.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Notably, more clients saw the recent crypto crash (after the collapse of FTX) as an opportunity, with a growing number directing fund managers to add crypto to their positions. Bitcoin and Ethereum are the most popular.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Digital assets are still the playground for hedge funds, but weighting in portfolios has increased from ATL 0.7% to represent 1.1% of portfolios. <a href="https://t.co/cCCogB3l1j">pic.twitter.com/cCCogB3l1j</a></p>
<p>&mdash; CoinShares (@CoinSharesCo) <a href="https://twitter.com/CoinSharesCo/status/1618594673018261506?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 26, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">But the asset manager says crypto&rsquo;s increased correlation to equities might be the reason fewer investors cite diversification as a key factor.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>When asked what reasons prevented investors from investing in digital assets, it is interesting to note that reputational risk saw a significant decline while regulation is still an important consideration</em>,&rdquo; CoinShares noted.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/institutional-investors-are-increasingly-bullish-on-ethereum-report/">Institutional investors are increasingly bullish on Ethereum: report</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/institutional-investors-are-increasingly-bullish-on-ethereum-report/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto bank Silvergate suspends preferred stock dividend</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-bank-silvergate-suspends-preferred-stock-dividend/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-bank-silvergate-suspends-preferred-stock-dividend/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 15:54:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-bank-silvergate-suspends-preferred-stock-dividend/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto-friendly bank Silvergate announced its suspended payment of dividends on its series A preferred stock. The company&#8217;s shares fell more than 11% pre-market after the announcement. Silvergate reported a $1 billion loss in the fourth quarter and also cut its staff by 20% amid the crypto bear market and impact of FTX collapse. Silvergate, a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-bank-silvergate-suspends-preferred-stock-dividend/">Crypto bank Silvergate suspends preferred stock dividend</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Crypto-friendly bank Silvergate announced its suspended payment of dividends on its series A preferred stock.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The company&rsquo;s shares fell more than 11% pre-market after the announcement.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Silvergate reported a $1 billion loss in the fourth quarter and also cut its staff by 20% amid the crypto bear market and impact of FTX collapse.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Silvergate, a crypto-friendly bank that&rsquo;s lately hit a rough stretch following the collapse of crypto exchange FTX, has suspended dividend payment on its preferred stock.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Specifially, the crypto bank says it is suspending payment of dividends on the its 5.375% Fixed Rate Non-Cumulative Perpetual Preferred Stock, Series A. The US-based company is taking the move to help preserve capital following the effects of recent turbulence across the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/">crypto ecosystem</a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>This decision reflects the company&rsquo;s focus on maintaining a highly liquid balance sheet with a strong capital position as it navigates recent volatility in the digital asset industry</em>,&rdquo; the firm said in a <a href="https://ir.silvergate.com/news/news-details/2023/Silvergate-Suspends-Series-A-Preferred-Stock-Dividend/default.aspx" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">press release</a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to the news release, the Board of Directors will re-examine the company&rsquo;s payment of quarterly dividends at a later date, with this dependent on how &ldquo;<em>market conditions evolve</em>.&rdquo;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Silvergate shares fall sharply</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Following Friday&rsquo;s news, shares of parent company Silvergate Capital (NYSE:SI) fell more than 11% in early morning trading, hitting lows of $12.55.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Despite a decent run for crypto in the last few weeks, where Bitcoin broke above $23k, Silvergate&rsquo;s shares have struggled amid negative sentiment.</p>
<p dir="ltr">At the time of writing, the shares were trading at around $12.93, still more than 8% down on the day. The company&rsquo;s stock is down nearly 27% year-to-date, with the losses coming on the back of a brutal bear market for the broader cryptocurrency industry.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As previously <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/silvergate-plunges-after-crypto-meltdown-triggered-deposit-run/">highlighted</a>, Silvergate reported a $1 billion loss during the fourth quarter and moved to slash its workforce by 20% as the negative impact of FTX&rsquo;s implosion hit the company.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The crypto bank also reported that customer digital assets deposits had fallen significantly as uncertainty swept through the crypto market.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-bank-silvergate-suspends-preferred-stock-dividend/">Crypto bank Silvergate suspends preferred stock dividend</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-bank-silvergate-suspends-preferred-stock-dividend/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
