<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 16:14:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>US SEC Reverses Decision to Officially Define Digital Assets</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-sec-decision-digital-assets/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-sec-decision-digital-assets/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 16:14:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=253310</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-sec-decision-digital-assets/">US SEC Reverses Decision to Officially Define Digital Assets</a></p>
<p>While enforcement actions have been a focus for the US SEC in the crypto industry lately, some crypto exchanges are now making efforts to expand into other territories.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-sec-decision-digital-assets/">US SEC Reverses Decision to Officially Define Digital Assets</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-sec-decision-digital-assets/">US SEC Reverses Decision to Officially Define Digital Assets</a></p>
<p>The United States Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) has <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/05/03/us-sec-changes-its-mind-on-officially-labeling-digital-assets/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">taken a step backward</a> by withdrawing from its decision to classify digital assets. The regulator achieved this by removing the first official definition of “digital asset” from its most recent household hedge withdrawal regulations.</p>
<p>Notably, the SEC first included the definition in its 2022 plan to alter mandated disclosures for hedge funds, but it was removed in the final rule authorized by the commissioners.</p>
<p>While commenting on the matter, Anne-Marie Kelley, a former SEC official stated that the SEC’s decision may have been influenced by concerns that it would be harder to argue in court that digital assets are securities.  Despite the agency’s decision, it is undoubtedly still interested in crypto-related issues. Remarkably, this has played a significant role in both its enforcement actions and ongoing rule proposals.</p>
<p>For instance, the regulator has <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-crypto-enforcement-team/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">announced</a> plans to increase its crypto investigation and enforcement staff. The newly formed staff roles, according to the SEC, would include trial attorneys, investigators, and fraud analysts.</p>
<p>Additionally, the securities regulator underlined five major areas of concentration on which they would concentrate their efforts. This includes cryptocurrency exchanges, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-decentralized-finance-defi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">DeFi</a> projects, lending and staking services, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NFTs</a>, and stablecoins.</p>
<h2>The SEC Clamps Down on Enforcement</h2>
<p>While the SEC&#8217;s approach to cryptocurrency regulation is complex and developing, many industry observers believe that the regulator has recently prioritized enforcement actions over establishing clear crypto guidelines.</p>
<p>In April, the regulator <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-sec-bittrex-violating-laws/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">filed</a> a lawsuit against Seattle-based crypto exchange Bittrex over allegations of violating Federal laws. In a press release, the SEC accused Bittrex of collaborating with cryptocurrency issuers to “delete problematic statements” in order to dodge regulatory scrutiny.</p>
<p>Interestingly, Bittrex received the lawsuit shortly after requesting clarification from the SEC on which digital assets on its platform constitute a security.</p>
<p>Similarly, Robinhood Markets <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/robinhood-crypto-subpoena-us-sec/">received</a> an investigative subpoena from the SEC for the company’s crypto operations. According to the details, the subpoena mentions a variety of topics, including cryptocurrency listings, cryptocurrency custody, and platform operations.</p>
<p>While enforcement actions have been a focus for the US SEC in the crypto industry lately, some crypto exchanges are now making efforts to expand into other territories.</p>
<p>For instance, cryptocurrency exchange <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase</a> has <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-international-exchange-btc-eth-futures/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">created</a> an international exchange to provide an expanded spectrum of crypto services to its thronging institutional clients. The new Coinbase International Exchange, according to the business description, provides contracts for Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a>) and Ether (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ETH</a>) perpetual futures.</p>
<p>The company promises that the international exchange offers secure customer protection, high-performance trading technology, and a strong risk management framework to protect clients. Overall, the SEC&#8217;s strategy for policing crypto is complex, and it will probably keep changing as blockchain technology and industry advance.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-officials-3-88b-genesis/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-sec-decision-digital-assets/">US SEC Reverses Decision to Officially Define Digital Assets</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-sec-decision-digital-assets/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>FTX Officials Seek to Recover Over $3.88B from DCG-backed Genesis Global</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-officials-3-88b-genesis/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-officials-3-88b-genesis/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 16:09:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alameda research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dcg]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[genesis trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ledgerx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sol]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[solana]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=253318</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-officials-3-88b-genesis/">FTX Officials Seek to Recover Over $3.88B from DCG-backed Genesis Global</a></p>
<p>The officials claim FTX-affiliated Alameda Research had largely repaid the $8 billion borrowed from Genesis Trading, a few weeks before the former filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy protection.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-officials-3-88b-genesis/">FTX Officials Seek to Recover Over $3.88B from DCG-backed Genesis Global</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-officials-3-88b-genesis/">FTX Officials Seek to Recover Over $3.88B from DCG-backed Genesis Global</a></p>
<p>The bankrupt <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a> and Alameda Research officials are stopping at nothing to recover lost funds by the former administration led by Sam Bankman-Fried (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/sam-bankman-fried/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SBF</a>). The crypto exchange under John J. Ray III, Chief Executive Officer and Chief Restructuring Officer, has sued several entities including soliciting politicians from both isles to refund cash donated by SBF. Furthermore, Ray indicated the exchange may never recover all the lost funds but remains focused to get as much as possible.</p>
<h2>FTX on Genesis Global</h2>
<p>According to Wednesday’s court filings, FTX and Alameda Research current officials are seeking to get back nearly $4 billion paid to DCG-backed Genesis Trading. The officials claim FTX-affiliated Alameda Research had largely repaid the $8 billion borrowed from Genesis Trading, a few weeks before the former filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy protection.</p>
<p>“The Avoidance Actions will seek to claw back funds received by Genesis and non-debtor affiliates so that these funds can be shared with all other creditors of the FTX Debtors in the FTX Chapter 11 Cases. These creditors include several million customers owed over $11 billion as of the time of filing of FTX Chapter 11 Cases,” the filing <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ftx-seeks-claw-back-nearly-214834097.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>.</p>
<p>Reportedly, Alameda Research repaid $1.8 billion in loans to Genesis Trading and pledged $273 million in the subsequent three months. Additionally, the filings noted that Genesis Trading withdrew another $1.6 billion from FTX, while Genesis Global Capital International withdrew another $213 million in that same period.</p>
<p>As a result, a motion hearing has been set for May 25 to discuss the matter in depth.</p>
<h2>A Close Reflection</h2>
<p>The current FTX officials have reportedly recovered around $5 billion in liquid assets including <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/solana/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Solana</a>, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a>, and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ETH</a>. At some point, the current FTX officials are looking at reopening the exchange to accrue more resources for the debtors. In a recent update to the FTX debtors, Ray noted that former officials significantly misguided investors while they continued to squander their assets.</p>
<p>“We are continuing our efforts to review the events that factored into the fall of FTX and to identify and recover as much value as possible for creditors,” Ray <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/ftx-debtors-release-report-on-ftx-groups-control-failures-301792891.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">noted</a>.</p>
<p>Recently, the current FTX officials noted that they entered into an agreement with M7 Holdings, LLC, an affiliate of Miami International Holdings, Inc., for the sale of LedgerX LLC, the futures and options exchange and clearinghouse unit of FTX. Reportedly, FTX debtors were able to recover approximately $50 million from the LedgerX LLC transaction.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, FTX international entities including the Japan subsidiary have made tremendous progress in repaying investors.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ecb-7th-interest-rate-hike/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-officials-3-88b-genesis/">FTX Officials Seek to Recover Over $3.88B from DCG-backed Genesis Global</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-officials-3-88b-genesis/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>ECB Announces 7th Consecutive Interest Rate Hike of 25 Basis Points after Eurozone Inflation Climbs 7% in April</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ecb-7th-interest-rate-hike/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ecb-7th-interest-rate-hike/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 15:51:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ecb]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[european central bank]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=253308</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ecb-7th-interest-rate-hike/">ECB Announces 7th Consecutive Interest Rate Hike of 25 Basis Points after Eurozone Inflation Climbs 7% in April</a></p>
<p>On Thursday, the ECB increased interest rates for the seventh consecutive time, with the latest figure aligning with analysts' predictions.  </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ecb-7th-interest-rate-hike/">ECB Announces 7th Consecutive Interest Rate Hike of 25 Basis Points after Eurozone Inflation Climbs 7% in April</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ecb-7th-interest-rate-hike/">ECB Announces 7th Consecutive Interest Rate Hike of 25 Basis Points after Eurozone Inflation Climbs 7% in April</a></p>
<p>The European Central Bank (ECB) has hiked interest rates for a seventh consecutive time as its war against inflation wages on. Today, the eurozone central bank hiked rates by 25 basis points as expected following its May policy meeting. The latest rate hike decision also sees the main refinancing operations&#8217; interest rate increased to 3.75%. In addition, the rate on the marginal lending facility and the deposit facility also grew to 4% and 3.25%, respectively. This is the seventh straight meeting ending in a hike.</p>
<h2>Analysts Predicted ECB Seventh Consecutive Interest Rates Hike Would Come in Relatively Low</h2>
<p>Economists and market observers expected the ECB&#8217;s seventh interest rate hike to be smaller than its predecessors due to contracting financial conditions. Although inflation still appeared unrelenting, rising 7% in April, the spate of accompanying rate hikes in the West threatened a recession. Analysts also pointed to the extreme drop in credit demand due to stricter lending criteria, proving that the ECB&#8217;s latest rate hike would be far from the higher end of its basis points (bps) range.</p>
<p>For instance, Davide Oneglia, an investment research analyst at macroeconomic forecasting consultancy TS Lombard, had weighed in ahead of the ECB&#8217;s latest hike. <a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/ecb-raise-interest-rates-seventh-time-inflation-fight-2023-05-03/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">According to Oneglia</a>, &#8220;from a risk management perspective, shifting to 25 basis points would give the ECB the flexibility to deal with both upside and downside risks to growth and inflation. So, a 25 basis points hike is not necessarily &#8216;dovish.&#8217; For now, we maintain our call for a 3.75% ECB terminal rate&#8221;.</p>
<h2>April Eurozone Inflation Numbers</h2>
<p>Inflation in the eurozone grew 7% in April, with Germany and France experiencing the highest increases in consumer prices. However, despite these increases, core inflation, excluding food, fuel, tobacco, and alcohol, in the eurozone has slowed from 5.7% to 5.6%. The core inflation development is lower than consensus expectations and marks the first decline since June 2022 as central banks angle for a sustained decrease. However, despite the slowdown in core inflation, the present figure still far exceeds the ECB&#8217;s target of 2%.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, analysts anticipated that food, alcohol, and tobacco would have the highest annual rate in April of 13.6% compared with March&#8217;s 15.5%. Coming in a distant second is non-energy industrial goods, which turned out at a yearly rate of 6.2% last month compared to 6.6% in March. Lastly, services increased 5.2% compared to March&#8217;s 5.1%, while energy prices climbed again by 2.5% after dropping 0.9% in March.</p>
<p>Opinions remain divided on the ECB&#8217;s rate hike stance to curtail swelling inflation amid a banking crisis. For instance, Italy&#8217;s central bank chief Ignazio Visco previously warned that further rate increases would hamper the economy and create financial risks. Furthermore, Visco pointed out that more people would suffer greatly due to excess rate increases. However, his Dutch counterpart Klaas Knot believes that the ECB should continue hiking interest rates into the summer.</p>
<p>The US <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/federal-reserve-system-frs-what-it-is-and-how-it-works/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Federal Reserve</a> also <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-fed-25-basis-point-rate-hike/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">recently hiked</a> rates by another 25 basis points, which took interest rates above 5%.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shell-q1-2023/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ecb-7th-interest-rate-hike/">ECB Announces 7th Consecutive Interest Rate Hike of 25 Basis Points after Eurozone Inflation Climbs 7% in April</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ecb-7th-interest-rate-hike/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shell Q1 2023 Report Surpasses Analyst Expectations, Adjusted Earnings Hit $9.6B</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/shell-q1-2023/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/shell-q1-2023/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 12:37:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[shell]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[shell stock]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=253283</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shell-q1-2023/">Shell Q1 2023 Report Surpasses Analyst Expectations, Adjusted Earnings Hit $9.6B</a></p>
<p>In 2022, the Big Oil companies, including TotalEnergies, ExxonMobil, Chevron, BP, and Shell smashed their previous year's earnings.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shell-q1-2023/">Shell Q1 2023 Report Surpasses Analyst Expectations, Adjusted Earnings Hit $9.6B</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shell-q1-2023/">Shell Q1 2023 Report Surpasses Analyst Expectations, Adjusted Earnings Hit $9.6B</a></p>
<p>The Q1 2023 fiscal report by the British oil giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/royal-dutch-shell/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Shell</a> (LON: SHEL) surpassed expectations, cruising analysts&#8217; predictions. In the recent report, Shell <a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2023/05/04/2661080/0/en/Shell-plc-publishes-first-quarter-2023-press-release.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announced</a> adjusted earnings of $9.6 billion for the first three months of the year. The performance is in continuation of its current bumper results run after commodity prices surged in 2022 due to Russia’s full-scale invasion of Ukraine. According to Refinitiv, analysts expect Shell to announce $8.6 billion in earnings in Q1 2023. Shell began its bumper results in Q1 2022 after posting adjusted earnings of $9.1 billion and completed 2022 with $9.8 billion in earnings in the last quarter.</p>
<h2>Shell Records Profits in Q1 2023</h2>
<p>After releasing the Q1 2023 fiscal results, Shell stock rose 2.2% during mid-morning trade. Interestingly, Shell has managed to maintain its share buyback program steady at $4 billion over the three months and kept its dividend at a constant rate of $0.2875 per share. According to top officials at Shell, the company’s quarterly reports reflected its improved operational performance and lower cost of daily business activity. Further explanations show that results from fuel trading and optimization counter the declining price of oil and gas. The British oil giant reported a net debt of $44.2 billion, a significant slash compared to 2022’s $48.5 billion.</p>
<p>Speaking on the Q1 2023 reports, the CEO of Shell PLC, Wael Sawan, said the company “delivered strong results and robust operational performance, against a backdrop of ongoing volatility, while continuing to provide vital supplies of secure energy.”</p>
<p>Shell’s first quarter report affected the shares of its immediate rival, BP PLC. Though the Q1 2023 performance of BP PLC’s robust oil and gas trading surpassed analysts’ expectations, the shares plummeted after it planned to slim down its share buyback.</p>
<h2>Shell Joins Other Big Oil Companies in Winning Streak</h2>
<p>In 2022, the Big Oil companies, including TotalEnergies (EPA: TTE), <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/exxonmobil/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ExxonMobil</a> (NYSE: XON), Chevron (NYSE: CVX), BP (LON: BP), and Shell smashed their previous year&#8217;s earnings. The volatile oil and gas prices in the wake of Russia’s invasion of Ukraine triggered the spiked financial results.</p>
<p>At the time, Shell posted adjusted earnings of $39.9 billion, exceeding its annual record of $28.4 billion in 2008. The 2022 annual report was X2 of the firm’s full-year 2021 profit of $19.29 billion.</p>
<p>Many have criticized these Big Oil companies for their bumper profits amid the current Russia-Ukraine chaos. Top executives have defended their gains by enumerating the importance of transitioning from fossil fuels. They suggested that increased taxes for such investments would mitigate further deposits. Shell aims to become a net-zero emission business by 2050, stating that the first-quarter adjusted earnings for its Renewable and Energy Solutions unit increased to $389 million compared to 2022’s $293 million.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/pacwest-sale-stock-drawdown/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shell-q1-2023/">Shell Q1 2023 Report Surpasses Analyst Expectations, Adjusted Earnings Hit $9.6B</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/shell-q1-2023/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>PacWest Bancorp Mulls Sale of Entire Holding Company amid 80% Stock Drawdown since March</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/pacwest-sale-stock-drawdown/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/pacwest-sale-stock-drawdown/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 12:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wall Street]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[first republic bank]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jpmorgan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pacwest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pacwest stock]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=253284</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/pacwest-sale-stock-drawdown/">PacWest Bancorp Mulls Sale of Entire Holding Company amid 80% Stock Drawdown since March</a></p>
<p>Los Angeles-based PacWest is considering several strategic options, including a sale, amid a banking crisis-induced stock plunge. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/pacwest-sale-stock-drawdown/">PacWest Bancorp Mulls Sale of Entire Holding Company amid 80% Stock Drawdown since March</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/pacwest-sale-stock-drawdown/">PacWest Bancorp Mulls Sale of Entire Holding Company amid 80% Stock Drawdown since March</a></p>
<p>Bank holding company PacWest Bancorp is reportedly mulling a sale following Wednesday’s 50% stock crash. The regional bank is weighing strategic options amid the US banking crisis, which sank three financial institutions in March. A <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-05-03/pacwest-said-to-weigh-strategic-options-including-possible-sale?leadSource=uverify%20wall" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Bloomberg report</a> said PacWest shelved previous efforts to raise capital to remain afloat and now strongly considers selling all its assets outright.</p>
<p>Inside sources revealed that PacWest has been working with a financial adviser on moving forward. These sources stressed that although the California-based lender is open to a sale, it has yet to begin a formal auction process. Also, according to people familiar with the matter, PacWest faces significant obstacles in its bid to sell outright because only a few potential buyers are interested in the entire Los Angeles-based bank. The entire PacWest Bancorp comprises community lender Pacific Western Bank and a handful of commercial and consumer lending ventures. Unfortunately, any potential buyer could also sustain a sizable loss marking down some of PacWest’s loans.</p>
<h2>PacWest Considers Full Asset Sale as a Way to Optimize Shareholder Value Amid Declining Stock</h2>
<p>PacWest views a potential sale as a way to “maximize shareholder value” amid its recently battered stock. The West Coast bank also noted that it had not sustained unusual deposit outflows since <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/jpmorgan-chase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">JPMorgan’s</a> (NYSE: JPM) <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/first-republic-bank/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">First Republic</a> sale was <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-chase-acquires-first-republic-bank/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">announced</a> Monday.</p>
<p>The PacWest development comes six weeks after the California lender announced a $1.4 billion fundraising to shore up liquidity. However, the bank has already projected excess financial buoyancy should it eventually find a buyer for its prime assets. According to <a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-regional-lenders-slump-banking-turmoil-fears-brew-2023-05-03/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Reuters</a>, the potential sale of PacWest’s $2.7 billion lender finance loan portfolio would prop up the common equity tier-one ratio. This increase would see the bank’s core tier 1 capital-to-total risk-weighted assets rise from 9.21% to at least 10%.</p>
<p>Although headquartered in Los Angeles, California, PacWest has branches in Durham, North Carolina, and Denver, Colorado. The bank’s recent 52% stock crash feeds into a broader 80% drawdown since the regional banking crisis began in March. However, PacWest is not the only financial institution to take a massive hit in value recently. According to reports, Phoenix-based rival Western Alliance Bancorp (NYSE: WAL) also suffered a 23% decline yesterday, which reflected bleak investor faith in regional banks. Following its drawdown, Western Alliance also sought to assuage investors that there was no cause for alarm. On Wednesday, the leading US bank claimed it had not experienced unusual withdrawals and had adequate liquidity. In a <a href="https://investors.westernalliancebancorporation.com/news-releases/news/news-details/2023/Western-Alliance-Bancorporation-Issues-Updated-Financial-Information/default.aspx" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">press release</a>, Western Alliance said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“The Bank has not experienced unusual deposit flows following the sale of First Republic Bank and other recent industry news. Total Deposits were $48.8 billion as of Tuesday, May 2, up from $48.2 billion as of Monday, May 1, and flat to Friday, April 28. Quarter to date, deposits are up $1.2 billion from $47.6 billion as of March 31.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Western Alliance also reaffirmed its previously-stated $2 billion quarter-over-quarter deposit growth rate guidance.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tenet-blockchain-testnet-lsd/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/pacwest-sale-stock-drawdown/">PacWest Bancorp Mulls Sale of Entire Holding Company amid 80% Stock Drawdown since March</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/pacwest-sale-stock-drawdown/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tenet Blockchain Opens Testnet as It Seeks to Boost LSD Functionalities</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tenet-blockchain-testnet-lsd/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tenet-blockchain-testnet-lsd/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 12:15:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ankr]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockdaemon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tenet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tenet Blockchain]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=253281</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tenet-blockchain-testnet-lsd/">Tenet Blockchain Opens Testnet as It Seeks to Boost LSD Functionalities</a></p>
<p>Just like most of the most advanced blockchain protocols in the industry, the Tenet Blockchain grants users the flexibility they need to thrive on the L1 outfit.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tenet-blockchain-testnet-lsd/">Tenet Blockchain Opens Testnet as It Seeks to Boost LSD Functionalities</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tenet-blockchain-testnet-lsd/">Tenet Blockchain Opens Testnet as It Seeks to Boost LSD Functionalities</a></p>
<p>Tenet, a brand-new layer-1 blockchain protocol has announced the launch of its testnet, creating a conduit to build on the potential of Liquid Staking Derivatives (LSD) protocols. As contained in a press release shared with Coinspeaker, the Tenet protocol is emerging from its stealth mode, making it possible for developers to interact and experiment with the protocol.</p>
<p>There are thousands of blockchain protocols around today, each with its own unique value proposition. In the case of Tenet, it seeks to enhance the opportunities surrounding LSD pools by allowing users to re-stake their assets on Tenet&#8217;s network and participate in Tenet&#8217;s DeFi ecosystem.</p>
<p>LSD platforms remove the drudgery that comes with staking assets in traditional Proof-of-Stake (PoS) protocols. With LSD platforms, users can still make use of locked tokens in a way that can generate additional value for stakers. Tenet will amplify these opportunities inherent in LSD platforms for all users.</p>
<p>Tenet is the brainchild of Greg Gopman, the CEO and COO Dan Peterson, both of whom are former executives with Ankr and Blockdaemon respectively. They designed the Tenet protocol to address some of the core challenges being experienced by existing L1 networks. The Tenet blockchain is secured using the Diversified Proof of Stake (DiPoS).</p>
<p>DiPoS enables users to stake on Tenet using any of the native tokens of the blockchains it is supporting. These tokens include <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/category/crypto/ethereum-guides/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a> (ETH), <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-binance-coin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance Coin</a> (BNB), <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/cosmos/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Cosmos</a> (ATOM), <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/solana/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Solana</a> (SOL) and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/matic-network/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Polygon</a> (MATIC). By reducing the barriers to entry in this way, Tenet is making it possible for asset preservation using the combined security of each of the underlying chains.</p>
<p>Another important offering from the Tenet blockchain is the opportunity to mint a Universal Stablecoin interest free. This stablecoin will enable holders to earn a yield on future LSD yields on the protocol.</p>
<h2>Tenet Blockchain and the Enshrined Flexibility</h2>
<p>Just like most of the most advanced blockchain protocols in the industry, the Tenet Blockchain grants users the flexibility they need to thrive on the L1 outfit. The Tenet protocol comes with inbuilt native gauges. This allows veTenet token holders to direct rewards to the pools they choose.</p>
<p>In all, Tenet’s design is hinged on taking advantage of the deep liquidity in the LSD world which saw a parabolic growth that surpassed even Decentralized Exchanges (DEXs) Total Value Locked (LSDs) last year.</p>
<p>&#8220;At Ankr, we helped bring Liquid Staking Tokens to eight Blockchains and built out some of the best LSD infrastructure in the industry, but no one used it. Tenet was really a golden opportunity for being first to market in utilizing best-in-class technology with almost $20B in untapped liquidity,” said Greg Gopman, co-founder and CEO of Tenet.</p>
<p>In a bid to bolster the growth of the Tenet protocol, the team plans to roll out a grants program in the near future. It also aims to float a hackathon to encourage developers to come to build on the network.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/pepe-coin-price-spiral-down/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tenet-blockchain-testnet-lsd/">Tenet Blockchain Opens Testnet as It Seeks to Boost LSD Functionalities</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tenet-blockchain-testnet-lsd/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>PEPE Coin Price May Spiral Further Down, Here’s Why</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/pepe-coin-price-spiral-down/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/pepe-coin-price-spiral-down/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 11:02:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[doge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meme coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pepe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PEPE Memecoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=253193</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/pepe-coin-price-spiral-down/">PEPE Coin Price May Spiral Further Down, Here&#8217;s Why</a></p>
<p>Despite regaining much of its losses, there are reasons to believe that the coast is not yet clear for PEPE.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/pepe-coin-price-spiral-down/">PEPE Coin Price May Spiral Further Down, Here&#8217;s Why</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/pepe-coin-price-spiral-down/">PEPE Coin Price May Spiral Further Down, Here&#8217;s Why</a></p>
<p>The new meme token <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/pepe/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">PEPE coin</a> recently enjoyed a spell of fortune after its price surged by more than 2000% shortly after launching a few weeks ago. However, it appears that it has now lost momentum and risks losing large portions of those earlier gains.</p>
<p>On Wednesday, PEPE entered a sharp correction that saw it lose over 35% of its record high value of $0.00000138, which it attained on May 1. The loss immediately impacted PEPE&#8217;s market capitalization by a negative $80 million. It was also enough to push the coin out of the top 100 cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>However, as of publication, the coin has regained its Wednesday losses. Now it is up 73% in the last 24 hours. According to CoinMarketCap <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/pepe/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">data</a>, PEPE currently trades at $0.000001608.</p>
<h2>PEPE Coin May Still Lose More Value in May</h2>
<p>Despite regaining much of its losses, there are reasons to believe that the coast is not yet clear for PEPE. At least, not for May, where it risks losing at least 20% of its present value.</p>
<p>To put the above statement into perspective, some indicators suggest a further slip in PEPE price. Firstly, there is the issue of dwindling interests. Google Trends show that searches for the keyword “Pepe Coin” has gone from 100 to 7 in just a day. This further proves that the dust is settling and the entire buzz around the coin might just be fading away. More so, daily trading volumes have also dropped across<span style="font-weight: 400;"> both centralized and decentralized exchanges even as prices fell.</span></p>
<p>Another thing that could be factored in as grounds for further downward movement in the coin price is the fear of potential price manipulation. As revealed by data tracker CoinCarp, PEPE has a questionable whale distribution. This is because 45% of the token presently in circulation is being controlled by the top 100 richest PEPE addresses — PEPE Whales.</p>
<p>But while these addresses may belong to 100 different individuals, it is also possible that an individual controls more than one. Therefore, a few sets of people, or whales, in this case, may manipulate PEPE price trends to their favor as time goes on. The revelation of CoinCarp, thus makes room for skepticism and expectations that the PEPE price will further slip in the month.</p>
<h2>Too Early to Predict?</h2>
<p>It should however be noted that the PEPE token is only a few weeks into the market. As such, it doesn&#8217;t have enough price history to forecast price movements.</p>
<p>Nonetheless, Dogecoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/dogecoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">DOGE</a>) has shown that meme coins such as PEPE can be very unpredictable. They could make major price moves over time and should never be written off. For instance, DOGE, on its part has gained over 7000% since 2020 when <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/elon-musk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Elon Musk</a> lent his voice to it.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-btc-price-29000-fed/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/pepe-coin-price-spiral-down/">PEPE Coin Price May Spiral Further Down, Here&#8217;s Why</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/pepe-coin-price-spiral-down/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin (BTC) Price Jumps Past $29,000 Soon after Fed Rate Hike</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-btc-price-29000-fed/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-btc-price-29000-fed/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 10:47:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ada]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[federal reserve]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[first republic bank]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jerome powell]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jpmorgan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[matic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[polygon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sol]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[solana]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=253203</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-btc-price-29000-fed/">Bitcoin (BTC) Price Jumps Past $29,000 Soon after Fed Rate Hike</a></p>
<p>Amid the unfolding banking crisis and interest rate hikes, Bitcoin has been showing strong resilience attempting another breakout above $30,000. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-btc-price-29000-fed/">Bitcoin (BTC) Price Jumps Past $29,000 Soon after Fed Rate Hike</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-btc-price-29000-fed/">Bitcoin (BTC) Price Jumps Past $29,000 Soon after Fed Rate Hike</a></p>
<p>On Wednesday, May 3, the US Federal Reserve <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-fed-25-basis-point-rate-hike/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">announced</a> another 25 basis points rate hike taking the US funds rate to more than 5% for the first time since 2007. In hours after the Fed announced the rate hike, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> (BTC) made a quick surge of more than 2% taking the price above $29,000.</p>
<p>This Bitcoin price surge amid the recovery in the broader cryptocurrency market. In the accompanying statement after the FOMC meeting, Fed Chairman <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/jerome-powell/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Jerome Powell</a> hinted that the US central bank could be pausing any further rate hikes from here onwards.</p>
<p>However, considering the strong labor market and stick inflation, the interest rates are likely to stay elevated for quite some time before resuming the downward trajectory.</p>
<p>On the other hand, Bitcoin continues to show strong resilience against the ongoing banking crisis. After the fall of the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/first-republic-bank/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">First Republic Bank</a> last week, another mid-sized US bank PacWest Bancorp. is on the brink of a collapse. On Wednesday, the shares of PacWest Bancorp. tanked by a staggering 50% during the trading session.</p>
<p>Last month in April, banking giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/jpmorgan-chase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">JPMorgan</a> said that the current banking crisis is a &#8220;vindication of the crypto system&#8221;. The company <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/05/03/first-mover-asia-bitcoin-recovers-from-fed-dip/?outputType=amp" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">stated</a> that “the US banking crisis and the intense shift in US bank deposits to US money market funds are viewed by crypto supporters as a vindication of the crypto ecosystem,” with analysts arguing that the crisis “exposed the weaknesses of the traditional financial system given bank’s maturity mismatch is susceptible to bank runs”.</p>
<h2>What&#8217;s Next for Bitcoin (BTC)?</h2>
<p>With the current move, it&#8217;s clear that Bitcoin bulls will be making yet another attempt to push the BTC price above $30,000. However, Bitcoin has been facing strong rejections at this price point every time it plans to cross this.</p>
<p>Thus, any breakthrough above the $30,000 level would be a definitive sign of growing investors&#8217; confidence in the asset instead of seeing it as a risky asset. Many analysts are already predicting a strong rally to $100,000.</p>
<p>On the other hand, the Bitcoin futures contracts are typically trading at a slight premium to the spot market indicating that sellers have been asking for more money to delay settlements.</p>
<p>Along with Bitcoin other altcoins have registered a strong recovery. The Ether (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ETH</a>) price also shot up by 2% shooting past $1,900 levels. Other altcoins like Cardano (ADA), Solana (SOL), Polygon (MATIC), etc. have gained between 1.5-2%.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-stop-bitcoin-borrow/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-btc-price-29000-fed/">Bitcoin (BTC) Price Jumps Past $29,000 Soon after Fed Rate Hike</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-btc-price-29000-fed/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase to Stop Issuing New Bitcoin-Backed Loans via Its Borrow Service</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-stop-bitcoin-borrow/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-stop-bitcoin-borrow/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Darya Rudz]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 10:44:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase borrow]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase borrow btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase crypto exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[paypal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=253173</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-stop-bitcoin-borrow/">Coinbase to Stop Issuing New Bitcoin-Backed Loans via Its Borrow Service</a></p>
<p>The reason behind the exchange's decision is not clear. According to those familiar with the matter, closing the service is not linked to the scrutiny from SEC which has alleged that Coinbase was offering and trading unregistered securities, thereby violating federal securities laws. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-stop-bitcoin-borrow/">Coinbase to Stop Issuing New Bitcoin-Backed Loans via Its Borrow Service</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-stop-bitcoin-borrow/">Coinbase to Stop Issuing New Bitcoin-Backed Loans via Its Borrow Service</a></p>
<p>Crypto exchange <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase Inc</a> (NASDAQ: COIN) has announced its decision to stop issuing loans through its Coinbase Borrow service where Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a>) has been serving as collateral. Starting from May 10, customers will no longer be able to access the feature. However, the existing outstanding loans will not be affected.</p>
<p>Coinbase spokesperson <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-05-03/crypto-exchange-coinbase-to-stop-new-loans-via-borrow-service?leadSource=uverify%20wall" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">commented</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We regularly evaluate our products to ensure we’re prioritizing the offerings that our customers care about most. Effective May 10, we will stop issuing new loans through Coinbase Borrow. There is no impact on customers’ outstanding loans, and no action is required from them at this time. You will continue to have access to your loan history and the full Borrow dashboard.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The program called Coinbase Borrow was <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-1m-loan-btc-collateral/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">launched</a> back in November 2021. It allowed users of the Coinbase platform to borrow up to $1 million with 30% of their Bitcoin holdings serving as the only collateral required. The feature came with an Annual Percentage Rate (APR) of 8%, and the loan was structured in such a way that users only needed to pay the interest due per month at a minimum rate of $10. Besides, the idea was to prevent users from liquidating their Bitcoin holdings whenever there is an emergency need. Rather than liquidate, users could utilize the loan feature and its very low-interest rate which could be accessed through a payment app from <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">PayPal Holdings Inc</a> (NASDAQ: PYPL), or via bank transfer through ACH.</p>
<h2>Why Is Coinbase Ceasing Borrow Program?</h2>
<p>The reason behind the exchange&#8217;s decision is not clear. According to those familiar with the matter, closing the service is not linked to the scrutiny from the US Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) which has alleged that Coinbase was offering and trading unregistered securities, thereby violating federal securities laws.</p>
<p>Some link ceasing the program to the crypto winter that started shortly after the launch of Coinbase Borrow. As crypto markets cooled down, fewer and fewer users began to take advantage of the product, leading to the decision to end support for it. The total number of those who actually used the advantages offered by the program is not clear.</p>
<p>Now, Coinbase is expecting enforcement action from the SEC. In March, the US regulatory agency <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-enforcement-action-coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">issued</a> a Wells notice to Coinbase warning of potential securities charges. In the notice, the SEC said it identified potential violations of US securities law and its intent to enforce action on the exchange. Coinbase&#8217;s response was firm, with its chief legal officer Paul Grewal stating that any kind of enforcement action against the exchange would lead to major &#8220;problematic risks&#8221; for the SEC and that the regulator would &#8220;fail on the merits&#8221;.</p>
<p>Currently, the SEC is eyeing the exchange’s spot market, staking service, Coinbase Prime, and Coinbase Wallet.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fed-interest-rate-hikes-impact/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-stop-bitcoin-borrow/">Coinbase to Stop Issuing New Bitcoin-Backed Loans via Its Borrow Service</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-stop-bitcoin-borrow/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fed Interest Rate Hikes Impact Everything from Credit Cards to Student, Auto, and Home Loans</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fed-interest-rate-hikes-impact/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fed-interest-rate-hikes-impact/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 10:40:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Work It]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[federal reserve]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=253189</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fed-interest-rate-hikes-impact/">Fed Interest Rate Hikes Impact Everything from Credit Cards to Student, Auto, and Home Loans</a></p>
<p>While inflation may be slowing, Americans are groaning under the direct and indirect impact of the Fed increasing the interest rate.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fed-interest-rate-hikes-impact/">Fed Interest Rate Hikes Impact Everything from Credit Cards to Student, Auto, and Home Loans</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fed-interest-rate-hikes-impact/">Fed Interest Rate Hikes Impact Everything from Credit Cards to Student, Auto, and Home Loans</a></p>
<p>The <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/federal-reserve-system-frs-what-it-is-and-how-it-works/">US Federal Reserve</a> (Fed) has continued raising the interest rate and on Wednesday increased the rate by another 0.25 percentage point, causing worry about the potential impact. The apex agency has been trying to stem a stubborn rise in inflation and has been increasing the rate consistently. The recent increase is the 10th in about a year and is the quickest succession of Fed rate hikes since the early ‘80s.</p>
<p>As the rate hike campaign seems to be working, the Fed is now considering pausing or completely stopping the rate hike. Although the agency has yet to announce exactly when it will do this, the idea might be valid if the aim of the hike is finally achieved. However, the hike has impacted the general public.</p>
<h2>Impact of the Fed’s Rate Hike</h2>
<p>The federal interest rate is exclusively under the Federal Reserve’s control. The Fed essentially decides how banks lend and borrow funds among themselves. While the Fed rate is not the rate customers pay the banks, consumers feel a ripple effect. This effect affects credit systems, including credit cards, loans, and savings accounts.</p>
<h2>Credit Cards</h2>
<p>Unfortunately for users, credit cards tie in with the Fed’s rate since the cards use a variable annual percentage rate (APR). Since this rate is flexible, it is easily influenced by the federal rate. While it may not immediately take effect, it may align in a maximum of two billing cycles.</p>
<p>This alignment causes problems for users as it spikes annual rates. At the moment, credit card users are stuck with increasing debt as rates have risen more than 20%. According to a <a href="https://wallethub.com/edu/sa/fed-rate-hike-survey/48053#survey" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">survey</a> by personal finance site WalletHub, consumers will spend an additional $1.7 billion over the next year. It also says people would have paid extra interest charges of $31.7 billion in the same period and that the Fed’s recent rate hikes would have cost $33.4 billion.</p>
<h2>Fed Rate Impact on Student, Auto, and Home Loans</h2>
<p>Most student, auto, and home loans are fixed, meaning borrowers do not quickly feel the brunt. In fact, people who have already taken these loans may already be safe. However, new borrowers may have much to worry about. For instance, federal student loans for the academic year ending in 2023 rose to 4.99%. It is expected that any new loans taken for the year ending in 2024 will be higher because of the hike.</p>
<p>For auto loans, new buyers have to worry about an increased rate. Consumer financial services company Bankrate puts the five-year new car loan at 6.58%. As the Fed hikes the rate, new buyers will likely pay more.</p>
<p>The same problem will affect new borrowers for mortgage rates tied to home loans. In addition to inflation, new homeowners would likely have to spend more money for the same or relatively cheaper homes. While mortgage rates largely depend on the economy and Treasury yields, new homeowners will likely feel the brunt of the Fed’s policy.</p>
<h2>Savings Accounts and CDs</h2>
<p>Savings accounts are not directly tied to Fed rates. However, deposit rates used by savings accounts and CDs may be directly influenced. Consumers may still feel the impact of the Fed interest rate, essentially leaving people with a lot less cash. Bankrate puts online savings accounts at 4.5%, while DepositAccounts.com puts 1-year online Certificates of Deposits at 5%.</p>
<p>According to the Bankrate survey, 27% more people are now upset at the recent rate than in March. 71% are spending more on monthly groceries because of inflation, and about 4x more people between 18 and 29 years old are worried that the Fed rate hike will impact their jobs.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-ai-bing-all-users/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fed-interest-rate-hikes-impact/">Fed Interest Rate Hikes Impact Everything from Credit Cards to Student, Auto, and Home Loans</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fed-interest-rate-hikes-impact/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4808 metric#misses=43 metric#hit-ratio=99.1 metric#bytes=1342571 metric#prefetches=212 metric#store-reads=21 metric#store-writes=14 metric#store-hits=218 metric#store-misses=4 metric#sql-queries=34 metric#ms-total=129.07 metric#ms-cache=7.01 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.2062 metric#ms-cache-ratio=5.4 -->