<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 23:49:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Should you buy Block stock on a boost to bitcoin revenue in Q1?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/buy-block-stock-bitcoin-revenue-q1/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wajeeh Khan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 23:49:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stock markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=138696</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Block didn&#8217;t see an impairment loss on its bitcoin holdings in Q1. Analysts at KeyBanc continue to see upside in its shares to $85. Block stock is currently down about 5.0% versus the start of 2023. Block Inc says it did not see an impairment loss related to its bitcoin hoard in the first financial [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/buy-block-stock-bitcoin-revenue-q1/">Should you buy Block stock on a boost to bitcoin revenue in Q1?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Block didn&rsquo;t see an impairment loss on its bitcoin holdings in Q1.</li>
<li>Analysts at KeyBanc continue to see upside in its shares to $85.</li>
<li>Block stock is currently down about 5.0% versus the start of 2023.</li>
</ul>
<p>Block Inc says it did not see an impairment loss related to its <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/bitcoin/">bitcoin</a> hoard in the first financial quarter. Shares are trading up in extended hours.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin price recovery helped</h2>
<p>The surge in BTC this year pushed the fintech company&rsquo;s bitcoin revenue in Q1 to $2.16 billion &ndash; up 18% sequentially and a whopping 25% versus the same quarter last year.</p>
<p>Gross profit from bitcoin holdings also increased 43% versus the previous quarter, as per its <a href="https://s29.q4cdn.com/628966176/files/doc_financials/2023/q1/Shareholder-Letter_Block_1Q23.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener">letter to shareholders</a>. Block generated $770 million of total gross profit in its recently concluded quarter &ndash; up 16% on a year-over-year basis.</p>
<p>The fair value of its position in bitcoin was $229 million as of March 31<sup>st</sup> versus the original purchase price of $220 million.</p>
<p>Year-to-date, Block stock is down about 5.0% at writing.</p>
<h2>Should you buy Block stock now?</h2>
<p>Block ended the quarter with 20 million monthly active users on &ldquo;Cash Card&rdquo; &ndash; up 34%. Earlier this week, K33 analyst Vetle Lunde <a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/amp/story/bitcoin-could-soon-reach-45-000-if-this-pattern-repeats-analyst-says-has-the-crypto-started-a-new-bull-market-8dc1701a?mod=mw_quote_news" target="_blank" rel="noopener">noted</a> the similarity in how bitcoin is performing this year and how it recovered after the bear market of 2018-2019.</p>
<p>If it continued on the same trajectory, he added, bitcoin could be worth as much as $45,000 in the coming weeks which could be a significant benefit to Block Inc both in terms of its financial performance as well as the share price.</p>
<p>Those interested in buying Block stock today should also know that analysts at KeyBanc continue to see upside in it to $85 &ndash; up roughly 40% from here.</p>
<p>Other notable bulls of the financial technology company include <a href="https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-news-today-03-24-2023/card/cathie-wood-s-ark-buys-dip-in-block-coinbase-WCR1JILbLudmIm2K6p5G" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Cathie Wood</a> &ndash; the Founder and Chief Executive of Ark Invest.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/buy-block-stock-bitcoin-revenue-q1/">Should you buy Block stock on a boost to bitcoin revenue in Q1?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Will Stacks price go back up? Here’s the short-term outlook for STX</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/will-stacks-price-go-back-up-heres-the-short-term-outlook-for-stx/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 18:39:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/will-stacks-price-go-back-up-heres-the-short-term-outlook-for-stx/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Stacks price has declined 4% in the past 24 hours and is -15% this past 30 days. STX currently trades near $0.78, and has a key supply zone near the psychological $1.00 level. The price of STX rose sharply in February and March as the Ordinals hype hit the market. The price of Stacks (STX) [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/will-stacks-price-go-back-up-heres-the-short-term-outlook-for-stx/">Will Stacks price go back up? Here’s the short-term outlook for STX</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<div class="fr-img-space-wrap">
<p class="fr-img-space-wrap2">Stacks price has declined 4% in the past 24 hours and is -15% this past 30 days.</p>
</div>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">STX currently trades near $0.78, and has a key supply zone near the psychological $1.00 level.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The price of STX rose sharply in February and March as the Ordinals hype hit the market.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">The price of <a href="https://coinjournal.net/stacks/">Stacks (STX)</a> made another higher low move on Wednesday, trading to highs of $0.82 after surging double digits alongside Bitcoin (BTC). The upside followed the crypto market&rsquo;s upward reaction to the US Federal Reserve&rsquo;s interest rate hike.</p>
<p dir="ltr">But as the FOMC tide cools, STX is down 4% in the past 24 hours, cutting weekly gains to just 5% and wiping out gains from key price bursts in April.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Will Stacks go back up after the recent dump?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Stacks (STX) is a digital asset that has shown considerable fluctuations in price in the past few weeks. As CoinJournal highlighted in<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/stacks-price-relentless-bull-run-gains-steam-is-it-still-a-buy/">&nbsp;<u>this article</u></a>, the main driver of Stacks price in February was the strong interest in Ordinals, a platform for <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> inscriptions (crypto assets similar to NFTs).</p>
<p dir="ltr">Stacks, which brings the power of smart contracts to Bitcoin, also surged in March as<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/stacks-stx-is-a-whale-aggressively-loading-up/">&nbsp;<u>whales loaded up on the native STX</u></a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As seen on the weekly chart below, STX/USD has been constrained between robust support at $0.64 and new resistance near $1.33 since 20 February. The coin is up 5% this week but is in the red on the monthly chart after today&rsquo;s declines helped erase gains made earlier in the year. STXUSD is down nearly 15% over the past 30 days.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Incidentally, STX rose 122% in one week in February and another 51% over seven days in mid-March. So the question is: will Stacks go back up after retreating from year-to-date highs above $1.32?&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The surge in Bitcoin ordinals, which on-chain data <a href="https://dune.com/dgtl_assets/bitcoin-ordinals-analysis" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">shows</a> reached over 3.5 million this week, suggests interest in the inscriptions is still high. The activity on the Ordinals Protocol and other layer 2s on the Bitcoin blockchain and the potential uptick in BTC price are likely to be major catalysts of upside momentum for the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/altcoin/">altcoin</a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Below is the outlook for Stacks price from a technical perspective.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Stacks price: short term outlook for STX</h2>
<p dir="ltr">For a short-term technical outlook for STX, we can look at its weekly chart focusing on the Relative Strength Index (RSI), Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD), and Fibonacci retracement levels.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><span class="fr-img-caption fr-fic fr-dib" style="width: 700px"><span class="fr-img-wrap"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/04/04/1683223211828-21871ca3-eb5d-4127-8513-f6230a61b33e.png" style="width: 700px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="700" height="259"><span class="fr-inner">Chart showing the price movement of Stacks (STX) with key technical indicators. Source:&nbsp;<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/fnsqMrDa/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">TradingView</a></span></span></span>As shown above, the RSI indicator for STX on is currently at 57. This suggests that STX is largely neutral, indicating its neither oversold nor overbought.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, the MACD indicator is suggesting a potential bearish crossover. We can see the MACD line is above the signal line but could cross below to give the advantage to the bears.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Meanwhile, the main barrier to the upside is likely to be at the Fibonacci retracement level at 23.6% that marks the retracement of the last swing from the highs of $3.37 to lows of $0.20. That level is currently around $0.95. Stacks also highlight the 50% and 61.8% retracement levels as main resistance areas.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In case the Stacks (STX) price continues its downward trend, the first support level could be at a long-term horizontal line near $0.45. The 50-week moving average line is currently leveling up around this area, while the $0.20 demand reload line provides a key buffer zone.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/will-stacks-price-go-back-up-heres-the-short-term-outlook-for-stx/">Will Stacks price go back up? Here’s the short-term outlook for STX</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>WOO, Conflux, KAVA prices lead gains as bank stocks plunge</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/woo-conflux-kava-prices-lead-gains-as-bank-stocks-plunge/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/woo-conflux-kava-prices-lead-gains-as-bank-stocks-plunge/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 17:50:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/woo-conflux-kava-prices-lead-gains-as-bank-stocks-plunge/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Woo Network, Conflux, and Kava prices held quite well even as American stocks continued plunging. WOO jumped by over 11.3% in the past 24 hours as we wrote&#160;here while&#160;Conflux and Kava soared by over 6%. Bitcoin remained steady at $29,000 while Ethereum and BNB prices held at $1,890 and $325, respectively.&#160; US equities plunge American [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/woo-conflux-kava-prices-lead-gains-as-bank-stocks-plunge/">WOO, Conflux, KAVA prices lead gains as bank stocks plunge</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Woo Network, Conflux, and Kava prices held quite well even as American stocks continued plunging. WOO jumped by over 11.3% in the past 24 hours as we wrote&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/woo-price-surged-by-12-today-can-it-hit-0-3500-soon/"><u>here</u></a> while&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/conflux/"><u>Conflux</u></a> and Kava soared by over 6%. Bitcoin remained steady at $29,000 while Ethereum and BNB prices held at $1,890 and $325, respectively.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">US equities plunge</h2>
<p dir="ltr">American stocks continued falling on Thursday as investors reacted to the latest interest rate decision by the Federal Reserve. In it, the bank decided to hike interest rates by 0.25%, bringing the headline rate to between 5.0% and 5.25%. That was the highest rate the US has been in more than a decade.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Analysts believe that the Federal Reserve will now pause rates as it observes the state of the financial market and inflation. The hope is that the elevated inflation will help to limit inflation. Data published last month showed that the headline consumer inflation dropped to 5.0% in March and analysts believe that the situation will continue as crude oil prices continue dropping.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Cryptocurrencies like WOO, CFX, and&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/kava/"><u>KAVA</u></a> did well even as the banking crisis in the US escalated. PacWest stock price has plunged by more than 50% on Thursday while Western Alliance and Comerica slumped. In all, the SPDR Regional Bank ETF dropped by over 5% and has crashed by more than 30% in the past three months.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, there is a likelihood that we will see more banks collapse this year. Already, companies like First Republic, Silicon Valley Bank, Signature, and Silvergate have all collapsed. And on Thursday, the Dow Jones, Nasdaq 100, and S&amp;P 500 indices dropped by almost 1% each.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bank collapses impact on crypto</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Analysts believe that the collapse of these regional banks has a positive impact on cryptocurrencies for two main reasons. First, some analysts and investors see cryptocurrencies as safe havens which do well when there are elevated risks. They, especially Bitcoin, are now being seen as safe-haven assets.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Second, the collapse of these banks will lead to a slowdown of the American economy and force the Fed to intervene. In periods like these, the Fed tends to intervene by either reducing its quantitative tightening or by reducing rates. &nbsp;A pivot of the Fed will likely be positive for WOO, Conflux, KAVA, and other cryptocurrencies as we saw during the pandemic.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy KAVA</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    Binance.US</h3>

    <p>Binance.US provides secure and reliable access to the world&rsquo;s most popular cryptocurrencies, with some of the lowest fees in the industry.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/binance-us-crypto?guid=MTM4NjY5&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy KAVA with Binance.US today            </a>
    </p><h3>
    Wazirx</h3>

    <p>WazirX is India's largest crypto exchange. Started in 2018, WazirX has grown to be the most trusted exchange in the Indian crypto market. It is a part of the binance group, serving users in 180 countries.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/wazirx-crypto?guid=MTM4NjY5&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy KAVA with Wazirx today            </a>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/woo-conflux-kava-prices-lead-gains-as-bank-stocks-plunge/">WOO, Conflux, KAVA prices lead gains as bank stocks plunge</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/woo-conflux-kava-prices-lead-gains-as-bank-stocks-plunge/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Report: Coinbase share price continues to fall, as regulators and crypto volumes worsen</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/report-coinbase-share-price-continues-to-fall-as-regulators-and-crypto-volumes-worsen/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/report-coinbase-share-price-continues-to-fall-as-regulators-and-crypto-volumes-worsen/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dan Ashmore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 16:25:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto exchange]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/report-coinbase-share-price-continues-to-fall-as-regulators-and-crypto-volumes-worsen/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key Takeaways Coinbase stock is down 87% from its IPO price, the company now worth $11 billion Regulators are moving in on the industry in the US, creating an increasingly hostile environment Share price reflects these developments, as well as plummeting volume in the crypto space, writes our Head of Research, Dan Ashmore&#160; Coinbase is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/report-coinbase-share-price-continues-to-fall-as-regulators-and-crypto-volumes-worsen/">Report: Coinbase share price continues to fall, as regulators and crypto volumes worsen</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2 dir="ltr">Key Takeaways</h2>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Coinbase stock is down 87% from its IPO price, the company now worth $11 billion</li>
<li dir="ltr">Regulators are moving in on the industry in the US, creating an increasingly hostile environment</li>
<li dir="ltr">Share price reflects these developments, as well as plummeting volume in the crypto space, writes our Head of Research, Dan Ashmore&nbsp;</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/coinbase/"><u>Coinbase</u></a> is at war.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The exchange is the only publicly traded crypto platform in the US, an attribute that appeared a massive strength at the time of its IPO in April 2021. This was a time when Bitcoin was trading at $63,500, dinner tables were filled with questions such as &ldquo;how high can it go?&rdquo;, and everybody wanted a piece of the crypto pie.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Things are a little different today. Coinbase&rsquo;s status as a public company may be helping it with regard to transparency in an increasingly opaque crypto industry, but it is also presenting its troubles for everybody to see. The stock is down 87% from the price it floated at.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/13639439">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<h2 dir="ltr">Coinbase faces a fight on multiple fronts</h2>
<p dir="ltr">I wrote a <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/what-is-wrong-with-coinbase-ceo-selling-2-of-stake-a-deep-dive/"><u>deep dive</u></a> on the prospects of the company last October, after it was revealed CEO Brian Armstrong had sold 2% of his stake. Seven months on, crypto prices have rebounded strongly but Coinbase&rsquo;s future seems murkier than ever.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The company faces challenges on multiple fronts. The first, obviously, is the state of the crypto industry. Prices, volumes and interest have evaporated at an alarming rate over the 18 months. The Federal Reserve&rsquo;s transition to tight monetary policy in the face of rising inflation has sucked liquidity out of the economy and crushed assets residing on the far end of the risk spectrum. And make no mistake, crypto is most definitely <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-still-trading-like-a-risk-asset-despite-claims-of-decoupling-amid-banking-crisis/">out there on the risk curve</a>.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin has careened down as low as $15,500 this cycle, a drawdown of 77% from its peak. It currently trades at $29,000 following a bumper first quarter of the year, but the issues with Coinbase go beyond merely crypto prices.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The industry has been under siege from regulators this year, with the SEC in particular clamping down on a space that conceived multiple scandals last year &ndash; most notably the spectacular collapse of not-so-stable stablecoin UST and <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ftx-insolvent-what-next-for-crypto/">crypto exchange FTX</a>.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Coinbase is bracing itself for action after it received a Wells notice earlier this year. A Wells notice is a formal warning from the SEC that evidence of proof of lawbreaking has been found, and legal action will likely be recommended.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The SEC claims Coinbase&rsquo;s staking service, Prime and Wallet products, as well as its general listing process, may all be in violation of federal securities law.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The exchange is fighting. It has accused the SEC of levelling legal accusations &ldquo;on the fly&rdquo; and contended that legal action against Coinbase would pose &ldquo;major programmatic risks&rdquo; and would &ldquo;fail on the merits&rdquo;.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The exchange has repeatedly criticised the lack of regulatory clarity for crypto. SEC chair Gary Gensler has contended that &ldquo;Crypto markets suffer from a lack of regulatory compliance. It&rsquo;s not a lack of regulatory clarity&rdquo;.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">But like it or loathe it, the SEC is calling the shots, and this is all very bad news for Coinbase. The fear is very real that the US environment is simply becoming too hostile for crypto. Coinbase knows this, even if it disagrees with why it is happening.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">This week, it announced the launch of the Coinbase International Exchange (CIE), an institutional platform for international derivatives trading. But the fear can really be seen in the share price. While we mentioned the fact the crypto industry has been ravaged, Coinbase has underperformed even Bitcoin significantly over the last year.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Perhaps the two best benchmarks for Coinbase&rsquo;s performance are Bitcoin and the Nasdaq. The below chart shows how wide the chasm has been.</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/13639517">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">Even this year, as prices have rebounded across the crypto industry, the exchange has failed to keep up. Its stock may be up 44% year-to-date, but Bitcoin is up 68%.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The bottom line is that Coinbase has two huge problems. The first is that the industry it operates is has melted down compared to the lofty highs during the pandemic, and the second is that regulators are very much threatening its existence as a US company.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Neither of those problems have easy fixes. And the share price reflects that.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/report-coinbase-share-price-continues-to-fall-as-regulators-and-crypto-volumes-worsen/">Report: Coinbase share price continues to fall, as regulators and crypto volumes worsen</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/report-coinbase-share-price-continues-to-fall-as-regulators-and-crypto-volumes-worsen/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>WOO price surged by 12% today: can it hit $0.3500 soon?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/woo-price-surged-by-12-today-can-it-hit-0-3500-soon/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/woo-price-surged-by-12-today-can-it-hit-0-3500-soon/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 16:08:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/woo-price-surged-by-12-today-can-it-hit-0-3500-soon/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways WOO is the best-performing cryptocurrency amongst the top 100 by market cap today. The rally comes as Woo Network listed new perpetual products and revamped its community ambassador programme. WOO could be eyeing the $0.3500 psychological level following its recent rally. WOO price stands at $0.2893, up by more than 12% today WOO, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/woo-price-surged-by-12-today-can-it-hit-0-3500-soon/">WOO price surged by 12% today: can it hit $0.3500 soon?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">WOO is the best-performing cryptocurrency amongst the top 100 by market cap today.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The rally comes as Woo Network listed new perpetual products and revamped its community ambassador programme.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">WOO could be eyeing the $0.3500 psychological level following its recent rally.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr">WOO price stands at $0.2893, up by more than 12% today</h2>
<p dir="ltr">WOO, the native token of the Woo Network, is the best performer amongst the top 100 cryptocurrencies by market cap today. The token is up by more than 12% in the last 24 hours.</p>
<p dir="ltr">At press time, the&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/woo-network/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>price of WOO</u></a> stands at $0.2883 and could rally higher in the near term.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The rally comes as the WOO Network listed the SUI perpetual token with zero fees on its platform. This&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>latest cryptocurrency news</u></a> means that traders on WOO can start trading SUI futures.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">&#127754; Ride the <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/SUInami?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#SUInami</a> on <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24SUI&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$SUI</a> &ndash; PERP with ZERO fees. <a href="https://twitter.com/SuiNetwork?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@SuiNetwork</a> the latest L1 platform token built with  Move, has arrived on WOO X.  </p>
<p>&#9654;&#65039; Start trading at <a href="https://t.co/lM1upFinM5">https://t.co/lM1upFinM5</a> <a href="https://t.co/iD6VKdLIyC">pic.twitter.com/iD6VKdLIyC</a></p>
<p>&mdash; WOO X (@_WOO_X) <a href="https://twitter.com/_WOO_X/status/1654053586161254400?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">May 4, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">In addition to that, the Woo Network recently revamped WOO Force, its community ambassador programme. The revamp is designed to extend the reach of WOO&rsquo;s growth initiatives.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">May the force forever be with <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24WOO&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$WOO</a> &#9883;&#65039;</p>
<p>&#128293; Recognizing the surging social activity around the <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24WOO&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$WOO</a> ecosystem, we've recently revamped WOO Force &ndash; our community ambassador programme.  </p>
<p>&#9654;&#65039; Learn about these changes and join the force today:<a href="https://t.co/lXTgCTkHop">https://t.co/lXTgCTkHop</a> <a href="https://t.co/dNSRkI6YiG">pic.twitter.com/dNSRkI6YiG</a></p>
<p>&mdash; WOO X (@_WOO_X) <a href="https://twitter.com/_WOO_X/status/1654093525300985857?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">May 4, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">These latest developments could be the major catalysts behind WOO&rsquo;s ongoing rally.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Could WOO reach the $0.3500 psychological level soon?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">WOO has been performing well in recent days and could be on its way to reaching new highs. At press time, WOO is trading above the $0.28 level.</p>
<p dir="ltr">If the rally continues, WOO could reach the $0.3500 psychological level for the first time since April 19.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The fundamental conditions of the broader cryptocurrency market could also help WOO rally toward that price.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Despite its recent positive performance, WOO remains 88% down from the all-time high of $2.4807 it achieved in November 2021.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/woo-price-surged-by-12-today-can-it-hit-0-3500-soon/">WOO price surged by 12% today: can it hit $0.3500 soon?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/woo-price-surged-by-12-today-can-it-hit-0-3500-soon/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>AltSignals (ASI) price outlook as AI hype sends AI-based tokens through the roof</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-asi-price-outlook-as-ai-hype-sends-ai-based-tokens-through-the-roof/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-asi-price-outlook-as-ai-hype-sends-ai-based-tokens-through-the-roof/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 14:55:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-asi-price-outlook-as-ai-hype-sends-ai-based-tokens-through-the-roof/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>AltSignals is a financial markets trading signals service provider and it is working on an AI-based algorithm. AltSignals is currently conducting the presale of its new AI-based native token ASI. The ASI presale is currently in the second phase. The hype around artificial intelligence (AI) technology has found its way into the crypto world and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-asi-price-outlook-as-ai-hype-sends-ai-based-tokens-through-the-roof/">AltSignals (ASI) price outlook as AI hype sends AI-based tokens through the roof</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>AltSignals is a financial markets trading signals service provider and it is working on an AI-based algorithm.</li>
<li>AltSignals is currently conducting the presale of its new AI-based native token ASI.</li>
<li>The ASI presale is currently in the second phase.</li>
</ul>
<p>The hype around artificial intelligence (AI) technology has found its way into the crypto world and AI-based cryptocurrencies are seeing quite a boom buoyed by the AI hype.</p>
<p>Most of the AI-based cryptocurrencies are relatively new and were launched after the launch of OpenAI&rsquo;s AI-based chatbot ChatGPT. Over the last seven days, most of these tokens have seen a triple-figure price rise. <a href="https://www.coinlore.com/coin/omax-token">Omax Coin (OMAX) has raised by 108%</a>, Forta (FORT) by 106%, and ChainGPT (CGPT) by 59%, just to mention the top three AI-based crypto gainers over the last seven days.</p>
<h2>AltSignals&rsquo; AI-based project prospects</h2>
<p>Since its launch in 2017, AltSignals has grown popular for providing quality trading signals to over 50,000 Telegram members. Its trading signal service has earned a 4.8 out of 5-star rating on Trustpilot.</p>
<p>Currently, the AltSignals team wants is working on upgrading its signal-generating service after its early success. The team is seeking to integrate artificial intelligence, natural language processing, machine learning, and advanced sentiment analysis in signal generation.</p>
<p>The new AI-powered trading platform, dubbed ActualizeAI, will be powered by the ASI cryptocurrency, which will be the unit of membership in ActualizeAI, with holders being able to vote on the governance of the platform.</p>
<p>AltSignals is currently conducting the presale of the ASI token and it is now at the second stage of the presale which at press time was 65.08 % sold out. Interested crypto investors can participate in the presale <a href="https://token.altsignals.io/">here</a>.</p>
<p>Going by the success that ChatGPT has had since its launch towards the end of 2022, AltSignals&rsquo; ActualizeAI project could also receive a significant uptake. The quick <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-traders-gear-up-and-flock-to-altsignals-new-token-asi/">sell-out of the first AltSignals&rsquo; presale stage</a>, the BETA stage, is already a testament that investors have confidence in the ActualizeAI project.</p>
<h2>Should I buy the ASI token?</h2>
<p>Well, the cryptocurrency market is extremely volatile and it can be quite a risky investment. Nevertheless, people have taken advantage of the crypto price movements and earned a good amount of money.</p>
<p>Although the ASI token is still new in the market, its price has been on the rise since the start of the presale. In the BETA stage, it was selling at $0.01200. It has increased by 25% to the current price of $0.015.</p>
<p>According to the schedule provided by AltSignals on its <a href="https://token.altsignals.io/">official website</a>, the ASI is expected to continue rising in the remaining presale stages. It is projected to sell at $0.02274 at the end of the presale.</p>
<h2>AtlSignals (ASI) price outlook after presale ends</h2>
<p>AltSignals has already earned itself a reputation within the trading signals service market, which is a good proponent for the ASI token. Investors at least know they are investing in a trusted company which has been in the market for the past five years.</p>
<p>The price of ASI could skyrocket just like its AI-based cryptocurrency peers once ActualizeAI goes live and starts attracting active users. Also, the ASI token is scheduled for listing on <a href="https://coinjournal.net/uniswap/what-is-uniswap/">Uniswap&nbsp;</a>and several other centralized exchanges once the presale is concluded; something that could further add impetus to the price surge.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-asi-price-outlook-as-ai-hype-sends-ai-based-tokens-through-the-roof/">AltSignals (ASI) price outlook as AI hype sends AI-based tokens through the roof</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-asi-price-outlook-as-ai-hype-sends-ai-based-tokens-through-the-roof/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>AltSignals (ASI) outlook strengthens as Fed signals rate pause</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-asi-outlook-strengthens-as-fed-signals-rate-pause/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-asi-outlook-strengthens-as-fed-signals-rate-pause/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 14:39:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US Federal Reserve]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-asi-outlook-strengthens-as-fed-signals-rate-pause/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>AltSignals (ASI) token sale continues as crypto is poised to react higher. This follows hints by the US Federal Reserve of pausing interest rate hikes. ASI token could also benefit from expected explosion in interest around artificial intelligence (AI) projects. Artificial intelligence continues to make waves, with both consumers and businesses looking to tap into [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-asi-outlook-strengthens-as-fed-signals-rate-pause/">AltSignals (ASI) outlook strengthens as Fed signals rate pause</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">AltSignals (ASI) token sale continues as crypto is poised to react higher.</li>
<li dir="ltr">This follows hints by the US Federal Reserve of pausing interest rate hikes.</li>
<li dir="ltr">ASI token could also benefit from expected explosion in interest around artificial intelligence (AI) projects.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Artificial intelligence continues to make waves, with both consumers and businesses looking to tap into opportunities being presented by the technological leap. Airbnb CEO Brian Chesky said in an <a href="https://twitter.com/SquawkCNBC/status/1654116763087372288" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">interview</a> with CNBC on Thursday that <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/ai/">AI</a> could be bigger than the internet revolution.</p>
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals, a trading signals platform looking to upgrade its algorithm by introducing an AI-powered layer, is among those attracting huge attention. The AltSignals presale is in progress, with the second stage nearly 70% sold out.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Fed pause could see crypto prices react higher</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">Bitcoin price</a> currently hovers near $29,000 after investors reacted positively to the US Federal Reserve&rsquo;s signal that it could pause its interest rate hike trajectory.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Fed&rsquo;s hint towards taking a more cautious approach came after it raised rates by another 25 basis points on Wednesday. The US central bank&rsquo;s interest rate rose to the 5.00%-5.25% range after the latest hike. It comes amid fresh uncertainties amid bank failures, warnings about the US debt ceiling and the continuing issue of inflation.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Fed Chair Jerome Powell hinted to this in his speech, with the next FOMC meeting now of key interest to investors. With an end to the rate hike cycle likely coming, it could be time for markets to find new momentum, which we highlight <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/feds-decision-had-no-impact-on-the-crypto-market-yet/">here</a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The scenario in the crypto sector will likely be where interest in established assets like Bitcoin, Ethereum, Litecoin and others, spills into projects in categories such as layer 2s, GameFi, play-to-earn and artificial intelligence.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Why would now be a good time to buy AltSignals?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Investors are likely to continue seeing Bitcoin as a safe haven asset amid ongoing bank failures and economic woes that impact traditional assets. Crypto as a whole is also proving quite attractive as a way for people to diversify their portfolios.</p>
<p dir="ltr">If the expected Bitcoin bull cycle sets in, soaring market could catapult ASI token higher &ndash; a scenario seen with other projects that launched during the last bull market. As crypto edges closer to the historically bullish period marked by BTC halving, taking positions with ASI at current presale prices could prove a great investment.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Even if crypto fails to take on a new bull run going into its 2024 halving, the utility that ASI offers and the growing adoption of AI-powered tools in the trading market could be enough to propel AltSignals higher when it launches. &nbsp;But as always, it is advisable to remember that investing comes with risks, which is true of crypto, including presales of new tokens.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What&rsquo;s unique about AltSignals?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals launched in 2017, offering a trading signals and market alerts for cryptocurrencies, stocks and forex. Now the platform has planned an upgrade to its trading algorithm, with artificial intelligence, machine learning and natural language processing.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The upgrade is set to launch later this quarter via an AI layer dubbed ActualizeAI, and will see traders benefit from 24/7 trading signals with improved accuracy and risk management. The system will be powered by the ASI token, a native token that will offer holders access to all trading signals on the new AI-powered system.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Unlike many new projects, AltSignals (ASI) is a project that already boasts a growing community and ready market for its product. Trade calls can be traded on major exchanges and brokers, including those for all the top cryptocurrencies and major forex pairs.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Taking a working product and bumping its capacity with new advanced capabilities is a strategy that could see AltSignals take huge strides as a leading trading signals provider &ndash; with traders able to benefit across both bear and bull markets.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As for the ASI token, holding it will not only give the investor access to ActualizeAI, but also to a membership club, trading tournaments and an upcoming DAO. The AltSignals presale could therefore be an opportunity for interested investors to buy the tokens at potentially low prices.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The AltSignals presale is expected to end in the next few weeks, with the token&rsquo;s price set to increase from $0.015 to $0.02274. The ASI token is issued on the Ethereum network and will trade on exchanges such as Uniswap when it goes live.</p>
<p dir="ltr">You can invest in AltSignals by buying the ASI token <a href="https://token.altsignals.io/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">here</a>.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-asi-outlook-strengthens-as-fed-signals-rate-pause/">AltSignals (ASI) outlook strengthens as Fed signals rate pause</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-asi-outlook-strengthens-as-fed-signals-rate-pause/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Venom Network’s public testnet records 69 million transactions</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/venom-networks-public-testnet-records-69-million-transactions/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/venom-networks-public-testnet-records-69-million-transactions/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 14:33:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/venom-networks-public-testnet-records-69-million-transactions/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways The Venom Network&#8217;s first testnet was successfully launched. The team revealed that 223,446 wallets created were created, and 69,000,000 transactions were completed. The Venom testnet is designed with ecosystem users and developers in mind. Venom Network launches its first public testnet Venom Foundation, a decentralised network aimed at accelerating Web3 development and which [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/venom-networks-public-testnet-records-69-million-transactions/">Venom Network’s public testnet records 69 million transactions</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The Venom Network&rsquo;s first testnet was successfully launched.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The team revealed that 223,446 wallets created were created, and 69,000,000 transactions were completed.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The Venom testnet is designed with ecosystem users and developers in mind.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr">Venom Network launches its first public testnet</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Venom Foundation, a decentralised network aimed at accelerating Web3 development and which is licensed by the Abu Dhabi Global Market (AGDM), announced on Wednesday, May 3rd, that it has successfully launched its first testnet.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Venom is a highly scalable layer-1 blockchain network designed to support a wide range of decentralised applications.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">A massive thank you to our incredible community for participating in this first week of <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/VenomTestnet?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#VenomTestnet</a>! </p>
<p>With your help, Venom will pave the way for a brighter future. </p>
<p>Last week in numbers&#128071; <a href="https://t.co/xqGuyhFH4I">pic.twitter.com/xqGuyhFH4I</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Venom Network (@Venom_network_) <a href="https://twitter.com/Venom_network_/status/1653767894948356097?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">May 3, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">According to the Venom Foundation, 223,446 wallets were created in the first week of the public testnet. Furthermore, the team revealed that a total of 69 million transactions were carried out during the testnet.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Venom Foundation&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/venom-foundation-announces-public-testnet-of-its-l1-blockchain/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>previously pointed out</u></a> that the public testnet going live is a huge milestone for the blockchain ahead of its mainnet launch.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">In addition to the testnet, the Venom Foundation also launched several dApps developed in-house as it grows its blockchain ecosystem.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Other than the testnet, Venom has also released multiple decentralized applications (dApps) developed in-house as part of the L1&rsquo;s growing ecosystem. Peter Knez, the Chair of the Venom Foundation Council,</p>
<p dir="ltr">While commenting on the testnet launch last week,&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;We&rsquo;re excited to announce the launch of Venom&rsquo;s public testnet, a crucial step towards our upcoming mainnet launch. With our highly scalable and reliable asynchronous blockchain, we&rsquo;re confident that developers will be able to build innovative dApps, while users will be able to experience them firsthand.&rdquo;</em></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">1,370,189 NFTs minted during testnet</h2>
<p dir="ltr">In addition to the record number of wallets created and transactions completed during the testnet&rsquo;s first week, Venom also reported another important milestone.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to the Venom Foundation, a total of 1,370,189 NFTs were minted during the first week of the testnet launch. This is an important milestone as Venom seeks to become a leading blockchain in the NFT ecosystem.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/venom-networks-public-testnet-records-69-million-transactions/">Venom Network’s public testnet records 69 million transactions</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/venom-networks-public-testnet-records-69-million-transactions/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>$22 billion of stablecoins has fled exchanges in 5 months: A report into crypto’s capital flight</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/22-billion-of-stablecoins-has-fled-exchanges-in-5-months-a-report-into-cryptos-capital-flight/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/22-billion-of-stablecoins-has-fled-exchanges-in-5-months-a-report-into-cryptos-capital-flight/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dan Ashmore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 12:37:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/22-billion-of-stablecoins-has-fled-exchanges-in-5-months-a-report-into-cryptos-capital-flight/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key Takeaways The balance of stablecoins on exchanges is at a 2-year low In the last 5 months, over half the stablecoin balance on exchanges has flowed out, equivalent to $22.8 billion Treasury yields above 5% have given viable alternatives for investors, with capital fleeing stablecoins BUSD shutting down and USD Coin getting caught up [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/22-billion-of-stablecoins-has-fled-exchanges-in-5-months-a-report-into-cryptos-capital-flight/">$22 billion of stablecoins has fled exchanges in 5 months: A report into crypto’s capital flight</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2 dir="ltr">Key Takeaways</h2>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">The balance of stablecoins on exchanges is at a 2-year low</li>
<li dir="ltr">In the last 5 months, over half the stablecoin balance on exchanges has flowed out, equivalent to $22.8 billion</li>
<li dir="ltr">Treasury yields above 5% have given viable alternatives for investors, with capital fleeing stablecoins</li>
<li dir="ltr">BUSD shutting down and USD Coin getting caught up with the SVB collapse has also pushed money out</li>
<li dir="ltr">Tether has its highest market share in two years, despite 30% of its supply on exchanges heading for the exit door since FTX collapsed six months ago</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p dir="ltr">A couple of months ago, I put together a <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/45-of-stablecoin-balance-has-left-crypto-exchanges-in-4-months-but-where-has-all-the-money-gone-a-deep-dive/"><u>deep dive</u></a> analysing the flood of stablecoins leaving exchanges.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">As of today, the exodus shows no sign of slowing down. Over half the total supply of stablecoins on exchanges has now fled in five months, equivalent to $22.8 billion.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/13612192">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">As the above chart shows, the outflows kicked off in Q4 of last year, following the collapse of FTX, a time period during which Binance also came under heavy fire for how opaque its operation was.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Some outflows are easily explained. In February, BinanceUSD issuer SEC was sued by the SEC for violations of securities law, the development meaning the Binance-branded stablecoin would be no more, its market cap set to gradually decline to zero.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">USD Coin, the US-domiciled stablecoin issued by Circle, has also had its issues. Firstly, being based in the US, there has been concern that regulators will come knocking for the same reason that Paxos came fire. More dramatically, however, was the collapse of Silicon Valley Bank, as 8.25% of the reserves backing USD Coin were held in the fallen bank.</p>
<p dir="ltr">While the SVB debacle ended with the US administration guaranteeing deposits, it did briefly drive the USDC peg down to 92 cents, amplifying the outflows of an already-slipping USDC market cap.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">In fact, when comparing to before the FTX collapse in November, all the major stablecoins have seen significant outflows from exchanges:</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/13612861">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<h2 dir="ltr">Tether market share growing</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Even Tether has seen large outflows, its balance falling 30%. This is despite the world&rsquo;s biggest stablecoin growing even more dominant in terms of market share, now with its greatest share in over two years, as analysed in a previous <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tethers-market-share-grows-to-61-a-two-year-high-as-crypto-centralisation-grows-a-report/"><u>data piece</u></a>.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/13441765">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">My deep dive two weeks ago assessed the implications for crypto as a whole of the growing dominance of Tether, but while its market share may be growing, its balance on exchanges is still falling &ndash; in line with the rest of the stablecoin space.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In truth, it goes beyond stablecoins. &nbsp;Elsewhere in crypto, liquidity is also thinning. The Bitcoin supply on exchanges is <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-supply-on-exchanges-lowest-since-2017-bull-market-peak-but-why-on-chain-report/"><u>at its lowest</u></a> since the prior bull market peak in 2017. Ethereum is the same &ndash; the balance of ETH at a <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/eth-on-exchanges-at-5-year-low-as-capital-continues-to-flee-crypto/"><u>5-year low</u></a>.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">This makes sense when one takes a step back and reviews what has happened in the crypto space. Even beyond the issues specific to stablecoins that were mentioned earlier, the industry has been absolutely ravaged.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Multiple scandals have rocked the space &ndash; LUNA, Celsius and FTX, to name a few. Regulators are moving quickly against some of the industry&rsquo;s biggest players. And most pernicious of all is the wider macro environment: last year saw the Nasdaq shed a third of its value, its worst return since 2008. This amounted to the first significant and prolonged pullback in wider markets in the history of crypto&rsquo;s short existence, as Bitcoin was only launched in 2009.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">A view of what has happened to Treasury yields should provide a clear picture of what has happened to liquidity. At the end of the day, interest rate hikes serve the purpose of slowing down the economy and pulling liquidity out of the system, helping to rein inflation in.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/13534181">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">With rates rocketing from 0% to north of 5% on Treasurys, is it any wonder liquidity is pouring out of a space that has been rocked with scandal to the same extent that crypto has?</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;Liquidity has evaporated from the cryptocurrency space at large&rdquo;, said Max Coupland, director of CoinJournal. &ldquo;Treasury yields are above 5%, while institutions have pulled investment following the scandals of FTX and LUNA. Despite the popular narrative that crypto is establishing itself as a mainstream asset class, the data suggests that money is moving in the exact opposite direction. This is true even if prices have risen in recent times, helped by the thin liquidity in markets&rdquo;.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Thin liquidity means higher volatility</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The flip side of this is that thinner liquidity means it takes less to move the price, with moves to both the upside and downside accentuated. This is a contributing factor to the run-up thus far this year.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">As the market has moved to softer forecasts regarding the future path of interest rates, we have seen prices start to come up again. In crypto, this has been aggressive, with Bitcoin up 68% thus far this year and most other coins printing similarly lofty gains.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">This dwindling supply of both Bitcoin and stablecoins on exchanges means volatility is <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-supply-is-dwindling-yet-volatility-will-be-the-biggest-benefactor/"><u>naturally higher</u></a>. And while the market is currently riding a wave of optimism that rate hikes are coming to an end (even if it is only because of banking wobbles proving the whole system is on the brink), this upward momentum could easily flip the other way around.</p>
<p dir="ltr">And with less liquidity, there is less to stop a runaway train &ndash; regardless of which direction it is heading.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>If you use our data, then we would appreciate a link back to&nbsp;</em><a href="https://coinjournal.net"><em><u>https://coinjournal.net</u></em></a><em>. Crediting our work with a link helps us to keep providing you with data analysis research.</em></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/22-billion-of-stablecoins-has-fled-exchanges-in-5-months-a-report-into-cryptos-capital-flight/">$22 billion of stablecoins has fled exchanges in 5 months: A report into crypto’s capital flight</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/22-billion-of-stablecoins-has-fled-exchanges-in-5-months-a-report-into-cryptos-capital-flight/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
