<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 11:22:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Biden Administration Seeks to Impose 30% Tax on Crypto Mining</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/biden-tax-crypto-mining/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/biden-tax-crypto-mining/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 11:22:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[joe biden]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=253044</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/biden-tax-crypto-mining/">Biden Administration Seeks to Impose 30% Tax on Crypto Mining</a></p>
<p>The White House Council of Economic Activities (CEA) is looking to penalize the crypto mining sector stating that the high energy consumption by crypto miners have spillover effects on the environment and quality of life. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/biden-tax-crypto-mining/">Biden Administration Seeks to Impose 30% Tax on Crypto Mining</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/biden-tax-crypto-mining/">Biden Administration Seeks to Impose 30% Tax on Crypto Mining</a></p>
<p>In a major move, the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/joe-biden/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Biden</a> administration is looking to impose a major tax on the crypto mining activities taking place in the United States. On Tuesday, May 2nd, the White House Council of Economic Activities (CEA) argued over the harms that crypto mining operations pose to society.</p>
<p>After the ban by China on crypto mining activities in 2021, the US witnessed a strong influx of crypto miners settling into crypto-friendly jurisdictions such as Texas and others. Now, the US is one of the top destinations contributing a large share of the global crypto mining activity.</p>
<p>The CEA made the case for a US tax equal to 30% of the energy costs incurred by a mining firm. This comes as an unusual industry-specific penalty that could threaten the profits of such businesses. The CEA lays out the case for the Digital Asset Mining Energy (DAME) excise tax. In the blog post appearing on the White House website on Tuesday, the CEA wrote:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Cryptominers’ high-energy consumption has negative spillovers on the environment, quality of life, and electricity grids where these firms locate across the country. Currently, cryptomining firms do not have to pay for the full cost they impose on others, in the form of local environmental pollution, higher energy prices, and the impacts of increased greenhouse gas emissions on the climate. The DAME tax encourages firms to start taking better account of the harms they impose on society.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Earlier this year in March 2023, the Biden administration had proposed the excise tax published by the US Treasury Department. This &#8220;Greenbook&#8221; lays out the administration&#8217;s proposal and priorities for generating revenue over the next year. As per estimates, this proposal could raise billions of dollars in revenue over the next decade.</p>
<h2>Crypto Industry Players Revolt against the Measures</h2>
<p>Critics of the proposed tax noted that the crypto-mining industry is been unfairly targeted. Speaking to Yahoo News, Tom Mapes, director of energy policy at the Chamber of Digital Commerce, <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/05/02/white-house-pushes-for-punitive-tax-on-crypto-mining/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“This puts a clear line in the sand that they do not like the industry. They are looking for ways to hamstring it. This is just a way to go after the industry which they do not support.”</p></blockquote>
<p>On the other hand, Congressional Republicans have resisted the efforts of the administration and regulators to penalize the crypto sector. There is a higher likelihood that the Republican-controlled House may not embrace taxes that would punish the industry.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-international-exchange-btc-eth-futures/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/biden-tax-crypto-mining/">Biden Administration Seeks to Impose 30% Tax on Crypto Mining</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/biden-tax-crypto-mining/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase Launches International Exchange with BTC and ETH Futures for Non-US Institutional Clients as SEC Crackdown Continues</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-international-exchange-btc-eth-futures/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-international-exchange-btc-eth-futures/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 10:38:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase international]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=253008</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-international-exchange-btc-eth-futures/">Coinbase Launches International Exchange with BTC and ETH Futures for Non-US Institutional Clients as SEC Crackdown Continues</a></p>
<p>The Coinbase International Exchange will provide institutional clients outside of the US with BTC and ETH contracts and up to 5x in leverage.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-international-exchange-btc-eth-futures/">Coinbase Launches International Exchange with BTC and ETH Futures for Non-US Institutional Clients as SEC Crackdown Continues</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-international-exchange-btc-eth-futures/">Coinbase Launches International Exchange with BTC and ETH Futures for Non-US Institutional Clients as SEC Crackdown Continues</a></p>
<p>Crypto exchange <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase</a> has launched an international exchange to offer its teeming institutional clients an expanded portfolio of crypto services. According to the company, the new Coinbase International Exchange lists contracts for Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a>) and Ether (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ETH</a>) perpetual futures.</p>
<p>In an <a href="https://www.coinbase.com/blog/introducing-coinbase-international-exchange" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">official announcement</a>, Coinbase said it received a regulatory license from the Bermuda Monetary Authority (BMA). The company said <a href="https://www.coinbase.com/international-exchange" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase International Exchange</a>’s perpetual futures trading is available in eligible jurisdictions outside of the US. However, it did not specify conditions for eligibility or countries where institutional clients can trade.</p>
<p>The official announcement promises that the international exchange offers secure customer protection, high-performance trading technology, and a strong risk management framework to protect clients. Coinbases says customers can enjoy round-the-clock risk management, liquidity from external market makers, and flexible margin requirements. Other features include a liquidation framework that meets compliance standards, and an exchange with enough capital to withstand volatile market events.</p>
<p>Coinbase says the contracts will initially allow up to 5x in leverage, and settle all trading in USDC without any on-ramps. Perpetual contracts, unlike traditional futures, allow traders to hold their positions as long as they would like. These futures have no expiration and therefore do not require traders to execute a deal at a particular time.</p>
<h2>Coinbase International Exchange Not Open to US Clients</h2>
<p>The new Coinbase International Exchange is not available in the US. According to Coinbase’s announcement, the US’ unfavorable crypto clime is to blame:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Rest assured that Coinbase is committed to the US, but countries around the world are increasingly moving forward with responsible crypto-forward regulatory frameworks to strategically position themselves as crypto hubs. We would like to see the US take a similar approach instead of regulation by enforcement which has led to a disappointing trend for crypto development in the US.”</p></blockquote>
<p>The US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has been tough on crypto business amid a wide and continuous crackdown. In March, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-enforcement-action-coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase received a Wells notice</a> from the agency, warning of potential charges. The notice said the SEC identified possible violations and may bring official action.</p>
<p>Coinbase, in an <a href="https://www.coinbase.com/blog/we-asked-the-sec-for-reasonable-crypto-rules-for-americans-we-got-legal" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">official response</a>, said it was “disappointed” at the development, specifying that the notice does not contain enough information for a proper response. The exchange also said that the notice comes after “multiple proposals to the SEC” seeking information and clarity on registration and related matters. Coinbase said the SEC did not respond to any of its proposals.</p>
<p>According to the exchange in the statement, the SEC asked for a possible resolution after an investigation last year. Following the request, Coinbase said it spent millions of dollars creating two different registration models since there was no existing way to register a crypto exchange. The SEC did not respond. Coinbase also asked the SEC to raise questions about any asset on its platform. The SEC also did not specify. Coinbase said it met with the SEC at least 30 times over a 9-month period, to no avail.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/pacwest-crash-banking-stock/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-international-exchange-btc-eth-futures/">Coinbase Launches International Exchange with BTC and ETH Futures for Non-US Institutional Clients as SEC Crackdown Continues</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-international-exchange-btc-eth-futures/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>PacWest Leads Crash in Banking Stock Falling 28% as Others Follow Suit</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/pacwest-crash-banking-stock/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/pacwest-crash-banking-stock/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 10:31:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wall Street]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jamie dimon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jpmorgan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jpmorgan chase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pacwest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pacwest stock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[wells fargo]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=253010</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/pacwest-crash-banking-stock/">PacWest Leads Crash in Banking Stock Falling 28% as Others Follow Suit</a></p>
<p>PacWest and Western Alliance banks recorded heavy losses on Tuesday as the market is still reeling from problems caused by recent collapses.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/pacwest-crash-banking-stock/">PacWest Leads Crash in Banking Stock Falling 28% as Others Follow Suit</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/pacwest-crash-banking-stock/">PacWest Leads Crash in Banking Stock Falling 28% as Others Follow Suit</a></p>
<p>Shares of bank holding company PacWest (NASDAQ: PACW) led a heavy crash in bank stocks on Tuesday. The stock tumbled nearly 28% as the general banking clime continues to sour following bank failures plaguing the sector.</p>
<p>PacWest stock closed at $6.55 after falling 27.78% on the day. In addition to PacWest, Arizona-based Western Alliance Bancorp (NYSE: WAL) also crashed yesterday. WAL fell more than 15% and lost nearly $6 to close the day at $30.93. Both banks set off multiple volatility halts as their values continually crashed.</p>
<p>The SPDR S&amp;P Regional Banking ETF (KRE) also lost 6.3% yesterday.</p>
<p>Apart from PacWest and Western Alliance, there were several other noticeable crashes in banking stocks. For instance, Metropolitan Bank Holding Corp. (NYSE: MCB) fell 20%, while Zions Bancorp (NASDAQ: ZION) and Comerica Inc. (NYSE: CMA) both lost 11% and 13%, respectively.</p>
<h2>PacWest Stock Crash Follows US Banking Woes</h2>
<p>Analysts and economists are still unsure about the main reason for the crash. Interestingly, the crash came a day after <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/jpmorgan-chase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">JPMorgan</a> CEO (NYSE: JPM) <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/jamie-dimon/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Jamie Dimon</a> said the ongoing turmoil in the banking sector could be over soon. He said this after JPMorgan purchased the failed First Republic Bank (NYSE: FRC).</p>
<p>JPM successfully <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/first-republic-bank-shares-q1-2023/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">acquired all First Republic deposits</a> and quite a few of its shares. In April, First Republic crashed more than 93% year-to-date (YTD). The crash disposed of all company gains in the past 10 years. In Q1, the bank’s revenue was $1.2 billion, a 13.4% loss year over year (YoY). Diluted earnings per share was $1.23, falling 39% from Q1 in 2022. Deposits also dropped 35.5% YoY to $104.5 billion.</p>
<p>Although there is some respite to the First Republic problem, Wells Fargo &amp; Co. analyst Mike Mayo believes the worst is not yet over. According to Mayo:</p>
<blockquote><p>“The resolution of First Republic helps to ease concerns but not eliminate them. A triple dose of negative sentiment is impacting the regionals: commercial real estate, diversification and regulation.”</p></blockquote>
<p>According to earnings published in April, PacWest and Western Alliance have numbers that have kept investor discomfort at bay. Both banks seem to have deposits that are now stable following fears from March outflows. However, investors are still paying close attention, especially after the recorded collapses of Signature Bank, Silicon Valley Bank, and Silvergate Capital Corp.</p>
<p>Bloomberg Intelligence analyst Herman Chan has <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-05-02/pacwest-western-alliance-lead-regional-bank-stock-rout?leadSource=uverify%20wall" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a> that although the FRC resolution is good, there is still another problem. Chan believes that there is still a palpable lack of confidence in regional banks. A possible solution would be a “more holistic response” from authorities.</p>
<p>For RBC Capital Markets analyst Jon Arfstrom, there might be light at the end of the tunnel for PacWest, Western Alliance, and Comerica. Arfstrom, suggests buying the dip regardless of the negative sentiment.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/non-us-derivatives-gemini-foundation/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/pacwest-crash-banking-stock/">PacWest Leads Crash in Banking Stock Falling 28% as Others Follow Suit</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/pacwest-crash-banking-stock/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gemini Launches Non-US Derivatives Platform Dubbed Gemini Foundation</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/non-us-derivatives-gemini-foundation/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/non-us-derivatives-gemini-foundation/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 08:05:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gemini]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gemini foundation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tyler winklevoss]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=253003</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/non-us-derivatives-gemini-foundation/">Gemini Launches Non-US Derivatives Platform Dubbed Gemini Foundation</a></p>
<p>The company has promised its customers that it will be expanding its derivatives offering with additional perpetual contracts, dated futures, and options in the coming weeks.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/non-us-derivatives-gemini-foundation/">Gemini Launches Non-US Derivatives Platform Dubbed Gemini Foundation</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/non-us-derivatives-gemini-foundation/">Gemini Launches Non-US Derivatives Platform Dubbed Gemini Foundation</a></p>
<p>One of the top traded centralized crypto exchanges, Gemini Trust Company LLC, has <a href="https://www.gemini.com/blog/gemini-foundation-a-non-us-derivatives-platform-is-now-live" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announced</a> the launch of its non-United States entity to serve markets outside the European market and the United Kingdom. According to the announcement, Gemini Foundation will begin to offer individual and institutional investors a <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> perpetual contract denominated in Gemini dollars (GUSD) with up to 100x leverage. Later, the company announced it will be unveiling aN ETH/GUSD perpetual contract for both retail and institutional investors.</p>
<p>Some of the jurisdictions that Gemini Foundation is available include Egypt, South Africa, Brazil, Singapore, Hong Kong, India, Argentina, Bahamas, Bermuda, British Virgin Islands (BVI), Bhutan, Nigeria, Panama, Peru, Philippines, Switzerland, Thailand, Turkey, Uruguay, and Vietnam, among others.</p>
<p>“Gemini Foundation offers customers a capital-efficient, highly available, and trusted venue to trade derivatives. Purpose-built for both individuals and institutions, Gemini Foundation combines powerful trading tools with an elegant user experience,” the company noted.</p>
<p>The company has promised its customers that it will be expanding its derivatives offering with additional perpetual contracts, dated futures, and options in the coming weeks.</p>
<h2>Gemini Flee Hostile United States</h2>
<p>The United States regulators have not yet unanimously come up with a solid plan to regulate the digital asset industry, similar to the European Union, UAE, Hong Kong or Singapore. As a result, local crypto companies including <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase Global Inc</a> (NASDAQ: COIN) have opted to diversify into the international markets for the sake of their future growth prospects.</p>
<p>Gemini is already under the radar of the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) for its Earn Program that succumbed to the FTX and Alameda Research quagmire.</p>
<p>“This past week, Genesis, Digital Currency Group (DCG), the Unsecured Creditors Committee (UCC), the Creditor Committee, and Gemini agreed to start a 30-day mediation process to drive to a final resolution as soon as possible,” Gemini recently noted.</p>
<p>As many other global jurisdictions enact crypto-friendly policies, Gemini exchange with more than 94k Bitcoins in its balance felt obligated to flee the United States market. Moreover, the company wants to get a huge share of global crypto users as adoption goes mainstream before the next bull market.</p>
<p>Notably, the SEC has charged several crypto exchanges for apparently providing unregistered securities to United States investors. Nevertheless, the agency has been slammed for issuing Coinbase with a green light to go public and later charging it for doing the same business.</p>
<p>“If lawmakers could come together and build a clear framework for crypto companies, it would be a huge boon for the US,” <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/tyler-winklevoss/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tyler Winklevoss</a> said adding that the company is not leaving the United States market but leaning to the global markets for future growth prospects.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/chegg-stock-chgg-ai-chatgpt/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/non-us-derivatives-gemini-foundation/">Gemini Launches Non-US Derivatives Platform Dubbed Gemini Foundation</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/non-us-derivatives-gemini-foundation/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chegg Stock (CHGG) Tanks 40% in One Day, Blames AI Chatbot ChatGPT for Disruption</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/chegg-stock-chgg-ai-chatgpt/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/chegg-stock-chgg-ai-chatgpt/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 07:50:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wall Street]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alphabet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chegg]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chegg stock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chgg]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[openai]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=252997</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/chegg-stock-chgg-ai-chatgpt/">Chegg Stock (CHGG) Tanks 40% in One Day, Blames AI Chatbot ChatGPT for Disruption</a></p>
<p>Chegg is facing massive disruptions in its education business amid the rapid growth of AI platforms. To contain this, Chegg is building its own AI platform CheggMate in collaboration with OpenAI. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/chegg-stock-chgg-ai-chatgpt/">Chegg Stock (CHGG) Tanks 40% in One Day, Blames AI Chatbot ChatGPT for Disruption</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/chegg-stock-chgg-ai-chatgpt/">Chegg Stock (CHGG) Tanks 40% in One Day, Blames AI Chatbot ChatGPT for Disruption</a></p>
<p>The introduction of ChatGPT by OpenAI has certainly created a massive disruption in the tech world while giving other tech giants like <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/alphabet-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Alphabet</a> (NASDAQ: GOOGL) a run for their money. Now, AI chatbot ChatGPt is causing a major disruption in the education industry as well, and online education firm Chegg is among the major ones to feel the heat.</p>
<p>On Tuesday, May 2, Chegg&#8217;s stock (NYSE: CHGG) price tanked by a massive 48% in a single day ending the trading session at $9.08. During the earnings call on Monday, May 2, Chegg CEO Dan Rosensweig said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“In the first part of the year, we saw no noticeable impact from ChatGPT on our new account growth and we were meeting expectations on new sign-ups. However, since March we saw a significant spike in student interest in ChatGPT. We now believe it’s having an impact on our new customer growth rate.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Over the years, Chegg has specialized in providing online tutoring and homework assistance. During the earnings call, the company cut down its revenue earnings to between $175 million and $178 million this quarter. This was far below the market estimate of $193.6 million.</p>
<p>Despite this, Chegg managed to beat first-quarter expectations on the top and the bottom line with earnings per share of 27 cents above the analysts&#8217; expectations of 26 cents.</p>
<h2>Analysts Downgrade Chegg Stock amid AI Disruption</h2>
<p>Amid the AI disruption caused by ChatGPT, several market analysts have started downgrading the Chegg stock. <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/morgan-stanley/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Morgan Stanley</a> analysts Josh Bear slashed the CHGG price target to $12 from the previous $18. The analyst also noted that AI has &#8220;completely overshadowed&#8221; the results for the company.</p>
<p>On the other hand, Jefferies has also downgraded the CHGG stock to hold from buy, citing the threat of artificial intelligence that the company is facing. As a result, Jefferies has also slashed the price target for CHGG stock to $11 from $25 earlier.</p>
<p>In order to be better placed in such disrupting times, Chegg is developing its own AI product, CheggMate. The goal of this product will be to help students with their homework. Interestingly, Chegg is building this product in collaboration with OpenAI, the same company that built ChatGPT. But Jefferies analyst Brent Thill believes that the impact of this product will be uncertain. He <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/02/chegg-drops-more-than-40percent-after-saying-chatgpt-is-killing-its-business.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">added</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“While CHGG plans to launch the CheggMate beta this month to a select few, the timing of a full launch is unclear. We don’t expect there to be any meaningful impact from CheggMate in FY23, believing any potential impact won’t show up until FY24 at the earliest.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Read other <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/business/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">business news</a> on Coinspeaker.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bp-stock-q1-2023-profit/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/chegg-stock-chgg-ai-chatgpt/">Chegg Stock (CHGG) Tanks 40% in One Day, Blames AI Chatbot ChatGPT for Disruption</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/chegg-stock-chgg-ai-chatgpt/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>BP Stock Tanked Over 5% Despite Company Beating Q1 2023 Profit Expectations</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bp-stock-q1-2023-profit/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 10:07:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wall Street]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bernard looney]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bp stock]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=252930</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bp-stock-q1-2023-profit/">BP Stock Tanked Over 5% Despite Company Beating Q1 2023 Profit Expectations</a></p>
<p>Amid lower fossil fuel costs, BP's profits tanked in comparison to the bumper profits recorded in 2022. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bp-stock-q1-2023-profit/">BP Stock Tanked Over 5% Despite Company Beating Q1 2023 Profit Expectations</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bp-stock-q1-2023-profit/">BP Stock Tanked Over 5% Despite Company Beating Q1 2023 Profit Expectations</a></p>
<p>On Tuesday, May 2, oil major <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/bp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">British Petroleum</a> (BP) reported stronger-than-expected first-quarter (<a href="https://www.bp.com/en/global/corporate/investors/results-and-presentations/quarterly-results-and-webcast.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Q1 2023</a>) profits, and rising from the previous quarter i.e. Q4 2022. However, the numbers were down from the exceptional profits that the company recorded during a blockbuster 2022 when fossil fuel prices shot up significantly following Russia&#8217;s invasion of Ukraine.</p>
<h2>BP Q1 2023 Performance</h2>
<p>During the first quarter, the British energy giant reported an underlying replacement cost profit of $4.96 billion. This was higher than the $4.8 billion net profit in Q4 2022 but lower than the $6.2 billion profit recorded in Q1 2022. Analysts expected British Petroleum to report $4.3 billion in profit during the first quarter this year.</p>
<p>The first quarter results from British Petroleum reflect robust oil and gas trading. Speaking on the development, BP CEO Bernard Looney <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/02/bp-earnings-q1-2023.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“This has been a quarter of strong performance and strategic delivery as we continue to focus on safe and reliable operations. And importantly we continue to deliver for shareholders, through disciplined investment, lowering net debt and growing distributions.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>BP Stock Price and Share BuyBack</h2>
<p>During the earning morning trade on the London stock exchange, shares of BP tanked by more than 5% while slipping to the bottom of the pan-European Stoxx 600 index. The energy giant said that it expects to deliver a share buyback of $4 billion a year. This is still at the lower end of the company&#8217;s $14 billion to $18 billion capital expenditure range.</p>
<p>For the year 2022, BP reported annual profits of $27.7 billion, more than double recorded in the previous year. The last time, the oil major recorded this massive profit was in 2008. Despite a barrage of criticism, big oil giants have sought to defend their profits highlighting the importance of energy security as the world transitions away from fossil fuel. BP is among the first energy giants to announce reaching an ambition of net-zero emissions by 2050.</p>
<p>However, shareholders have shared disappointment with some of the UK&#8217;s biggest pension funds expressing deep frustration. Some 17% of the shareholders have voted in favor of a resolution put forward by Dutch Group Follow This. This resolution calls for BP to align its 2030 emission reduction targets with the landmark Paris Agreement.</p>
<p>In addition to BP, French oil major TotalEnergies also kicked off its earnings season for the first quarter in line with analyst expectations. Amid lower fossil fuel prices, the company reported a 27% drop in net income to $6.5 billion.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sothebys-art-selling-nft-marketplace/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bp-stock-q1-2023-profit/">BP Stock Tanked Over 5% Despite Company Beating Q1 2023 Profit Expectations</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sotheby’s Launches Secondary Art-selling NFT Marketplace for Collectors &amp; Artists</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sothebys-art-selling-nft-marketplace/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 10:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sotheby's]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web3]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=252924</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sothebys-art-selling-nft-marketplace/">Sotheby’s Launches Secondary Art-selling NFT Marketplace for Collectors &#038; Artists</a></p>
<p>The new secondary art NFT marketplace by Sotheby’s also pays royalties from sales directly to the artists, from payments made by collectors.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sothebys-art-selling-nft-marketplace/">Sotheby’s Launches Secondary Art-selling NFT Marketplace for Collectors &#038; Artists</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sothebys-art-selling-nft-marketplace/">Sotheby’s Launches Secondary Art-selling NFT Marketplace for Collectors &#038; Artists</a></p>
<p>Sotheby’s has <a href="https://twitter.com/Sothebysverse/status/1653049950786265094" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">launched</a> an on-chain non-fungible token (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NFT</a>) marketplace that facilitates the sale of secondary digital art items. According to <a href="https://decrypt.co/138514/sothebys-launches-on-chain-nft-marketplace-for-secondary-art-sales" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Decrypt</a>, the New York-based auction house now supports secondary NFT sales, allowing artists to transact directly with collectors. For example, interested collectors can list and make offers on work from select artists.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="474" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">The next evolution of <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/SothebysMetaverse?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank">#SothebysMetaverse</a> is here! The most trusted and dynamic destination to collect, buy and sell remarkable digital works. </p>
<p>Explore: <a href="https://t.co/hZvYIkO3xx" target="_blank">https://t.co/hZvYIkO3xx</a> <a href="https://t.co/dCkaCKlXVm" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/dCkaCKlXVm</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Sotheby&#39;s Metaverse (@Sothebysverse) <a href="https://twitter.com/Sothebysverse/status/1653049950786265094?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank">May 1, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Sotheby’s Vice President and Head of NFTs and Digital Art, Michael Bouhanna, discussed the secondary NFT marketplace. According to Bouhanna, the offering marks an essential step in Sotheby’s evolution within the decentralized technology and Web3 space.</p>
<h2>More on Sotheby’s Secondary NFT Marketplace</h2>
<p>The Web3-embracing Sotheby’s peer-to-peer and fully on-chain secondary NFT initiative launched Monday on the auction house’s Metaverse platform. This latest addition supports NFT artwork minted on the Ethereum blockchain and scaling protocol Polygon. In a statement, Sotheby’s described both popular all-encompassing blockchains as the “networks of choice for NFT creators and collectors”.</p>
<p>Sotheby’s Metaverse secondary sales are wholly facilitated by automated smart contracts that accept <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ETH</a> and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/matic-network/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">MATIC</a> as payment for art collectibles. Powered by Serotonin-developed NFT tech and commerce suite Mojito, Sotheby’s Metaverse platform initially went live in October 2021. The popular auction house’s marketplace differs from OpenSea’s broad-scale, peer-to-peer NFT platform in terms of offerings. According to Sotheby’s, the value proposition of its NFTs is in the “rotating, curated selection of leading artists” carefully selected by its specialists. Furthermore, the British-founded American venture pointed out that its selection of secondary marketplace artists will change every few months.</p>
<p>Sotheby’s also revealed that its initial wave of artists would see collectors list and make offers on NFTs from 13 creators the company deems as pioneers. These digital art world leaders include Claire Silver, Tyler Hobbs, Sam Spratt, Diana Sinclair, Sofi Crespo, The Sarah Show, and XCOPY.</p>
<h2>Secondary Marketplaces &amp; On-chain Royalty Fees</h2>
<p>The secondary sales NFT marketplace is set up in a way that rewards artists via specified secondary on-chain royalty fees. Sotheby’s explained it will subtract a creator royalty fee from any secondary sales, typically 5% to 10% of the sale price. This fee is automatically paid into the artist’s wallet as broader discussions regarding NFT resale royalties take center stage.</p>
<p>For instance, in late March, generative art NFT platform Art Blocks debuted its NFT marketplace with enforced creator royalties. At the time, Art Blocks said it would not receive any platform fee for secondary trades through its marketplace. Instead, the company looked to honor artists’ own specified creator royalties.</p>
<p>In March, Art Blocks founder and chief executive officer Erick Calderon exposited further, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>“We are here to support the artists and the artists’ practices. How many artists had quit their jobs to be full-time artists because they were just thrilled with the idea of getting to pursue this?&#8230;The creator economy is empowering the creator with control over their own creation.”</p></blockquote>
<p>At the time, Calderon added that the most compelling thing in the secondary marketplace is a creator who provides a meaningful reward.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-chase-acquires-first-republic-bank/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sothebys-art-selling-nft-marketplace/">Sotheby’s Launches Secondary Art-selling NFT Marketplace for Collectors &#038; Artists</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>JPMorgan Chase Acquires First Republic Bank After Months-Long Crisis</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-chase-acquires-first-republic-bank/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 09:49:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Deals News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[first republic bank]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jamie dimon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jpmorgan chase]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=252940</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-chase-acquires-first-republic-bank/">JPMorgan Chase Acquires First Republic Bank After Months-Long Crisis</a></p>
<p>American multinational banking giant JPMorgan Chase has emerged as the lucky buyer of the embattled regional banking firm, First Republic Bank.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-chase-acquires-first-republic-bank/">JPMorgan Chase Acquires First Republic Bank After Months-Long Crisis</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-chase-acquires-first-republic-bank/">JPMorgan Chase Acquires First Republic Bank After Months-Long Crisis</a></p>
<p>As <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/01/first-republic-bank-failure.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reported</a> by CNBC, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/jpmorgan-chase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">JPMorgan Chase &amp; Co</a> (NYSE: JPM) acquired all of the deposits of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/first-republic-bank/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">First Republic Bank</a> (NYSE: FRC) and a substantial number of its shares. The acquisition was made possible after regulators took a hold of the bank on Monday. This notably placed the collapse of First Republic Bank as the worst in the US banking ecosystem since 2008. According to JPMorgan, it considers the acquisition as its own way of helping to maintain the integrity of the US financial ecosystem.</p>
<p>“Our government invited us and others to step up, and we did,” <a href="https://www.jpmorganchase.com/ir/news/2023/jpmc-acquires-substantial-majority-of-assets-and-assumes-certain-liabilities-of-first-republic-bank" target="_blank" rel="noopener">said</a> Chairman and Chief Executive Officer of JPMorgan Chase <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/jamie-dimon/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Jamie Dimon</a>. “Our financial strength, capabilities and business model allowed us to develop a bid to execute the transaction in a way to minimize costs to the Deposit Insurance Fund.”</p>
<p>According to JPMorgan Chase, the deal saw it scoop up $173 billion of loans and approximately $30 billion of securities belonging to First Republic Bank. The combined deposit value of FRC acquired by JPMorgan came in at $92 billion. Notably, this includes the $30 billion that was <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/first-republic-shares-bank-rescue/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">availed</a> to the collapsed bank by large financial institutions in the US. The firm said these deposits will be repaid in full before closing the deal.</p>
<p>“This acquisition modestly benefits our company overall, it is accretive to shareholders, it helps further advance our wealth strategy, and it is complementary to our existing franchise,” Dimon said.</p>
<p>There has been a lot of commentary with respect to the takeover of FRC by JPMorgan. While some have tagged the acquisition as a way in which the government is consolidating the financial system in readiness for a potential Digital Dollar, others believe the whole move reveals the fragility of the US banking system.</p>
<h2>Future of First Republic as a JPMorgan Offshoot</h2>
<p>JPMorgan is one of the biggest banking giants in the United States and for what it is worth, First Republic will benefit from the deep capital base the firm has, as well as its deep client base.</p>
<p>JPMorgan said that it expects the transaction to be “modestly EPS accretive and generate more than $500 million of incremental net income per year, not including the approximately $2.6 billion one-time post-tax gain or approximately $2.0 billion of post-tax restructuring costs expected over the course of 2023 and 2024.”</p>
<p>Despite the collapse of First Republic, it was acknowledged that the bank dealt with its clients with a high level of integrity. This, JPMorgan noted, will be beneficial to sustaining the bank’s business moving forward.</p>
<p>The shares of JPMorgan popped following the acquisition news. At the close of Monday’s trading session, JPM closed at 2.14% to $141.20. First Republic stock is down 45% in the after hours.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-market-q1-2023/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-chase-acquires-first-republic-bank/">JPMorgan Chase Acquires First Republic Bank After Months-Long Crisis</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>European Market Shakes Off Recession Fears but Misses Q1 2023 Growth Estimates</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-market-q1-2023/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 13:44:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ecb]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=252849</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-market-q1-2023/">European Market Shakes Off Recession Fears but Misses Q1 2023 Growth Estimates</a></p>
<p>The European market recorded a gross domestic product (GDP) of  0.0 percent in the first quarter of 2023 compared with the fourth quarter of 2022.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-market-q1-2023/">European Market Shakes Off Recession Fears but Misses Q1 2023 Growth Estimates</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-market-q1-2023/">European Market Shakes Off Recession Fears but Misses Q1 2023 Growth Estimates</a></p>
<p>The European economy displayed market resilience during the first quarter despite being cut off from the Russian oil and gas supply since the invasion of Ukraine. The EU market was, however, marred by rising inflation amid bank deposits flight similar to the United States banking crisis. Nonetheless, the European Central Bank has continued to raise interest rates, with the recent update pushing by 50 basis points, to fight the high core inflation.</p>
<p>Notably, some ECB policymakers are working on further raising interest rates next week by about 25 basis points, which could push the core interest rate above 3 percent. The Euro Zone is currently fighting inflation of 6.9 percent and core inflation of about 5.7 percent.</p>
<h2>European Market Economic Outlook</h2>
<p>During the first quarter, the Euro Zone economy grew by 0.1 percent, according to preliminary figures released on Friday. The EU bloc missed analysts’ forecast on first quarter growth, which was expected at 0.2 percent, according to a poll conducted by Reuters. Nonetheless, the European economy expanded by approximately 1.3 percent on an annualized basis but still missed analysts&#8217; expectations of 1.4 percent.</p>
<p>According to a report by <a href="https://www.destatis.de/EN/Press/2023/04/PE23_169_811.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">destatis</a>, the European market recorded a gross domestic product (GDP) of  0.0 percent in the first quarter of 2023 compared with the fourth quarter of 2022. Additionally, data from the Federal Statistical Office (Destatis) showed that the final consumption expenditure of both households and the government declined at the beginning of 2023 in the Eurozone. Reportedly, positive contributions came from capital formation and exports in the European market during the first quarter.</p>
<p>Earlier this month, data from Eurostat showed a revision downward in the fourth-quarter 2022 GDP estimate for the eurozone from 0.1 percent quarterly growth to no growth, following a 0.4 percent growth during the third quarter of last year.</p>
<p>The European market was able to evade a much-feared recession during the first quarter of 2023. According to Carsten Brzeski, global head of macro at Dutch bank ING, the fall in wholesale energy prices, warmer-than-expected weather, and fiscal stimulus helped the European market dodge a widely-feared recession over the winter.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, Brzeski indicated that the data from individual countries will be crucial for the bloc&#8217;s future growth prospects. Moreover, the ongoing race between positive momentum in European countries and wage growth on the other hand has pushed the ECB to further monetary tightening policies.</p>
<p>As a result, the European Union regulators could be looking at diversifying leading economies like Germany, and France amid the looming United States feared recession in the second half of 2023.</p>
<p>Read other <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/markets/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">market news</a> on our website.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/h-c-wainwright-crypto-winter/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-market-q1-2023/">European Market Shakes Off Recession Fears but Misses Q1 2023 Growth Estimates</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Investment Bank H.C. Wainwright Believes Crypto Winter Is Over, Rates Coinbase Stock as ‘Buy’ </title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/h-c-wainwright-crypto-winter/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 13:05:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coin stock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase stock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[h c wainwright]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=252833</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/h-c-wainwright-crypto-winter/">Investment Bank H.C. Wainwright Believes Crypto Winter Is Over, Rates Coinbase Stock as ‘Buy’ </a></p>
<p>Analysts at H.C. Wainwright have said that the crypto winter of 2022 ceases to have any bearing on related stocks. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/h-c-wainwright-crypto-winter/">Investment Bank H.C. Wainwright Believes Crypto Winter Is Over, Rates Coinbase Stock as ‘Buy’ </a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/h-c-wainwright-crypto-winter/">Investment Bank H.C. Wainwright Believes Crypto Winter Is Over, Rates Coinbase Stock as ‘Buy’ </a></p>
<p>H.C. Wainwright believes that the crypto winter is over and has called for a buy on <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase</a> (NASDAQ: COIN) stock. According to the New York-based investment bank, Coinbase stands to benefit from global digital asset economy growth sooner rather than later. H.C. Wainwright released a <a href="https://hcwco.bluematrix.com/sellside/EmailDocViewer?encrypt=2b411f55-2386-4e7f-8f86-4cf9037b824d&amp;mime=pdf&amp;co=Hcwco&amp;id=jayson.derrick@investoogroup.com&amp;source=mail" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">statement</a> on Wednesday that underscored its bullishness on the prices of crypto assets.</p>
<p>The investment banking platform wrote:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Crypto asset prices have rallied 45% YTD, supported by a 67% increase in BTC prices, indicating to us that crypto winter is over and that we have likely now entered BTC’s next bull price cycle (not baked into current estimates), which has historically resulted in significant growth in total crypto market cap, incremental retail, and institutional adoption, and higher crypto trading volumes.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Summing up these key metrics as a driver of Coinbase’s operating results, including transaction revenues, H.C. Wainwright also said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“[As a leading exchange in the US and the world], we believe Coinbase is uniquely positioned to benefit from the large and rapidly growing global crypto economy given its trusted brand, easy-to-use products, and focus on compliance and regulation, and we expect the company to gain market share in 2023.”</p></blockquote>
<p>According to the bank, Coinbase’s revenues would become more “durable” over time due to its increasingly alternate revenue sources. Besides generating income from transaction-based fees, Coinbase has started leaning toward subscription and service revenues.</p>
<h2>H.C. Wainwright Analyst Identifies Coinbase as Only Exchange Valued at Over $10 Billion in Light of Crypto Winter</h2>
<p>H.C. Wainwright analyst Mike Colonnese posted a ‘Buy’ rating for Coinbase, explaining that “rewards outweigh risks at these prices.” Furthermore, the analyst stated that COIN, currently trading at $54.17, is a “scarce asset” unlikely to change over the near term. Colonnese also pointed out that the major crypto exchange is the only US publicly-listed crypto company with a market cap exceeding $10 billion. As a result, the analyst concluded that competition for investor capital remains extremely limited.</p>
<p>Although the Nasdaq-listed COIN closed 3% lower on Wednesday and at 85% lower than its November 2021 peak, Wainwright analysts opine the stock is still an attractive prospect. These analysts say Coinbase’s share price levels offer investors an attractive entry point because the stock trades at a 35% discount to historical highs.</p>
<h2>Coinbase vs SEC</h2>
<p>In other recent Coinbase news, the exchange sued the Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) over crypto regulatory guideline differences. In its lawsuit, the American exchange asked the court to require crypto clarity from the securities regulator. Coinbase called for the SEC to respond to its July 2022 petition promptly. In the previous petition, the exchange suggested that the Commission propose and adopt more explicit regulatory guidelines for the US crypto space via its formal rulemaking process. More than 1,700 individuals and entities have since submitted comments on Coinbase’s petition, also calling for more regulatory clarity from the SEC.</p>
<p>Yesterday, Coinbase <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-sec-wells-notice-securities/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">firmly responded</a> to a Wells Notice from the SEC last month, claiming no violation of securities laws. The exchange’s chief legal officer Paul Grewal accused the regulator of refusing to engage in meaningful dialogue regarding crypto regulations. Furthermore, Coinbase also suggested that the SEC had been intimidating several other exchanges over securities law violations. However, Coinbase expressed its intent to remain unshaken as it has not committed any wrongdoings.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-cloud-polygon-web3/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/h-c-wainwright-crypto-winter/">Investment Bank H.C. Wainwright Believes Crypto Winter Is Over, Rates Coinbase Stock as ‘Buy’ </a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4571 metric#misses=43 metric#hit-ratio=99.1 metric#bytes=1230172 metric#prefetches=188 metric#store-reads=22 metric#store-writes=22 metric#store-hits=195 metric#store-misses=4 metric#sql-queries=34 metric#ms-total=100.72 metric#ms-cache=7.26 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.1687 metric#ms-cache-ratio=7.2 sample#redis-hits=644892704 sample#redis-misses=53118227 sample#redis-hit-ratio=92.4 sample#redis-ops-per-sec=337 sample#redis-evicted-keys=24206259 sample#redis-used-memory=413108440 sample#redis-used-memory-rss=499056640 sample#redis-memory-fragmentation-ratio=1.2 sample#redis-connected-clients=2 sample#redis-tracking-clients=0 sample#redis-rejected-connections=0 sample#redis-keys=670139 -->