<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 20:36:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Tezos price prediction: a look at XTZ and network metrics</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/tezos-price-prediction-a-look-at-xtz-and-network-metrics/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/tezos-price-prediction-a-look-at-xtz-and-network-metrics/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 20:36:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tezos News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XTZ]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/tezos-price-prediction-a-look-at-xtz-and-network-metrics/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Tezos (XTZ) price is down 2% this past week as cryptocurrencies struggle for direction. XTZ trades near $0.80 and risks declines to $0.65 if bears take control. However, network metrics suggest a resurgence in activity after recent upgrades &#8211; which could catalyse upside momentum. Tezos is largely unchanged in the past 24 hours as most [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tezos-price-prediction-a-look-at-xtz-and-network-metrics/">Tezos price prediction: a look at XTZ and network metrics</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Tezos (XTZ) price is down 2% this past week as cryptocurrencies struggle for direction.</li>
<li dir="ltr">XTZ trades near $0.80 and risks declines to $0.65 if bears take control.</li>
<li dir="ltr">However, network metrics suggest a resurgence in activity after recent upgrades &ndash; which could catalyse upside momentum.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/tezos/">Tezos</a> is largely unchanged in the past 24 hours as most cryptocurrencies either retreat from recent highs or consolidate at levels that have held for much of July.</p>
<p dir="ltr">XTZ, which traded to highs of $0.90 on Monday, looks to be in the former group as its price hovers near $0.80. The coin&rsquo;s current price levels are at a similar base seen on July 12 when bulls went on to test resistance above $0.92.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Tezos upgrades could catalyse network growth</h2>
<p dir="ltr">According to data shared by crypto market intelligence platform Messari, Tezos has seen reduced activity since Q4, 2022. Account-related metrics such as active accounts have declined by 20% in the last three months compared to the first quarter.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The network has also recorded a decrease in new account registrations, with this down 16% QoQ, Messari pointed out in a <a href="https://messari.io/report/state-of-tezos-q2-2023" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">report</a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, according to Messari, Tezos&rsquo; recent upgrades of Mumbai and Nairobi could catalyse fresh network growth. For instance, Mumbai has enabled decentralised app development via different languages, a scenario that will attract more developers to build on the network.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">5/ Additionally, the recently released <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Nairobi?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Nairobi</a> upgrade added notable features including an up to 8x increase in TPS, new functionality for Smart Rollups, a renaming of endorsements to attestations, faster propagation of pre-attestations, and more.</p>
<p>&mdash; Messari (@MessariCrypto) <a href="https://twitter.com/MessariCrypto/status/1683897441622564864?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 25, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">The Nairobi upgrade is another development that could bump usage, particularly with the TPS increased 8x and <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/xtz-price-outlook-as-mumbai-upgrade-goes-live-on-tezos/">introduction of Smart Rollups</a> among other improvements. Can these positives help XTZ price?</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">XTZ price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr">As shown in the chart below, the price of Tezos&rsquo; native token has largely fluctuated between $0.65 and $1.2 since November 2022. &nbsp;But with a breakdown below $1 in recent weeks, it looks like bears could aim for the range lows again.</p>
<div class="fr-img-space-wrap"><span class="fr-img-caption fr-fic fr-dib fr-draggable" style="width: 700px"><span class="fr-img-wrap">
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/25/1690317078562-98a0b850-c7e7-4512-a6ce-e7efe71dd49b.png" style="width: 700px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="700" height="320"><span class="fr-inner">Tezos price on a weekly chart.Source:&nbsp;<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/ANL6q0oh/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">TradingView</a></span></p>
<p></p></span></span>
<p class="fr-img-space-wrap2">The weekly RSI is beneath the neutral point and sloping to strengthen the bearish outlook. However, bulls can still take control if they push towards the psychological area mentioned above.</p>
</div>
<p dir="ltr">Here the 20 and 50 EMA suggest robust resistance at $0.98 and $1.26. Tezos bulls can target $2.0 if they achieve the above.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tezos-price-prediction-a-look-at-xtz-and-network-metrics/">Tezos price prediction: a look at XTZ and network metrics</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/tezos-price-prediction-a-look-at-xtz-and-network-metrics/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase makes special announcement for HNT, BLUR, ARB and four other altcoins</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-makes-special-announcement-for-hnt-blur-arb-and-four-other-altcoins/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-makes-special-announcement-for-hnt-blur-arb-and-four-other-altcoins/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 18:09:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Germany]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-makes-special-announcement-for-hnt-blur-arb-and-four-other-altcoins/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto exchange Coinbase has listed 8 tokens accessible on Coinbase.com and mobile HNT, BLUR, ARB, EGLD, 00, AUDIO, LDO, ATA &#160;are now tradable on Coinbase in Germany. Dogecoin continues to outperform the market after X news. Coinbase, the leading US-based cryptocurrency exchange, has made a special announcement touching on eight altcoins. The crypto exchange&#8217;s announcement [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-makes-special-announcement-for-hnt-blur-arb-and-four-other-altcoins/">Coinbase makes special announcement for HNT, BLUR, ARB and four other altcoins</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Crypto exchange Coinbase has listed 8 tokens accessible on Coinbase.com and mobile</li>
<li dir="ltr">HNT, BLUR, ARB, EGLD, 00, AUDIO, LDO, ATA &nbsp;are now tradable on Coinbase in Germany.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Dogecoin continues to outperform the market after X news.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/coinbase/">Coinbase</a>, the leading US-based cryptocurrency exchange, has made a special announcement touching on eight <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/altcoins/">altcoins</a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The crypto exchange&rsquo;s announcement says these tokens are now available for trading in <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/germany/">Germany</a>, one of the European countries with the highest number of crypto owners.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Helium (HNT), Blur (BLUR), Arbitrum (ARB)&nbsp;</h2>
<p dir="ltr">According to the platform, these tokens are Helium (HNT), Blur (BLUR), Arbitrum (ARB), MultiversX (EGLD), 00 Token (00), Audius (AUDIO), Lido DAO (LDO) and Automata (ATA). The crypto assets are &ldquo;available to Germany residents&rdquo;, the announcement read.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">HNT, BLUR, ARB, EGLD, 00, AUDIO, LDO, ATA are now available to Germany residents.</p>
<p>&mdash; Coinbase Assets &#128737;&#65039; (@CoinbaseAssets) <a href="https://twitter.com/CoinbaseAssets/status/1683863901983608837?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 25, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>Users can log in to buy, sell, convert, send, receive, or store these assets at Coinbase.com along with the Coinbase iOS and Android apps. To access trading, users may need to refresh their application</em>,&rdquo; the company posted on its Coinbase Assets account on X (formerly Twitter).</p>
<p dir="ltr">Some of the listed tokens saw a surge in their prices following the development. However, many remained constrained as top cryptocurrencies struggled to hold onto gains. As Bitcoin hovered near $29k, altcoins like XRP and Solana were looking to keep bears off near key technical levels.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Meanwhile, <a href="https://coinjournal.net/dogecoin/">Dogecoin</a> continued to see upside action following yesterday&rsquo;s Twitter rebranding to X. With speculation about a potential integration of DOGE as a payment currency on X Payments, the price of DOGE rose more than 10% in the past 24 hours.</p>
<p dir="ltr">At the time of writing, the meme coin was trading above $0.081, its highest price since April.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-makes-special-announcement-for-hnt-blur-arb-and-four-other-altcoins/">Coinbase makes special announcement for HNT, BLUR, ARB and four other altcoins</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-makes-special-announcement-for-hnt-blur-arb-and-four-other-altcoins/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alchemix, Connext eye bridge security with xERC20 token standard</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/alchemix-connext-eye-bridge-security-with-xerc20-token-standard/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 17:21:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/alchemix-connext-eye-bridge-security-with-xerc20-token-standard/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Alchemix and Connext say the new token standard will benefit token issuers. DeFi bridges suffered exploits that saw over $2 billion stolen in 2022. Multichain bridge, which recently announced it was ending operations, is among those to be drained this year. DeFi protocol Alchemix and cross-chain bridge Connext have partnered in an effort that aims [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/alchemix-connext-eye-bridge-security-with-xerc20-token-standard/">Alchemix, Connext eye bridge security with xERC20 token standard</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Alchemix and Connext say the new token standard will benefit token issuers.</li>
<li dir="ltr">DeFi bridges suffered exploits that saw over $2 billion stolen in 2022.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Multichain bridge, which recently announced it was ending operations, is among those to be drained this year.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">DeFi protocol Alchemix and cross-chain bridge Connext have partnered in an effort that aims to introduce robust security to crypto bridges.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As announced by Alchemix, the two platforms are working together on a new Ethereum token standard dubbed xERC-20. The platforms <a href="https://twitter.com/ConnextNetwork/status/1683504352139288578" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">revealed</a> the move on Monday.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">We&rsquo;re extremely excited to embrace the <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/xERC20?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#xERC20</a> token standard that encourages open competition &amp; innovation. Reduced liquidity costs for token issuers + granular security &#128588;.<a href="https://twitter.com/AlchemixFi?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@AlchemixFi</a> is the 1st adopter via <a href="https://twitter.com/ConnextNetwork?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@ConnextNetwork</a>, with more trailblazers to follow!</p>
<p>1/9 <a href="https://t.co/ujUCVjhTY9">pic.twitter.com/ujUCVjhTY9</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Connext (@ConnextNetwork) <a href="https://twitter.com/ConnextNetwork/status/1683504352139288578?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 24, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">xERC20 token standard increases DeFi bridge security</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Per Alchemix and Connext, the new token standard empowers token issuers in several ways, including in bridge management, setting of mint limits, and allowing certain bridges to access identical token mints.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>It&rsquo;s a bridge-agnostic public good and requires minimal or no custom work for most ecosystems to support</em>,&rdquo; Connext noted.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>We&rsquo;re wholeheartedly embracing xERC20 at Connext because we envision a secure and innovative future for tokens and blockchain communication. As the HTTP of Web3, we&rsquo;re all about making blockchain apps more user-friendly &amp; minimizing security risks</em>,&rdquo; the protocol added in details shared on X.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to the team, projects that deploy the new xERC20 token standard with Connext benefit from increased security against potential DeFi exploits. There&rsquo;s also 1:1 token transfers between chains with zero slippage.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The integration comes not long after the Multichain Bridge was breached in an attack that saw it lose close to $130 million. The protocol recently <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/cross-chain-bridge-protocol-multichain-ceases-operations/">announced</a> it was halting operations.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Chainalysis <a href="https://blog.chainalysis.com/reports/cross-chain-bridge-hacks-2022/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>reported</u></a> that token bridge exploits saw more than $2 billion in crypto assets stolen in 2022. This year has continued to see such vulnerability, with millions siphoned from platforms as the sector grapples with increased hacks.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/alchemix-connext-eye-bridge-security-with-xerc20-token-standard/">Alchemix, Connext eye bridge security with xERC20 token standard</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Avalanche Foundation allocates $50M to new tokenization program</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/avalanche-foundation-allocates-50m-for-tokenized-assets-purchase-program/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 16:24:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Avalanche News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/avalanche-foundation-allocates-50m-for-tokenized-assets-purchase-program/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Avalanche Foundation wants to promote tokenization on Avalanche with the $50 million program. The tokenized assets initiative is dubbed Avalanche Vista. A recent survey report suggested 77% of capital markets participants believe in tokenization of securities. The Avalanche Foundation has announced an allocation of up to $50 million towards an initiative aimed at pioneering the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/avalanche-foundation-allocates-50m-for-tokenized-assets-purchase-program/">Avalanche Foundation allocates $50M to new tokenization program</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Avalanche Foundation wants to promote tokenization on Avalanche with the $50 million program.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The tokenized assets initiative is dubbed Avalanche Vista.</li>
<li dir="ltr">A recent survey report suggested 77% of capital markets participants believe in tokenization of securities.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">The Avalanche Foundation has <a href="https://www.avax.network/blog/avalanche-foundation-vista-asset-tokenization" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">announced</a> an allocation of up to $50 million towards an initiative aimed at pioneering the future of tokenization on the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/avalanche/">Avalanche</a> blockchain.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to the foundation, the funds will be used to purchase tokenized assets, or &ldquo;real world assets&rdquo; minted on Avalanche.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Today, the Avalanche Foundation introduces Avalanche Vista, a $50M initiative to pioneer tokenization on <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Avalanche?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Avalanche</a></p>
<p>Tokenization is poised to be one of the most impactful blockchain innovations of the next decade, and Avalanche is uniquely equipped to power these systems. <a href="https://t.co/ZWy109CMCi">pic.twitter.com/ZWy109CMCi</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Avalanche &#128314; (@avax) <a href="https://twitter.com/avax/status/1683843321670807554?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 25, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Eyeing tokenization on Avalanche</h2>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;Avalanche Vista,&rdquo; is meant to demonstrate how tokenization is a valuable process in the creation of an on-chain digital representation of real world assets, the team noted. The allocation will help accelerate the growth of on-chain finance, with tokenization showcasing the critical role of blockchain across use cases such as asset issuance, settlement, and transfer.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Per the announcement, Avalanche Vista will apply across all types of assets, both traditional and blockchain-native. For the former, the program will consider equity, real estate, commodities, and credit.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>Asset tokenization isn&rsquo;t just the future of capital markets, it&rsquo;s a critical driver of the present</em>,&rdquo; Ava Labs President John Wu said.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">He noted that the industry is seeing greater momentum from institutions building on-chain, and that Avalanche Vista is a milestone for Avalanche Foundation with regard to promoting this initiative.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Avalanche&rsquo;s program follows a number of key developments within the asset tokenization space. Among these was the tokenization of interest in the KKR fund and the launch of tokenized assets marketplace IntainMARKETS.</p>
<p dir="ltr">A recent report by Security Token Advisors revealed that about 77% of participants across the capital markets see traditional securities being digitized over the next five to ten years. Meanwhile, the tokenized securities market is projected to grow to $20 trillion by 2030.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/avalanche-foundation-allocates-50m-for-tokenized-assets-purchase-program/">Avalanche Foundation allocates $50M to new tokenization program</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Avalanche price prediction as it targets a $30 trillion industry</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/avalanche-price-prediction-as-it-targets-a-30-trillion-industry/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/avalanche-price-prediction-as-it-targets-a-30-trillion-industry/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 15:59:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Avalanche News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/avalanche-price-prediction-as-it-targets-a-30-trillion-industry/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Avalanche has underperformed the crypto market in the past few weeks. Avalanche is now targeting the $30 trillion tokenization industry. Avalanche price remained under pressure as cryptocurrencies retreated. The AVAX coin retreated to a low of $12.84, the lowest level since July 13th. It has dropped by more than 16% from the highest point this [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/avalanche-price-prediction-as-it-targets-a-30-trillion-industry/">Avalanche price prediction as it targets a $30 trillion industry</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Avalanche has underperformed the crypto market in the past few weeks.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Avalanche is now targeting the $30 trillion tokenization industry.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/avalanche/"><u>Avalanche</u></a> price remained under pressure as cryptocurrencies retreated. The AVAX coin retreated to a low of $12.84, the lowest level since July 13th. It has dropped by more than 16% from the highest point this month.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Avalanche focuses on tokenization</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Avalanche crypto price has been under intense pressure in the past few months as activity in its ecosystem continues. A closer look at its DeFi platform shows that the total value locked (TVL) in its ecosystem stands at over $1.76 billion.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">At its peak, Avalanche had a TVL of over $21 billion. Some of the most popular dApps in its ecosystem are Wonderland,&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/aave/"><u>Aave</u></a>, Benqi, GMX, and Trader Joe among others. These dApps have seen their activity retreat. For example, the trading volume of GMX in Arbitrum is much bigger than that in Avalanche.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Avalanche is now focusing on tokenization. In a statement, the Avalanche Foundation said that it willl purchase tokenized assets minted in its ecosystem worth over $50 million. This program has been christened as Avalanche Vista.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Most analysts believe that tokenization is the future of the crypto industry. For example, Franklin Templeton, one of the biggest companies in finance, announced that its OnChain US Government Money Market Fund (FOBXX) was now in Polygon. In a report, Boston Consulting Group has estimated that tokenized assets could jump to over $30 trillion.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Avalanche is now entering an industry that is highly competitive. Some of the top players in the industry are Ethereum, Zilliqa,&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/solana"><u>Solana</u></a>, and Polygon. In a note, the CEO of Intain said:</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;Moving parts of the asset administration process on-chain allows issuers to have one workflow and one system of record, enabling a better, more seamless user experience for service providers and investors.&rdquo;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Avalanche price prediction</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/25/1690300735746-fb3e281d-f32f-45a2-86e6-0f5afa63e4e6.png" style="width: 693px;height: 337.26px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="693" height="337.26"></p>
<p dir="ltr">The daily chart shows that the AVAX price has been under pressure in the past few days. It has moved below the 25-day and 50-day exponential moving averages (EMA). The token has moved slightly above the lower side of the ascending channel shown in black. Further, the MACD is nearing the neutral point.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, the AVAX token will likely continue falling as sellers target the key support at $11.10, the lowest level on June 18th.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy Avalanche</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>

    <p>eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=MTQ3NTM2&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy AVAX with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    Public</h3>

    <p>Public is an investing platform that allows you to invest stocks, ETFs, crypto, and alternative assets like fine art and collectibles&mdash;all in one place.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/public-crypto?guid=MTQ3NTM2&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy AVAX with Public today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptocurrency execution and custody services are provided by Apex Crypto LLC (NMLS ID 1828849) through a software licensing agreement between Apex Crypto LLC and Public Crypto LLC. Crypto trading on Public platforms is served by Public Crypto LLC and offered through APEX Crypto. Please ensure that you fully understand the risks involved before trading." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/avalanche-price-prediction-as-it-targets-a-30-trillion-industry/">Avalanche price prediction as it targets a $30 trillion industry</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/avalanche-price-prediction-as-it-targets-a-30-trillion-industry/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin drops to $29k: will it dip further to the $25k support level?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-drops-to-29k-will-it-dip-further-to-the-25k-support-level/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-drops-to-29k-will-it-dip-further-to-the-25k-support-level/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 15:48:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-drops-to-29k-will-it-dip-further-to-the-25k-support-level/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways Bitcoin dropped below the $29k level on Monday as the market sheds its recent gains. AltSignal&#8217;s stage two presale has now surpassed the $1.2 million mark. The cryptocurrency market has been underperforming in recent weeks. Barring last week&#8217;s rally fueled by Ripple&#8217;s win against the US SEC, the market has underperformed. Despite the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-drops-to-29k-will-it-dip-further-to-the-25k-support-level/">Bitcoin drops to $29k: will it dip further to the $25k support level?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin dropped below the $29k level on Monday as the market sheds its recent gains.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">AltSignal&rsquo;s stage two presale has now surpassed the $1.2 million mark.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">The cryptocurrency market has been underperforming in recent weeks. Barring last week&rsquo;s rally fueled by Ripple&rsquo;s win against the US SEC, the market has underperformed.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Despite the market&rsquo;s poor performance, AltSignals&rsquo; presale continues to proceed excellently, with the team raising $1.2 million so far in stage two of the presale.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitcoin struggling around the $29k region</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin, the world&rsquo;s leading cryptocurrency by market cap, has been underperforming in recent weeks. BTC has lost more than 2% of its value since the start of the week and is struggling to maintain its value above $29k.</p>
<p dir="ltr">At press time, the&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>price of Bitcoin</u></a> stands at $29,197. Despite the recent bearish trend, most market analysts are optimistic that Bitcoin could rally higher over the coming months. The recent pullback is considered by many as a buying opportunity.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Despite the market&rsquo;s poor performance, AltSignals&rsquo; presale has been going on excellent.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The&nbsp;<a href="https://token.altsignals.io/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=invezz&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>AltSignals</u></a> team has completed more than 50% of stage two of its presale, with more than $1.2 million raised so far.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">AltSignals&rsquo; second stage of presale tops $1.2 million</h2>
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals began the second stage of its presale a few weeks ago and has already crossed an important milestone. The team has raised $1.2 million so far, 53% of the total amount required in this presale stage.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">During the stage one presale, the ASI token was sold for $0.015 USDT. however, the ASI token is now going for 0.01875 USDT. With a target of over $2 million in the second stage, AltSignals has already raised more than $1.2 million so far.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://token.altsignals.io/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=invezz&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>AltSignals</u></a> is currently working on launching numerous products for its users. It is a unique project that seeks to leverage AI and blockchain technology to make it easier for people to trade Bitcoin and a host of other cryptocurrencies.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://token.altsignals.io/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=invezz&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Click here</u></a> to read more about the AltSignals presale.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is AltSignals?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals is a cryptocurrency project that targets traders within the crypto and broader financial market. Its products could be beneficial to crypto traders, forex, stock, commodities, and indices traders.</p>
<p dir="ltr">With AltSignals, traders would have access to trading signals and other trading resources, making it easier for them to trade crypto and other financial assets.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to their whitepaper, the funds raised from the presale would be used to develop ActualizeAI, an AI solution that could make it easier for people to trade cryptos and other financial assets.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">ActualizeAI is an automated trading solution that operates 24/7. The solution helps traders to identify various patterns in the market, eliminating some of the pain points traders experience.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">ASI token is the utility token that powers the entire&nbsp;<a href="https://token.altsignals.io/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=invezz&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>AltSignals</u></a> ecosystem. The platform will leverage numerous technologies, including natural language processing, machine learning, regression, and predictive modelling, to enhance its services.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Following the end of its presale, ASI would be listed on centralised and decentralised cryptocurrency exchanges, including Uniswap.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">AltSignals (ASI) price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Predicting ASI&rsquo;s price in the medium or long term is quite impossible due to the fact that the token is still in its presale stage.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The ASI token will be listed on numerous cryptocurrency exchanges once the presale stages are completed. Listing on crypto exchanges could see ASI&rsquo;s price soar higher in the near or medium term.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Furthermore,&nbsp;<a href="https://token.altsignals.io/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=invezz&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>AltSignals&rsquo;</u></a> adoption by traders could help push ASI&rsquo;s price higher over the next few months and years&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Another factor that could positively affect ASI&rsquo;s price is the performance of the broader cryptocurrency market. Bitcoin and other major cryptocurrencies are up by more than 40% year-to-date.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">If the market sentiment improves, ASI could become one of the biggest winners in the market.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Should I buy AltSignals in its presale?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Assets in their presale stage are usually smart investments as they mostly trade at their lowest. Some of the leading cryptocurrency projects, including Solana and Ethereum, generated thousands of percentages in ROI for early investors.</p>
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals is a project that could gain massive adoption, especially by cryptocurrency traders, if the development team fulfils its promise and deliver excellent products to its users.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-drops-to-29k-will-it-dip-further-to-the-25k-support-level/">Bitcoin drops to $29k: will it dip further to the $25k support level?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-drops-to-29k-will-it-dip-further-to-the-25k-support-level/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ducati announces NFT debut on XRP Ledger</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/ducati-announces-nft-debut-on-xrp-ledger/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/ducati-announces-nft-debut-on-xrp-ledger/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 14:29:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/ducati-announces-nft-debut-on-xrp-ledger/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ducati will debut its digital collectibles on the XRP Ledger. The Bologna-based motorcycle company will work with NFT PRO on this project. XRP Ledger is a decentralised public blockchain that uses XRP as its native cryptocurrency. Ducati, a Bologna-based motorcycle manufacturer, is making a foray into Web3 with an upcoming launch of a digital collectible [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ducati-announces-nft-debut-on-xrp-ledger/">Ducati announces NFT debut on XRP Ledger</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Ducati will debut its digital collectibles on the XRP Ledger.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The Bologna-based motorcycle company will work with NFT PRO on this project.</li>
<li dir="ltr">XRP Ledger is a decentralised public blockchain that uses XRP as its native cryptocurrency.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Ducati, a Bologna-based motorcycle manufacturer, is making a foray into Web3 with an upcoming launch of a digital collectible project.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The company said in an <a href="https://www.ducati.com/ww/en/news/ducati-announces-its-entry-into-the-world-of-web-3-0-in-partnership-with-nft-pro" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">announcement</a> on Tuesday that it will deploy its new NFT collection on the XRP Ledger, a decentralised public blockchain network. <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/ripple/">Ripple</a> is a contributor on the XRPL.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Ducati makes entry into Web3</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Ducati has partnered with NFT PRO, a corporate white-label NFT solution, to bring the project to life. According to the company, the digital collectibles project its digital strategy as it looks to add to the engagement and experiences of its fans. &nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>Entering WEB 3.0 is another way to get closer to the Ducatisti community by further extending the number of services offered to them. It also represents an opportunity to meet and make ourselves known to a new community of NFT enthusiasts, giving them the opportunity to live unique Ducati-style experiences and collect the digital assets that we will develop exclusively for this new dimension of the brand</em>,&rdquo; Claudio Domenicali, Ducati CEO, said in a statement.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The bike company says it will release more details in coming months as it rolls out new digital services and goods.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Ripple&rsquo;s <em>XRP Markets Report</em> <a href="https://ripple.com/insights/q1-2023-xrp-markets-report/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">published</a> in April indicated that the XRP Ledger logged increased activity in the first quarter compared to the previous three month period. In terms of on-chain activity, the company noted a 9% increase in transactions from 106 million to 116 million between Q4, 2022 and Q1, 2023.</p>
<p dir="ltr">NFTs are a key component of the XRPL activities, as it has seen users mint more than 1 million assets. DEX volumes, which jumped 34% in the period covered in the report, also demonstrated the increased usage of the blockchain network, Ripple said.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ducati-announces-nft-debut-on-xrp-ledger/">Ducati announces NFT debut on XRP Ledger</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/ducati-announces-nft-debut-on-xrp-ledger/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Venom blockchain surpasses one million registered wallets in three months</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/venom-blockchain-surpasses-one-million-registered-wallets-in-three-months/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/venom-blockchain-surpasses-one-million-registered-wallets-in-three-months/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 14:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/venom-blockchain-surpasses-one-million-registered-wallets-in-three-months/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways The Venom blockchain has reached one million registered wallets within three months. The Venom Foundation is focused on making the adoption of blockchain technology mainstream. The Venom Foundation announced on Tuesday, July 25th, that its blockchain has surpassed one million registered wallets. This latest milestone was achieved within three months. The Venom testnet [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/venom-blockchain-surpasses-one-million-registered-wallets-in-three-months/">Venom blockchain surpasses one million registered wallets in three months</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The Venom blockchain has reached one million registered wallets within three months.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The Venom Foundation is focused on making the adoption of blockchain technology mainstream.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">The Venom Foundation announced on Tuesday, July 25th, that its blockchain has surpassed one million registered wallets.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This latest milestone was achieved within three months. The Venom testnet took place on April 26th, and the team achieved the milestone on July 25th.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">In a press release shared with Coinjournal, the Venom Foundation added that the substantial growth signifies the accelerating popularity and adoption of Venom&rsquo;s various blockchain solutions.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The foundation further added that Venom&rsquo;s rapid growth can be attributed to its innovative technology, rigorous regulatory compliance, and secure, user-friendly environment.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Smooth operations and regular updates on the&nbsp;<a href="https://venom.network/" rel="nofollow"><u>Venom testnet</u></a> also help to strengthen the blockchain&rsquo;s appeal, helping to attract and retain users.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Last month, Venom achieved some exciting milestones. Some of the blockchain&rsquo;s achievements last month include;</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">277 million transactions, a significant increase of 46% from the previous month.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">A 65% increase in the number of accounts with smart contracts, which now stand at 28 million.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">A 93% surge in minted NFTs, with more than 5.8 million NFTs minted on the blockchain.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr">Venom wants to take blockchain adoption mainstream</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The Venom Foundation said it is focused on making the adoption of blockchain technology mainstream while adhering to regulatory compliance.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">While commenting on this&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>latest cryptocurrency news</u></a>, Christopher Louis Tsu, acting CTO and CEO of Venom Foundation, stated that;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;Frankly speaking, it took me completely by surprise. We had 250,000 users in the first six days. Can you imagine opening a new shop in town, drawing the curtains back and seeing a quarter of a million people lined up outside your door&rdquo;</em></p>
<p dir="ltr">In May, the Venom Foundation entered into a&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/venom-foundation-announces-strategic-partnership-with-the-government-of-kenya/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>strategic partnership</u></a> with the Kenyan government. The partnership will see the two entities work together to establish a &ldquo;blockchain hub&rdquo; in Africa, focusing on the development of Web3 and blockchain technology applications.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Venom Foundation provides scalable blockchain solutions for real-world applications, delivering performance and security.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/venom-blockchain-surpasses-one-million-registered-wallets-in-three-months/">Venom blockchain surpasses one million registered wallets in three months</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/venom-blockchain-surpasses-one-million-registered-wallets-in-three-months/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Xandeum, the L1 with Scalable Storage Layer, Announces Grand Launch on July 30</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/xandeum-the-l1-with-scalable-storage-layer-announces-grand-launch-on-july-30/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/xandeum-the-l1-with-scalable-storage-layer-announces-grand-launch-on-july-30/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire &#160;]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 13:10:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=147508</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Las Vegas, Nevada, July 25th, 2023, Chainwire Xandeum, a trailblazing blockchain startup committed to accelerating humanity&#8217;s transition to decentralized control, announces its highly anticipated launch on July 30, 2023, at 11:00 am PT. Leveraging the power of blockchain technology, Xandeum&#8217;s mission is to empower collective self-determination by creating a scalable, blockchain-based storage layer for smart [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/xandeum-the-l1-with-scalable-storage-layer-announces-grand-launch-on-july-30/">Xandeum, the L1 with Scalable Storage Layer, Announces Grand Launch on July 30</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Las Vegas, Nevada, July 25th, 2023, Chainwire</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://xandeum.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Xandeum</a>, a trailblazing blockchain startup committed to accelerating humanity&rsquo;s transition to decentralized control, announces its highly anticipated launch on July 30, 2023, at 11:00 am PT.</p>
<p>Leveraging the power of blockchain technology, Xandeum&rsquo;s mission is to empower collective self-determination by creating a scalable, blockchain-based storage layer for smart contracts, which adds a new dimension to the decentralized web. Named External Global Grouped Storage (EGGS), this solution pioneers a new era of storage-enabled Web3 apps (sedApps) on Xandeum.</p>
<p>In a departure from the traditional model of seeking venture capital, Xandeum prioritizes community control by selling node licenses directly to its users. The grand launch will introduce an incentivized purchase model, creating a buzz for this revolutionary blockchain project.</p>
<blockquote><p>&ldquo;Xandeum is all about transforming the world of blockchain,&rdquo; said Bernie Blume, founder of Xandeum. &ldquo;We&rsquo;re not just creating another blockchain; we&rsquo;re creating a holistic platform that integrates advanced blockchain technology with a revolutionary storage solution, paving the way for fully-fledged, storage-enabled Web3 apps.&rdquo;</p></blockquote>
<p>The grand launch introduces an attractive purchase model: the first transaction to purchase a node will receive a generous 50% rebate, the second 49%, the third 48%, and so on until the 50th transaction, which will still secure a 1% rebate.</p>
<p>This follows Xandeum&rsquo;s track record of success, already having sold over 2,809 nodes for proceeds surpassing $1.9 million under the prior brand name Bitoku. By opening the market to its community, Xandeum aims to foster further expansion and innovation.</p>
<blockquote><p>&ldquo;Our community just loves to embark on this journey so early, at least 4 to 5 months ahead of the ICO, in order to reap the maximum benefits.&rdquo; notes Blume.</p></blockquote>
<p>Post-launch, Xandeum will roll out an incentivized Devnet on August 15, followed by a Testnet in the fall, an ICO of the XAND token in November and a beta version of the mainnet scheduled for 2024.</p>
<blockquote><p>&ldquo;Join us in this exciting journey. Visit our website, explore the lightpaper and the RFC version of our technical whitepaper, check out the roadmap, and prepare to participate in our grand launch,&rdquo; urged Blume.</p></blockquote>
<p>Users are invited to join the blockchain revolution at xandeum.com and prepare for the Grand Launch. <a href="https://xandeum.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Xandeum.com</a> is set to take blockchain technology to the next level.</p>
<h3>About Xandeum</h3>
<p><a href="https://xandeum.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Xandeum</a> is a blockchain startup aimed at advancing blockchain technology. With projects like the development of the Xandeum blockchain, the integration of the Move language, and building the EGGS storage layer for smart contracts, Xandeum is pushing the boundaries of decentralized control and collective self-determination.</p>
<p>For more information: <a href="https://xandeum.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Official Website</a> | <a href="https://discord.com/channels/943357342626496592/943357343578595391" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Discord</a> | <a href="https://twitter.com/XandeumLabs" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Twitter</a></p>
<h3>Contact</h3>
<p>CEO, Bernie Blume, Xandeum Labs, bernieb@xandeum.com</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/xandeum-the-l1-with-scalable-storage-layer-announces-grand-launch-on-july-30/">Xandeum, the L1 with Scalable Storage Layer, Announces Grand Launch on July 30</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/xandeum-the-l1-with-scalable-storage-layer-announces-grand-launch-on-july-30/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
