<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 13:44:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Tel Aviv Stock Exchange (TASE) Taps Fireblocks to Introduce Crypto Services</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tase-fireblocks-crypto-services/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tase-fireblocks-crypto-services/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 13:44:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bnp paribas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fireblocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jpmorgan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[six]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tel aviv stock exchange]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=265707</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tase-fireblocks-crypto-services/">Tel Aviv Stock Exchange (TASE) Taps Fireblocks to Introduce Crypto Services</a></p>
<p>TASE’s strategic partnership with Fireblocks comes as the result of a broader vision set forth by the stock exchange.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tase-fireblocks-crypto-services/">Tel Aviv Stock Exchange (TASE) Taps Fireblocks to Introduce Crypto Services</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tase-fireblocks-crypto-services/">Tel Aviv Stock Exchange (TASE) Taps Fireblocks to Introduce Crypto Services</a></p>
<p>The Tel Aviv Stock Exchange (TASE) has <a href="https://www.ledgerinsights.com/tel-aviv-tase-digital-assets-fireblocks/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">unveiled</a> a significant infrastructure partnership with Fireblocks, a leading platform for secure digital asset management.</p>
<p>This collaboration, announced earlier this week underscores TASE’s commitment to embracing the digital revolution and offering a diverse array of secure and innovative digital asset products and services.</p>
<p>The primary goal of this collaboration is to launch a portfolio of regulated digital asset goods and services. TASE’s reputation for regulatory compliance complements Fireblocks’ technological prowess in digital asset management. The result is a powerful synergy that promises institutional-grade solutions tailor-made for regulated entities.</p>
<p>Orly Grinfeld, TASE’s clearing executive, aptly captures the essence of this transformative collaboration as she emphasizes its profound implications.</p>
<p>“We are unwavering in our pursuit of revolutionizing the industry and the local capital market, and this collaboration epitomizes our dedication to delivering secure, regulated, and innovative digital asset solutions,” Grinfeld said.</p>
<p>The stock exchange’s determination to embrace innovation, security, and regulation in the digital asset space is evident in this partnership. By harnessing Fireblocks’ cutting-edge technology and TASE’s established market presence, a new era of possibilities is on the horizon.</p>
<p>TASE&#8217;s journey into the world of digital assets is not merely about innovation but includes cultivating a safe and regulated environment for investors. The consultation held earlier this year, focused on rule changes to facilitate licensed securities brokers’ participation in the crypto market.</p>
<p>Fireblocks’ role in this partnership is pivotal. Renowned for its expertise in securely moving, storing, and issuing digital assets, Fireblocks brings a level of sophistication and robustness that aligns seamlessly with TASE’s vision.</p>
<h2>TASE Expanding into the Horizon with Fireblocks</h2>
<p>TASE’s strategic partnership with Fireblocks comes as the result of a broader vision set forth by the stock exchange. Building on a digital asset strategy <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tel-aviv-stock-exchange-digital-strategy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">introduced</a> last October, TASE aspired to revolutionize the traditional realms of trading, clearing, and custody through the power of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/difference-blockchain-distributed-ledger-technology-dlt/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Distributed Ledger Technology</a> (DLT).</p>
<p>Additionally, TASE announced two months ago that its <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/israel-government-tel-aviv-bonds-blockchain/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">government bond issuance</a> trial with the Ministry of Finance had been successful. The proof of concept included five local banks as well as six major global banks, including <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/bnp-paribas/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BNP Paribas SA</a> (EPA: BNP) and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/jpmorgan-chase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">JPMorgan Chase &amp; Co</a> (NYSE: JPM). Fireblocks was one of the partners.</p>
<p>While the trial demonstrated TASE’s expertise in traditional securities and bonds, the collaboration with Fireblocks suggests a broad future. Beyond bonds and tokenizing physical assets, TASE has stated a strong desire to delve deeper into the world of digital assets.</p>
<p>The stock exchange has shown interest in crypto, utility tokens, and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Non-Fungible Tokens</a> (NFTs), indicating a commitment to diversify products and meet the changing needs of contemporary investors.</p>
<p>It is worth noting that that is not the first stock exchange to see the value of digital assets and tokenization. Among the trailblazers in this arena is the Swiss Stock Exchange, SIX, with its innovative SIX Digital Exchange (SDX).</p>
<p>Clearstream, a subsidiary of Deutsche Boerse, has also made its mark in the realm of digital assets with the launch of D7.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shiba-inu-defi-ids/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tase-fireblocks-crypto-services/">Tel Aviv Stock Exchange (TASE) Taps Fireblocks to Introduce Crypto Services</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tase-fireblocks-crypto-services/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu Aims to Become Serious DeFi Contender, Add Digital IDs</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/shiba-inu-defi-ids/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/shiba-inu-defi-ids/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 13:39:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[shib]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[shiba uni]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[shibarium]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=265692</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shiba-inu-defi-ids/">Shiba Inu Aims to Become Serious DeFi Contender, Add Digital IDs</a></p>
<p>Shiba Inu is gearing up for the mainnet launch of Shibarium scheduled ahead of this month at the upcoming Blockchain Futuristic Conference.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shiba-inu-defi-ids/">Shiba Inu Aims to Become Serious DeFi Contender, Add Digital IDs</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shiba-inu-defi-ids/">Shiba Inu Aims to Become Serious DeFi Contender, Add Digital IDs</a></p>
<p>Shiba Inu has become more than just a memecoin with developers working on several interesting projects aimed at expanding the Shiba Inu ecosystem. In order to further strengthen trust among SHIB users and governments, the Shiba Inu developers plan to tie up all applications to a blockchain-based digital identity. This shows that the Shiba Inu ecosystem is further expanding its horizon from being a mere memecoin platform to becoming a serious contender in the crowded decentralized finance (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-decentralized-finance-defi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">DeFi</a>) blockchain market.</p>
<h2>Shiba Inu in DeFi Space</h2>
<p>Self-Sovereign Identity (SSI) is basically a digital version of user identity documents, such as passports and driver&#8217;s licenses. It empowers users to have greater control over their personal data and how it is shared online.</p>
<p>Shiba Inu developers are collaborating with community projects, especially those using SHIB or planning to build on Shibarium blockchain, to prioritize Self-Sovereign Identity (SSI) deployment. They believe the increasing interest in digital identities and data protection in Canada and the European Union could distinguish Shiba Inu as a more controlled and secure project compared to other blockchains. Speaking to CoinDesk, Shiba Inu lead developer Shytoshi Kusama said:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We are laying the groundwork for a new global standard in decentralized digital trust and international identity verification. In this way, Shibarium is the herald of a new digital age where faith in systems is restored and enhanced.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>Developments in Shibarium</h2>
<p>Shibarium is the Layer-2 scalability platform built atop <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a> by the Shiba Inu developers. This layer 2 network will utilize BONE, TREAT, SHIB, and LEASH tokens for applications developed on the blockchain.</p>
<p>&#8220;Layer 2&#8221; refers to off-chain systems or separate blockchains built on top of layer 1 protocols, which help overcome scaling and data limitations. They bundle multiple off-chain transactions into a single layer 1 transaction, reducing data load and fees.</p>
<p>Shiba Inu&#8217;s Layer 2 platform, Shibarium, has achieved an important milestone. The testnet called Puppynet has recorded a total of 34 million transactions, which shows impressive growth. According to <a href="https://puppyscan.shib.io/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Puppyscan</a>, the total number of transactions on the testnet has reached 34,103,383, and the number of blocks has risen to 1,938,771.</p>
<p>Moreover, the total wallet addresses have reached 17,063,326, indicating significant expansion. This progress comes as Shytoshi Kusama, the lead of Shiba Inu, announces a major update before the mainnet launch.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="474" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">See you at <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Blockchainfuturistconference?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Blockchainfuturistconference</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/shibarmy?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#shibarmy</a> <a href="https://t.co/Cf1TPSm9VO">https://t.co/Cf1TPSm9VO</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Shytoshi Kusama™ (@ShytoshiKusama) <a href="https://twitter.com/ShytoshiKusama/status/1686056660928806930?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 31, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The Shibarium mainnet launch shall happen ahead of this month at the upcoming Blockchain Futuristic Conference. Lead developer Shytoshi Kusama has extended an invitation to Elon Musk.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-cloud-open-sourced-ai/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shiba-inu-defi-ids/">Shiba Inu Aims to Become Serious DeFi Contender, Add Digital IDs</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/shiba-inu-defi-ids/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alibaba Cloud Unveils Open-Sourced AI Models to Challenge Meta’s Llama 2</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-cloud-open-sourced-ai/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-cloud-open-sourced-ai/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 13:04:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alibaba]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chatgpt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[llama]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Meta]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=265695</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-cloud-open-sourced-ai/">Alibaba Cloud Unveils Open-Sourced AI Models to Challenge Meta&#8217;s Llama 2</a></p>
<p>The move follows Meta's release of its own open-sourced LLM, Llama 2, in July</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-cloud-open-sourced-ai/">Alibaba Cloud Unveils Open-Sourced AI Models to Challenge Meta&#8217;s Llama 2</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-cloud-open-sourced-ai/">Alibaba Cloud Unveils Open-Sourced AI Models to Challenge Meta&#8217;s Llama 2</a></p>
<p>Alibaba Cloud, the cloud computing arm of the Chinese tech giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/alibaba-group/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Alibaba Group</a>, has <a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/alibaba-unveils-open-sourced-ai-model-similar-metas-llama-2-2023-08-03/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">introduced</a> two open-sourced artificial intelligence (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/technology/artificial-intelligence-news/">AI</a>) language models named Gwen-7B and Gwen-7B-Chat. With each model boasting up to 7 billion parameters, the company has become the first major Chinese enterprise to embrace open-source LLM. In an official press release on August 3, the company said the two open-sourced language models were built with up to 7 billion parameters each, making them potent contenders in the AI landscape.</p>
<p>The move follows<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/meta/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"> Meta</a>&#8216;s release of its own open-sourced LLM, Llama 2, in July. While Alibaba&#8217;s Gwen models have 7 billion parameters each, Meta&#8217;s Llama 2, a commercial version of its open-sourced model Llama, has 70 billion parameters, making it one of the largest open-sourced LLMs globally. Last week, Alibaba Cloud <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-llama-ai-model-alibaba/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">partnered</a> with Meta to make Llama accessible to Chinese businesses, enabling the companies to create customized AI applications.</p>
<h2>Alibaba Cloud Makes New AI Models Available for Free</h2>
<p>The Alibaba cloud unit had previously <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-chatgpt-rival-tongyi-qianwen/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">introduced</a> its LLM named Tongyi Qianwen in April, offering various versions with different parameter counts. The newly open-sourced Gwen-7B and Gwen-7B-Chat are smaller-size iterations of Tongyi Qianwen, catering to small and medium businesses seeking to harness the power of AI.</p>
<p>The company aims to make the code, model weights, and documentation of the two models freely accessible to users, including academic researchers and commercial institutions worldwide. However, entities with over 100 million monthly active users will require a license from Alibaba to utilize the models. Similarly, Meta&#8217;s Llama 2 also demands a permit from the company for companies with over 700 million users.</p>
<p>The open-sourcing of these large language models is part of the effort to help democratize AI technology. By making these models available for free, more businesses and developers will be able to use them to develop new AI-powered applications.</p>
<p>LLM AI models can process massive amounts of data and generate content across various formats, including text, images, audio, and video. These tools serve as the backbone of AI chatbots like ChatGPT, driving innovation and enhancing user experiences across multiple domains.</p>
<h2>Chinese Authorities Encourage AI Development in the Country</h2>
<p>While <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-cloud-layoff-spinoff/">Alibaba Cloud</a> has not disclosed the higher-parameter versions of Tongyi Qianwen, this move signifies a significant stride in China&#8217;s bid to catch up with the United States in the AI domain. The Chinese government actively encourages local companies like Alibaba, Tencent, and Huawei to develop competitive and &#8220;controllable&#8221; AI models, challenging the supremacy of US-based AI technologies.</p>
<p>The open-sourcing of Alibaba Cloud&#8217;s LLM is expected to advance the technical capabilities and industrial applications of Chinese LLMs. Furthermore, the tools will simplify the model training and deployment process for enterprises, lowering the threshold for AI application and enabling the creation of tailor-made industry-specific LLMs with greater efficiency.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, aside from Alibaba and Meta, other tech giants like Google and Microsoft are also working on large language models for various applications, including text generation, language translation, and question-answering systems.</p>
<p>The global AI landscape is witnessing intense competition and rapid innovation, driving the growth and adoption of AI technologies in diverse industries, including crypto.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hawaii-expensive-us-states/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-cloud-open-sourced-ai/">Alibaba Cloud Unveils Open-Sourced AI Models to Challenge Meta&#8217;s Llama 2</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-cloud-open-sourced-ai/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hawaii Is Most Expensive of US States According to Monthly Household Expenditure</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/hawaii-expensive-us-states/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/hawaii-expensive-us-states/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 12:58:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[doxo]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=265693</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hawaii-expensive-us-states/">Hawaii Is Most Expensive of US States According to Monthly Household Expenditure</a></p>
<p>While Hawaii and California are the most expensive, doxo also found that West Virginia and Mississippi are the least costliest US states.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hawaii-expensive-us-states/">Hawaii Is Most Expensive of US States According to Monthly Household Expenditure</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hawaii-expensive-us-states/">Hawaii Is Most Expensive of US States According to Monthly Household Expenditure</a></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">All-in-one bill payment service doxo has released a report ranking the most and least expensive states in the US. The report includes details of average household bills in individual US states.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">According to doxo in its </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.doxo.com/doxoinsights/doxoinsights-2023-state-by-state-bill-pay-market-report-reveals-the-average-american-now-spends-25000-per-year-on-household-bills/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">United States of Bill Pay: State by State Bill Pay Market Report</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> for 2023, the average US household spends $24,557 on annual bills and $2,046 monthly. The report also lists the ten most common bills for the average household in the US. These expenses include mortgage, auto loans, rent, health insurance, and life insurance. Others are mobile phone bills, alarm and security. The last two on the list are cable, internet and phone bills, as well as utilities, such as waste, electricity, gas, sewage, water, and recycling.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The doxo report concludes that Hawaii is the most expensive US state, with the average household spending $3,070 monthly. Hawaii’s monthly average household bill is 50% above the $2,046 national average. According to doxo, the state’s average monthly rent is $1,856, while the average mortgage is $2,247.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The report places California as the second most expensive of US states, with the average household bill at $2,838 each month, 38.7% over the national average. The average California resident spends $1,762 on monthly rent and $2,402 on mortgage. In San Ramon, the most expensive city in California, the average monthly bill is $4,390. Others among the 10 most expensive states for household bills are New Jersey, Massachusetts, Maryland, and Connecticut. Of these 10, Alaska is the cheapest, with $2,335 per household, more than 14% above the national average.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">According to doxo, the consumer bill pay market in the US is $3.87 trillion.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Least Expensive States in the US</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The doxo report also lists the least expensive states in the US. Atop the list is Alabama at $1,772 per month, which is 40% of household income and 13.4% less than the national average. Other states on the list are Missouri, New Mexico, South Dakota, Indiana, Kentucky, and Oklahoma. However, doxo reports that the least expensive of US states based on monthly household bills is West Virginia with $1,530, which is 38% of household income, and 25.2% less than the country’s national average. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In the report, doxo says a unique view of expenses, especially with inflation in the US, is necessary. Quoting another </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.doxo.com/doxoinsights/how-americans-pay-their-bills-report-2023/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">report</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, doxo says most Americans are already feeling the brunt of inflation, or are worried about the near future:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">“A recent </span><span data-preserver-spaces="true">doxoINSIGHTS report</span><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> found that three in four consumers (73%) say that inflation is impacting their ability to pay bills. 86% of consumers said they are worried about the impact that inflation will have on their financial health in the future, with 72% saying it would take six months or more until their household’s financial health improves.” </span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Following West Virginia is Mississippi, the second least expensive, with $1,616 in average household expenses. This is 41% of household income, and 21.1% less than the national average.</span></p>
<p>Read other <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/personal-finance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">personal income news</a> on our website.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hashkey-crypto-exchange-hong-kong/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hawaii-expensive-us-states/">Hawaii Is Most Expensive of US States According to Monthly Household Expenditure</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/hawaii-expensive-us-states/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>HashKey Becomes First Crypto Exchange to Get Licensed for Retail Services in Hong Kong</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/hashkey-crypto-exchange-hong-kong/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/hashkey-crypto-exchange-hong-kong/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Temitope Olatunji]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 11:18:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[HashKey]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hashkey group]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=265649</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hashkey-crypto-exchange-hong-kong/">HashKey Becomes First Crypto Exchange to Get Licensed for Retail Services in Hong Kong</a></p>
<p>Despite China's strict ban on cryptocurrency transactions, Hong Kong has taken a different approach, welcoming cryptocurrency firms and even encouraging banks to work with them.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hashkey-crypto-exchange-hong-kong/">HashKey Becomes First Crypto Exchange to Get Licensed for Retail Services in Hong Kong</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hashkey-crypto-exchange-hong-kong/">HashKey Becomes First Crypto Exchange to Get Licensed for Retail Services in Hong Kong</a></p>
<p>The HashKey exchange has made history as the first company in Hong Kong to secure a license under the new regulatory framework that enables crypto trading platforms to cater to retail services.</p>
<p>HashKey is a Hong Kong-based cryptocurrency exchange and trading platform. The exchange trades a wide range of digital assets and provides professional services to both retail and institutional traders. HashKey Group, a FinTech company that manages digital assets and provides various blockchain solutions, founded the company in 2018.</p>
<p>Previously holding Type 1 and Type 7 licenses, this new approval allows HashKey to expand its scope to serve not only professional investors but also retail users. With this, the exchange aims to provide a secure and user-friendly platform for buying, selling, and storing cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>In a statement, HashKey Exchange expressed its excitement about the license upgrade, which was obtained through a simplified process. This upgrade aligns with market demand for a licensed platform that offers a safer and more straightforward experience for retail users entering the cryptocurrency space.</p>
<p>The license was granted to HashKey after Hong Kong amended its laws to offer Virtual Asset Services Providers licenses. The amendment included provisions that will assist financial institutions in better tracking crypto asset purchases, such as submitting audited accounts and financial information, among other things. It also has penalties for activities like the illegal sale of digital assets.</p>
<p>The COO of HashKey Group <a href="https://group.hashkey.com/en/newsroom/hashkey-type1-7-licence-uplift?utm_medium=email&amp;_hsmi=268863914&amp;_hsenc=p2ANqtz--G6-W5zXtvWgM0-skqG2_lNKwbPv8OI5-SNZizRwh-zMPmTCNGquHiNLuxSRuRO4lXCzFk6O" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">stated</a>:</p>
<blockquote>
<p style="text-align: left;">&#8220;We are thrilled to become the first licenced trading platform in Hong Kong dedicated to serving retail users. With the establishment of licenced trading platforms and the further clarity of regulatory frameworks in Hong Kong, the industry as a whole will witness increased transparency, leading to a significant boost in investor confidence. As an industry leader, we will continue to fulfill our commitments in compliance, safety and security, ensuring our user benefits are fully protected and creating a trading platform tailored to retail users.&#8221;</p>
</blockquote>
<h2>Hong Kong Has Been Embracing Crypto Services and Solutions</h2>
<p>Despite China&#8217;s strict ban on <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/crypto/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">cryptocurrency</a> transactions, Hong Kong has taken a different approach, welcoming cryptocurrency firms and even encouraging banks to work with them. Hong Kong&#8217;s authorities issued policy statements this year to strengthen the city&#8217;s position as a global financial hub. The Legislative Council passed an amendment in December that established a full licensing system for virtual asset service providers.</p>
<p>A recent study published in June by the Hong Kong government revealed concerns about the city falling behind its East Asian and Gulf counterparts in web3 development. The government is eager to address this issue and propel Hong Kong into a more competitive position in the rapidly changing digital landscape, and upgrading the license of exchanges, just like in the case of HashKey, is a crucial move towards it.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-dubai-us-bankruptcy/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hashkey-crypto-exchange-hong-kong/">HashKey Becomes First Crypto Exchange to Get Licensed for Retail Services in Hong Kong</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/hashkey-crypto-exchange-hong-kong/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>FTX Seeks Exclusion of Dubai Unit from US Bankruptcy Proceedings</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-dubai-us-bankruptcy/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-dubai-us-bankruptcy/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 11:07:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx sam bankman-fried]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sam bankman-fried]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sbf]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=265599</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-dubai-us-bankruptcy/">FTX Seeks Exclusion of Dubai Unit from US Bankruptcy Proceedings</a></p>
<p>The attorneys claimed that FTX Dubai has a solvent balance sheet.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-dubai-us-bankruptcy/">FTX Seeks Exclusion of Dubai Unit from US Bankruptcy Proceedings</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-dubai-us-bankruptcy/">FTX Seeks Exclusion of Dubai Unit from US Bankruptcy Proceedings</a></p>
<p>Troubled crypto exchange <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a> plans to remove its Dubai subsidiary from ongoing bankruptcy proceedings in the United States, Coindesk <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/08/03/ftx-wants-dubai-unit-removed-from-us-bankruptcy-proceedings/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reported</a> on Thursday, citing a recent court filing on August 3. When the exchange filed for bankruptcy last year, it initiated Chapter 11 cases for 102 affiliated entities around the world, including FTX Dubai, which was established in February by the company&#8217;s European arm before its unfortunate collapse in November.</p>
<p>Recall that the FTX unit <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-virtual-asset-license-dubai/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">received</a> an operational license from Dubai&#8217;s Virtual Assets Regulatory Authority (VARA) in March, a few weeks after its launch. The grant allowed it to offer crypto services to a selected group of customers. However, the country&#8217;s financial regulator suspended the license shortly after the crash of its parent company to protect users from getting exposed.</p>
<p>The bankrupt company is now seeking to exclude its Dubai subsidiary from the ongoing wind-down proceedings in the US. Lawyers representing the company claimed in the filing that the Dubai unit had not conducted any business in the United Arab Emirates (UAE) before the bankruptcy filing, making it unlikely to rehabilitate its operations.</p>
<h2>A Solvent Balance Sheet</h2>
<p>The attorneys also said that FTX Dubai has a solvent balance sheet, suggesting that a voluntary liquidation procedure in accordance with UAE laws would allow for the timely distribution of the positive cash balance after settling all liabilities and liquidating assets.</p>
<p>&#8220;Additionally, FTX Dubai&#8217;s balance sheet is solvent. Therefore, the Debtors believe that a solvent voluntary liquidation procedure in accordance with the laws of the United Arab Emirates would allow a timely distribution of the positive cash balance after payment of all outstanding liabilities and liquidation of all assets,&#8221; the filing reads.</p>
<p>While the estate argued that any court orders related to FTX Dubai when it was part of the proceedings should stand, it deems the dismissal necessary to protect the debtors and authorize payments of pre-bankruptcy wages, salaries, compensation, benefits, and expenses to Dubai employees.</p>
<p>A court hearing for the case is scheduled for later this month, on August 23.</p>
<h2>FTX to Restart Crypto Exchange for International Customers</h2>
<p>Meanwhile, before the recent court filing seeking dismissal, Coinspeaker <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-draft-creditor-repayment-plan-hints-at-reboot/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a> that the company had unveiled its reorganization plan, classifying claimants into specific classes with plans to reboot the exchange as an offshore entity for international customers.</p>
<p>The plan includes 13 different classes of claims, such as FTX.com customer entitlement claims, US customer claims, and non-fungible token (NFT) customer claims. The global settlement will involve valuing claims in USD using a methodology prepared by FTX, subject to bankruptcy court approval.</p>
<p>The proposed plan also addresses the compensation of FTX exchange organizations for unauthorized borrowing and misappropriation of assets allegedly carried out by former CEO <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/sam-bankman-fried/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Sam Bankman-Fried</a> (SBF), who is currently awaiting trial for his involvement in the collapse of the exchange and other company executives.</p>
<p>Intercompany claims are set to be canceled, while FTT holders may not be compensated for their token holdings. The plan includes the intent to liquidate FTX&#8217;s estates for payout distributions to customers and creditors in cash but also hints at the possibility of an offshore exchange restart, offering specific creditors the option for a share of equity, tokens, and other interests.</p>
<p>FTX&#8217;s bankruptcy proceedings include a lawsuit against Bankman-Fried and other implicated directors, seeking to recover over $1 billion in allegedly misappropriated funds.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nintendo-q1-2024-revenue/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-dubai-us-bankruptcy/">FTX Seeks Exclusion of Dubai Unit from US Bankruptcy Proceedings</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-dubai-us-bankruptcy/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nintendo Q1 2024 Revenue Jumps amid Eclectic Super Mario Movie Release</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nintendo-q1-2024-revenue/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nintendo-q1-2024-revenue/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 11:03:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gaming News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nintendo]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Super Mario Bros]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[zelda]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=265659</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nintendo-q1-2024-revenue/">Nintendo Q1 2024 Revenue Jumps amid Eclectic Super Mario Movie Release</a></p>
<p>Nintendo’s flagship Switch games console series remains a dominant force in the gaming industry.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nintendo-q1-2024-revenue/">Nintendo Q1 2024 Revenue Jumps amid Eclectic Super Mario Movie Release</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nintendo-q1-2024-revenue/">Nintendo Q1 2024 Revenue Jumps amid Eclectic Super Mario Movie Release</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/nintendo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Nintendo Co Ltd</a> (TYO: 7974), the legendary Japanese gaming company has once again proven its prowess by reporting a significant surge in revenue and operating profit for the June quarter.</p>
<p>This incredible achievement can be ascribed to the popularity of both the “Super Mario Bros. Movie” and the most recent installment in the beloved Zelda games for the Nintendo Switch system.</p>
<h2>Nintendo’s Market Strategy and Innovations</h2>
<p>Nintendo stated in an <a href="https://www.nintendo.co.jp/ir/pdf/2023/230803_2e.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">earnings release</a> that net sales for the first quarter increased by a remarkable 50.0% year over year, reaching an astonishing 461.3 billion yen. On the other hand, operating profits rose by 82.4% reaching 185.4 billion Yen, while ordinary profit increased by an astonishing 52.2% to 253.7 billion yen.</p>
<p>At the heart of Nintendo’s Q1 success is the triumph of “The Super Mario Bros. Movie”. Released in April, the film has not only captivated audiences with its nostalgic charm but has also become a major phenomenon, amassing an impressive $1 billion at the Box Office.</p>
<p>Produced in collaboration with Universal Studios, the movie’s success has acted as a halo effect, enticing users to explore other offerings from the Japanese gaming giant. Nintendo reported that the film played a pivotal role in supporting sales of games featuring the beloved character, Mario.</p>
<p>The effect extended to titles like &#8220;Mario Kart 8 Deluxe&#8221;, showcasing the interconnected nature of Nintendo&#8217;s intellectual properties and their ability to drive each other&#8217;s success. Beyond games, the Mario movie also had a substantial impact on Nintendo&#8217;s mobile and intellectual property-related business.</p>
<p>The company reported a staggering 190% year-on-year increase in revenue, reaching 31.8 billion Japanese Yen.</p>
<p>Alongside the cinematic success, Nintendo’s gaming division has also made waves with the release of &#8220;The Legend of Zelda: Tears of the Kingdom&#8221;. Launched in May, this highly-acclaimed title has shattered records, becoming the fastest-selling game in the history of the revered Legend of Zelda series.</p>
<p>The latest installment in the revered Zelda franchise achieved remarkable sales figures, with 18.51 million units sold in the quarter alone.</p>
<h2>Nintendo Switch Console Boosts Revenue</h2>
<p>Meanwhile, Nintendo’s flagship Switch games console series remains a dominant force in the gaming industry, as evidenced by the company’s recent sales figures and the ongoing speculation surrounding a potential refresh.</p>
<p>Nintendo had initially projected sales of 15 million units for the current fiscal year ending in March 2024 for its Switch console series. This forecast represents a modest decrease from the previous fiscal year&#8217;s sales total of just under 18 million units. However, the company&#8217;s recent performance paints a more optimistic picture.</p>
<p>Nintendo reported sales of 3.91 million Switch units in the June quarter, a 13.9% rise over the previous year. This surge in sales is a significant achievement, given the console’s age and the potential concerns about waning interest.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, Nintendo stock is up marginally and is pegged at 6,357 Japanese yen.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-shares-q2-2023/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nintendo-q1-2024-revenue/">Nintendo Q1 2024 Revenue Jumps amid Eclectic Super Mario Movie Release</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nintendo-q1-2024-revenue/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>PayPal (PYPL) Shares Fall 7% as Q2 2023 Report Disappoints Investors</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-shares-q2-2023/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-shares-q2-2023/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 10:59:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wall Street]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dan schulman]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[paypal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[paypal stock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pypl stock]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=265656</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-shares-q2-2023/">PayPal (PYPL) Shares Fall 7% as Q2 2023 Report Disappoints Investors</a></p>
<p>Despite investor disappointment, CEO Dan Schulman is confident that Q2 2023 shows that PayPal is on the right path to growth.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-shares-q2-2023/">PayPal (PYPL) Shares Fall 7% as Q2 2023 Report Disappoints Investors</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-shares-q2-2023/">PayPal (PYPL) Shares Fall 7% as Q2 2023 Report Disappoints Investors</a></p>
<p>Online payments company <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">PayPal Holdings Inc</a> (NASDAQ: PYPL) has released its Q2 2023 report showing figures that disappointed investors. The company’s shares fell 7% in response to the figures.</p>
<p>PayPal <a href="https://s201.q4cdn.com/231198771/files/doc_financials/2023/q2/Q2-23-PayPal-Earnings-Release.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reported</a> its adjusted operating margin for Q2 2023 at 21.4%, lower than the 22% expected. This was likely due to the poor performance of branded products following competition from other giants like Apple.</p>
<p>However, PayPal also reported growth across a few metrics. For instance, its net revenue grew 7% to $7.3 billion, with a total of 431 million active accounts, higher than the 429 million reported in the same period last year. PayPal also recorded a 12% increase to 54.7 payment transactions per active account on a trailing twelve-month basis and a 10% jump in the total number of payment transactions to 6.1 billion.</p>
<p>PayPal CEO Dan Schulman is optimistic about the company’s growth and believes that Q2 2023 points to better performance in the future. Schulman said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Our second quarter results show continued momentum. We have high confidence that our business is on the right path and we’re seeing clear signs that the investments we’ve made are paying off. Our teams are energized, and I’m confident that we’re well positioned to continue to grow our leadership in digital payments.”</p></blockquote>
<p>PayPal mentioned a partnership with leading investment firm KKR as part of its projections for the rest of the year. The “exclusive multi-year relationship for European buy now, pay later receivables” will close sometime in the second half of 2023. The agreement will see KKR-managed private accounts and credit funds buy up to €40 billion of existing and future BNPL loans in the UK and Europe. PayPal says it expects around $1.8 billion worth of the proceeds.</p>
<h2>Other Highlights from Q2 2023 Report</h2>
<p>PayPal provided a few other highlights in the report. For instance, earnings per diluted share came in at $0.92, while net revenue was $7.287 billion, up 7% from $6.806 billion in Q2 2022. Its operating margin was 15.5%, up from 11.2% in the same period last year.</p>
<p>The Q2 2023 report also includes financial guidance for Q3 and the full year. The company expected net revenue to hit $7.4 billion, while GAAP earnings per diluted share dropped to $0.85-$0.87. This is also a fall from $1.15 in the previous year.</p>
<p>For full-year guidance, the company expects GAAP earnings per diluted share at $3.49, nearly 70% higher than the $2.09 from the full year 2022.</p>
<p>In April, Coinspeaker <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-ceo-remuneration/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a> that PayPal cut CEO Schulman’s salary by 32% from last year. Following the company’s poor performance and inability to meet targets, the company paid Schulman $22 million for the financial year, down from $32 million paid the previous year. PayPal missed targets for adjusted operating margin, new net active users, and revenue. The payment cut is also a way for the company to reduce spending in hopes of supporting its balance sheet. Despite cutting the CEO’s pay, PayPal’s board still trusts that Schulman is the right man for the job.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-fitch-ratings-downgrade/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-shares-q2-2023/">PayPal (PYPL) Shares Fall 7% as Q2 2023 Report Disappoints Investors</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-shares-q2-2023/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>JPMorgan Chief Reacts to Fitch Ratings US Downgrade to AA+</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-fitch-ratings-downgrade/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-fitch-ratings-downgrade/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 10:55:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wall Street]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fitch ratings]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jamie dimon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jpm]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=265648</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-fitch-ratings-downgrade/">JPMorgan Chief Reacts to Fitch Ratings US Downgrade to AA+</a></p>
<p>In reaction to the Fitch Ratings downgrade, the JPMorgan CEO said that “it doesn’t really matter that much”.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-fitch-ratings-downgrade/">JPMorgan Chief Reacts to Fitch Ratings US Downgrade to AA+</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-fitch-ratings-downgrade/">JPMorgan Chief Reacts to Fitch Ratings US Downgrade to AA+</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/jpmorgan-chase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">JPMorgan Chase</a> (NYSE: JPM) CEO <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/jamie-dimon/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Jamie Dimon</a> has reacted to the Fitch Ratings downgrade of the United States&#8217; long-term credit rating. Credit rating agency Fitch Ratings recently <a href="https://www.fitchratings.com/research/sovereigns/fitch-downgrades-united-states-long-term-ratings-to-aa-from-aaa-outlook-stable-01-08-2023" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">downgraded</a> the US long-term foreign-currency issuer default rating from AAA to AA+. The capital market company issued a release to announce the development, noting that the Country Ceiling has been affirmed at ‘AAA’.</p>
<p>According to the rating agency, the downgrade signified the fiscal decline expected over the next three years. It also shows the high and increasing general government debt burden and the “erosion of governance reactive to ‘AA’ and &#8216;AAA-rated peers over the last two decades that has manifested in repeated debt limit standoffs and last-minute resolutions.”</p>
<p>Fitch is of the opinion that governance standards have been gradually deteriorating for the past 20 years. The team mentioned other factors, like the repeated debt-limited political standoffs, lack of minimum-term fiscal framework, and more, as reasons for the steady deterioration in governance standards, which led to the downgrade.</p>
<h2>JPMorgan CEO Says Fitch Ratings US Downgrade Is &#8216;Ridiculous&#8217;</h2>
<p>In reaction to the Fitch Ratings downgrade, the JPMorgan CEO said that “it doesn’t really matter that much.” Speaking to CNBC, Dimon emphasized the fact that rating agencies do not have power over borrowing costs. Rather, he said, the market determines borrowing costs. Additionally, he said it is “ridiculous” that other countries have higher credit ratings than the US. In his opinion, other countries depend on the United State’s stability and military, which is why it is surprising that other countries are rated higher.</p>
<blockquote><p>“To have them be triple-A and not America is kind of ridiculous. It’s still the most prosperous nation on the planet.”</p></blockquote>
<p>As Congress met concerning the debt ceiling and put the country to near-default in May, the rating agency placed the US rating on watch. As for Dimon, getting rid of the debt ceiling is crucial.</p>
<p>In addition to stating his stance on the Fitch Ratings downgrade, the JPMorgan executive also talked about the buzzing AI trend, bank regulations, geopolitics, and the US economy. He belongs to the school of thought that supports the adoption of artificial intelligence. Dimon specifically said these technological tools, such as ChatGPT, are game changers that could help future generations. However, he warned that its use should be in the proper manner as “bad guys” are already taking advantage.”</p>
<p>JPMorgan has been amassing gains for the past year, increasing over 38% in the last twelve months. The company has added 15.88% since the beginning of the year and surged more than 15% in the last three months. Over the past month, JPM increased 8.51%.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/worldcoin-verification-services/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-fitch-ratings-downgrade/">JPMorgan Chief Reacts to Fitch Ratings US Downgrade to AA+</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-fitch-ratings-downgrade/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Worldcoin Foundation Pauses Verification Services</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/worldcoin-verification-services/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/worldcoin-verification-services/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Babafemi Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 10:39:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[worldcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Worldcoin Foundation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=265497</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/worldcoin-verification-services/">Worldcoin Foundation Pauses Verification Services</a></p>
<p>The Worldcoin Foundation said it will use the pause to develop an onboarding program with more robust crowd control measures.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/worldcoin-verification-services/">Worldcoin Foundation Pauses Verification Services</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/worldcoin-verification-services/">Worldcoin Foundation Pauses Verification Services</a></p>

<p>The Worldcoin Foundation has temporarily suspended its verification services in Kenya. This information was contained in a statement sent to Coinspeaker. According to the statement, the Foundation is pausing the personhood verification as a precautionary measure while it works out a crowd control plan.</p>
<p>The Foundation launched its World ID project to address the lack of official ID for 850 million people globally. The project uses a device called the Worldcoin Orb to scan the iris of willing participants. It then ascribes them to a unique digital identity. In exchange, participants get 25 Worldcoin tokens (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/worldcoin/">WLD</a>).</p>
<p>In Kenya, the verification attracted a mammoth crowd. The Worldcoin Foundation noted the overwhelming response has led to long waiting times, sometimes reaching three days. “The demand for Worldcoin’s proof of personhood verification services in Kenya has been overwhelming,”  it said. This is not surprising given that the 25 WLD translates to about KES7500, which is half of the average monthly pay of low-wage earners in Kenya. </p>
<p>The Worldcoin Foundation said it will use the pause to develop an onboarding program with more robust crowd control measures. The team also plans to work with local officials to increase understanding of the privacy measures and commitments Worldcoin implements globally.</p>
<h2>Kenya Ministry Suspends Worldcoin Activities</h2>
<p>The temporary suspension of the verification services comes at the same time the Kenyan Ministry of Interior and National Administration is investigating the company’s operation. The <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/kenya-suspends-worldcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ministry suspended Worldcoin operations</a> in the country to allow relevant security, financial services and data protection agencies to ascertain the legality of their approach.</p>
<p>Under the Kenyan <a href="https://www.odpc.go.ke/regulations/data-protection-general-regulations-2021/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Data Protection Act 2021</a>, anyone who acts as a data controller or processor must register with the data commissioner. While Worldcoin is registered under its parent company’s name, Tools for Humanity GmbH, its data storage and usage data is attracting criticism. If found guilty of non-compliance with the Act, the Worldcoin Foundation could pay a fine of up to KES 5 million ($35,000). Otherwise, it could pay 1% of the undertaking’s annual turnover, whichever is lower.</p>
<p>Following this, the foundation has reiterated its commitment “to providing an inclusive, privacy-preserving, decentralized on-ramp to the global digital economy”. It also looks forward to resuming its services in Kenya and plans to work closely with local regulators and stakeholders to make it happen. </p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/space-and-time-sql-zk/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/worldcoin-verification-services/">Worldcoin Foundation Pauses Verification Services</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/worldcoin-verification-services/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4071 metric#misses=42 metric#hit-ratio=99.0 metric#bytes=1068215 metric#prefetches=196 metric#store-reads=20 metric#store-writes=2 metric#store-hits=202 metric#store-misses=3 metric#sql-queries=34 metric#ms-total=101.92 metric#ms-cache=4.78 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.2276 metric#ms-cache-ratio=4.7 -->