<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 14:37:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Binance Stops Deposits and Withdrawals for 8 Multichain-Bridged Tokens Until Further Notice</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-stops-deposits-withdrawals-8-multichain-tokens/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-stops-deposits-withdrawals-8-multichain-tokens/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 14:37:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261790</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-stops-deposits-withdrawals-8-multichain-tokens/">Binance Stops Deposits and Withdrawals for 8 Multichain-Bridged Tokens Until Further Notice</a></p>
<p>Binance will no longer allow the affected Multichain-connected tokens on its platform from the 7th of July, according to an announcement.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-stops-deposits-withdrawals-8-multichain-tokens/">Binance Stops Deposits and Withdrawals for 8 Multichain-Bridged Tokens Until Further Notice</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-stops-deposits-withdrawals-8-multichain-tokens/">Binance Stops Deposits and Withdrawals for 8 Multichain-Bridged Tokens Until Further Notice</a></p>
<p>Binance has announced it would stop support for withdrawals and deposits for 8 Multichain-bridged tokens from Friday. The crypto exchange <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/support/announcement/updates-on-the-suspension-of-deposits-withdrawals-for-multichain-bridged-tokens-3c7d279dd37043bd8290ac718b5c08a4" target="_blank" rel="noopener">said</a> the suspension would last until further notice.</p>
<p>The recent cessation comes following a previous suspension of the affected tokens because of a problem with the Multichain (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/multichain/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">MULTI</a>) protocol. On May 25, Binance had previously suspended these tokens because transactions via the Multichain protocol were stalling. Many transactions were stuck, leaving users wondering without word from the protocol.</p>
<p>The affected tokens are Harvest Finance (FARM) via BSC, Travala (AVA) via ETH, Alchemy Pay (ACH) via BSC, and Polkastarter (POLS) via BSC. Others are SuperVerse (SUPER) via BSC, Alpaca Finance (ALPACA) via Fantom, Beefy.Finance (BIFI) via Fantom, and Spell Token (SPELL) via Avalanche C-Chain.</p>
<p>In a <a href="https://twitter.com/MultichainOrg/status/1661443109019062272?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener">tweet</a> on May 24, Multichain revealed: “some of the cross-chain routes are unavailable due to force majeure, and the time for service to resume is unknown.” Multichain also said in the tweet that it will automatically credit pending transactions, and compensate all users affected.</p>
<h2>Market Reactions to Multichain Problem</h2>
<p>At the time, a <a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/binance-suspends-deposits-for-bridged-tokens-seeks-clarity-from-multichain-team" target="_blank" rel="noopener">report</a> stated that Binance was not the only crypto firm to react to Multichain. Blockchain analysis service Lookonchain reported MULTI outflows of $3 million. In addition, a Fantom Foundation wallet address removed $2.4 million (449,740) of liquidity on SushiSwap.</p>
<p>Intelligence firm Arkham Intelligence also confirmed in a <a href="https://twitter.com/ArkhamIntel/status/1661405156469030915?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1661405156469030915%7Ctwgr%5Ecb822edae6d5607dcdaee499ec2bccce38465295%7Ctwcon%5Es1_&amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fcointelegraph.com%2Fnews%2Fbinance-suspends-deposits-for-bridged-tokens-seeks-clarity-from-multichain-team" target="_blank" rel="noopener">tweet</a> that wallets moved around $3 million worth of MULTI tokens to crypto exchange Gate.io. The move scared investors and caused MULTI’s price to plunge 26.5% in 24 hours. Arkham Intelligence’s tweet also referenced a rumor that authorities in Shanghai arrested the Multichain team.</p>
<p>Binance’s announcement states that all mentioned tokens are still available via other networks supported on the exchange. According to data from CoinGecko, MULTI is trading at $3.13 after losing 6.1% in 24 hours and 7.4% in the past week. MULTI’s 24-hour high is $3.34, with a 7-day high at $3.53.</p>
<h2>Binance Multichain Suspension a Likely Move to Protect Funds and Avoid Regulatory Attention</h2>
<p>The world’s largest cryptocurrency exchange by volume, Binance is facing a lot of regulatory stress and is likely acting carefully with Multichain to avoid further problems. In May, Binance announced it would suspend access to some privacy coins in specific European countries to comply with EU regulations. Binance named XVG, DASH, NAV, MOB, and several more, announcing they would no longer be available in Spain, Poland, Italy, and France. However, the exchange <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-privacy-coins-eu-regulations/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">opted not to delist</a> these tokens by reclassifying its assessment of privacy coins.</p>
<p>Away from the EU, Binance still has problems in Australia. In February, the Australian Securities and Investments Commission (ASIC) <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/regulator-asic-binance-accounts/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">began investigating</a> the exchange over the wrongful closure of some accounts. In April, the exchange <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/asic-binance-crypto-license/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">asked</a> the Australian ASIC to revoke its derivatives license granted through a local subsidiary. The revocation meant that Binance had to close all existing derivatives positions by April 21. As of yesterday, the ASIC <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-australia-offices-raided/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">raided</a> Binance’s office in Australia, according to a Bloomberg report.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/india-rbi-central-banks-digital-rupee/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-stops-deposits-withdrawals-8-multichain-tokens/">Binance Stops Deposits and Withdrawals for 8 Multichain-Bridged Tokens Until Further Notice</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-stops-deposits-withdrawals-8-multichain-tokens/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Reserve Bank of India (RBI) in Talks with Other Central Banks to Promote Digital Rupee for Cross-border Payments</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/india-rbi-central-banks-digital-rupee/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/india-rbi-central-banks-digital-rupee/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 14:17:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Currencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital rupee]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[rbi]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261804</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/india-rbi-central-banks-digital-rupee/">Reserve Bank of India (RBI) in Talks with Other Central Banks to Promote Digital Rupee for Cross-border Payments</a></p>
<p>The RBI Governor Shaktikanta Das has severally admitted that the country is moving towards CBDC adoption amid de-dollarization. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/india-rbi-central-banks-digital-rupee/">Reserve Bank of India (RBI) in Talks with Other Central Banks to Promote Digital Rupee for Cross-border Payments</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/india-rbi-central-banks-digital-rupee/">Reserve Bank of India (RBI) in Talks with Other Central Banks to Promote Digital Rupee for Cross-border Payments</a></p>
<p>With 19 of the G20 nations in the advanced stage of Central Bank Digital Currency (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-central-bank-digital-currency-cbdc/amp/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">CBDC</a>) development, the most populous country in the world, the Republic of India, has been working towards the same goal. According to a recent <a href="https://m.economictimes.com/news/economy/finance/rbi-in-talks-with-leading-global-peers-to-promote-digital-rupee-payments/articleshow/101288604.cms" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a> by the Economic Times, the Reserve Bank of India (RBI) is currently in discussions with more than 18 global central banks on how to use the digital rupee in cross-border payments. The South Asian country has seen its economy significantly grow in the past few years fueled by modern technology adoption.</p>
<h2>Indian Market and Digital Rupee</h2>
<p>The report noted that RBI Governor, Shaktikanta Das, has severally pointed out the importance of foreign trade infrastructure for the digital rupee. India already hosts billions of cross-border payments from its citizens working abroad. However, it is worth noting that most of the need for third parties in cross-border payments has significantly been reduced since the onset of Bitcoin and other crypto assets. Moreover, the RBI forecasts the digital rupee will hit 1 million users soon.</p>
<p>“But cross-border payments will also become much quicker, more seamless, and very cost-effective. That is another area where a lot of attention needs to be given. We are constantly in dialogue with other central banks that have introduced or are introducing CBDCs,” Shaktikanta noted during a speech in London recently.</p>
<p>With the supply of the United States dollar becoming a hustle to traders seeking to import goods in most countries, Shaktikanta highlighted that a digital rupee will help streamline the supply chain. Moreover, more countries will have digital rupee in their Vostro accounts to facilitate seamless cross-border payments with less friction.</p>
<p>“In India, we have no shortage of dollars, but in some other markets, due to a shortage of dollars, they are unable to do imports,” Shaktikanta added.</p>
<h2>Bigger Picture</h2>
<p>India has already joined forces with other countries including Russia, China, Brazil, and South Africa in breaking away from the United States dollar dependence as the global reserve currency. Undeniably, the United States regulators are already feeling the heat of more countries ditching the dollar as the reserve currency. Moreover, inflation has been rising despite the Fed&#8217;s rising interest rates in the past 10 months.</p>
<p>Undeniably, the RBI intends to counter the rising use of Bitcoin among other crypto assets as a means of fast payments.</p>
<p>However, the Indian government has severely tried to ban the use of crypto assets to no avail in the past few years. In response, the Indian government has imposed a harsh crypto tax for crypto uses in a bid to discourage their use.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-academy-coursera-blockchain/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/india-rbi-central-banks-digital-rupee/">Reserve Bank of India (RBI) in Talks with Other Central Banks to Promote Digital Rupee for Cross-border Payments</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/india-rbi-central-banks-digital-rupee/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Academy Partners with Coursera to Promote Blockchain Technology</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-academy-coursera-blockchain/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-academy-coursera-blockchain/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 14:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Binance News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance academy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain adoption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coursera]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261342</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-academy-coursera-blockchain/">Binance Academy Partners with Coursera to Promote Blockchain Technology</a></p>
<p>Binance has been always working with the belief that education is the cornerstone of progress and innovation.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-academy-coursera-blockchain/">Binance Academy Partners with Coursera to Promote Blockchain Technology</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-academy-coursera-blockchain/">Binance Academy Partners with Coursera to Promote Blockchain Technology</a></p>
<p>Binance Academy, the educational arm of top cryptocurrency exchange <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a>, has collaborated with the popular online learning platform Coursera. According to the official announcement, the partnership will help in its bid to foster the global adoption of blockchain technology.</p>
<p>By leveraging Coursera&#8217;s wide audience, which sits at over 124 million learners worldwide, Binance Academy can bring more than simple awareness of blockchain technology.</p>
<p>With the new partnership, Binance hopes to draw up a comprehensive suite of learning programs that it can launch over the next few months.</p>
<h2>Binance Academy Eyes Global Recognition for the Blockchain Industry</h2>
<p>According to the firm, the programs it intends to float will focus on blockchain, Web3, and crypto technologies. There will be courses for beginners with zero knowledge of these fields who are looking to just gain a basic understanding.</p>
<p>Binance will also develop certification courses for those that may want to explore career opportunities within the blockchain industry.</p>
<p>The programs will consist of several courses and would also come with video lectures, readings, practice assignments, and graded tasks.</p>
<p>In a statement about the recent partnership, Yi He, Binance co-founder and Chief Marketing Officer said the firm is focused on making blockchain technology accessible to everyone, adding that Coursera provides the platform to achieve exactly that. Part of the statement reads:</p>
<blockquote><p>“We&#8217;re combining the strengths of two industry leaders with a shared vision &#8211; to provide best-in-class education that will drive adoption and build the foundations for Web3.”</p></blockquote>
<p>For what it&#8217;s worth, the partnership with Coursera is only one of several educational initiatives that Binance Academy has embarked upon. It currently has other initiatives such as multimedia content, <a href="https://academy.binance.com/en/learn-and-earn/2" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Learn &amp; Earn campaigns</a>, and the University Outreach Program among others.</p>
<p>The firm has always worked with the belief that education is the cornerstone of progress and innovation. So, with the Coursera partnership, the firm appears set to be a front-runner as far as blockchain adoption is concerned. But more importantly, the partnership will also help it create a global system that will bring millions of people into the digital economy.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-slashes-price-japan/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-academy-coursera-blockchain/">Binance Academy Partners with Coursera to Promote Blockchain Technology</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-academy-coursera-blockchain/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tesla Slashes Price of Model 3 and Y Electric Vehicles in Japan</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-slashes-price-japan/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-slashes-price-japan/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 13:49:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Transportation News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[model 3]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[model y]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tesla]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261793</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-slashes-price-japan/">Tesla Slashes Price of Model 3 and Y Electric Vehicles in Japan</a></p>
<p>By reducing prices, Tesla aims to offer a compelling value proposition compared to other electric vehicle options in terms of features, performance, range, and affordability.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-slashes-price-japan/">Tesla Slashes Price of Model 3 and Y Electric Vehicles in Japan</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-slashes-price-japan/">Tesla Slashes Price of Model 3 and Y Electric Vehicles in Japan</a></p>
<p>American multinational Electric Vehicle (EV) giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/tesla/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tesla Inc</a> (NASDAQ: TSLA) has recently announced a price reduction for its Model 3 and Model Y cars in Japan. The company implemented a low single-digit percentage price cut, effective from the beginning of this month.</p>
<p>According to <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tesla-cuts-prices-japan-model-100649805.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reports</a>, Tesla reduced the prices of all variants of its lower-priced Model 3 by approximately 3%, as reflected on its official website. Additionally, the costs of all Model Y variants were reduced by around 4%.</p>
<p>The Tesla&#8217;s move has highlighted that the recent price reduction of the Model 3 in Japan has made it more affordable than ever before, especially when considering various subsidies that can be applied to the purchase. This move is in line with Tesla&#8217;s ongoing efforts to make EVs more accessible to a broader customer base.</p>
<p>Notably, the price cuts come approximately two months after Tesla had previously increased the prices of Model 3 and Model Y prices  Asian nation. With this adjustment, the Model 3 now has a price tag of 5,245,600 Yen ($36,362), while the Model Y is priced at 5,637,000 Yen.</p>
<p>In addition to the price reductions for the Model 3 and Model Y in Japan, it is worth noting that Tesla has maintained the prices of its higher-end electric vehicles, the Model S and Model X. These premium models have retained their existing price points, as Tesla continues to accept orders for them in the Japanese market.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, CEO <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/elon-musk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Elon Musk</a> emphasized during <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-q1-2023-deliveries/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tesla&#8217;s Q1 2023</a> earnings call, that the firm is focused on increasing sales volumes rather than increasing margins. This strategy suggests Tesla&#8217;s commitment to expanding its market presence and capturing a larger share of the electric vehicle market.</p>
<h2>Is Tesla Inc’s Price Cut Influenced by Heightened Competition?</h2>
<p>Tesla Inc&#8217;s unwavering commitment to innovation, technological advancement, global expansion, and customer satisfaction has positioned it as a formidable player in the electric vehicle market. According to <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-auto-production-shanghai/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reports</a>, Tesla automobiles accounted for over a quarter of total auto production in Shanghai last year.</p>
<p>However, as more traditional automakers and new entrants embrace electrification, the market has become more crowded, prompting Tesla to navigate this landscape strategically. One approach Tesla has considered to maintain its competitive edge is by implementing price reductions.</p>
<p>Notably, heightened competition puts pressure on Tesla to evaluate its pricing strategy. Lowering prices can help Tesla stay ahead of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/byd-tesla-denza-n7-electric-suv/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">rivals</a> by making its electric vehicles more attractive to consumers.</p>
<p>By reducing prices, Tesla aims to offer a compelling value proposition compared to other electric vehicle options in terms of features, performance, range, and affordability.</p>
<p>However, it&#8217;s important to note that Tesla&#8217;s pricing decisions are multifaceted and take into account various factors. Some of these factors vary by region and it includes production efficiency, economies of scale, competition and profitability amongst others.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/singapore-bank-dbs-launches-merchant-platform-enabling-e-cny-collection/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-slashes-price-japan/">Tesla Slashes Price of Model 3 and Y Electric Vehicles in Japan</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-slashes-price-japan/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Singapore Bank DBS Launches Merchant Platform Enabling e-CNY Collection</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/singapore-bank-dbs-launches-merchant-platform-enabling-e-cny-collection/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/singapore-bank-dbs-launches-merchant-platform-enabling-e-cny-collection/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Temitope Olatunji]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 13:12:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dbs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[development bank of singapore]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[e-cny]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261760</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/singapore-bank-dbs-launches-merchant-platform-enabling-e-cny-collection/">Singapore Bank DBS Launches Merchant Platform Enabling e-CNY Collection</a></p>
<p>The merchant program ensures automated settlement of e-CNY into businesses' DBS bank accounts.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/singapore-bank-dbs-launches-merchant-platform-enabling-e-cny-collection/">Singapore Bank DBS Launches Merchant Platform Enabling e-CNY Collection</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/singapore-bank-dbs-launches-merchant-platform-enabling-e-cny-collection/">Singapore Bank DBS Launches Merchant Platform Enabling e-CNY Collection</a></p>
<p>Clients of the Development Bank of Singapore (DBS) can now get payments from their customers in e-CNY, electronic Chinese Yuan. The e-CNY is the digital currency of the Chinese central bank, issued by the People&#8217;s Bank of China. The announcement about this was made on Wednesday, July 5.</p>
<p>The merchant program launched by the bank helps businesses receive payments in digital currency while having automated settlement of e-CNY in their DBS bank deposit accounts.</p>
<p>Based on the information from the Development Bank of Singapore, at least one client has transacted using the platform. With this, when a client pays a business using e-CNY, the fund will automatically appear in the business&#8217;s DBS account.</p>
<p>Ginger Cheng, the Chief Executive Officer of DBS Bank (China), <a href="https://www.dbs.com/newsroom/DBS_launches_e_CNY_merchant_collection_solution_for_mainland_businesses_to_receive_CBDC_payments_completes_first_client_transaction" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">stated</a>:</p>
<blockquote>
<p style="text-align: left;">&#8220;We received strong interest from several clients for the solution since its launch, and we are pleased to have completed the first e-CNY collection for a client &#8211; a catering company in Shenzhen. By seamlessly integrating a CBDC collection and settlement method into our clients&#8217; existing payment systems, this will help position their business for a digital future where consumers in China use e-CNY for their daily activities.&#8221;</p>
</blockquote>
<h2>DBS Committed to Making Digital Innovations to Facilitate Payments with e-CNY</h2>
<p>DBS is also engaging in other initiatives in the financial technology space. The bank is participating in Project Guardian, a program launched by the Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS) to see how asset tokenization and decentralized finance (defi) will work with a bank like DBS. The project will explore the potential benefits and the likely challenges banks may face when incorporating these new technologies.</p>
<p>Project Guardian includes institutions like <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/jpmorgan-chase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">JP Morgan</a>, Japan&#8217;s SBI Digital, Marketnode, and Temasek. It uses technologies like Aave, Uniswap, and Polygon as part of the infrastructure for testing the DeFi and asset tokenization programs.</p>
<p>In the first phase of Project Guardian testing, transactions were carried out with tokenized versions of the Singapore dollar (SGD), Japanese Yen (JPY), Singapore government securities, and Japanese government bonds.</p>
<p>The bank is also involved in projects surrounding the creation of infrastructure for issuing programmable digital Singapore dollars. The project seeks to determine how to create a digital version of the Singapore dollar that can carry out specific functions based on how it is programmed. This is no doubt related to the goal of creating a more efficient financial service.</p>
<p>Apart from the projects that have been described, DBS has been involved in several other projects. In 2021, it co-founded Partior, a solution for carrying out payments across borders and also easing the global movement of value for banks. It was also a part of Project Orchid, which aimed at creating a structure for issuing programmable digital Singapore dollars.</p>
<p>These developments show that the Development Bank of Singapore is committed to exploring digital innovations to make payments safer and more efficient. These are solid moves toward transforming the future of money.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/foxconn-q2-sales/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/singapore-bank-dbs-launches-merchant-platform-enabling-e-cny-collection/">Singapore Bank DBS Launches Merchant Platform Enabling e-CNY Collection</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/singapore-bank-dbs-launches-merchant-platform-enabling-e-cny-collection/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Foxconn Sees 14% Drop in Q2 2023 Sales, Shares Robust Outlook for Q3</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/foxconn-q2-sales/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/foxconn-q2-sales/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 13:01:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[foxconn]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261755</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/foxconn-q2-sales/">Foxconn Sees 14% Drop in Q2 2023 Sales, Shares Robust Outlook for Q3</a></p>
<p>Foxconn expressed optimism about the upcoming third quarter, anticipating a brighter outlook as they approach the peak shopping season at the end of the year.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/foxconn-q2-sales/">Foxconn Sees 14% Drop in Q2 2023 Sales, Shares Robust Outlook for Q3</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/foxconn-q2-sales/">Foxconn Sees 14% Drop in Q2 2023 Sales, Shares Robust Outlook for Q3</a></p>
<p>On Wednesday, July 5, Taiwan-based leading iPhone assembler Foxconn announced that its second-quarter (Q2) revenue dropped by 14% on the year-on-year timeline. Foxconn is one of the world&#8217;s largest contract electronics makers.</p>
<h2>Foxconn in Q2</h2>
<p>According to a statement by Foxconn, the company noted a decline in revenue for smart consumer electronics products, including smartphones, in the second quarter compared to the previous year. However, specific details were not provided.</p>
<p>The revenue for the April-June period stood at T$1.3 trillion ($41.76 billion), pretty much in line with the company&#8217;s expectations. For the last month of June 2023, the sales at Foxconn dropped by 19.7% year-on-year. However, the sales numbers stood at T$422.8 billion which makes it the second-highest figure by numbers for the month of June. In a statement recorded by Reuters, the company <a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/foxconn-q2-sales-slip-14-q3-outlook-brighter-ahead-year-end-peak-2023-07-05/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;With the second half of the year peak season currently underway, operations will gradually ramp up. The outlook for the third quarter, which will be better than the second quarter, is expected to increase at an on quarter pace higher than seen in the previous two years. When compared to the pre-pandemic period, the growth rate is expected to be approximately on par.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Foxconn Predicts Robust Sales for Q3</h2>
<p>Traditionally, the first half of the year tends to be slower for tech manufacturers in Taiwan, as major electronics companies like Apple often release new products closer to the year-end holiday season. On August 14, Foxconn is set to report its second-quarter earnings.</p>
<p>In the first quarter, Foxconn experienced a significant decline in net profit, plunging by 56%, which was larger than anticipated. This marked their largest quarterly fall in three years. The decline was attributed to a $565 million write-off associated with their 34% stake in Japanese electronics maker Sharp Corp.</p>
<p>Foxconn expressed optimism about the upcoming third quarter, anticipating a brighter outlook as they approach the peak shopping season at the end of the year. Foxconn <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/foxconn-ai-demand-server-business/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">expects</a> substantial growth in its AI server business driven by strong demand. As people increasingly rely on AI applications like ChatGPT, the need for AI servers is expanding. Foxconn forecasts a three-digit percent increase in the growth of its AI servers in 2023.</p>
<p>While Foxconn shares have seen an 8.6% increase this year, they have not performed as well as the broader Taiwan market, which has risen by 20.1%. On Wednesday, Foxconn shares closed down 1.4%, compared to a 0.5% drop in the broader market.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/grammys-ai-generated-music/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/foxconn-q2-sales/">Foxconn Sees 14% Drop in Q2 2023 Sales, Shares Robust Outlook for Q3</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/foxconn-q2-sales/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Grammys Embraces AI-Generated Music, Considers It Eligible for Award Nominations</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/grammys-ai-generated-music/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/grammys-ai-generated-music/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 12:57:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[grammy awards]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[grammys]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261703</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/grammys-ai-generated-music/">Grammys Embraces AI-Generated Music, Considers It Eligible for Award Nominations</a></p>
<p>The role of AI in music has generated both excitement and debate among artists.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/grammys-ai-generated-music/">Grammys Embraces AI-Generated Music, Considers It Eligible for Award Nominations</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/grammys-ai-generated-music/">Grammys Embraces AI-Generated Music, Considers It Eligible for Award Nominations</a></p>
<p>The Grammy Awards, known for honoring artistic brilliance, are breaking new ground by acknowledging the growing influence of AI-generated music. In a recent <a href="https://apnews.com/article/grammys-ceo-ai-rules-interview-dea135035893deab37719c354f31a889">interview</a> with the Associated Press, Harvey Mason Jr., CEO and President of the Recording Academy, shed light on the Grammy eligibility for AI-generated music.</p>
<p>According to him, if an AI voice model takes on the lead vocals of a track, it may be considered for the songwriting category but not for performance. Mason further explained that the performance aspect, which lacks human creation, does not align with the Academy&#8217;s vision of artistic expression and, therefore, will not be nominated or awarded.</p>
<p>The Academy&#8217;s CEO emphasized that human involvement and meaningful contributions are paramount in Grammy considerations. As long as humans play a crucial role in the creative process, their contributions will always be recognized and eligible for nomination, but not to the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/technology/artificial-intelligence-news/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">AI</a> part.</p>
<p>&#8220;As long as the human is contributing in a more than contributing in a more than a minimis amount, which to us means a meaningful way, they are and will always be considered for a nomination or a win. We don&#8217;t want to see technology replace human creativity. We want to ensure technology enhances, embellishes, or adds to human creativity. That&#8217;s why we took this particular stand in this award cycle,&#8221; Mason told AP in an interview.</p>
<h2>AI-Generated Songs Are Eligible for Nominations</h2>
<p>These clarifications come in response to the Academy&#8217;s revised rules and eligibility criteria announced on June 28. The guidelines were introduced after Paul McCartney revealed that an AI was used to extract John Lennon&#8217;s voice for the &#8220;last Beatles record&#8221;.</p>
<p>The newly updated rules explicitly stated that music without human authorship is ineligible in any Grammy category. However, Mason has clarified that the AI-infused compositions will be considered for nominations at the upcoming 2024 Grammy Awards.</p>
<p>&#8220;AI, or music that contains AI-created elements, is absolutely eligible for entry and for consideration for Grammy nomination. Period,&#8221; Mason said.</p>
<h2>Music Artists Express Concerns about AI-Generated Works</h2>
<p>The role of AI in music has generated both excitement and debate among artists. Grimes, a Canadian musician who has never received a Grammy award before, welcomed the use of AI technology and even offered to share royalties with creators who successfully incorporated her voice into their tracks.</p>
<p>The Canadian-born artist recently launched AI software that allows her fans and music creators around the world to integrate her voice into their music at will without facing any legal repercussions.</p>
<p>Unlike Grimes, Ice Cube has expressed concerns, referring to AI as &#8220;demonic&#8221; and expressing a willingness to take legal action against those imitating their voice on AI tracks and the platforms hosting such songs.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fourth-paradigm-hong-kong-ipo/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/grammys-ai-generated-music/">Grammys Embraces AI-Generated Music, Considers It Eligible for Award Nominations</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/grammys-ai-generated-music/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fourth Paradigm Receives Hong Kong IPO Green Light from Chinese Regulator after Fourth Attempt at Public Listing</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fourth-paradigm-hong-kong-ipo/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fourth-paradigm-hong-kong-ipo/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 12:08:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[IPO News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[csrc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[didi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fourth paradigm]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261728</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fourth-paradigm-hong-kong-ipo/">Fourth Paradigm Receives Hong Kong IPO Green Light from Chinese Regulator after Fourth Attempt at Public Listing</a></p>
<p>Following acceptance by the CSRC, Fourth Paradigm should proceed with launching its IPO in the Hong Kong market.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fourth-paradigm-hong-kong-ipo/">Fourth Paradigm Receives Hong Kong IPO Green Light from Chinese Regulator after Fourth Attempt at Public Listing</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fourth-paradigm-hong-kong-ipo/">Fourth Paradigm Receives Hong Kong IPO Green Light from Chinese Regulator after Fourth Attempt at Public Listing</a></p>
<p>Chinese artificial intelligence (AI) company Fourth Paradigm Technology has completed the process required for an initial public offering (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-initial-public-offering-ipo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">IPO</a>) in Hong Kong. The company has now received a regulatory green light from the China Securities Regulatory Commission (CSRC).</p>
<p>Fourth Paradigm is one of only a few companies to receive the green light from the CSRC this year after the Commission instituted <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-new-rules-overseas-ipos-march/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">new rules</a> for offshore listings. Introduced in February, the rules became effective from March 31 and provided clarity for companies interested in overseas IPOs. As of June 15, the CSRC had received filings for offshore IPOs from 14 companies and was reportedly waiting for 38 others.</p>
<p>According to the new rules, Fourth Paradigm and other companies looking for foreign IPOs must file with the CSRC first. In addition, each of these companies must receive approval from other regulators. These regulators are now involved in the VIE (variable interest entity) process Chinese companies use to list overseas. Agencies that could potentially be involved in the process include the National Development and Reform Commission and the Cyberspace Administration of China (CAC).</p>
<p>Fourth Paradigm’s IPO nod dissolves some uncertainty surrounding adherence to the new rules and the difficulty of listing abroad. Upon announcing the new rules, the CSRC said that any firm in violation could pay a fine of up to 10 million yuan, about $1.5 million. This fine also applies to any persons or companies who share wrong information.</p>
<h2>China&#8217;s Crackdown on Foreign IPOs</h2>
<p>China has always been particular about offshore listings, although they were much easier. Even before adopting the rules, the CAC &#8211; China’s cybersecurity regulator &#8211; requires firms holding personal data of at least 1 million users to apply for a cybersecurity review before an offshore IPO.</p>
<p>This was why the CAC slammed transport company <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/didi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Didi</a> with a $1.19 billion fine last year. Didi reportedly did not complete a cybersecurity review before listing on the New York Stock Exchange (NYSE). The CAC also fined Didi founder Cheng Wei and president Jean Liu, 1 million yuan each.</p>
<h2>Fourth Paradigm Filed for the Hong Kong IPO in March</h2>
<p>The current attempt at an IPO is <a href="https://www.scmp.com/tech/big-tech/article/3218258/chinese-ai-firm-4paradigm-files-hong-kong-ipo-after-three-failed-attempts-citing-us-sanctions-risks" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Fourth Paradigm’s fourth</a> after previous ones failed. Founded in 2014, Fourth Paradigm filed for an IPO in August 2021 and in February 2022, with both attempts expiring for unidentified reasons. The startup filed the fourth attempt in March, only a few days before the third attempt &#8211; filed last September &#8211; was to expire.</p>
<p>Fourth Paradigm was sanctioned by the US and placed on the Commerce Department’s Entity List in March. Companies on this list need a license to buy or access specific goods, services, or technologies. Following its addition to the list, Fourth Paradigm allayed public fears. The company clarified that the inclusion “should not have a material impact on the business or operations of the group”. Fourth Paradigm company also said none of its suppliers, customers, or investors, have withdrawn their commitments to the company.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/turkey-inflation-recovers-lira/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fourth-paradigm-hong-kong-ipo/">Fourth Paradigm Receives Hong Kong IPO Green Light from Chinese Regulator after Fourth Attempt at Public Listing</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fourth-paradigm-hong-kong-ipo/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Turkey’s Inflation Recovers despite Decline in Turkish Lira</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/turkey-inflation-recovers-lira/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/turkey-inflation-recovers-lira/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 11:41:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Currencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[inflation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[lira]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261743</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/turkey-inflation-recovers-lira/">Turkey’s Inflation Recovers despite Decline in Turkish Lira</a></p>
<p>The Central Bank raised the country's key interest rate from 8.5% to 15% last month.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/turkey-inflation-recovers-lira/">Turkey’s Inflation Recovers despite Decline in Turkish Lira</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/turkey-inflation-recovers-lira/">Turkey’s Inflation Recovers despite Decline in Turkish Lira</a></p>
<p>Despite the decline of the Turkish Lira following the re-election of President Recep Tayyip Erdogan, Turkey&#8217;s inflation rate is showing signs of recovery.</p>
<p>According to <a href="https://data.tuik.gov.tr/Bulten/Index?p=Consumer-Price-Index-June-2023-49658" target="_blank" rel="noopener">data</a> released by the Turkish Statistical Institute, Turkey&#8217;s consumer price index (CPI) rose by 3.92% on a month-on-month basis in June. Additionally, On a year-on-year basis, Turkey&#8217;s inflation rate rose by 38.21%, slightly lower than Reuters&#8217; forecasts of 39.47%.</p>
<p>While still high by global standards, this reading came in lower than the forecasted 4.84% by Reuters and marked a significant tick compared to the 0.04% rise observed in May.</p>
<p>Among the various categories contributing to the CPI growth, tobacco, and alcoholic beverage prices experienced the largest gains, surging by 11.13%. This notable increase in prices for these goods likely influenced the overall CPI reading for the month.</p>
<p>Additionally, prices in the restaurant and hotel sector saw a modest increase of 4.31%, contributing to the overall inflation rate.</p>
<h2>Managing the Economic Crisis in Turkey</h2>
<p>In recent years, Turkey has been grappling with stubbornly high inflation rates, which have adversely affected the purchasing power of its citizens and strained the overall economy. In a previous <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/turkish-lira-slumps-erdogan/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">report</a>, Wells Fargo’s Emerging Markets Economist and FX Strategist Brendan McKenna projected that the Lira could drop as low as 23 against the dollar.</p>
<p>However, the Turkish government has been implementing various measures to combat inflation.</p>
<p>In an effort to address the economic challenges, Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan appointed Mehmet Simsek as the new Treasury and Economy Minister. Simsek, known for his market-friendly policies, is expected to bring stability and implement measures to tackle the economic difficulties in the nation</p>
<p>Additionally, the Central Bank raised the country&#8217;s key interest rate from 8.5% to 15% last month. The apex bank affirmed its commitment to further gradual monetary tightening until the inflation situation improves.</p>
<h2>Turkey&#8217;s Inflation: Analysts Express Their Views</h2>
<p>This unexpected development has caught the attention of economists and analysts, sparking discussions about the factors influencing Turkey&#8217;s inflation dynamics and the implications for the country&#8217;s economic outlook.</p>
<p>Conotoxia&#8217;s Market Analyst Bartosz Sawicki expressed a pessimistic outlook, stating that there is “little reason for optimism.” Sawicki&#8217;s perspective reflects a cautious stance toward Turkey&#8217;s economic situation, despite the recent moderation in inflation rates.</p>
<p>Sawicki noted that the recent freefall of the Turkish Lira is starting to have adverse effects on the economy, reigniting cost pressures. This perspective aligns with the notion that a weakened currency can lead to inflationary pressures, as imported goods become more expensive and businesses face higher production costs.</p>
<p>On the other hand, Timothy Ash, Senior EM Sovereign Strategist at BlueBay Asset Management, acknowledged that the inflation numbers could have been higher given the significant depreciation of the Turkish Lira following the elections.</p>
<p>Additionally, Ash noted the importance of the role of the Central Bank in implementing appropriate policies in order to manage inflation.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-africa-crypto-exchange-licensing-rules/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/turkey-inflation-recovers-lira/">Turkey’s Inflation Recovers despite Decline in Turkish Lira</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/turkey-inflation-recovers-lira/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>South Africa Updates Crypto Exchange Licensing Rules</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-africa-crypto-exchange-licensing-rules/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-africa-crypto-exchange-licensing-rules/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Babafemi Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 11:33:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fsca]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261014</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-africa-crypto-exchange-licensing-rules/">South Africa Updates Crypto Exchange Licensing Rules</a></p>
<p>Crypto exchanges will be classified as financial service providers.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-africa-crypto-exchange-licensing-rules/">South Africa Updates Crypto Exchange Licensing Rules</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-africa-crypto-exchange-licensing-rules/">South Africa Updates Crypto Exchange Licensing Rules</a></p>

<p>With an <a href="https://triple-a.io/crypto-ownership-data/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">estimated</a> 6 million people in South Africa owning cryptocurrencies, South Africa&#8217;s financial regulator has <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-07-04/south-africa-to-require-crypto-exchanges-licensing-by-year-end" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">updated</a> its crypto exchange licensing rules.</p>
<p>Currently, crypto exchanges operating in South Africa do so without any specific legislation guiding their operation. With no rules in place, these exchanges are not subject to any standards regarding customer protection, anti-money laundering, or taxation. </p>
<h2>New Crypto Exchange Licensing Rules</h2>
<p>Per the new announcement, all crypto exchanges must obtain licenses from the Financial Sector Conduct Authority (FSCA) by the end of 2023.</p>
<p>To begin with, crypto exchanges will be classified as financial service providers. Consequently, they will be subject to various requirements and obligations under the Financial Advisory and Intermediary Services Act (FAIS Act). To obtain their license, exchanges must implement adequate governance, risk management, and compliance frameworks. They must also provide adequate disclosure and information to customers regarding the risks and benefits of using crypto assets.</p>
<p>Where crypto exchanges fail to comply with the licensing requirements, the new rule empowers the FSCA to impose sanctions and penalties on them. These could include fines, suspension, or revocation of licenses.</p>
<h2>Creating a Balanced and Effective Regulatory Framework</h2>
<p>The FSCA’s announcement is expected to bring more clarity, certainty, and stability to the regulatory environment for crypto exchanges. This could boost investor confidence and attract more capital and innovation to the sector. Likewise, it could improve customer protection and security while reducing illicit activities with crypto assets.</p>
<p>Contrarily, it could affect smaller and newer exchanges that may not be able to meet up with the licensing requirements. It may also limit the ability of exchanges to adapt to the dynamic and evolving nature of the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-market-booming-with-bitcoin-solana-collateral-network/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">crypto market</a>.</p>
<p>Since the goal is to create a balanced and effective regulatory framework, the new rules are far from done. The crypto exchange licensing rule has been opened for public consultation and will also pass through parliamentary approval before they become law. This leaves room for various stakeholders, including crypto exchanges, users, experts, and regulators to add their input.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-bing-integration-chatgpt/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-africa-crypto-exchange-licensing-rules/">South Africa Updates Crypto Exchange Licensing Rules</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-africa-crypto-exchange-licensing-rules/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=3896 metric#misses=41 metric#hit-ratio=99.0 metric#bytes=1063230 metric#prefetches=184 metric#store-reads=20 metric#store-writes=2 metric#store-hits=191 metric#store-misses=2 metric#sql-queries=34 metric#ms-total=95.82 metric#ms-cache=5.36 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.2554 metric#ms-cache-ratio=5.6 -->