<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 18:28:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Arthur Hayes says the Chinese trader will drive crypto’s next bull market</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/arthur-hayes-says-the-chinese-trader-will-drive-cryptos-next-bull-market/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/arthur-hayes-says-the-chinese-trader-will-drive-cryptos-next-bull-market/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 18:28:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitmex]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[China]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/arthur-hayes-says-the-chinese-trader-will-drive-cryptos-next-bull-market/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Arthur Hayes says the crypto autumn rally will be catalysed by Chinese traders. According to the BitMEX co-founder, a weakening of the yuan amid massive credit issuance will drive capital into crypto markets. He notes that &#8220;Hong Kong will be the conduit through which Chinese capital is allowed to own crypto.&#8221; Arthur Hayes, the co-founder [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/arthur-hayes-says-the-chinese-trader-will-drive-cryptos-next-bull-market/">Arthur Hayes says the Chinese trader will drive crypto’s next bull market</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Arthur Hayes says the crypto autumn rally will be catalysed by Chinese traders.</li>
<li dir="ltr">According to the BitMEX co-founder, a weakening of the yuan amid massive credit issuance will drive capital into crypto markets.</li>
<li dir="ltr">He notes that &ldquo;Hong Kong will be the conduit through which Chinese capital is allowed to own crypto.&rdquo;</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Arthur Hayes, the co-founder and former CEO of crypto exchange <a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/bitmex/">BitMEX</a>, believes the next crypto market rally will be shaped by the Chinese trader.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In an opinion laid out in his latest <a href="https://cryptohayes.substack.com/p/fungible" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">blog post</a>, Hayes highlights that the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC)&rsquo;s current crackdown on crypto might be a negative trigger. The crypto market is likely to freak out and crater even further due to this.</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, according to the entrepreneur, it is not the US but <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/china/">China</a> that could hold the baton as crypto heads into the next bull market. And the one catalyst to watch out for would be the &ldquo;return of the Chinese trader&rdquo; amid the weakening of the Chinese yuan.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>The return of the Chinese crypto trader through the financial pipes of Hong Kong will reignite the market at the same time the broke-ass American mass affluent are effectively shut out</em>,&rdquo; Hayes wrote in the blog post published June 16.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Hayes explains how China leads the next bull rally</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The current market setup is much like the summer of &nbsp;2015, that &ldquo;nuclear bear market&rdquo; whose catalyst was the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/after-8-years-mt-gox-creditors-may-start-receiving-their-btc-this-month/">implosion of Mt. Gox</a>.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Just as then, the 2022 bear market that included the implosion of FTX has volatility and trading volumes dried up and the sideways price action excruciatingly boring. Indeed, compared to 2015 when Bitcoin price traded near $200 for a long time, 2023 is seeing this with prices ranged below $30k since the breakdown in November 2022.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>But in August of 2015, the PBOC suddenly sparked a rally in China&rsquo;s interest for Bitcoin with a &ldquo;shock&rdquo; devaluation vs. the USD. From August to November of 2015, the price of Bitcoin tripled, with Chinese traders driving the market higher. I believe something similar could happen in 2023</em>,&rdquo; Hayes noted.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to the BitMEX co-founder, the above is an outlook he sees materializing as the world&rsquo;s second-largest economy embarks on an insane credit issuance spree. On why selling now amid concerns around the US regulatory environment &ldquo;is misplaced.&rdquo; Why?</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>At some point, the selling will stop, and then we get the dreaded sideways. The boring sideways price action will reign until something jump starts the degen spirits of crypto traders</em>.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">That trigger, he says, will be a slowdown in China&rsquo;s economy and the subsequent money printing spree that will weaken the yuan and see massive inflows into crypto. He explained:</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>The less the Chinese economy grows, the more credit will be issued. Then the currency will weaken, capital will be allowed to &ldquo;flee&rdquo; into appropriate vehicles, and finally, the crypto capital markets will be provided with the spark to hopefully start the autumn rally</em>.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">To weaken the currency, Hayes says the Peoples Bank of China (PBOC) will look to encourage credit growth sectors of the economy deemed &ldquo;good.&rdquo; These areas include semiconductors, artificial intelligence (AI), clean energy, and property. The central bank will allow these &ldquo;good&rdquo; sectors to access higher loan quotes, with banks &ldquo;instructed to lend a certain amount of yuan to these sectors.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The weakening of the yuan, and the focused approach to attracting crypto and blockchain in <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-bulls-tap-hong-kong-news-to-test-key-resistance/">Hong Kong</a> are going to be key factors, he added. It is a trajectory that best suits HODLers. The crypto bull summed up his market outlook:</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>I have predicted before and continue to believe that Hong Kong will be the conduit through which Chinese capital is allowed to own crypto financial assets</em>.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/arthur-hayes-says-the-chinese-trader-will-drive-cryptos-next-bull-market/">Arthur Hayes says the Chinese trader will drive crypto’s next bull market</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/arthur-hayes-says-the-chinese-trader-will-drive-cryptos-next-bull-market/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Investors grab $245K Chancer tokens within days of presale opening</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/investors-grab-245k-chancer-tokens-within-days-of-presale-opening/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/investors-grab-245k-chancer-tokens-within-days-of-presale-opening/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Motiur Rahman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 13:27:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technical Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/investors-grab-245k-chancer-tokens-within-days-of-presale-opening/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Chancer presale opened on June 13 and raised $245K in 3 days The predictive markets application has attracted users interested in P2P betting and investments $CHANCER could become a crypto sensation in 2023 with triple and four-digit percentage price increases Investors are accumulating Chancer tokens ($CHANCER) fast amid enthusiasm for the world&#8217;s first blockchain-based [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/investors-grab-245k-chancer-tokens-within-days-of-presale-opening/">Investors grab $245K Chancer tokens within days of presale opening</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The Chancer presale opened on June 13 and raised $245K in 3 days</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The predictive markets application has attracted users interested in P2P betting and investments</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">$CHANCER could become a crypto sensation in 2023 with triple and four-digit percentage price increases</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Investors are accumulating Chancer tokens ($CHANCER) fast amid enthusiasm for the world&rsquo;s first blockchain-based predictive markets app. The presale opened on June 13, with $245,568 raised out of a total of $1,000,000. Predictably, $CHANCER could record one of the fastest presales as demand remains high.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Chancer: Unlocking the power of decentralised and P2P bets&nbsp;</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer&rsquo;s robust presale underlines its value proposition in the betting market. At a glance, Chancer aims to bring betting to the user, allowing them to create their own market, and set rules and odds. The user can invite friends and anyone worldwide in their betting market. They can also join markets created by others, thus permitting peer-to-peer betting relationships via a decentralised blockchain ecosystem.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer brings flexibility and makes betting accessible to anyone. Users are not restricted to what their bookmakers offer. They can create a market to bet on almost everything. It could be anything from football to predicting that a friend will win an upcoming maths contest. Investors will use $CHANCER to place bets and claim winnings.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">$CHANCER will be launched on the secure BSC Chain, and real-time communications will be enabled via Google&rsquo;s WebRTC. That means investors have enhanced security and can enjoy live streaming through the WebRTC capabilities.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Multiple income opportunities through $CHANCER</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Betting is one of the ways $CHANCER holders earn by participating in live markets. There are also market-making rewards for users creating Chancer markets through the dApp and the live stream feature.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Staking is the other earning avenue for investors, which involves committing the tokens on the platform for a chance to earn interest on them. The staking feature unlocks liquidity, enabling traders to opt in and out of positions easily.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Being a blockchain platform also means Chancer is accessible worldwide. As such, the Chancer team has made it possible to spread the word about the platform and earn. This is enabled through a Share2Earn feature. And to make the platform cost-effective for users, token holders get discounted fees for the markets they create and participate in.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Is $CHANCER the next token to explode?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">The overwhelmingly bearish crypto market means investors could be searching for new projects with the potential to return big. Newly launched tokens make it to this list since their price movement is rarely influenced by the general market mood.</p>
<p dir="ltr">$CHANCER is a token launching with a new use case in betting. Predicting that this token will explode is both realistic and prudential. We can base this prediction on the quickly selling presale, which suggests that demand is strong and increasing.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">$CHANCER could explode as the token launches on exchanges and its main betting platform is created. Of course, the prediction is not outright, as it will depend on whether $CHANCER will sustain demand. Early suggestions are that it could. Consequently, we should expect an increase in the token&rsquo;s value as more investors discover the platform.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>$CHANCER prediction in 2023 and 2024</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">With the excitement around the launch of a platform that allows P2P betting and investment, $CHANCER could make robust price gains. However, a double percentage price increase for 2023 should be considered realistic, given that the token lists in the third quarter.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">With the current presale value at 0.01 BUSD, a price target of 0.1 BUSD or slightly higher in 2023 should be taken. There is still no harm in expecting a 10x increase in 2023, as $CHANCER&rsquo;s high demand could fuel strong moves.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Nonetheless, more sustained $CHANCER gains are likely to be driven by the continued usage of the platform. The mainnet will launch in the first quarter of 2024, which could unlock liquidity through real-world use cases. In my prudential approach, a 1,000% gain or higher should be expected of the token in 2024.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/investors-grab-245k-chancer-tokens-within-days-of-presale-opening/">Investors grab $245K Chancer tokens within days of presale opening</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/investors-grab-245k-chancer-tokens-within-days-of-presale-opening/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>AltSignal’s presale raises over $1 million as JPMorgan survey lauds AI-based trading</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-presale-raises-over-1-million-as-jpmorgan-survey-lauds-ai-based-trading/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-presale-raises-over-1-million-as-jpmorgan-survey-lauds-ai-based-trading/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Motiur Rahman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 13:24:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technical Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-presale-raises-over-1-million-as-jpmorgan-survey-lauds-ai-based-trading/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>AltSignals presale has surpassed $1 million in sales amid enthusiasm around its AI trading signal service. JPMorgan survey points to growing interest in AI-based trading among traders. $ASI is attractive at presale as exchange listing could fuel price increases. AltSignals (ASI) has been a&#160;presale sensation, with investors angling for a share of its AI trading [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-presale-raises-over-1-million-as-jpmorgan-survey-lauds-ai-based-trading/">AltSignal’s presale raises over $1 million as JPMorgan survey lauds AI-based trading</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals presale has surpassed $1 million in sales amid enthusiasm around its AI trading signal service.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">JPMorgan survey points to growing interest in AI-based trading among traders.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">$ASI is attractive at presale as exchange listing could fuel price increases.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals (ASI) has been a&nbsp;<a href="https://token.altsignals.io/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=price_prediction" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>presale</u></a> sensation, with investors angling for a share of its AI trading signal service platform by purchasing the token. With nearly 93% of tokens sold out, the AltSignals team has raised over $1 million to actualize its dream of an AI-powered trading platform. This could be an excellent opportunity for new investors to join the trading signal service, which has accumulated over 52,000 members on Telegram since its founding in 2017 in the UK.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Why has AltSignals generated so much interest?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals has been a very successful trading signal service. Thousands of traders are using the service, with signals averaging accuracy rates of 64%. Much credit for its success has been attributed to its experienced team and the AltAlgo&trade; software used to generate the signals. Overall, AltSignals has generated over $2.2 million in trading revenues. With the growth and demand for its service, analysts believe Altsignals could benefit immensely from artificial intelligence.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">$ASI presale welcomes a new era of AI trading signal generation for AltSignals. The company will launch an AI trading signal service platform dubbed, ActualizeAI. The blockchain-based platform will be powered by $ASI and is expected to increase the quality of signals generated by AltSignals. The service incorporates predictive modelling, machine learning, natural language processing, and sentimental analysis. The highly successful presale underlines investors&rsquo; belief that AI will be core to the growth of an already successful trading signal service.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>AI trading to dominate trading in 3 years &ndash; JPMorgan Survey</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Traders are betting that AI will dominate the future of financial markets trading, according to a new survey by JPMorgan. The survey, which included 835 professional and institutional traders, found increased automation and adoption of AI in trading.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The survey establishes that AI has grown popular since the release of ChatGPT, with investors growing curious about what AI can do in business. The strategists predict the domination of the technology in trading in the next three years. That places proprietary platforms like AltSignals and its AI platform ActualizeAI at a pole position to grow.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Beyond trading signals, ActualizeAI offers new ways to earn</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">ActualizeAI&rsquo;s benefits are not only about trading signals. Investors can earn in a variety of ways, including the ability to participate in trading competitions and get rewarded with $ASI. This could also be an opportunity for traders to sharpen their skills in trading.</p>
<p dir="ltr">$ASI holders also have access to the AI Members Club. They earn more tokens by contributing ideas and giving feedback to ActualizeAI projects. There are also exclusive presale opportunities for traders in the future.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The exciting bit is that traders can vote on matters affecting ActualizeAI using their tokens. As such, AltSignals will be a community-led platform, giving its members a voice over issues that affect them.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Should you buy $ASI in the presale?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Investment can be made at any stage of newly launched tokens, including when listed on exchanges. It depends on the value an investor sees by investing in a particular instrument. However, there is an advantage to buying tokens during their presale.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">One is the advantage of gaining access to the platform before the rest. For AltSignals, investors buying the token at presale can access ActualizeAI early enough. It means exclusive access to other presales and market opportunities.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The second advantage is obviously buying a token that is low-priced. Tokens on presale have a restricted demand since they are unavailable on exchanges. It means the price is still low, and buying at that point offers a chance to generate value from value increases. The tokens have gone to increase in value by up to 10 times from the presale price. As the $ASI presale in stage 1 draws close, it could be the right time to invest before the price skyrockets.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-presale-raises-over-1-million-as-jpmorgan-survey-lauds-ai-based-trading/">AltSignal’s presale raises over $1 million as JPMorgan survey lauds AI-based trading</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-presale-raises-over-1-million-as-jpmorgan-survey-lauds-ai-based-trading/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto exchange Binance announces exit from the Dutch market</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-exchange-binance-announces-exit-from-the-dutch-market/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-exchange-binance-announces-exit-from-the-dutch-market/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 11:30:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-exchange-binance-announces-exit-from-the-dutch-market/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways Crypto exchange Binance is leaving the Dutch market after failing to register as a VASP in the Netherlands.&#160; Binance recently applied to deregister its local unit in Cyprus and also exited the Canadian market. The cryptocurrency exchange is also facing regulatory challenges in the United States. Binance exits the Dutch market Binance, the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-exchange-binance-announces-exit-from-the-dutch-market/">Crypto exchange Binance announces exit from the Dutch market</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Crypto exchange Binance is leaving the Dutch market after failing to register as a VASP in the Netherlands.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Binance recently applied to deregister its local unit in Cyprus and also exited the Canadian market.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The cryptocurrency exchange is also facing regulatory challenges in the United States.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr">Binance exits the Dutch market</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Binance, the world&rsquo;s leading cryptocurrency exchange by daily trading volume, announced on Friday, June 16th, that it is exiting the Dutch market.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>latest cryptocurrency news</u></a> comes as the company failed to register as a Virtual Asset Service Provider (VASP) in the Netherlands. In its&nbsp;<a href="https://www.binance.com/en/support/announcement/notice-on-changes-of-services-in-the-netherlands-b5a647be31cf469b87fc3337fd461ced?ref=AZTKZ9XS&amp;utm_source=BinanceTwitter&amp;utm_medium=GlobalSocial&amp;utm_campaign=GlobalSocial" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>blog post</u></a>, Binance wrote that;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;We regret to announce that Binance is leaving the Dutch market. With immediate effect, no new users residing in the Netherlands will be accepted. Starting from 2023-07-17 at 00:00 UTC (2023-07-17 at 02:00 UTC+2), existing Dutch resident users will only be able to withdraw assets from the Binance platform. No further purchases, trades or deposits will be possible. We encourage users to take appropriate action by withdrawing assets from their Binance accounts.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p dir="ltr">The cryptocurrency exchange said although it explored many alternative avenues to service Dutch residents in compliance with Dutch regulations, it hasn&rsquo;t been successful in obtaining a VASP registration in the Netherlands.</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, Binance said it would continue to work to obtain authorisations to provide its products and services to users in the Netherlands.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Binance&rsquo;s exodus continues</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Binance has been under pressure in recent weeks and has exited some markets during that period. The cryptocurrency exchange&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-announces-exit-from-canada/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>exited the Canadian market</u></a> last month, citing the new guidelines that make the Canadian market no longer tenable for its operations.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The company also filed to deregister its local unit in Cyprus earlier this week. All these come at a time when Binance is facing regulatory pressure from the United States.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC)&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sec-sues-binance-and-cz-for-breaking-us-securities-rules/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>sued Binance</u></a> earlier this month for allegedly breaking securities laws. The securities regulator has also&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-sec-is-seeking-court-order-to-freeze-binance-uss-assets/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>filed for a temporary restraining order</u></a> to freeze Binance.US&rsquo;s assets.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-exchange-binance-announces-exit-from-the-dutch-market/">Crypto exchange Binance announces exit from the Dutch market</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-exchange-binance-announces-exit-from-the-dutch-market/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase may be losing retail crypto traders to Robinhood: Mizuho</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-losing-retail-crypto-traders-robinhood-mizuho/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wajeeh Khan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 18:39:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robinhood]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=143409</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Mizuho analyst says Coinbase may be losing share in retail crypto trading. Dan Dolev continues to see downside in the crypto exchange to $27 a share. Coinbase stock is currently down 35% versus its year-to-date high in March. Coinbase Global Inc remains at the risk of having its stock price cut in half, says Dan [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-losing-retail-crypto-traders-robinhood-mizuho/">Coinbase may be losing retail crypto traders to Robinhood: Mizuho</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Mizuho analyst says Coinbase may be losing share in retail crypto trading.</li>
<li>Dan Dolev continues to see downside in the crypto exchange to $27 a share.</li>
<li>Coinbase stock is currently down 35% versus its year-to-date high in March.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/coinbase/">Coinbase Global Inc</a> remains at the risk of having its stock price cut in half, says Dan Dolev. He&rsquo;s a Senior Analyst at Mizuho.</p>
<h2>Coinbase stock could crash to $27</h2>
<p>Dolev maintained his &ldquo;underperform&rdquo; rating on the crypto exchange today. His $27 price objective suggests shares could tank an alarming 50% from here.</p>
<p>The analyst is super bearish on Coinbase stock partially because he suspects that it&rsquo;s losing share in retail trading to peer Robinhood Markets Inc.</p>
<blockquote><p>Our analysis suggests that COIN&rsquo;s share of combined COIN retail + Hood crypto volumes trended lower in April vs. the approx. 65% ratio in the prior three quarters.</p></blockquote>
<p>Part of it may be related to the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-sec-strikes-again-first-binance-now-coinbase/">lawsuit</a> the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission filed against the crypto company last week.</p>
<h2>Coinbase has increased trading fees</h2>
<p>Dan Dolev also cited trading fees as a possible reason why Coinbase Global Inc is losing to Robinhood.</p>
<p>The crypto exchange has resorted to higher fees for small-ticket traders to offset volume declines which may have pushed them to Robinhood as it has refrained from increasing fees so far, the Mizuho analyst told clients in a research note today.</p>
<blockquote><p>If we assume that COIN maintained share and retail take rate held constant at 168bps in April &hellip; this would imply $117 million of retail transactions for April.</p></blockquote>
<p>In comparison, the company recently <a href="https://s27.q4cdn.com/397450999/files/doc_financials/2023/q1/Shareholder-Letter-Q1-2023.pdf?pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a> a lower $110 million of total transaction revenue in April. Coinbase stock is currently down 35% versus its year-to-date high.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-losing-retail-crypto-traders-robinhood-mizuho/">Coinbase may be losing retail crypto traders to Robinhood: Mizuho</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>GamCare Calls For Crypto Trading Self-Exclusion: Will GamStop Take Actions?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/gamcare-calls-for-crypto-trading-self-exclusion-will-gamstop-take-actions/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/gamcare-calls-for-crypto-trading-self-exclusion-will-gamstop-take-actions/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 18:24:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/gamcare-calls-for-crypto-trading-self-exclusion-will-gamstop-take-actions/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>GamCare is the leading provider of information, advice, support, and free referrals to prevent and resolve gambling problems in the UK. To the surprise of many, recently, GamCare equated crypto trading with gambling activities and stressed the&#160;necessity of self-exclusion for traders. The reason for this is the appearance of the first signs similar to gambling [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/gamcare-calls-for-crypto-trading-self-exclusion-will-gamstop-take-actions/">GamCare Calls For Crypto Trading Self-Exclusion: Will GamStop Take Actions?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">GamCare is the leading provider of information, advice, support, and free referrals to prevent and resolve gambling problems in the UK. To the surprise of many, recently, GamCare equated crypto trading with gambling activities and stressed the&nbsp;<a href="https://www.gamcare.org.uk/news-and-blog/news/gamcare-highlights-need-for-self-exclusion-scheme-for-consumers-involved-in-high-risk-and-cryptocurrency-trading/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>necessity of self-exclusion for traders</u></a>. The reason for this is the appearance of the first signs similar to gambling addiction, which has negative consequences.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Cryptocurrency Trading and Gambling: Similarities According To GamCare</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The crypto market appeared relatively recently but has already experienced an uncountable number of ups and downs. The crypto traders and miners lost and earned on fluctuations in cryptocurrency rates literally staggered the imagination. Cryptocurrency trading, compared to ordinary stock trading, is considered a particularly risky activity. Having tools that can&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/gamban-blocks-crypto-platforms-will-gamstop-take-actions/"><u>block crypto trading such as Gamban</u></a> may have a positive influence on both traders and cryptocurrency platforms. The crypto market is highly volatile, and it is often impossible to predict in which direction the price of coins will turn.</p>
<p dir="ltr">GamCare believes that the addiction of traders can be even stronger than that of poker players, for example, especially if we are talking about a lover who gets a dose of adrenaline by betting on the growth of certain coins.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Crypto creates the misconception that coins have a reputation for being high-tech means of payment. This provides constant faith in the growth of quotes and turns investors into gamblers.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In pursuit of profit, a crypto trader must constantly take risks. On the day, he can make many transactions as the price of some small coins rises or collapses at one moment. The conditions under which a trader (or, in this context, a gambler) must constantly be in the &ldquo;game&rdquo; are similar to gambling in an online casino. Based on this and a number of other aspects, GamCare made this decision and added crypto trading to the number of gambling activities.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How GamStop Experience Can Be Applied For Crypto Trading?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">GamStop and GamCare have the same goals, but so far different in that the former does not yet extend its activities to crypto trading. But according to experts and analysts, it may soon do so. The reason for this is the great experience and the availability of the necessary tools used for online casinos, bookmakers, etc., which can be applied in the field of crypto trading.</p>
<p dir="ltr">One obvious tool is the self-exclusion periods that traders can set for themselves. Just like in the case of&nbsp;<a href="https://nonstopcasino.org/not-gamstop-casinos/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>non GamStop casino online</u></a> accepting crypto, when customers exclude themselves from playing casino games, crypto traders could use a piece of software that would force them to take temporary breaks, do things IRL, and analyze everything without making impulsive decisions. Most crypto market players actually understand that they will lose money. But they still decide on super-risk operations &ndash; and miss the moment when the amount of potential loss becomes fatal.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Also, the most important advantage of the GamStop program is the voluntary nature and the company&rsquo;s policy of independent choice. This can also apply to cryptocurrency trading. Traders who feel they need a break can voluntarily make this decision, and no one will force them to do so.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">The Benefits of Crypto Trading Self-Exclusion Software Like GamStop</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/05/15/1686852986867-50f8af71-784e-49ae-9f0c-4caa0a858dfd.png" style="width: 800px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="800" height="307"></p>
<p dir="ltr">The GamStop program has been showing quality and performance since its first launch in April 2018. Many gamblers were sceptical about this, but still, they understood the importance of controlling gambling activity and fighting addiction to gambling, betting, and all that. Similarly to gambling platforms, the possible collaboration of self-exclusion programs like GamStop and crypto platforms could be used to the great advantage of all people involved in high-risk crypto trading operations.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Regulated Environment</h3>
<p dir="ltr">As in gambling, crypto trading is known for various fraudulent and fake platforms. Using self-exclusion programs will create a safe environment and guarantee the protection of traders in all aspects. There is nothing wrong with trading cryptocurrencies if you approach the issue rationally and wisely. But not everyone follows&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/gamstop-crypto-fostering-responsible-gambling-for-a-sustainable-ecosystem/"><u>responsible gambling rules</u></a> and is honest in this business.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Take a Break From Cryptocurrency Trading</h3>
<p dir="ltr">What was mentioned earlier is an important part of any activity. Crypto trading is no exception. Successful traders rely not on luck but on their own calculation, which can only be obtained in a calm and &ldquo;quiet&rdquo; environment.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Learn About Possible Negative Impacts</h3>
<p dir="ltr">Crypto trading is a rather specific and difficult field. But still, at some point, it is difficult to overcome the addiction. Self-exclusion programs have a large knowledge base, advisors, telephone support, and other valuable educational features. This will help traders understand what addiction is and what negative aspects it can bring to life.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Great Budget Control Tool</h3>
<p dir="ltr">Many traders are skilled in money management and budgeting. But this is only before they become addicted, and these actions become systematic and, to a greater extent, lead to the loss of real money. Self-exclusion programs allow you to set budget limits, which will help you control money-related activities.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Conclusion</h2>
<p>According to GamCare,&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/why-is-nobody-talking-about-crypto-trading-addiction/"><u>crypto trading is similar to gambling addiction</u></a>, especially in the case of people who trade crypto on a daily basis, lose large sums of money, and start chasing losses. Self-exclusion programs for gambling platforms familiar to many have demonstrated their effectiveness and usefulness for a long time. GamCare was the first to announce the expansion of the scope of the self-exclusion program. How effective it is and whether other companies will use it, like GamStop, time will tell.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/gamcare-calls-for-crypto-trading-self-exclusion-will-gamstop-take-actions/">GamCare Calls For Crypto Trading Self-Exclusion: Will GamStop Take Actions?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/gamcare-calls-for-crypto-trading-self-exclusion-will-gamstop-take-actions/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Blk DNM Introduces Intelligence Into Clothing With Blockchain, In First Use Of ‘Connected Fashion’</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/blk-dnm-introduces-intelligence-into-clothing-with-blockchain-in-first-use-of-connected-fashion/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/blk-dnm-introduces-intelligence-into-clothing-with-blockchain-in-first-use-of-connected-fashion/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire &#160;]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 16:59:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=143400</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Stockholm, Sweden, June 15th, 2023, Chainwire BLK DNM bridging the Physical and Virtual Worlds of Fashion through Blockchain Innovation Swedish-American fashion brand BLK DNM today unveils the first-ever example of connected fashion (garments that exist both physically and virtually, each aspect &#8216;twinned&#8217; via technology) with the launch of BLK DNM Society and integration of blockchain-powered [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/blk-dnm-introduces-intelligence-into-clothing-with-blockchain-in-first-use-of-connected-fashion/">Blk DNM Introduces Intelligence Into Clothing With Blockchain, In First Use Of ‘Connected Fashion’</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Stockholm, Sweden, June 15th, 2023, Chainwire</strong></p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">BLK DNM bridging the Physical and Virtual Worlds of Fashion through Blockchain Innovation</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Swedish-American fashion brand <a href="https://www.blkdnm.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">BLK DNM</a> today unveils the first-ever example of connected fashion (garments that exist both physically and virtually, each aspect &lsquo;twinned&rsquo; via technology) with the launch of <strong>BLK DNM Society</strong> and integration of blockchain-powered hardware and software into its products.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">BLK DNM Society, built on tech designed by blockchain innovator and BLK DNM owner <a href="https://chromaway.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">ChromaWay</a>, will grant each garment a unique and recordable identity in both the physical and virtual worlds, while also rewarding ethical behaviour and granting brand influence to owners.</p>
<ul>
<li>Blockchain-powered &lsquo;digital garment ID&rsquo; microchips will give each item a unique identity and record of its history</li>
<li>Chips form the hardware element of BLK DNM Society, which launches in tandem and rewards responsible behavior and ownership</li>
<li>Tech will first appear in BLK DNM&rsquo;s FW 2023 collection</li>
</ul>
<h2 class="ql-align-justify">The Hardware: Digital Garment IDs</h2>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Future BLK DNM clothing will be fitted with a &lsquo;digital garment ID&rsquo; &ndash; an undetectable chip that gives each physical item a unique and recordable identity. Some of the first features of the digital garment IDs will include:</p>
<ul>
<li>Authentication of the garment as genuine, eliminating fakes and counterfeiting</li>
<li>Rewarding responsible behaviours of treasuring and caring for clothing long-term, such as refurbs and second-hand purchases</li>
<li>Recording each individual garment&rsquo;s unique history &ndash; owners, events and places worn, repairs and alterations &ndash; enabling the item to accrue emotional and monetary value over time</li>
<li>Acting as a digital ticket for entry to events</li>
<li>Access to and voting rights within BLK DNM Society</li>
</ul>
<h2 class="ql-align-justify">BLK DNM Society</h2>
<p class="ql-align-justify">The digital garment IDs are the first hardware elements of BLK DNM Society, which launches in tandem. The first example of connected fashion, BLK DNM Society is a community of BLK DNM owners, connected virtually by their physical items, who are rewarded for responsible behaviours and are granted voting rights on key brand decisions based on item ownership &ndash; thereby beginning the first ever process of decentralising a fashion brand&rsquo;s stewardship.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Each digital garment ID will create a &lsquo;digital reflection&rsquo; of the physical garment: a twin in the virtual world where the physical item&rsquo;s history and place within BLK DNM Society is recorded. The digital reflection can also be worn in the metaverses, catering especially to younger generations whose identities in virtual worlds are equally as important as in the physical.</p>
<h2 class="ql-align-justify">FW 2023</h2>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Digital garment IDs will be revealed at BLK DNM&rsquo;s FW event in Paris on June 21st. For this first collection, the chips will be embedded in only leather items, with subsequent collections introducing more items to BLK DNM Society through embedded blockchain-enabled hardware.</p>
<blockquote><p>Henrik Hjelte, CEO and Co-founder of ChromaWay, comments: &ldquo;This is totally futuristic. Nothing like this has been attempted in fashion before. It&rsquo;s very exciting for us, after much hard work, to see our technology elevating one of fashion&rsquo;s iconic brands into something completely unique. This has the potential to transform people&rsquo;s relationships with the clothes they wear and the brands they buy. No longer does the relationship with the customer end at the checkout. And each beautiful garment now becomes its own living, evolving piece of history.&rdquo;</p></blockquote>
<p class="ql-align-justify"><img decoding="async" src="https://invezz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/DSCF4500-3_2_1686842385CWogefXm84.jpg"></p>
<p>Toni Collin, CEO of BLK DNM, and Henrik Hjelte, CEO and Co-founder of ChromaWay</p>
<blockquote><p>Toni Collin, CEO of BLK DNM, comments: &ldquo;BLK DNM&rsquo;s philosophy is one of community, and our clothing is designed, through both its craftsmanship and timeless aesthetic, to be treasured and passed down through generations &ndash; the antithesis of irresponsible fast fashion. Now, with the introduction of BLK DNM Society and the first embedded hardware in our garments, we take those two pillars to a revolutionary new level. By embedding intelligence in every item, we hope we can inspire our industry to join us in using connected fashion to do better.&rdquo;</p></blockquote>
<h3>About BLK DNM</h3>
<p class="ql-align-justify">BLK DNM is a Swedish-American fashion brand that specialises in timeless tailoring, leather, and denim of extraordinary quality. Following its 2023 relaunch as an entry-luxury fashion house under the stewardship of new Creative Director Jessy Heuvelink, BLK DNM&rsquo;s focus on both enduring craftsmanship and aesthetic timelessness encourages customers to love and treasure each item for decades and across generations.</p>
<h3>About ChromaWay</h3>
<p>ChromaWay is an industry leader in blockchain technology and specializes in creating and deploying cutting-edge, scalable blockchain solutions for both businesses and governments. The company, which was established in 2014 and has its headquarters in Stockholm, Sweden, has been at the forefront of driving the widespread adoption of blockchain technology. Its flagship product, relational blockchain Chromia, enables developers to build decentralized applications (dApps) with a relational database model that offers unprecedented scalability and flexibility.</p>
<p><strong>Contact</strong></p>
<p>Fati Hakim, Fati.Hakim@ChromaWay.com</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/blk-dnm-introduces-intelligence-into-clothing-with-blockchain-in-first-use-of-connected-fashion/">Blk DNM Introduces Intelligence Into Clothing With Blockchain, In First Use Of ‘Connected Fashion’</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/blk-dnm-introduces-intelligence-into-clothing-with-blockchain-in-first-use-of-connected-fashion/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase partners with Bitkey Wallet to promote Bitcoin self-custody</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-partners-with-bitkey-wallet-to-promote-bitcoin-self-custody/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-partners-with-bitkey-wallet-to-promote-bitcoin-self-custody/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 15:14:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wallets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-partners-with-bitkey-wallet-to-promote-bitcoin-self-custody/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Coinbase&#8217;s partnership with Bitkey, Block&#8217;s self-custody bitcoin wallet, will span six continents. The platforms will integrate Coinbase Pay to allow users buy/sell or transfer Bitcoin to their Bitkey self-custody wallet. Coinbase said the collaboration will allow customers to easily buy, store and manage their BTC. Coinbase and Bitkey, the self-custody Bitcoin (BTC) wallet built by [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-partners-with-bitkey-wallet-to-promote-bitcoin-self-custody/">Coinbase partners with Bitkey Wallet to promote Bitcoin self-custody</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Coinbase&rsquo;s partnership with Bitkey, Block&rsquo;s self-custody bitcoin wallet, will span six continents.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The platforms will integrate Coinbase Pay to allow users buy/sell or transfer Bitcoin to their Bitkey self-custody wallet.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Coinbase said the collaboration will allow customers to easily buy, store and manage their BTC.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/coinbase/">Coinbase</a> and Bitkey, the self-custody <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">Bitcoin (BTC)</a> wallet built by the Block, Inc., have<a href="https://www.coinbase.com/blog/announcing-a-global-partnership-with-blocks-bitkey-wallet" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">&nbsp;<u>announced</u></a> a global partnership that will see the two companies promote self-custody usage.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The partnership, which will span six continents, will see Bitkey users buy and sell BTC on Coinbase, as well as transfer their holdings to their self-custody Bitkey wallets. The wallet includes a mobile app, hardware device and set of recovery tools, the companies said in a blog announcement on Thursday.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to the announcement, Coinbase and Bitkey will leverage Coinbase Pay to allow customers easy access to fiat-to-crypto onramps, the US-based crypto exchange noted in the blog post. It is a key component to powering the next adoption phase of the Bitcoin economy.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>At Bitkey, we&rsquo;re building a self-custody bitcoin wallet designed to empower the next 100 million people to truly own and manage their Bitcoin &ndash; safely and easily</em>,&rdquo; Lindsey Grossman, Business Lead at Bitkey said.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>Partners play a key role in bringing self-custody to a wider group of people around the world, and we are incredibly proud to have partnered with leading companies like Coinbase to make self-custody both secure and easy to use</em>.&rdquo;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitkey launches global beta program</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The collaboration between Coinbase and Bitkey is kicking off as the self-custody wallet launches its global beta program.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Customers in the beta program will be able to transfer their Bitcoin from centralized exchanges to Bitkey&rsquo;s self-custody wallet. Buying and selling as well as direct transfers between Coinbase and Bitkey will be enabled when the wallet launches to the public later this year.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As noted above, Bitkey and Coinbase will offer the service to customers in six continents. Some of the countries include the US, Canada, the UK, Brazil, and Australia.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-partners-with-bitkey-wallet-to-promote-bitcoin-self-custody/">Coinbase partners with Bitkey Wallet to promote Bitcoin self-custody</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-partners-with-bitkey-wallet-to-promote-bitcoin-self-custody/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance introduces Bitcoin mining cloud services amid regulatory pressure</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-introduces-bitcoin-mining-cloud-services-amid-regulatory-pressure/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-introduces-bitcoin-mining-cloud-services-amid-regulatory-pressure/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 14:19:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-introduces-bitcoin-mining-cloud-services-amid-regulatory-pressure/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways Binance users interested in Bitcoin mining can now subscribe to Binance&#8217;s cloud mining services starting today. The new service comes despite Binance currently facing regulatory pressure in the United States.&#160; Binance launches its Bitcoin mining cloud services The world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency exchange by daily trading volume, Binance, has launched new Bitcoin subscription-based cloud [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-introduces-bitcoin-mining-cloud-services-amid-regulatory-pressure/">Binance introduces Bitcoin mining cloud services amid regulatory pressure</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Binance users interested in Bitcoin mining can now subscribe to Binance&rsquo;s cloud mining services starting today.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The new service comes despite Binance currently facing regulatory pressure in the United States.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr">Binance launches its Bitcoin mining cloud services</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The world&rsquo;s largest cryptocurrency exchange by daily trading volume, <a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/binance/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Binance</u></a>, has launched new Bitcoin subscription-based cloud mining products.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">https://twitter.com/binance/status/1669212701443379201</p>
<p dir="ltr">Starting today, June 15, Binance users interested in Bitcoin mining but who don&rsquo;t have the hardware can subscribe to the cryptocurrency exchange&rsquo;s cloud mining services and purchase hashrates.</p>
<p dir="ltr">At the moment, the cryptocurrency exchange is selling 1 Terahash per second (Th/s) at $10.7280. As a user purchases more hashrate. The probability of higher income in terms of the Bitcoin earned through mining increases.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Binance revealed that its BTC mining subscription service would be active for six months. For each TH/s purchased, users stand a chance to earn 0.0004338 BTC during the 180-day period.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The product is currently available on the Binance global website, which means that it is not available to its users in the United States.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Binance continues to face regulatory pressure</h2>
<p dir="ltr">This latest development comes at a time when Binance is facing regulatory pressure in the United States.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC)&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sec-sues-binance-and-cz-for-breaking-us-securities-rules/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>sued Binance</u></a> earlier this month for allegedly breaking securities laws. The regulatory agency has also filed for a temporary restraining order to&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-sec-is-seeking-court-order-to-freeze-binance-uss-assets/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>freeze Binance.US&rsquo;s assets</u></a>.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Binance.US has already hired former SEC enforcement co-director George Canellos as part of its legal team as it defends itself against the regulatory agency&rsquo;s allegations.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Last week, Binance.US announced the suspension of USD deposits on its platform as it transitions into an all-crypto exchange.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The SEC also&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-sec-strikes-again-first-binance-now-coinbase/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>sued rival cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase</u></a> for failing to register as a broker, national securities exchange or clearing agency.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-introduces-bitcoin-mining-cloud-services-amid-regulatory-pressure/">Binance introduces Bitcoin mining cloud services amid regulatory pressure</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-introduces-bitcoin-mining-cloud-services-amid-regulatory-pressure/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
