<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 09:54:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>One of the original Bitcoin core developers losses all his BTC in hack</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/one-of-the-original-bitcoin-core-developers-losses-all-his-btc-in-hack/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/one-of-the-original-bitcoin-core-developers-losses-all-his-btc-in-hack/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 09:54:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/one-of-the-original-bitcoin-core-developers-losses-all-his-btc-in-hack/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin OG and core developer, Dashjr, claimed virtually all his bitcoins were stolen. The hackers accessed the developer&#8217;s PGP key. On November 17, 2022, Dashjr,&#160;noted his server had been compromised. A Bitcoin OG and one of the original Bitcoin&#8217;s core developers, Luke Dashjr, has claimed that he virtually lost all his bitcoins after his Pretty [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/one-of-the-original-bitcoin-core-developers-losses-all-his-btc-in-hack/">One of the original Bitcoin core developers losses all his BTC in hack</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitcoin OG and core developer, Dashjr, claimed virtually all his bitcoins were stolen.</li>
<li>The hackers accessed the developer&rsquo;s PGP key.</li>
<li>On November 17, 2022, Dashjr,&nbsp;noted his server had been compromised.</li>
</ul>
<p>A <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/what-is-bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> OG and one of the original Bitcoin&rsquo;s core developers, Luke Dashjr, has claimed that he virtually lost all his bitcoins after his Pretty Good Privacy (PGP) keys were compromised on December 31, 2022, just before the new year.</p>
<p>PGP key is a common security method that uses two keys to gain access to encrypted information.</p>
<p>In a <a href="https://twitter.com/LukeDashjr/status/1609613748364509184?s=20&amp;t=eDL6QcUYyrfMNvjVEa3QdQ">post on Twitter</a> on January 1, 2023, Dashjr was asking for help from the PSA:</p>
<p><em>&ldquo;PSA: My PGP key is compromised, and at least many of my bitcoins stolen. I have no idea how. Help please.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p>In a <a href="https://twitter.com/LukeDashjr/status/1609647203890372609?s=20&amp;t=eDL6QcUYyrfMNvjVEa3QdQ">follow-up tweet</a>, Dashjr appeared distressed asking why he could not reach anyone from the FBI or IC3 before following it up with a tweet containing a wallet address, which is believed to be one of the Bitcoin wallets where some of the stolen BTC was sent to.</p>
<p><em>&ldquo;What the heck @FBI @ic3 &nbsp;why can&rsquo;t I reach anyone???</em></p>
<p>Although Dashjr did not disclose how many bitcoins were stolen from his wallet, the wallet address that he shared showed four bitcoin transactions on December 31 that totalled to 216.93 BTC.</p>
<h2>Dashjr server compromised in November 2022</h2>
<p>Although the developer said that he had no idea as to how hackers gained access to his PGP key, some community members have drawn a possible connection to an earlier claim that Dashjr had made on November 17, 2022, that his server had been compromised by &ldquo;&ldquo;new malware/backdoors on the system.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Unfortunately, Dashjr, says that he learnt of the hack after getting emails from Kraken and Coinbase about login attempts.</p>
<p>The hack also caught the attention of Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao (CZ) who consoled the developer on <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1609663902610034691">Twitter saying</a>:</p>
<p><em>&ldquo;Sorry to see you lose so much. Informed our security team to monitor. If it comes our way, we will freeze it. If there is anything else we can help with, please let us know. We deal with these often, and have Law Enforcement (LE) relationships worldwide.&rdquo;</em></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/one-of-the-original-bitcoin-core-developers-losses-all-his-btc-in-hack/">One of the original Bitcoin core developers losses all his BTC in hack</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/one-of-the-original-bitcoin-core-developers-losses-all-his-btc-in-hack/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lido now has the highest TVL in DeFi after overtaking MakerDAO</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/lido-now-has-the-highest-tvl-in-defi-after-overtaking-makerdao/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/lido-now-has-the-highest-tvl-in-defi-after-overtaking-makerdao/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 09:06:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[De-Fi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Maker]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/lido-now-has-the-highest-tvl-in-defi-after-overtaking-makerdao/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Lido has overtaken MakerDAO in TVL in DeFi by $0.05 billion. At press time, Lido had $5.96b DeFi TVL. Lido seems to be benefitting from Ethereum&#8217;s merge upgrade. At press time, Lido which specializes in liquid staking had a total value staked of $5.96 billion which is $0.05 billion higher than MakerDAO&#8217;s TVL of $5.91 [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/lido-now-has-the-highest-tvl-in-defi-after-overtaking-makerdao/">Lido now has the highest TVL in DeFi after overtaking MakerDAO</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul class="decimal_type">
<li>Lido has overtaken MakerDAO in TVL in DeFi by $0.05 billion.</li>
<li>At press time, Lido had $5.96b DeFi TVL.</li>
<li>Lido seems to be benefitting from Ethereum&rsquo;s merge upgrade.</li>
</ul>
<p>At press time, Lido which specializes in liquid staking had a total value staked of $5.96 billion which is $0.05 billion higher than MakerDAO&rsquo;s TVL of $5.91 billion according to <a href="https://defillama.com/">Defillama</a>. MakerDao has had the largest DeFi TVL for many years and the overtaking means Lido is gaining ground despite the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-winter-may-not-end-anytime-soon/">ongoing crypto winter</a>.</p>
<p>Besides, the increasing staked digital assets, the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/lido-dao/">price of LDO</a>, Lido DAO&rsquo;s native token, has been on a consistent rise having gained over 18% in the past 7 days. It had surged by 14.67% in the past 24 hours at press time.</p>
<p>The rise of interest in Lido among decentralized finance participants is highly thought to be due to the increased demand for Ether staking solutions since Ethereum shifted to a proof-of-stake (PoS) consensus mechanism after the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-successfully-completes-the-merge-eth-price-analysis/">merge upgrade</a> in September 2022.</p>
<h2>Digital assets staked on Lido</h2>
<p>According to Lido Finance&rsquo;s website as of January 2023, Ether (ETH) was the largest staked digital asset with over $5.86 billion worth of staked ETH tokens. Solana follows closely with over $26.087 million worth of staked SOL tokens.</p>
<p>The other notables tokens staked on Lido include Polygon&rsquo;s MATIC with over $45.093 million worth of staked MATIC tokens, Polkadot&rsquo;s DOT with over $11.395 million worth of staked DOT tokens, and Kusama&rsquo;s KSM with over $2.238 million worth of staked KSM tokens.</p>
<h2>No 32 ETH min. needed to stake Ether on Lido</h2>
<p>Lido&rsquo;s model allows users to access Ethereum staking without having to commit the traditional minimum of 32 ETH to be allowed to stake Ether. This has greatly increased the number of people choosing to stake ETH on Lido compared to other DeFi staking platforms.</p>
<p>According to Lido&rsquo;s staking model, users stake any amount of tokens including Ether and access daily staking rewards. In addition to the daily staking rewards, the users also receive liquid stTokens that can be used across DeFi to compound more to the daily staked rewards.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/lido-now-has-the-highest-tvl-in-defi-after-overtaking-makerdao/">Lido now has the highest TVL in DeFi after overtaking MakerDAO</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/lido-now-has-the-highest-tvl-in-defi-after-overtaking-makerdao/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Report: $300m of FTX debtors transferred without authorization</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/report-300m-of-ftx-debtors-transferred-without-authorization/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/report-300m-of-ftx-debtors-transferred-without-authorization/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Daniela Kirova]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 08:12:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/report-300m-of-ftx-debtors-transferred-without-authorization/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This cryptocurrency is currently held in a single digital wallet at Fireblocks The Bahamas Commission instructed Sam Bankman-Fried to transfer the funds to this wallet FTX debtors (FTX Trading Ltd. and affiliates) published information on their cryptocurrency in the control of the Bahamas Commission (Securities Commission of the Bahamas).&#160; After the chapter 11 bankruptcy case [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/report-300m-of-ftx-debtors-transferred-without-authorization/">Report: $300m of FTX debtors transferred without authorization</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>This cryptocurrency is currently held in a single digital wallet at Fireblocks</li>
<li>The Bahamas Commission instructed Sam Bankman-Fried to transfer the funds to this wallet </li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p>FTX debtors (FTX Trading Ltd. and affiliates) <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/ftx-debtors-provide-information-concerning-bahamas-crypto-seizure-301711610.html">published information</a> on their cryptocurrency in the control of the Bahamas Commission (Securities Commission of the Bahamas).&nbsp;</p>
<p>After the chapter 11 bankruptcy case commenced on November 12, 2022, digital assets of the FTX debtors worth just under 200 million <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ftx-token-whats-happening-with-the-dead-ftt/">FTT</a> were transferred without their authorization, as well as around 1,938 ether.&nbsp;</p>
<h2>Crypto held in a single Fireblocks wallet&nbsp;</h2>
<p>According to blockchain data, this <a href="https://coinjournal.net/cryptocurrencies/">cryptocurrency</a> is currently held in a single digital wallet at Fireblocks. The Bahamas Commission instructed Sam Bankman-Fried to transfer the funds to this wallet on November 12. The Commission admitted to arranging these transfers. &nbsp;</p>
<p>At the time of the transfer, the value of the crypto in this Fireblocks wallet was just under $300 million at spot prices according to etherscan.io, if one assumes the whole amount of FTT could be sold at spot prices then. This value had dropped to around $167 million on December 30. Such a large amount of FTT won&rsquo;t necessarily be sold at spot prices, if at all.</p>
<h2>Debtors to seek return of seized crypto&nbsp;</h2>
<p>The FTX Debtors informed the Bahamas Commission that no entity had been authorized by them to take the cryptocurrency. The debtors will request the return of the seized cryptocurrency for the creditors&rsquo; benefit to their chapter 11 estates promptly.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The Bahamas Commission was only responsible for regulating FTX DM (FTX Digital Markets Ltd.), a local service company on the islands. This company neither owns nor operates the FTX exchange or owns or holds custody of the crypto seized.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/report-300m-of-ftx-debtors-transferred-without-authorization/">Report: $300m of FTX debtors transferred without authorization</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/report-300m-of-ftx-debtors-transferred-without-authorization/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin (BTC) Price Slides as Inflation Is Going Up &#8211; Here&#8217;s Why Crypto New Projects Like Metacade (MCADE) Could Surge</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-btc-price-slides-as-inflation-is-going-up-heres-why-crypto-new-projects-like-metacade-mcade-could-surge/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice Davies]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 12:08:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-btc-price-slides-as-inflation-is-going-up-heres-why-crypto-new-projects-like-metacade-mcade-could-surge/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Real-world economic performance undeniably impacts global cryptocurrency markets, with Bitcoin (BTC), the biggest crypto asset by market capitalization, proving an excellent guide to the health of the crypto industry. Recent increases in inflation worldwide, but particularly in the US, have seen the value of Bitcoin slide during the second half of 2022 as the global [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-btc-price-slides-as-inflation-is-going-up-heres-why-crypto-new-projects-like-metacade-mcade-could-surge/">Bitcoin (BTC) Price Slides as Inflation Is Going Up &#8211; Here&#8217;s Why Crypto New Projects Like Metacade (MCADE) Could Surge</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Real-world economic performance undeniably impacts global cryptocurrency markets, with Bitcoin (BTC), the biggest crypto asset by market capitalization, proving an excellent guide to the health of the crypto industry. Recent increases in inflation worldwide, but particularly in the US, have seen the value of Bitcoin slide during the second half of 2022 as the global economic crisis takes hold.</p>
<p dir="ltr">While this isn&rsquo;t great news for existing investors in the world&rsquo;s leading cryptocurrencies, such as BTC, excellent investment opportunities in exciting new crypto projects remain. One of the most enticing new crypto projects is <a href="https://metacade.co/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade</u></a>, which saw an enthusiastic uptake during its beta presale stage, raising almost $1 million in just three weeks.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Metacade?</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://metacade.co/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade</u></a> is the world&rsquo;s first virtual gaming arcade that uses Web3 and blockchain technology to revolutionize the GameFi metaverse industry. The platform will host the broadest range of play-to-earn (P2E) games in the metaverse and offer gamers the same level of fun and social interaction they&rsquo;d get visiting a real-life video arcade from the comfort of their gaming chair or sofa.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The P2E element of the community is one of several ways community users benefit from the platform. The other revenue stream initiatives are:</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Compete2Earn &ndash; earning by staking tokens and gaining tournament rewards</li>
<li dir="ltr">Create2Earn &ndash; earning by interacting with the community and its members</li>
<li dir="ltr">Work2Earn &ndash; earning through finding new Web3 role on the jobs board, which launches in Q1 2024.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">In addition to the opportunities to earn, Metacade is a platform that allows budding developers to earn their stripes by supporting them to learn game development and has plans to become a self-sufficient and fully-fledged DAO by Q4 2024.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How Metacade works</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Unlike many GameFi platforms,&nbsp;<a href="https://metacade.co/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade</u></a> has a diverse offering that stretches beyond the P2E element. The native token for the platform is the MCADE coin, and there are several ways Metacade generates revenue.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade&rsquo;s revenue-generating features include a range of pay-to-play arcade games, just like gamers would expect to find in a real-world video arcade. There&rsquo;s also advertising on the platform, entry fees for prize draws and to compete in tournaments, and the launchpad initiative, which allows external companies to release games in Metacade for a price. These revenue streams provide the funds that flow into gamers&rsquo; wallets as they earn rewards.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The number of titles available on Metacade will continue to grow. This growth will be aided from Q3 2023 by the introduction of the Metagrants initiative. Metagrants are a source of funding for developers to build games on the platform. Developers submit gaming proposals to be voted on by MCADE token holders, who determine the community&rsquo;s favorite ideas. The winning developers will receive funding to help turn their proposals into reality. The first Metagrant-backed games hit the Metacade library in Q1 2024.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Other features in the pipeline include introducing a jobs board in Q1 2024 to boost the Work2Earn initiative. The board will feature a range of opportunities from internships, short-term gig work, and full-time roles within the GameFi industry with Metacade-approved partners, giving anyone with a genuine interest in working in Web3 development a helping hand to get started in the industry.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Meanwhile, Metacade&rsquo;s transition into becoming a DAO begins in Q2 2023, with the process estimated to take 18 months before community members assume all of the critical roles. This autonomy is one of Metacade&rsquo;s leading lights; it hands control of the platform&rsquo;s future direction to the most important community members.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Why could MCADE surge?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The breadth of Metacade&rsquo;s plans, found in more detail in their <a href="https://metacade.co/whitepaper.pdf" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>white paper</u></a>, makes it an exciting prospect for investors hunting for new crypto projects. With many other GameFi developments focusing on a minimal range of options, it&rsquo;s easy for them to become little more than a fad.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade&rsquo;s offering will not fall into that trap. The range of games on offer will continue to increase, providing additional opportunities to earn, whether through competitions, playing, or creating social content to engage with the community. Furthermore, the continual addition of new games means there&rsquo;s no risk of the platform becoming boring or stale since it will continually reinvent itself with the regular release of new and exciting titles. As a result, Metacade has solid project longevity.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Additionally, the community will ultimately have complete autonomy over how Metacade develops. Gamers&rsquo; interests will forever be at the heart of the platform&rsquo;s development, unlike in more traditional gaming, where developers have to balance that with providing a return to shareholders.</p>
<p dir="ltr">These plans place Metacade at the forefront of the blockchain gaming revolution.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to purchase MCADE tokens</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The Metacade beta sale sold out in less than four weeks, making it one of the most attractive new crypto projects currently in its presale stage. The price will increase by more than double as &nbsp;the ninth and final presale round concludes, raising a total market cap of $28 million.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Getting on board with Metacade couldn&rsquo;t be simpler. Tokens can be purchased on Metacade&rsquo;s website by anyone with a Wallet Connect-supported crypto wallet.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">You can purchase MCADE with ETH (Ethereum) or USDT (Tether). First, connect your wallet to Metacade&rsquo;s website to access the DEX, and then accept the option to purchase MCADE with ETH or USDT.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>You can buy BTC at eToro&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://coinjournal.net/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=OTg5NzA" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong><u>here</u></strong></a><strong>.</strong></p>
<p><strong>You can participate in the Metacade pre-sale&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://metacade.co/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong><u>here</u></strong></a><strong>.</strong></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-btc-price-slides-as-inflation-is-going-up-heres-why-crypto-new-projects-like-metacade-mcade-could-surge/">Bitcoin (BTC) Price Slides as Inflation Is Going Up &#8211; Here&#8217;s Why Crypto New Projects Like Metacade (MCADE) Could Surge</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nic Carter: BitMEX, Kraken top proof-of-reserves ranking</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/nic-carter-bitmex-kraken-top-proof-of-reserves-ranking/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 11:28:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitmex]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kraken]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/nic-carter-bitmex-kraken-top-proof-of-reserves-ranking/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>BitMEX and Kraken crypto exchanges received highest scores for their proof of reserves attestations. Binance ranked lower for its &#8216;incomplete&#8217; PoR among other metrics. Nic Carter says the PoR momentum is good for crypto and a &#8220;silver lining&#8221; out of the FTX chaos. BitMEX and Kraken score highly in an assessment of proof-of-reserves attestations by [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/nic-carter-bitmex-kraken-top-proof-of-reserves-ranking/">Nic Carter: BitMEX, Kraken top proof-of-reserves ranking</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>
<div class="fr-img-space-wrap">
<p class="fr-img-space-wrap2">BitMEX and Kraken crypto exchanges received highest scores for their proof of reserves attestations.</p>
</div>
<p></p></strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>Binance ranked lower for its &lsquo;incomplete&rsquo; PoR among other metrics.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><strong><em>Nic Carter says the PoR momentum is good for crypto and a &ldquo;silver lining&rdquo; out of the FTX chaos.</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/wallets/bitmex/">BitMEX</a> and Kraken score highly in an assessment of proof-of-reserves attestations by major crypto exchanges.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">That&rsquo;s according Nic Carter, one of the most popular Bitcoin advocates out there.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In a Medium article highlighting the score list and rankings of some of the leading crypto trading platforms, Carter points out the latest PoR results and offers insight into why some of the exchanges just getting to publish their cryptographic proof of reserves may still have a lot of work to offer the assurances the market seeks.</p>
<p dir="ltr">While Kraken and BitMEX rank highest, the world&rsquo;s largest crypto platform <a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/binance/">Binance</a> posts a relatively low score. But according to the crypto analyst, the move to have PoRs is undeniably one in the right direction. He sees the momentum as a good signal for <a href="https://coinjournal.net/cryptocurrencies/">cryptocurrencies</a>, terming it &ldquo;<em>a genuine silver lining from the FTX debacle</em>.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>We may well yet emerge from this crisis with a major step forward in exchange credibility</em>,&rdquo; he <a href="https://medium.com/@nic__carter/the-status-of-proof-of-reserve-as-of-year-end-2022-48120159377c" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">wrote</a> in his &lsquo;The Status of Proof of Reserve as of Year End 2022&rsquo;.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">BitMEX, Kraken rank higher on various metrics</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Looking at crypto exchange reserves attestations via metrics such as assets for which the platform provided the attestation, estimates of deposits covered and disclosure of liabilities, BitMEX scored the highest with 5 out of 6.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Crypto platform Kraken was second, while Deribit, KuCoin and OKX ranked third to fifth in that order.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><span class="fr-img-caption fr-fic fr-dib fr-fil" style="width: 591px"><span class="fr-img-wrap"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2022/11/30/1672399269120-3d422d43-6837-4f75-8590-3bed35c02573.png" style="width: 600px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="600" height="190"><span class="fr-inner">Exchange proof of reserves scores and ranking. Source: Nic Carter on Medium</span></span></span>While some platforms scored highly Binance&rsquo;s proof of reserves was mostly &lsquo;incomplete&rsquo; and thus the exchange scored poorly. &nbsp;In a comment on this, Carter wrote:</p>
<p>&ldquo;<em>Binance&rsquo;s first PoR doesn&rsquo;t grant strong assurances. It only covers Bitcoin, which only represents 16.5% of their client assets. It does allow individual users to verify their inclusion in the liability set but does not contain the entire liability list, making it hard for a third party to verify the procedure</em>.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/nic-carter-bitmex-kraken-top-proof-of-reserves-ranking/">Nic Carter: BitMEX, Kraken top proof-of-reserves ranking</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Polkadot price will not recover in 2023 until this happens</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/polkadot-price-will-not-recover-in-2023-until-this-happens/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/polkadot-price-will-not-recover-in-2023-until-this-happens/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 09:41:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polkadot News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/polkadot-price-will-not-recover-in-2023-until-this-happens/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Polkadot price plunged hard in 2022. The decline was caused by both internal and external factors. It will only recover if the Fed shifts its tone and its ecosystem rebounds. Polkadot price plunged by more than 84% in 2022m capping its worst year on record. DOT slipped to a low of $4.2, which was lower [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/polkadot-price-will-not-recover-in-2023-until-this-happens/">Polkadot price will not recover in 2023 until this happens</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Polkadot price plunged hard in 2022.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The decline was caused by both internal and external factors.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">It will only recover if the Fed shifts its tone and its ecosystem rebounds.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Polkadot price plunged by more than 84% in 2022m capping its worst year on record. DOT slipped to a low of $4.2, which was lower than its record high of $55. This performance was due to the overall weakness of cryptocurrencies, high-interest rates, and the collapse of key players in the crypto industry.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Polkadot parachain challenges</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/polkadot/"><u>Polkadot</u></a> price had its worst year on record due to multiple factors. First, it suffered from the biggest&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/"><u>crypto news</u></a><strong>&nbsp;</strong>during the year following the collapse of FTX and Alameda Research. This collapse led to major challenges in the industry as exchanges like Binance and Coinbase recorded remarkable outflows.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Polkadot also plunged following the collapse of Terra and its ecosystem, which led to over $40 billion in total losses. The collapse pushed more people to lose faith in crypto tokens.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Further, an extremely hawkish Federal Reserve had an impact on Polkadot and other cryptocurrencies. The Fed hiked rates by 450 basis points and pointed towards more in 2023. This happened as inflation jumped to a 40-year high.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Internally. Polkadot&rsquo;s ecosystem faced issues of its own. The most significant was the de-pegging of Acala Dollar, an algorithmic stablecoin developed by Acala Network. The stablecoin is yet to regain its peg.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Other Polkadot parachains also had major challenges. For example, Enjin&rsquo;s Efinity saw little traction as demand for Non-Fungible Tokens (NFT) collapsed. Total NFTs sold dropped by more than 90% from January.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Meanwhile, Moonriver and Moonbeam have also struggled to gain traction in the DeFi and other industries like the metaverse.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Looking forward, the main driver for Polkadot price in 2023 will be the actions of the Federal Reserve. A dovish shift by the Fed will lead to more growth for the stock. DOT and other coins will not recover until the Fed shifts its tone and its ecosystem rebounds.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Polkadot price outlook</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2022/11/30/1672393229912-cf184665-6545-4071-813d-15575fdd32c5.png" style="width: 631px;height: 313.397px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="631" height="313.397"></p>
<p dir="ltr">Turning to the daily chart, we see that the DOT price sell-off caught no breather in 2022. The coin continued falling as risks in the industry rose. As it crashed, it managed to move below all moving averages. It also moved to the lower side of the Bollinger Bands.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, the coin will likely continue falling as bears target the next key support level at $2. A rebound to about $20 will only happen if the Fed suddenly becomes dovish.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy Polkadot</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>

    <p>eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=OTg5NjY&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=IA&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy DOT with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    Binance</h3>

    <p>Binance is one of the largest cryptocurrency exchanges in the world. It is better suited to more experienced investors and it offers a large number of cryptocurrencies to choose from, at over 600.

Binance is also known for having low trading fees and a multiple of trading options that its users can benefit from, such as; peer-to-peer trading, margin trading and spot trading.
</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/binance-crypto?guid=OTg5NjY&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=IA&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy DOT with Binance today            </a>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/polkadot-price-will-not-recover-in-2023-until-this-happens/">Polkadot price will not recover in 2023 until this happens</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/polkadot-price-will-not-recover-in-2023-until-this-happens/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto price prediction: Mirror (MIR), Serum (SRM), Solana</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-mirror-mir-serum-srm-solana/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-mirror-mir-serum-srm-solana/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 09:04:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-mirror-mir-serum-srm-solana/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrency prices drifted downwards on the final week of the year as concerns about a global recession coincided with those of high interest rates. Bitcoin darted lower and reached a low of $16,485. Other coins like XRP, ETH, and ADA dropped as well. Here is the crypto price prediction from the last week of the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-mirror-mir-serum-srm-solana/">Crypto price prediction: Mirror (MIR), Serum (SRM), Solana</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/price/"><u>Cryptocurrency prices</u></a> drifted downwards on the final week of the year as concerns about a global recession coincided with those of high interest rates. Bitcoin darted lower and reached a low of $16,485. Other coins like XRP, ETH, and ADA dropped as well. Here is the crypto price prediction from the last week of the year.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Mirror Protocol (MIR)</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Mirror Protocol, a dead cryptocurrency, was one of the best-performing cryptocurrencies in the final week of the year. It spiked to a high of $0.24, which was about 173% above the lowest level this year. It has now pulled back to $0.14.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Mirror Protocol was an important part of Terra&rsquo;s ecosystem, as I wrote&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/terra-luna-classic-price-prediction-as-lunc-goes-vertical/"><u>here</u></a>. It used its technology to make it possible for people to buy and sell financial assets in a tokenized manner. For example, it was possible for people to buy Apple shares in a token form. The benefit of this was that users could trade these tokens on a 24-hour basis.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Mirror went obsolete following the collapse of Terra Protocol and the Terra USD stablecoin. Now, the price has moved above the 25-day and 50-day moving averages while the Relative Strength Index (RSI) has moved to the neutral point at 50. Therefore, I suspect that MIR price will remain under pressure as sellers target the key support at $0.1225.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2022/11/30/1672390993046-5f5bd653-adbc-4d92-bbfd-145997eb63d2.png" style="width: 618px;height: 306.94px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="618" height="306.94"></p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/MIRUSD/?exchange=COINBASE"><u>MIR/USD chart by TradingView</u></a></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy Mirror Protocol</h2>
<p dir="ltr">
                </p><p>As MIR is such a new asset, it's yet to be listed on major exchanges. You can still purchase MIR using a DEX (decentralised exchange) though, which just means there are a few extra steps. To buy MIR right now, follow these steps:</p>

                                    <h3>1. Buy ETH on a regulated exchange or broker, like <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=OTg5NjQ&amp;component=news-table-1inch" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">eToro &rsaquo;</a></h3>
                    <p>We suggest <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=OTg5NjQ&amp;component=news-table-1inch" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">eToro</a> because it's one of the world's leading multi-asset trading platforms, an exchange and wallet all-in-one with some of the lowest fees in the industry. It's also beginner-friendly, and has more payment methods available to users than any other available service.</p>
                                    <h3>2. Send your ETH to a compatible wallet like Trust Wallet or MetaMask</h3>
                    <p>You'll need to create your wallet, grab your address, and send your coins there.</p>
                                    <h3>3. Connect your wallet to the 1Inch DEX</h3>
                    <p>Head to 1Inch, and 'connect' your wallet to it.</p>
                                    <h3>4. You can now swap your ETH for MIR</h3>
                    <p>Now that you're connected, you'll be able to swap for 100s of coins including MIR.</p>
                
<h2 dir="ltr">Serum (SRM)</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/serum/"><u>Serum</u></a> is another dead cryptocurrency. It was a leading player in Solana&rsquo;s ecosystem, where it had a total value locked (TVL) of more than $1.5 billion. Serum&rsquo;s problem was that its personal key was held by FTX, which led to a loss of confidence in the ecosystem. Today, Serum&rsquo;s total value locked has slumped to less than $395k.</p>
<p dir="ltr">SRM dropped to a low of $0.115 this week and then zoomed higher to $0.15. It has managed to move above the moving averages but it has also gotten overbought. Therefore, I believe that the bearish momentum will resume during the weekend. If this happens, it will likely retest the important support point at $0.12.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2022/11/30/1672390993255-c6df600e-02bd-4454-b976-75575ada05ac.png" style="width: 596px;height: 296.013px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="596" height="296.013"></p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/SRMUSD/?exchange=KRAKEN"><u>SRM/USD chart by TradingView</u></a></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy Serum</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    Binance</h3>

    <p>Binance is one of the largest cryptocurrency exchanges in the world. It is better suited to more experienced investors and it offers a large number of cryptocurrencies to choose from, at over 600.

Binance is also known for having low trading fees and a multiple of trading options that its users can benefit from, such as; peer-to-peer trading, margin trading and spot trading.
</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/binance-crypto?guid=OTg5NjQ&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=IA&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy SRM with Binance today            </a>
    </p><h3>
    Wazirx</h3>

    <p>WazirX is India's largest crypto exchange. Started in 2018, WazirX has grown to be the most trusted exchange in the Indian crypto market. It is a part of the binance group, serving users in 180 countries.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/wazirx-crypto?guid=OTg5NjQ&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=IA&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy SRM with Wazirx today            </a>
    </p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Solana (SOL)</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Solana had one of the hardest downfalls in 2022. It plunged from an all-time high of $260 to $10. The most recent sell-off was due to its close affiliation to FTX and Alameda, which were its key funders. Therefore, the collapse of FTX led to a major liquidation, which pushed the price significantly lower.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">On the daily chart, Solana remains below all moving averages and the psychological level of $10. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) has moved below the oversold level. Therefore, Solana will likely continue falling as sellers target the next key support point at $5.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2022/11/30/1672390993021-872f0361-71d4-44b2-a140-46053a8b94a8.png" style="width: 636px;height: 315.88px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="636" height="315.88"></p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/SOLUSD/?exchange=COINBASE"><u>SOL/USD chart by TradingView</u></a></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy Solana</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>

    <p>eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=OTg5NjQ&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=IA&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy SOL with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    Public</h3>

    <p>Public is an investing platform that allows you to invest stocks, ETFs, crypto, and alternative assets like fine art and collectibles&mdash;all in one place.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/public-crypto?guid=OTg5NjQ&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=IA&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy SOL with Public today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptocurrency execution and custody services are provided by Apex Crypto LLC (NMLS ID 1828849) through a software licensing agreement between Apex Crypto LLC and Public Crypto LLC. Crypto trading on Public platforms is served by Public Crypto LLC and offered through APEX Crypto. Please ensure that you fully understand the risks involved before trading." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-mirror-mir-serum-srm-solana/">Crypto price prediction: Mirror (MIR), Serum (SRM), Solana</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-mirror-mir-serum-srm-solana/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>UK’s NFT industry expected to grow to $9,257 million by 2028</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/uks-nft-industry-expected-to-grow-to-9257-million-by-2028/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/uks-nft-industry-expected-to-grow-to-9257-million-by-2028/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 16:25:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto adoption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[UK]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/uks-nft-industry-expected-to-grow-to-9257-million-by-2028/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The United Kingdom&#8217;s NFT industry is expected to grow at a CAGR of 34.5% over the next 5-6 years. NFT spend in the UK will increase from $1,725.2 million in 2022 to $9,257.0 million by 2028. Increased adoption, government support and venture funding are key factors to that growth. The global non-fungible tokens (NFT) market [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/uks-nft-industry-expected-to-grow-to-9257-million-by-2028/">UK’s NFT industry expected to grow to $9,257 million by 2028</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>The United Kingdom&rsquo;s NFT industry is expected to grow at a CAGR of 34.5% over the next 5-6 years.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>NFT spend in the UK will increase from $1,725.2 million in 2022 to $9,257.0 million by 2028.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><strong><em>Increased adoption, government support and venture funding are key factors to that growth.</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">The global non-fungible tokens (NFT) market took a hit alongside the rest of the market in 2022, with sales volumes and creator revenue seeing a significant decline.</p>
<p dir="ltr">But despite the brutal crash that&rsquo;s characterised the crypto sector throughout the year, the latest trends and projections suggest the NFT industry will continue to grow over the next six years.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Key segments in the next few years will be collectibles and art, real estate, sports, gaming, fashion &amp; luxury and utility.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">UK&rsquo;s NFT industry to grow at a CAGR of 34.5% up to 2028</h2>
<p dir="ltr">2021 remains a benchmark year for various sectors, yet according to a recent Research and Markets NFT industry <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/united-kingdom-nft-market-intelligence-report-2022-2028---nft-marketplaces-are-raising-funding-rounds-to-drive-their-growth-301710934.html" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">report</a>, 2022-2028 would see growth at a CAGR of 34.5%.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The United Kingdom will see its NFT industry grow from $1,725.2 million in 2022 to $9,257 million by 2028. The forecast put the NFT Spend Value for the UK on an upwards trajectory of an annual 48% for this year.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Research and Markets report highlighted on Thursday forecasts widespread adoption of digital assets across the country&rsquo;s different user groups will spark even further interest in NFTs.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Among factors to aid the UK NFT industry is the increased participation from innovative startups, sports clubs and even real estate giants. Just recently, Premier League giants Manchester United unveiled their NFT collection, joining an industry that&rsquo;s already boasting of major global brands.As <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tezos-strike-deal-with-manchester-united/">previously reported</a>, the soccer club partnered blockchain platform Tezos in February this year.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The growing recognition and support for the industry from the UK government is another factor, as is the rising number of investors backing NFT startups.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/uks-nft-industry-expected-to-grow-to-9257-million-by-2028/">UK’s NFT industry expected to grow to $9,257 million by 2028</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/uks-nft-industry-expected-to-grow-to-9257-million-by-2028/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Metacade’s Presale Set To Explode in 2023 &#8211; Get In Cheap Before It’s Too Late</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/metacades-presale-set-to-explode-in-2023-get-in-cheap-before-its-too-late/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/metacades-presale-set-to-explode-in-2023-get-in-cheap-before-its-too-late/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice Davies]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 16:03:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/metacades-presale-set-to-explode-in-2023-get-in-cheap-before-its-too-late/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto is famous for producing insane returns, and getting in on crypto presales is the easiest way to ensure the highest potential for gains. This high potential for earning, followed by a decrease, is caused by an economic principle called the law of diminishing returns, which states that an asset&#8217;s value growth will begin to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/metacades-presale-set-to-explode-in-2023-get-in-cheap-before-its-too-late/">Metacade’s Presale Set To Explode in 2023 &#8211; Get In Cheap Before It’s Too Late</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Crypto is famous for producing insane returns, and getting in on crypto presales is the easiest way to ensure the highest potential for gains. This high potential for earning, followed by a decrease, is caused by an economic principle called the <em>law of diminishing returns</em>, which states that an asset&rsquo;s value growth will begin to slow down over time.</p>
<p dir="ltr">One presale that has proven to be a significant success is Metacade (MCADE). Metacade is building a major GameFi platform to rival some of the biggest names in the space, so it&rsquo;s worth investigating before the price rises even further.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">The Metacade presale is a big investment opportunity</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Crypto presales are extremely popular, especially for projects with strong fundamentals like&nbsp;<a href="https://metacade.co/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade</u></a>. Case in point, the beta phase of the MCADE presale attracted over $1.3 million worth of investment in just four weeks, reflecting the project&rsquo;s long-term potential.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade launched its MCADE token at $0.008 at the beginning of its crypto presale, but now the price is rising. The price will continue growing until it reaches $0.02 at the end of the presale. For investors looking to get a good deal, the sooner you pick up tokens the better.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">MCADE price prediction: 2023 and beyond</h2>
<p dir="ltr">After reaching $0.02 at the end of its presale, MCADE will be launched on decentralized exchanges (DEXs), and the team will start to form partnerships to expand the reach of the token. Aside from this, the MCADE token will gain utility once it opens the comprehensive gaming experience planned for the Metacade platform.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The long-term potential of Metacade is very promising as a result. Experts predict explosive price action during 2023, which could see gains of up to 50x. This price explosion would give the MCADE token a value of $1 &ndash; a significant increase from its final crypto presale value of $0.02.</p>
<p dir="ltr">After 2023, analysts expect the crypto market to begin its next bull run once Bitcoin&rsquo;s halving event ends during 2024. Bull markets usually produce major gains across the board, which could push the MCADE token up in value even further. <strong>By this time, MCADE could reach over $5, a massive 250x increase between the crypto presale and 2025.</strong></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Metacade?</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://metacade.co/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade</u></a> is creating the biggest arcade on the blockchain, bringing advanced gaming capabilities to the world of Web3. GameFi enthusiasts can play a wide range of arcade-style games that each offer crypto rewards and participate in paid entry tournaments to win MCADE prizes.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Several additional features truly make Metacade stand out as a prime investment opportunity during its crypto presale. First, the project aims to serve Web3 users directly by providing a central location for gamers to get together and access valuable information about the space.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Over time, Metacade aims to become a decentralized autonomous organization (<a href="https://www.coindesk.com/learn/what-is-a-dao/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>DAO</u></a>). This shift will give complete control over the platform to the Metacade community, as all MCADE token holders will be able to vote in governance proposals and help drive the project&rsquo;s future progress.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How does Metacade work?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Blockchain gamers can access endless challenges across many play-to-earn (<a href="https://www.securitytokenizer.io/what-is-gamefi"><u>P2E</u></a>) games. Whether looking to play casually or competitively, Metacade offers players the chance to enjoy various addictive arcade games while earning MCADE tokens for their efforts.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In the Metacade, gamers also earn crypto tokens for contributing useful information to the community. These contributions can include the latest tips and tricks and anything else to help other gamers make the most out of their blockchain gaming experience.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Another key feature offered by Metacade is the chance to test out brand-new blockchain games before they officially launch. These beta-testing roles allow players to provide feedback to game developers, who can implement any improvements suggested by the Metacade community, including bug fixes and gameplay optimizations.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Metacade is expanding the reach of blockchain-based gaming</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade also aims to provide a critical service that can help the wider GameFi industry to grow. Its Metagrants program will provide funding for the most in-demand blockchain games, as the Metacade community will be able to vote for the titles that they most want to play in the future.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Blockchain is a technological advancement hub, and Metacade supports continuing progress in this area. Early-stage funding is critical in the process, as creating and launching new games requires a high level of support. <strong>Through connecting developers with its community of gamers, Metacade is directly helping to expand the scope and scale of innovation in blockchain.</strong></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Is Metacade worth buying in 2023?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The Metacade presale is a significant buying opportunity for crypto investors. Luckily, $0.008 is a meagre price for a project that offers real promise for the future, and it&rsquo;s no surprise that the beta phase sold out quickly.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The presale will see the MCADE token rise to $0.02, so investors still have time to make some bear market gains. However, Metacade is undoubtedly a great addition to any investment portfolio, and it will be fascinating to see if it will reach the $1 mark during 2023.</p>
<p><strong>You can participate in the MCADE presale&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://metacade.co/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong><u>here</u></strong></a><strong>.</strong></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/metacades-presale-set-to-explode-in-2023-get-in-cheap-before-its-too-late/">Metacade’s Presale Set To Explode in 2023 &#8211; Get In Cheap Before It’s Too Late</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/metacades-presale-set-to-explode-in-2023-get-in-cheap-before-its-too-late/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
