<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 17:42:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>CoinDesk Lays Off 45% of Its Editorial Staff as It Explores Sales Option</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coindesk-lays-off-editorial-staff/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coindesk-lays-off-editorial-staff/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 17:42:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coindesk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dcg]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Layoffs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266890</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coindesk-lays-off-editorial-staff/">CoinDesk Lays Off 45% of Its Editorial Staff as It Explores Sales Option</a></p>
<p>The investor letter noted that CoinDesk has enlisted the expertise of financial advisers to facilitate the process of onboarding new institutional and strategic investors, in collaboration with  DCG.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coindesk-lays-off-editorial-staff/">CoinDesk Lays Off 45% of Its Editorial Staff as It Explores Sales Option</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coindesk-lays-off-editorial-staff/">CoinDesk Lays Off 45% of Its Editorial Staff as It Explores Sales Option</a></p>
<p>Coindesk, a prominent player in the crypto media landscape, has made significant headlines with its <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/15qwhcv/coindesk_lays_off_45_of_editorial_staff_as_it/">recent decision</a> to lay off 45% of its editorial staff while simultaneously exploring potential avenues to sell the business.</p>
<h2>CoinDesk Made a Bold Move with Its Staff Layoff</h2>
<p>According to a memo authored by CoinDesk CEO Kevin Worth, the layoffs are primarily concentrated within the media team. Worth noted that the layoffs were a necessary step to ensure the company&#8217;s financial stability moving forward and to facilitate the impending sale of CoinDesk Inc.</p>
<p>Reports suggest that a total of 20 employees are affected by the layoff, equating to 45% of Coindesk&#8217;s editorial team. This personnel reduction corresponds to a 16% cut in the entire workforce, highlighting the company&#8217;s emphasis on its editorial division.</p>
<p>Behind this seemingly drastic step lies a broader strategic vision. Digital Currency Group (DCG), the parent company of CoinDesk, has been in discussions to bring on board strategic investors. While the layoffs are clearly painful for the impacted employees and the company&#8217;s operations, they are framed as a necessary preparation for a major transition.</p>
<p>Notably, sources indicate that DCG is close to concluding a significant sale of a stake worth over $125 million, backed by crypto investor Matthew Roszak of Tally Capital. Under the terms of this impending deal, DCG will not completely divest from CoinDesk, instead, it is set to maintain a stake in the media property.</p>
<p>CoinDesk’s prospective sale was first <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coindesk-full-partial-sale/">reported</a> in January, sending shockwaves across the crypto space at the time. This revelation came amid the backdrop of financial struggles faced by DCG, which had been acquired through the acquisition of Genesis Trading, a brokerage firm that had gone <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/genesis-files-bankruptcy/">bankrupt</a>.</p>
<p>The intricacies of financial management in the crypto space had caught up with DCG, prompting the company to investigate several ways for raising cash and repositioning itself for long-term success.</p>
<h2>CoinDesk to Onboard New Investors</h2>
<p>In a recent shareholder letter for the second quarter of 2023, DCG disclosed pivotal developments within its Coindesk subsidiary.</p>
<p>The investor letter noted that CoinDesk has enlisted the expertise of financial advisers to facilitate the process of onboarding new institutional and strategic investors, in collaboration with  DCG. These discussions have reportedly been underway for several months, highlighting the seriousness of the initiative and the interest it has generated within the investment community.</p>
<p>Coindesk&#8217;s endeavors seem to be complemented by its strong performance during the quarter. The letter highlights the remarkable achievement of $15 million in revenues attributed to the Consensus 2023 festival, held in April.</p>
<p>CoinDesk&#8217;s strategic shift is further contextualized by DCG’s broader business operations. DCG, which operates across various sectors within the crypto ecosystem, has been actively exploring avenues to attract new investors for its ventures. This includes the search for investors for Luno, its crypto exchange subsidiary.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fednow-dlt-micropayment-hedera/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coindesk-lays-off-editorial-staff/">CoinDesk Lays Off 45% of Its Editorial Staff as It Explores Sales Option</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coindesk-lays-off-editorial-staff/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>FedNow Adopts DLT Micropayment Partner for Retail Transactions on Hedera</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fednow-dlt-micropayment-hedera/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fednow-dlt-micropayment-hedera/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 15:49:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FinTech News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dropp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fednow]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hedera]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266882</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fednow-dlt-micropayment-hedera/">FedNow Adopts DLT Micropayment Partner for Retail Transactions on Hedera</a></p>
<p>The collaboration between FedNow and Dropp has garnered mixed reactions from the crypto community.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fednow-dlt-micropayment-hedera/">FedNow Adopts DLT Micropayment Partner for Retail Transactions on Hedera</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fednow-dlt-micropayment-hedera/">FedNow Adopts DLT Micropayment Partner for Retail Transactions on Hedera</a></p>
<p>The United States Federal Reserve&#8217;s instant payment system FedNow has added support for Dropp, a cutting-edge payment application based on the Hedera Hashgraph (HBAR) Network. The company, which uses advanced blockchain technology to expedite payment processes and enhance financial transactions, has now joined a growing list of payment providers for the FedNow service.</p>
<p>The FedNow payment platform was <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-federal-reserve-fednow-payment/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">officially launched</a> in July to connect financial institutions and businesses with innovative service providers for instant transactions.</p>
<p>On August 14, the Federal Reserve&#8217;s payment platform added Dropp to the showcase section of its <a href="https://explore.fednow.org/explore-the-city?id=10&amp;postId=108&amp;vendor=dropp-inc." target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">website</a> as one of its partners. Through this partnership with the duo, Dropp will be able to continue its services of empowering merchants to receive payments from consumers without incurring substantial transaction fees.</p>
<h2>Dropp Accepts Both Crypto and Fiat Payments</h2>
<p>As a micropayment processor, Dropp accepts both crypto and fiat currencies for payments. With the addition of the platform in FedNow&#8217;s showcase section, users can pay for services using various crypto assets, including HBAR, the native crypto of the distributed ledger technology (DLT) Hedera.</p>
<p>Dropp&#8217;s approach represents a shift away from the traditional subscription model. Unlike conventional content subscription plans, the company enables customers to pay only for the content they consume, offering greater flexibility and cost efficiency.</p>
<p>Although FedNow&#8217;s inclusion of the payment processor seemed like an embrace of DLT technology, the central bank warned that the materials presented on its website serve as a convenient reference for potential FedNow service participants.</p>
<p>The Federal Reserve Financial Services (FRFS) emphasized that its role is restricted to hosting applications in the showcase section of the FedNow platform. Adding that it neither supports nor endorses any particular showcase provider.</p>
<p>&#8220;Federal Reserve Financial Services (FRFS) is merely the host of the showcase and does not support or endorse any showcase providers, and the inclusion or exclusion of a provider should in no way imply any recommendation or endorsement by FRFS,&#8221; FedNow wrote.</p>
<h2>Not the First Payment System Adopted by FedNow</h2>
<p>While Dropp is not the first payment processor adopted by FedNow to execute retail transactions, the platform has demonstrated a pattern of removing payment providers days after being added to the platform.</p>
<p>Earlier this year, certain blockchain networks announced partnerships with FedNow but were subsequently removed from the platform. Another crypto company, Metal Blockchain, declared its interest in May to integrate with FedNow but was removed from the showcase after a short period.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the collaboration between FedNow and Dropp has garnered mixed reactions from the crypto community. Some community members expressed concern that adopting blockchain technology might compromise the original principles of cryptocurrencies as an alternative to traditional financial systems.</p>
<p>A Reddit <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/15qrd9g/where_is_there_no_longer_any_emphasis_on/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">user</a> lamented that while people might be pursuing better financial situations, it should not come at the expense of compromising the principles of fairness and transparency.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/q2-earnings-foxconn/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fednow-dlt-micropayment-hedera/">FedNow Adopts DLT Micropayment Partner for Retail Transactions on Hedera</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fednow-dlt-micropayment-hedera/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Foxconn Maintains Caution on Global Uncertainties despite Beating Forecasts in Q2 2023 Earnings</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/q2-earnings-foxconn/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/q2-earnings-foxconn/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 14:35:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[foxconn]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266874</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/q2-earnings-foxconn/">Foxconn Maintains Caution on Global Uncertainties despite Beating Forecasts in Q2 2023 Earnings</a></p>
<p>Foxconn sees sluggish demand for electronics within the global economy for the rest of the year and thus it has reduced its revenue estimates. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/q2-earnings-foxconn/">Foxconn Maintains Caution on Global Uncertainties despite Beating Forecasts in Q2 2023 Earnings</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/q2-earnings-foxconn/">Foxconn Maintains Caution on Global Uncertainties despite Beating Forecasts in Q2 2023 Earnings</a></p>
<p>On Monday, August 14, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/apple-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Apple</a> supplier Foxconn announced its second-quarter (Q2) earnings beating market estimates. These strong Q2 earnings came on the backdrop of a booming artificial intelligence sector. However, the company still maintains a cautious outlook for the year 2023 amid global uncertainties.</p>
<h2>Foxconn in Q2 2023</h2>
<p>Foxconn&#8217;s net profit for the second quarter fell by 1%, but it was still higher than what analysts predicted. The company&#8217;s net profit went down to T$33 billion ($1.0 billion) in the April-June period, compared to T$33.29 billion from the previous year. This result was better than the average prediction of T$25.57 billion profit from 13 analysts, according to Refinitiv.</p>
<p>Foxconn also mentioned that it anticipates a slight decrease in revenue for its smart consumer electronics products in the third quarter. This category includes smartphones and contributes about half of Foxconn&#8217;s total revenue.</p>
<p>The Taiwan-based largest electronics manufacturer worldwide downgraded its outlook for the full-year revenue of 2023. With this, Foxconn joins the list of companies that have been facing the heat of a sluggish recovery in China and a weak global economy.</p>
<p>Chairman Liu Young-way described Foxconn&#8217;s outlook as &#8220;relatively cautious&#8221;. He <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/08/14/apple-supplier-foxconn-cautious-despite-beating-earnings-forecasts.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">added</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“At present, there are many external variables: global monetary policy tightening, geopolitical tensions, inflation and other uncertainties.”</p></blockquote>
<p>At the earnings briefing, Liu said that he sees a lot of potential in India wherein they are rapidly expanding their manufacturing capabilities. Additionally, the company has committed “several billion dollars in investment&#8221; which it calls just the beginning.</p>
<p>However, just during the last month of July, Foxconn pulled out of a joint venture with Vedanta in India. But the company is still keen on applying for different incentives under the country&#8217;s chip production plan.</p>
<h2>Foxconn Gearing for an EV Push and AI</h2>
<p>Foxconn, a company that makes things like phones and electronics, might start making batteries for electric cars at its factory in Wisconsin. The electronics manufacturer sees a great opportunity in this rapidly evolving EV market, however, it didn&#8217;t give many details regarding the same.</p>
<p>With the rise of generative AI apps, Foxconn is getting more popular for servers in this area. They think they can work more closely with customers in North America. This is good news because demand for smartphones and computers has been a bit slower. “AI growth has been strong, but we have not seen any pick-up for other products,&#8221; the company noted.</p>
<p>Before announcing its results, Foxconn, the company responsible for assembling about 70% of iPhones, experienced a 1.4% increase in its shares. In contrast, the main market saw a 1.3% decrease. Foxconn&#8217;s shares have risen by 10% in total this year.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-canada-expansion/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/q2-earnings-foxconn/">Foxconn Maintains Caution on Global Uncertainties despite Beating Forecasts in Q2 2023 Earnings</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/q2-earnings-foxconn/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase Global Announces Its Canada Expansion via Strategic Partnership with Peoples Trust Company</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-canada-expansion/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-canada-expansion/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 14:29:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266876</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-canada-expansion/">Coinbase Global Announces Its Canada Expansion via Strategic Partnership with Peoples Trust Company</a></p>
<p>Coinbase has committed to accelerating its international expansion amid the mainstream adoption of digital assets and blockchain technology.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-canada-expansion/">Coinbase Global Announces Its Canada Expansion via Strategic Partnership with Peoples Trust Company</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-canada-expansion/">Coinbase Global Announces Its Canada Expansion via Strategic Partnership with Peoples Trust Company</a></p>
<p>Leading publicly traded cryptocurrency exchange based in the United States <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase Global Inc</a> (NASDAQ: COIN), announced on Monday that it has opened its services to crypto users in Canada. The crypto company noted in the announcement that it has partnered with Peoples Trust Company, part of Peoples Group, to enable seamless on/off ramping services. Furthermore, Coinbase users in Canada can access the Interac e-Transfers, which are simple and secure. Additionally, the company noted that the Interac feature was the most requested by Canadians. Notably, the company highlighted that depositing funds to Coinbase using Interac is free and almost instant to all eligible users.</p>
<p>The crypto company noted that the official launch in Canada is a move geared toward making the crypto market accessible to more investors around the world. Meanwhile, the company has faced significant regulatory hurdles in the United States after the collapse of FTX and Alameda Research late last year, thus accelerating its international expansion to ensure its future growth prospects.</p>
<p>“Canada is well positioned to be a global leader in the crypto economy thanks to the high levels of crypto awareness, a passionate local tech ecosystem, and the progress towards a strong regulatory framework,” said Nana Murugesan, Vice President, International and Business Development, Coinbase. “As Coinbase’s next Go Deep Market, we are making significant investments to help Canadians access the benefits of cryptocurrency.”</p>
<p>Similar sentiments were echoed by Lucas Matheson, the Coinbase country director in Canada, who highlighted that the official launch in the country will help democratize finance in the country.</p>
<h2>Coinbase Launch in Canada</h2>
<p>The Canadian crypto market has significantly grown over the past few years, as it even has a functional Bitcoin ETF among other regulatory frameworks. As a result, a study conducted by Ontario Securities Commission (OSC) found that 15 percent of Canadian investors have already invested in the crypto market and more than double expect to purchase digital assets within the year. As a result, Coinbase has remained keen to widen its services to investors in Canada in the recent past. Moreover, Coinbase is now a leading crypto employer in the country, which works in line with the government’s agenda.</p>
<p>Coinbase has previously worked closely with Canadian regulators to help create a strong digital asset regulatory framework. Resultantly, its strategic partnership with Peoples Group has been commended for combining traditional financial institutions with neo-banking services</p>
<p>“Peoples Group is pleased to partner with industry leader Coinbase, to enable this money movement tool for their Canadian customers and expand payment possibilities,” <a href="https://investor.coinbase.com/news/news-details/2023/Coinbase-Accelerates-International-Expansion-with-Official-Launch-in-Canada/default.aspx" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a> David Furlong, Chief Operating Officer of Peoples Group.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Coinbase shares traded around $81.11, up approximately 0.12 during Monday’s per-market.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/yen-level-us-dollar-2022/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-canada-expansion/">Coinbase Global Announces Its Canada Expansion via Strategic Partnership with Peoples Trust Company</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-canada-expansion/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Japanese Yen Slumps to Lowest Level Against US Dollar Since November 2022</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/yen-level-us-dollar-2022/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/yen-level-us-dollar-2022/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 12:51:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Currencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[japanese yen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[yen]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266845</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/yen-level-us-dollar-2022/">Japanese Yen Slumps to Lowest Level Against US Dollar Since November 2022</a></p>
<p>While the Japanese currency is headed towards a downward trajectory, the US dollar has displayed a strong uptrend since the close of July.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/yen-level-us-dollar-2022/">Japanese Yen Slumps to Lowest Level Against US Dollar Since November 2022</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/yen-level-us-dollar-2022/">Japanese Yen Slumps to Lowest Level Against US Dollar Since November 2022</a></p>
<p>The Japanese yen experienced a massive decline on Monday, August 14, slipping to its lowest level against the US dollar for the first time since November 2022. This downward trajectory resulted in the yen breaking through the crucial 145 mark. According to a CNBC <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/08/14/yen-breaches-145-level-against-usd-raises-expectations-boj-may-intervene.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report,</a> the currency briefly touched the same level last Friday before eventually recovering some ground.</p>
<p>The decline has brought about speculation that the country&#8217;s central bank, the Bank of Japan (BOJ), may intervene to restore the value of the Japanese currency. A recent Forex report released by HSBC on Monday provided insights into the potential outcomes of the bank&#8217;s support.</p>
<p>The report suggested that the Japanese Ministry of Finance might consider intervention within the range of 145-148 to stabilize the yen&#8217;s decline. It&#8217;s worth noting that both the BOJ and the Japanese government had previously intervened by purchasing yen when it <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/japanese-yen-24-year-low-yield/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">breached</a> the 145-to-dollar exchange rate in September 2022. One month after the government got involved, the currency <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/japanese-yen-falls-dollar-32-years/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">declined</a> further to 150% against the US dollar.</p>
<h2>Japanese Bonds Hit 10-Year High As BOJ Modifies Policy</h2>
<p>However, HSBC also noted the possibility of short positions on the yen increasing further if the BOJ and Japanese authorities choose not to intervene this time.</p>
<p>The report highlighted that these positions had been reduced by over 30% in July, coinciding with the buildup to the BOJ&#8217;s monetary policy meeting on July 28. The BOJ said during the conference that it would offer to purchase 10-year Japanese government bonds at a fixed rate of 1% in a move that aims to expand the trading band on long-term yields.</p>
<p>The central bank further stated that it would still maintain the previous 0.5% cap on these yields, making it look more like a reference point rather than a rigid limit. Reacting to the news, the country&#8217;s bonds surged to a 10-year high of 0.572% two weeks ago.</p>
<h2>US Dollar Hits One Month High Despite Plummeting Yen</h2>
<p>While the Japanese currency is headed towards a downward trajectory, the US dollar has displayed a strong uptrend since the close of July, with the dollar index surging from its July 13 low of 99.77 to its current level of 102.99.</p>
<p>HSBC drew attention to a &#8220;new factor&#8221; contributing to the strength of the dollar – particularly, the elevated longer-term US yields due to concerns about the country&#8217;s budget deficit and treasury supply. The bank acknowledged that this might be a temporary phenomenon, occurring alongside the existing USD framework that is not signaling a robust downtrend for the US dollar.</p>
<h2>Japan to Unveil Its Gross Domestic Product Tomorrow</h2>
<p>Meanwhile, Japan is gearing up to reveal its gross domestic product (GDP) data for the quarter ending in June on Tuesday, August 15.</p>
<p>Additionally, inflation figures for July are set to be released later this Friday. <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/hsbc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">HSBC</a> highlighted that any deviations in the data could strengthen negative sentiments.</p>
<p>Market experts are projecting a 0.8% growth in GDP on a quarter-on-quarter basis, and the core consumer price index, excluding fresh food prices, is expected to reach 3.1%, as a Reuters <a href="https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/yen-breaks-above-145dlr-level-choppy-trading-dollar-firm-2023-08-14/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">poll</a> indicates.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coca-cola-masterpiece-nft-collection-on-base/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/yen-level-us-dollar-2022/">Japanese Yen Slumps to Lowest Level Against US Dollar Since November 2022</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/yen-level-us-dollar-2022/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coca-Cola Launches Masterpiece NFT Collection on Base</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coca-cola-masterpiece-nft-collection-on-base/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coca-cola-masterpiece-nft-collection-on-base/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Babafemi Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 12:47:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[base]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coca cola]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nft]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266757</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coca-cola-masterpiece-nft-collection-on-base/">Coca-Cola Launches Masterpiece NFT Collection on Base</a></p>
<p>This is not Coca-Cola’s first foray into the world of NFTs. In July 2021, Coca-Cola auctioned its first-ever NFTs as a single asset.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coca-cola-masterpiece-nft-collection-on-base/">Coca-Cola Launches Masterpiece NFT Collection on Base</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coca-cola-masterpiece-nft-collection-on-base/">Coca-Cola Launches Masterpiece NFT Collection on Base</a></p>

<p>The household brand name <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coca-cola/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coca-Cola</a> has launched its Masterpiece NFT collection on the Coinbase layer-2 network, Base. Recall that last week, the Base mainnet officially <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-base-network-live-web3/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">opened to the general public</a> with over 100 Dapps and service providers.</p>
<p>Coinbase <a href="https://twitter.com/coinbase/status/1690763490674503680" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announced</a> Coca-Cola&#8217;s NFT launch as part of its “Onchain Summer” initiative which began on August 9. The OnChain Summer initiative is to celebrate Base’s mainnet launch with on-chain art, gaming, and music projects. The aim is to demonstrate the efficiency and cost-effectiveness of the Layer 2 chain.</p>
<h2>About the Masterpiece NFT Collection</h2>
<p>The Coca-Cola NFT collection features either a classic or a modern artwork, intertwined with the iconic Coca-Cola bottle. Classics such as &#8220;The Scream&#8221; by Edvard Munch and &#8220;Girl with a Pearl Earring&#8221; by Johannes Vermeer are used in the collection. The collection includes eight NFT versions, available from 0.0011 ETH to 0.014 ETH.</p>
<p>“Coca-Cola is bringing their Global Masterpiece campaign on-chain with iconic works from leading artists,” the announcement said.</p>
<p>Since announcing the mint on Sunday, nearly 50,000 NFTs have been minted via the mint.fun platform. One can expect that many more will be minted with the minting period not due to end until Wednesday.</p>
<h2>Not the First Rodeo</h2>
<p>This is not Coca-Cola’s first foray into the world of NFTs. In July 2021, Coca-Cola auctioned its first-ever NFTs as a single asset. <a href="https://www.coca-colacompany.com/media-center/coca-cola-nft-auction-fetches-more-than-575000" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">The auction</a> was a big hit with fans and the crypto community and sold for over $575k. The proceeds were then donated to Special Olympics International. Later in July 2022, the company launched another 136 digital collectibles to celebrate Pride Month.</p>
<p>Coca-Cola is not the first major brand to join the NFT craze. Other companies such as Nike, Asics, Louis Vuitton, Mattel Creations and Taco Bell have all launched NFT collections in recent months. However, Coca-Cola&#8217;s Masterpiece NFT collection is unique in its use of Base. The brand could very well be the largest consumer brand to be involved with Base so far.</p>
<p>Later this month, other digital collectible projects like Zora, Pixelmon, Showtime, and Indelible are also expected to launch on Base. As more brands follow suit, it will be interesting to see how Base paves the way for more mainstream adoption of NFTs.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/mastercard-minority-stake-mtn/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coca-cola-masterpiece-nft-collection-on-base/">Coca-Cola Launches Masterpiece NFT Collection on Base</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coca-cola-masterpiece-nft-collection-on-base/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mastercard to Acquire Minority Stake in MTN’s Fintech Business</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/mastercard-minority-stake-mtn/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/mastercard-minority-stake-mtn/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 12:04:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FinTech News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investors News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mastercard]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mtn]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266830</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/mastercard-minority-stake-mtn/">Mastercard to Acquire Minority Stake in MTN’s Fintech Business</a></p>
<p>In the midst of this strategic partnership, MTN has delivered impressive financial results for the first half of the year.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/mastercard-minority-stake-mtn/">Mastercard to Acquire Minority Stake in MTN’s Fintech Business</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/mastercard-minority-stake-mtn/">Mastercard to Acquire Minority Stake in MTN’s Fintech Business</a></p>
<p>MTN Group Ltd (JSE: MTN), Africa’s largest wireless carrier, has announced that <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/mastercard/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Mastercard Inc</a> (NYSE: MA) is planning to purchase a minority stake in its financial technology business. This investment deal values the fintech arm at approximately $5.2 billion, representing almost 40% of MTN&#8217;s total market value.</p>
<p>MTN’s Chief Executive Officer, Ralph Mupita stated in a recent <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-08-14/mastercard-to-buy-stake-in-mtn-s-5-2-billion-fintech-unit" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a> that the signing of the definitive investment agreements between MTN and Mastercard is anticipated to take place in the near term.</p>
<h2>Promise of the MTN-Mastercard Partnership</h2>
<p>This strategic partnership with Mastercard holds immense promise for both companies. MTN’s extensive reach across the African continent, combined with Mastercard’s expertise in secure payment technology, is poised to accelerate the growth and accessibility of fintech services in the region.</p>
<p>This influx of funds can serve as a temporary substitute for dividends from subsidiaries, providing financial flexibility and allowing MTN to address short-term financial needs or allocate resources to strategic initiatives.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the cash injection from Mastercard’s investment can partly offset the impact of increased 2023 capital spending guidance for MTN, which has been affected by forex (foreign exchange) fluctuations.</p>
<p>This balance-sheet reinforcement, combined with Mastercard&#8217;s <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/mastercard-acquires-ciphertrace/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">expertise</a> in payment technology and financial services will position MTN to pursue its digital transformation efforts and expand its fintech offerings more aggressively.</p>
<p>Mastercard&#8217;s investment in MTN’s mobile money unit reflects a broader industry trend, with companies such as Airtel Africa and Safaricom likewise focusing on transitioning from basic voice and text mobile services to comprehensive digital solutions. This precedent, set by other industry giants like India&#8217;s Jio Platforms Ltd, underscores the importance of collaboration and strategic investment in driving innovation and growth in the digital economy.</p>
<p>As MTN seeks to raise funds through asset sales, including the sale and lease-back of mobile-phone towers and potentially divesting its stake in IHS Holding Ltd., the market will closely watch the execution of these plans, as they could further enhance MTN’s financial position and support its growth objectives.</p>
<h2>MTN Reports Impressive Half-Year Earnings</h2>
<p>In the midst of this strategic partnership, MTN has delivered impressive financial results for the first half of the year. The company revealed a 7.1% increase in its half-year earnings.</p>
<p>MTN reported that its headline earnings per share (EPS), a key measure of profitability, rose from 506 cents in the same period the previous year to 542 cents in the first six months of the current year. This robust financial performance signals the company’s resilience and adaptability in a dynamic market environment.</p>
<p>The company has faced operational challenges due to frequent power outages, which compelled it to allocate substantial capital to backup power systems. Despite these hurdles, MTN has remained proactive in its pursuit of strategic partnerships that could enhance its fintech offerings.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/anthropic-100m-investment-sk-telecom/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/mastercard-minority-stake-mtn/">Mastercard to Acquire Minority Stake in MTN’s Fintech Business</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/mastercard-minority-stake-mtn/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Google-backed AI Firm Anthropic Secures $100M Investment from SK Telecom</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/anthropic-100m-investment-sk-telecom/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/anthropic-100m-investment-sk-telecom/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 11:56:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investors News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alphabet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[anthropic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chatgpt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[google]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[opeai]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sk telecom]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266811</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/anthropic-100m-investment-sk-telecom/">Google-backed AI Firm Anthropic Secures $100M Investment from SK Telecom</a></p>
<p>As part of their partnership, Anthropic and SK Telecom will work together for building large language models (LLMs) for telcos. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/anthropic-100m-investment-sk-telecom/">Google-backed AI Firm Anthropic Secures $100M Investment from SK Telecom</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/anthropic-100m-investment-sk-telecom/">Google-backed AI Firm Anthropic Secures $100M Investment from SK Telecom</a></p>
<p>US-based artificial intelligence startup Anthropic PBC announced that it has secured a staggering $100 million in investments from South Korea&#8217;s largest telecommunications company SK Telecom. With this investment, SK Telecom also seeks to bolster its telecommunications-driven AI business.</p>
<p>The two players have entered into a partnership wherein Anthropic will build large language models (LLMs) customized or telcos. Anthropic is already competing with players like OpenAI in building different AI foundation models. It also stands to be one of the most well-funded AI firms in the market. earlier this year in May 2023, Anthropic raised $450 million from investors such as Spark Capital and Alphabet Inc&#8217;s <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/google/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Google</a>.</p>
<p>Established in 2021 by CEO Dario Amodei and his sister Daniela, both of whom were former senior team members at OpenAI, Anthropic&#8217;s mission revolves around creating trustworthy AI systems and conducting research on the potentials and challenges of AI.</p>
<p>Unlike OpenAI, Anthropic takes a different approach. While OpenAI employs reinforcement learning from human feedback (RLHF) to enhance safety and minimize risks, Anthropic utilizes reinforcement learning from AI feedback (RLAIF). This feedback mechanism involves one AI model correcting another based on a set of &#8220;rules or principles,&#8221; known as &#8220;Constitutional AI&#8221; by Anthropic.</p>
<p>As part of their collaboration, SK Telecom and Anthropic are set to co-create a multilingual Large Language Model (LLM), catering to various languages like Korean, English, German, Japanese, Arabic, and Spanish.</p>
<p>The two entities, SK Telecom, and Anthropic, are collaborating to integrate this multilingual LLM into the Telco AI Platform, which is currently under development by the Global Telco AI Alliance.</p>
<h2>Anthropic&#8217;s Claude 2 Model</h2>
<p>Anthropic&#8217;s Claude series of large language models (LLMs) have been in direct competition with OpenAI&#8217;s ChatGPT. Recently, Anthropic unveiled its Claude 2 model in order to compete with ChatGPT-4.</p>
<p>Anthropic asserts that Claude 2 boasts enhanced performance, longer response capabilities. Users can now access them through an API, along with its new public beta website called Claude.ai. Marketed as a relatively &#8220;harmless&#8221; AI system, Claude can handle a diverse range of conversational and text-related tasks.</p>
<p>The company further <a href="https://www.anthropic.com/index/claude-2" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">added</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“We have heard from our users that Claude is easy to converse with, clearly explains its thinking, is less likely to produce harmful outputs and has a longer memory. We have made improvements from our previous models on coding, math and reasoning&#8221;.</p></blockquote>
<p>Merely a week ago, Anthropic introduced an upgraded edition of Claude Instant, a swifter and more cost-effective text-generation model accessible via an API. The company asserts that this new version exhibits &#8220;substantial&#8221; enhancements in domains like mathematics, coding, reasoning, and safety.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-cyber-sei-tokens/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/anthropic-100m-investment-sk-telecom/">Google-backed AI Firm Anthropic Secures $100M Investment from SK Telecom</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/anthropic-100m-investment-sk-telecom/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Lists CyberConnect (CYBER) and Sei (SEI) Tokens, Set to Begin Trading within 24 Hours</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-cyber-sei-tokens/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-cyber-sei-tokens/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 11:49:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cyber]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sei Network]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[token launch]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[token listing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266812</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-cyber-sei-tokens/">Binance Lists CyberConnect (CYBER) and Sei (SEI) Tokens, Set to Begin Trading within 24 Hours</a></p>
<p>CYBER's initial circulating supply is expected to be 11,038,000.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-cyber-sei-tokens/">Binance Lists CyberConnect (CYBER) and Sei (SEI) Tokens, Set to Begin Trading within 24 Hours</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-cyber-sei-tokens/">Binance Lists CyberConnect (CYBER) and Sei (SEI) Tokens, Set to Begin Trading within 24 Hours</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a>, the world&#8217;s largest crypto exchange by trading volume, has <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/support/announcement/binance-will-open-trading-for-cyberconnect-cyber-and-sei-sei-fe281e1fa6e7493788969242995ba04a" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announced</a> the listing of its new projects – CyberConnect (CYBER) and Sei (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-sei-36th-project/">SEI</a>). According to the announcement, the tokens are set to go live on August 15, 2023, at 12:00 (UTC). And for a start, both tokens will only be able to trade on five pairs. That is, the platform will allow CYBER to trade on CYBER/BNB, CYBER/BTC, CYBER/FDUSD, CYBER/TRY, and CYBER/USDT. Similarly, it will open trading for SEI on the SEI/BNB, SEI/BTC, SEI/FDUSD, SEI/TRY, and SEI/USDT trading pairs.</p>
<p>Although only three trading pairs will be immediately available, Binance, says it will enable its Spot Grid for the CYBER/BTC, CYBER/USDT, SEI/BTC, and SEI/USDT trading pairs within 48 hours after trading launches.</p>
<p>Binance also notes that it will apply Seed Tag to CYBER and SEI. However, it was also quick to clarify that the &#8216;TRY&#8217; in its trading pairs is not another digital currency, but rather a fiat currency. And for the CYBER/FDUSD and SEI/FDUSD trading pairs, Binance says users will enjoy zero maker fees, at least for now.</p>
<h2>CYBER and SEI Tokens</h2>
<p>CYBER is the native token of the web3 social network CyberConnect, which enables developers to create social apps that focus on helping users gain full ownership of their digital identity and content. Per Binance, the total token supply of CYBER is 100,000,000. However, once listed on Binance, CYBER&#8217;s initial circulating supply is expected to be 11,038,000 ( about 11.04% of the total supply).</p>
<p>SEI, on the other hand, is layer 1 blockchain Sei Network&#8217;s native token. SEI&#8217;s circulating supply upon listing will be 1.8 billion or 18% of the total supply of 10 billion, <a href="https://research.binance.com/en/projects/sei#:~:text=The%20project%20has%20raised%2035MM,of%20the%20total%20token%20supply)." target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-vars-slk="per Binance" data-vars-tar="research.binance.com" data-vars-tar-uri="/en/projects/sei">per Binance</a>. However, it has been tipped to reach nearly a half-billion market cap on debut. That is even as an early price of 26 cents is enough to bring its market cap to $486 million and put it in the top 100 cryptocurrencies.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-cryptocurrencies-hub-pyusd/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-cyber-sei-tokens/">Binance Lists CyberConnect (CYBER) and Sei (SEI) Tokens, Set to Begin Trading within 24 Hours</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-cyber-sei-tokens/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>PayPal Unveils Cryptocurrencies Hub Following PYUSD Stablecoin Launch</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-cryptocurrencies-hub-pyusd/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-cryptocurrencies-hub-pyusd/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 11:08:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[paypal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[paypal usd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pyusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266803</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-cryptocurrencies-hub-pyusd/">PayPal Unveils Cryptocurrencies Hub Following PYUSD Stablecoin Launch</a></p>
<p>While PayPal's new crypto service allows users to explore the crypto industry, access to this innovative feature has been restricted in certain jurisdictions and for specific individuals.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-cryptocurrencies-hub-pyusd/">PayPal Unveils Cryptocurrencies Hub Following PYUSD Stablecoin Launch</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-cryptocurrencies-hub-pyusd/">PayPal Unveils Cryptocurrencies Hub Following PYUSD Stablecoin Launch</a></p>
<p>Leading American payment company <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">PayPal</a> has taken another step into the digital asset industry with the launch of its Cryptocurrencies Hub. This feature allows users to interact with different crypto assets such as Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a>) and Ethereum (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ETH</a>). The move comes just one week after introducing its native <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/stablecoins-how-manage-operate/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">stablecoin</a> dubbed PYUSD, which is backed 1:1 by the US dollar.</p>
<p>According to a <a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/paypal-cryptocurrencies-hub-launch" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a> by Cointelegraph, the payment giant updated its terms and conditions to offer insights into how users can leverage the newly introduced Cryptocurrencies Hub to explore the world of digital assets. This strategic maneuver demonstrates the company&#8217;s ambition to establish itself as a prominent crypto-friendly platform.</p>
<p>PayPal&#8217;s foray into the emerging economy began in October 2020 when the company expanded its services to allow users to buy, sell, and hold assets in their accounts. Shortly after that, in March 2021, the company extended its crypto services, enabling customers to checkout at other online businesses using cryptocurrency.</p>
<h2>PayPal Unveils Its Cryptocurrencies Hub</h2>
<p>The US-based payments company has now deepened its foothold in the industry with the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-paypal-usd-stablecoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">launch</a> of the controversial stablecoin and the subsequent introduction of the Cryptocurrencies Hub. This new feature aims to facilitate the seamless buying and selling of cryptocurrencies. Notably, it empowers users to use the proceeds from their crypto transactions to purchase through the PayPal platform.</p>
<p>Upon its official launch, the Cryptocurrencies Hub will be seamlessly integrated with users&#8217; existing PayPal accounts, accessible using their existing login credentials.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the new crypto offering is designed to enable swift conversions between PYUSD and a diverse range of other digital assets. According to the company, any balance shown in the Cryptocurrencies Hub represents the total amount of each asset displayed.</p>
<p>&#8220;Any balance in your Cryptocurrencies Hub represents your ownership of the amount of each Crypto Asset shown. You will not hold the digital Crypto Assets themselves in your Crypto Asset balance,&#8221; the company explained in the newly updated terms of service.</p>
<h2>Hawaii Users Are Exempted from Using PayPal&#8217;s New Service</h2>
<p>While PayPal&#8217;s new crypto service allows users to explore the crypto industry, access to this innovative feature has been restricted in certain jurisdictions and for specific individuals. The company has chosen a personalized approach to grant access to the newly introduced service.</p>
<p>According to the payment firm, to be eligible for the Cryptocurrencies Hub, new users must open a personal PayPal account and maintain a Balance Account in good standing. Additionally, users must provide key identification information, including their full name, physical address, date of birth, and taxpayer identification number.</p>
<p>However, these rules do not apply to Hawaii residents as the company has excluded them from using the new crypto service.</p>
<p>&#8220;Your access to the Cryptocurrencies Hub will be through your personal PayPal account&#8217;s Balance Account. If you are a Hawaii resident, you will not be permitted to set up a Cryptocurrencies Hub at this time,&#8221; the company said.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-mom-hester-peirce-gensler-sec/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-cryptocurrencies-hub-pyusd/">PayPal Unveils Cryptocurrencies Hub Following PYUSD Stablecoin Launch</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-cryptocurrencies-hub-pyusd/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4046 metric#misses=42 metric#hit-ratio=99.0 metric#bytes=1024264 metric#prefetches=194 metric#store-reads=20 metric#store-writes=3 metric#store-hits=200 metric#store-misses=3 metric#sql-queries=36 metric#ms-total=108.87 metric#ms-cache=9.06 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.4118 metric#ms-cache-ratio=8.3 -->