<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 19:41:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Prof. Alexander: ‘I’m not sure SEC will succeed against Binance’</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/sec-may-fail-against-binance-prof-alexander/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wajeeh Khan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 19:41:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Interview]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=143005</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Professor Carol Alexander says the U.S. SEC may lose to Binance. She reiterated the need for crypto in an interview with CNBC today. Prof. Alexander expects regulatory clarity to bring price stability. It is conceivable that the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission may fail in its lawsuit against Binance, says Professor Carol Alexander of the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sec-may-fail-against-binance-prof-alexander/">Prof. Alexander: ‘I’m not sure SEC will succeed against Binance’</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Professor Carol Alexander says the U.S. SEC may lose to Binance.</li>
<li>She reiterated the need for crypto in an interview with CNBC today.</li>
<li>Prof. Alexander expects regulatory clarity to bring price stability.</li>
</ul>
<p>It is conceivable that the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission may fail in its <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/sec-sues-crypto-exchange-binance-over-u-s-rule-violations-6918ed0f" target="_blank" rel="noopener">lawsuit</a> against Binance, says Professor Carol Alexander of the University of Essex.</p>
<h2>Here&rsquo;s why SEC may lose to Binance</h2>
<p>Professor Alexander is not entirely convinced that the regulator is financially strong enough to take on Binance especially after spending lavishly on its ongoing battle with <a href="https://u.today/huge-sec-emails-suggest-xrp-is-not-security" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ripple</a>.</p>
<blockquote><p>I&rsquo;m not sure the SEC is going to succeed. Binance has very deep pockets and I&rsquo;m not too sure about the financing of the SEC. After all, it comes from traditional finance and equity firms.</p></blockquote>
<p>It is noteworthy, though, that Binance and affiliates together with <a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/coinbase/">Coinbase Global Inc</a> lost more than $4.0 billion in outflows last week following the SEC lawsuits.</p>
<p>On Monday, <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/nigerias-sec-orders-binance-nigeria-limited-to-stop-operations/">Binance Nigeria Limited</a> was ordered to halt operations as well.</p>
<h2>Prof. Alexander reiterates the need for crypto</h2>
<p>Nonetheless, Professor Carol Alexander did concur that some of the cryptocurrencies could indeed be classified as securities. It&rsquo;s what the SEC claims in its <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-sec-strikes-again-first-binance-now-coinbase/">lawsuit</a> against Coinbase as well.</p>
<p>On CNBC&rsquo;s &ldquo;<a href="https://www.cnbc.com/video/2023/06/12/us-sec-may-not-succeed-in-crypto-lawsuits-professor.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Squawk Box Europe</a>&rdquo;, she agreed that crypto could facilitate financial scams and fraudulent activities but said:</p>
<blockquote><p>We must have crypto. We can&rsquo;t have digital economy without blockchain. Can&rsquo;t have blockchain without crypto. So, it must be regulated properly. Then we&rsquo;ll only have few bad players.</p></blockquote>
<p>Prof. Alexander also noted that the conventional financial landscape is not entirely free of fraudsters either. She expects regulatory clarity to bring price stability to the broader crypto space.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sec-may-fail-against-binance-prof-alexander/">Prof. Alexander: ‘I’m not sure SEC will succeed against Binance’</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin and Ethereum network revenues spiked in May despite significant headwinds: ETC Group report</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-and-ethereum-network-revenues-spiked-in-may-despite-significant-headwinds-etc-group-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 18:23:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-and-ethereum-network-revenues-spiked-in-may-despite-significant-headwinds-etc-group-report/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin revenue jumped 249% YoY in May, while Ethereum network fees rose 53.7% in May, according to a research report by the ETC Group. Ordinals and enterprise adoption drove network revenues for Bitcoin and Ethereum respectively. Regulation and macroeconomics remain key factors even as benefits of tokenisation attracts major banks. The current market outlook for [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-and-ethereum-network-revenues-spiked-in-may-despite-significant-headwinds-etc-group-report/">Bitcoin and Ethereum network revenues spiked in May despite significant headwinds: ETC Group report</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Bitcoin revenue jumped 249% YoY in May, while Ethereum network fees rose 53.7% in May, according to a research report by the ETC Group.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Ordinals and enterprise adoption drove network revenues for Bitcoin and Ethereum respectively.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Regulation and macroeconomics remain key factors even as benefits of tokenisation attracts major banks.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">The current market outlook for <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> and crypto continues to suffer from the flurry of activities around the actions of the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) after it sued Binance and Coinbase.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">While June started off with wild volatility that has pegged prices below key levels, a new report suggests the market headwinds in May did little to slow down network revenue generation for the world&rsquo;s two largest blockchains by market cap over the month.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitcoin and Ethereum network growth</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The report by German-based ETP (exchange-traded products) issuer ETC Group highlights a significant jump in network revenue for both Bitcoin and <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/">Ethereum</a> over the past month.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">ETC Group Research team&rsquo;s Tom Rodgers (Head of Research) and Hanut Singh (a Research Analyst at ETC Group and formely with CoinJournal), shared the outlook via an overview of the biggest trends and events in crypto over the month &ndash; from regulation to macroeconomics and adoption as signaled by on-chain data.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Writing in the <em>Digital Assets and Metaverse Monthly Review: May 2023</em>, Rodgers and Hanut noted that although continued headwinds saw the total crypto market cap flatline near $1.1 trillion.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">On the macro level, the uncertainty around the US debt ceiling debate weighed on crypto markets. Elsewhere, the regulatory front saw the non-friendly approach by the US SEC and UK&rsquo;s Financial Conduct Authority (FCA) continue to impact sentiment.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, despite these factors, there was noteworthy growth in terms of network revenue for the leading blockchains.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;&hellip;r<em>evenues generated by the two largest blockchains by market cap rose substantially in May due to increasing user bases and new technological developments, most notably Ordinals for Bitcoin, and increasing adoption for Ethereum enterprise solutions</em>,&rdquo; the ETC Group research team wrote.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Ordinals helped push Bitcoin revenue up 249% YoY in May</h3>
<p dir="ltr">According to the ETC Group report, the weekly revenue on the Bitcoin network increased by 249% year over year in May. This was largely driven by the spike in Ordinals, which as CoinJournal <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/why-are-bitcoin-transaction-fees-rising-and-what-are-brc-20-tokens/">reported here</a>, saw BTC miners record multi-year highs in transaction revenue.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The demand for the Bitcoin Ordinals meant transaction fees amounted to 29.57% of monthly revenue for miners &ndash; the last time it was that high was during the 2017 bull market that had seen the first real foray into crypto by institutional investors.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Ethereum network fees jumped 53.7% in May</h3>
<p dir="ltr">For Ethereum, renewed interest in staking was visible in May despite the fears of a major withdrawal rout after the Shapella upgrade. Indeed, as the ETC Group report highlights, the supply of staked ETH on the mainnet rose from 14% to almost 20% at the end of the month. About $46 billion worth of ETH was staked, representing a 200% jump in the percentage of supply locked on the network.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This has happened even as ETH supply has declined since the Merge. Meanwhile, monthly fees rose by 53.7% in the month &ndash; from $241 million in April to $448 million in May. Increased demand for Ethereum blockspace is behind the jump in total network fees, the researchers noted.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Crypto regulation in the US</h2>
<p dir="ltr">While US presidential candidates Ron DeSantis (R) and Robert F. Kennedy Jr. (D) have indicated support for Bitcoin, the overall outlook on US crypto regulation remains largely hostile even with bipartisan engagements.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The SEC recently ramped up its crackdown with the lawsuits against Binance and Coinbase, even as the crypto community highly anticipates the outcome of another high profile case between the SEC and Ripple Labs over the XRP token.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This even as Asia emerged as a strong destination for crypto, led by Hong Kong&rsquo;s recent regulatory guidelines that have seen OKX, Huobi and other exchanges apply for licenses. The <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/can-mica-rules-help-the-struggling-cryptocurrency-industry/">adoption of the MiCA rules</a> by Europe was also a notable event that could make the bloc attractive to more US-based crypto businesses.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Tokenisation sees major banks eye blockchain adoption</h2>
<p dir="ltr">May also witnessed increased institutional interest in blockchain amid further growth in tokenisation.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Interest peaked after State Street, the second-oldest US bank, hinted at a move likely to help bring $1.4 trillion worth of assets onto the blockchain via tokenisation of ETFs. The issue of tokenisation and its benefits had also previously been highlighted by the Bank of New York Mellon.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">That&rsquo;s also the view of Citibank, which has suggested tokenisation could see up to $4 trillion of liquid and illiquid assets brought on-chain.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-and-ethereum-network-revenues-spiked-in-may-despite-significant-headwinds-etc-group-report/">Bitcoin and Ethereum network revenues spiked in May despite significant headwinds: ETC Group report</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Should you buy the Chancer token, as the presale officially launches on June 13th?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/should-you-buy-the-chancer-token-as-the-presale-officially-launches-on-june-13th/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/should-you-buy-the-chancer-token-as-the-presale-officially-launches-on-june-13th/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 17:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Events]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/should-you-buy-the-chancer-token-as-the-presale-officially-launches-on-june-13th/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways The Chancer presale will launch in roughly 20 hours, allowing investors to have a stake in the project. The team seeks to raise $15 million to fund the development of its platform and other products.&#160; The Chancer presale launch is set to kickstart in a few hours, enabling investors to purchase the token [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/should-you-buy-the-chancer-token-as-the-presale-officially-launches-on-june-13th/">Should you buy the Chancer token, as the presale officially launches on June 13th?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The Chancer presale will launch in roughly 20 hours, allowing investors to have a stake in the project.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The team seeks to raise $15 million to fund the development of its platform and other products.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">The Chancer presale launch is set to kickstart in a few hours, enabling investors to purchase the token before it lists on cryptocurrency exchanges. The development team will use the funds raised from the presale to develop its platform and work on other products.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The cryptocurrency market has performed positively since the start of the year. However, with the recent developments in the market, is this a good time to invest in the Chancer project?</p>
<p dir="ltr">We will look at Chancer and help you determine if this project could be worth it for investors.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Chancer?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Before you participate in the Chancer presale, you need to know the important information about this project.</p>
<p dir="ltr">For starters, Chancer is a &nbsp;pioneering Web3 peer-to-peer (P2P) custom betting platform that allows users to live stream betting events.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">What makes Chancer an interesting project is that it seeks to develop a decentralised betting platform that allows users to bet on a wide range of events, beyond the sporting and popular ones.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The P2P betting markets on Chancer are in real-time and based on user interests, expertise, and social media connections.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">With&nbsp;<a href="https://chancer.com/"><u>Chancer</u></a>, users are no longer constrained by what bookmakers offer, and their odds. Users have the option of setting up their own custom P2P betting markets through a decentralized platform.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Another point that could entice investors is the fact that Chancer is a betting platform that is not exclusive to sporting or popular events. While users can bet on sporting events like football matches, they can also bet on virtually anything, including the day man will walk on Mars and personal bet amongst friends to see whether they can complete a task with specific parameters in place.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">CHANCER presale to commence on the June 13th</h2>
<p dir="ltr">CHANCER is the token that powers the&nbsp;<a href="https://chancer.com/"><u>Chancer</u></a> ecosystem. With the token, holders could become an integral part of the Chancer platform&rsquo;s success and the markets it house.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The CHANCER token makes it possible for holders to create markets and also invest in markets created by other users.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to the whitepaper, the CHANCER token will also allow holders to create, participate in, and profit from their very own predictive markets based on their interests, expertise, and social opportunities.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Since CHANCER is on the Binance Smart Chain, there is a staking option available to holders. Token holders can stake their tokens to earn more money and ensure that the ecosystem runs as it should.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Similar to BNB and other ecosystem tokens, CHANCER holders will enjoy fees for creating and participating in markets.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Finally, &nbsp;the&nbsp;<a href="https://chancer.com/"><u>Chancer</u></a> tokens will be used to reward participants for successful betting outcomes, incentivising users to engage with the platform.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The development team seeks to raise $15 million over the course of the 12 stages of the token presale, and it starts tomorrow, June 13th.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer supports various wallets for participating in the presale. Investors can purchase CHANCER tokens by connecting their Trust Wallet, MetaMask, Coinbase Wallet, and Rainbow wallets to the Chancer platform.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Once that is complete, investors can choose from the list of supported cryptocurrencies to purchase CHANCER.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">At press time, the Chancer team is yet to publicly announce the presale token price. The price could likely be displayed once the presale launches in a few hours.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Should you buy CHANCER?</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://chancer.com/"><u>Chancer</u></a> could be an interesting project to invest in due to its unique niche. The cryptocurrency market is filled with DeFi, NFT, and meme projects. However, very few have entered the betting ecosystem, which makes Chancer an interesting project.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">With Chancer, users could enjoy transparent and easier betting processes. The increased betting options also make it an interesting project.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Historically, early-stage investors make more money than investors that come in once a project launches on crypto exchanges. Early investors in Ethereum, Solana, and Cardano, enjoyed thousands of percentages in ROI.</p>
<p dir="ltr">At the moment, Chancer is still in its early stage, with the team working on its products and the token yet to get listed on crypto exchanges. Once that happens, CHANCER could experience a price surge.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/should-you-buy-the-chancer-token-as-the-presale-officially-launches-on-june-13th/">Should you buy the Chancer token, as the presale officially launches on June 13th?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/should-you-buy-the-chancer-token-as-the-presale-officially-launches-on-june-13th/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Solo Bitcoin miner beats the odds to win 6.25 BTC block reward</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/solo-bitcoin-miner-beats-the-odds-to-win-6-25-btc-block-reward/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/solo-bitcoin-miner-beats-the-odds-to-win-6-25-btc-block-reward/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 15:45:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/solo-bitcoin-miner-beats-the-odds-to-win-6-25-btc-block-reward/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A solo Bitcoin miner earned the 6.25 BTC block reward after beating the odds to solve block 793607. The miner reportedly used an Antminer S9 with about 17 TH. At today&#8217;s Bitcoin mining difficulty and with 17 TH, a solo miner would need an average of 450 years to land a block. With Bitcoin price [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/solo-bitcoin-miner-beats-the-odds-to-win-6-25-btc-block-reward/">Solo Bitcoin miner beats the odds to win 6.25 BTC block reward</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">A solo Bitcoin miner earned the 6.25 BTC block reward after beating the odds to solve block 793607.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The miner reportedly used an Antminer S9 with about 17 TH.</li>
<li dir="ltr">At today&rsquo;s Bitcoin mining difficulty and with 17 TH, a solo miner would need an average of 450 years to land a block.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">With Bitcoin price struggling below $26,000, and the wider crypto market impacted by recent regulatory events, there&rsquo;s has been very little to cheer Bitcoiners.</p>
<p dir="ltr">But for a solo <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/mine/">BTC miner</a>, a lucky break had them strike gold with the winning of a block reward. According to on-chain data, the miner beat staggering odds to mine block 793607 and earn the 6.25 BTC block reward.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">BTC miner with single Antminer S9 hits jackpot</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The solo miner reportedly achieved the once-in-a-life-time feat using a single Antminer S9 and accounted for only 17 terahashes (TH). Their &ldquo;lottery&rdquo; win was worth about $160,000 at the time of block reward.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>Congratulations to miner 151XTfHBfaDqoNWGGeYobNX2YzFFWuB5YD with only ~17TH for solving the 275th block at http://solo.ckpool.org! That is likely a single S9 miner. A miner of this size would only solve a block once every ~450 years on average</em>,&rdquo; <a href="https://twitter.com/ckpooldev/status/1667282510424969219" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">tweeted</a> Con Kolivas, a CGMiner software engineer and the admin of Solo CKPool. &nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">It&rsquo;s not the first time a solo miner has hit such a jackpot, with CKPool apparently seeing <a href="https://twitter.com/altair_tech/status/1667283976912863233" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">seven</a> such instances since January. However, the feat is increasingly difficult as the Bitcoin hashrate and mining difficulty have increased.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to data from <a href="https://www.blockchain.com/explorer/charts/difficulty" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Blockchain.com</a>, the current Bitcoin mining difficulty is 51.23 trillion hashes. Mining difficulty looks at how difficult it is to mine the next block, that is how many hashes a miner must generate to find and solve a valid block. The current <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-mining-difficulty-hits-all-time-high-above-50-trillion-hashes/">difficulty is at all-time highs</a> and has most blocks solved by major mining pools and companies.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The difficulty adjusts every 2016 blocks (about two weeks&rsquo; time) and can go up or down. The next adjustment expected on June 14 will see the difficulty jump by about 2.92% to 52.73 T.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/solo-bitcoin-miner-beats-the-odds-to-win-6-25-btc-block-reward/">Solo Bitcoin miner beats the odds to win 6.25 BTC block reward</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/solo-bitcoin-miner-beats-the-odds-to-win-6-25-btc-block-reward/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto volumes continue to lag, Bitcoin &#038; Ether fees down for fourth consecutive week</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-volumes-continue-lag-bitcoin-ether-fees-down-for-fourth-consecutive-week/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-volumes-continue-lag-bitcoin-ether-fees-down-for-fourth-consecutive-week/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dan Ashmore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 15:32:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[On-Chain data]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-volumes-continue-lag-bitcoin-ether-fees-down-for-fourth-consecutive-week/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key Takeaways On-chain activity for Bitcoin and Ethereum has fallen for the fourth consecutive week DEX share of trading volume had jumped up from 14% to 22% last month amid regulatory crackdown on centralised exchanges DEX volume has fallen back again since, however, and entire crypto space is seeing thin liquidity &#160; Many speculate the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-volumes-continue-lag-bitcoin-ether-fees-down-for-fourth-consecutive-week/">Crypto volumes continue to lag, Bitcoin &amp; Ether fees down for fourth consecutive week</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2 dir="ltr">Key Takeaways</h2>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">On-chain activity for Bitcoin and Ethereum has fallen for the fourth consecutive week</li>
<li dir="ltr">DEX share of trading volume had jumped up from 14% to 22% last month amid regulatory crackdown on centralised exchanges</li>
<li dir="ltr">DEX volume has fallen back again since, however, and entire crypto space is seeing thin liquidity</li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Many speculate the regulatory crackdown in the US will push crypto two ways: offshore and/or into the decentralised realm. For the former, that doesn&rsquo;t need much explanation. Tightening the noose on crypto companies in the US will force those same companies to move abroad if they want to continue their operations at the same capacity (or at all).</p>
<p dir="ltr">But whether this will push activity on-chain presents as a more interesting debate. Decentralised exchanges took off during the pandemic hysteria, however their volumes fell drastically throughout 2022. While volume also fell for centralised exchanges (CEXs), the ratio of the volume of DEX trading to CEX volume fell from 16.9% at the start of 2022 to 9.6% twelve months later, showing DEXs fell further than their more conventional counterparts.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Could the regulatory travails of Coinbase, Binance and other centralised exchanges reverse this trend? The below chart shows that there was indeed an increased portion of activity accounted for by DEXs in May, with DEX trading capturing 22.1% of volume, compared to 14.7% the prior month. However, the share has dropped back down to 15.4% through the first twelve days of June.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="fr-fic fr-dib" style="width: 600px" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/05/12/1686577679144-3ab23e1c-dfd1-497f-af63-158d0f751794.png" width="600" height="314">Binance was sued on June 5th and Coinbase on June 6th, which is curious when looking at the above trend as the DEX share has dropped since. Then again, these lawsuits may have been largely priced in. Coinbase was served with a Wells notice a few months ago, while Binance was (and still is) facing numerous investigations from different lawmakers. The price of Bitcoin will tell you all you need to know &ndash; it fell only 5% on news Binance had been formally sued, while the Coinbase news didn&rsquo;t budge it much at all.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In truth, whatever the reasons, it is hard to draw conclusions from the above data. Volume remains incredibly thin, as I have discussed in-depth <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/45-of-stablecoin-balance-has-left-crypto-exchanges-in-4-months-but-where-has-all-the-money-gone-a-deep-dive/"><u>previously</u></a>. In fact, on-chain activity and fees have actually fallen for the fourth consecutive week for Bitcoin, the immense <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/why-are-bitcoin-transaction-fees-rising-and-what-are-brc-20-tokens/"><u>spike in activity</u></a> caused by the Ordinals protocol and BRC-20 tokens fading into the rear window. Despite this fall, however, it should be noted that fees are still significantly higher than the start of the year.</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14102721">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">It is not just Bitcoin. Fees and activity are dwindling across the crypto space. The below is the same chart but for Ethereum, which has also seen four straight weeks of declining fees. In contrast to Bitcoin, the activity is inching down closer to where it was in January, however.</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14102749">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">All in all, volume in the cryptocurrency space remains incredibly thin. This is due to a variety of factors. The first is the collapse in prices. When prices fall, people invariably trade crypto less. And with Bitcoin still 60% off its peak from late 2021, the hysteria and jammed order books feel a long way off.</p>
<p dir="ltr">But regulation is also a key factor. This has suppressed enthusiasm for the space immeasurably, with particular implications for institutions. We saw a telltale sign of that over the weekend, with Crypto.com suspending its US institutional exchange. While its retail platform will remain operational, the company cited limited demand from institutions as the reason behind the decision.</p>
<p dir="ltr">A cocktail of freefalling prices and an increasingly punitive regulatory regime is the worst possible scenario for the industry, and it is not hard to see why institutions have pulled back from the space.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The jump in DEX volume portrayed by the above on-chain data may seem promising at first glance, but that trend seems to have reversed. Additionally, for institutional capital to flow significantly into the space, centralised exchanges provide a vital function. So many were optimistic of these institutions pouring in only a couple of years ago, when companies like Tesla were stashing Bitcoin on balance sheets, but that feels a long way off now.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-volumes-continue-lag-bitcoin-ether-fees-down-for-fourth-consecutive-week/">Crypto volumes continue to lag, Bitcoin &amp; Ether fees down for fourth consecutive week</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-volumes-continue-lag-bitcoin-ether-fees-down-for-fourth-consecutive-week/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Litecoin price analysis ahead of the FOMC decision, US inflation data</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/litecoin-price-analysis-ahead-of-the-fomc-decision-us-inflation-data/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/litecoin-price-analysis-ahead-of-the-fomc-decision-us-inflation-data/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 13:03:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/litecoin-price-analysis-ahead-of-the-fomc-decision-us-inflation-data/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Litecoin has formed a triple-top pattern on the daily chart. The main news is the recent lawsuits against Coinbase and Binance. The Federal Reserve will deliver its next interest rate decision. Litecoin price has come under intense pressure in the past few days as investors focus on the recent SEC lawsuits against Coinbase and Binance. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/litecoin-price-analysis-ahead-of-the-fomc-decision-us-inflation-data/">Litecoin price analysis ahead of the FOMC decision, US inflation data</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Litecoin has formed a triple-top pattern on the daily chart.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The main news is the recent lawsuits against Coinbase and Binance.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The Federal Reserve will deliver its next interest rate decision.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/litecoin/"><u>Litecoin</u></a> price has come under intense pressure in the past few days as investors focus on the recent SEC lawsuits against Coinbase and Binance. LTC token retreated to a low of $73.98, lower than the year-to-date high of $105.70.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Fed interest rate decision</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Litecoin, like other cryptocurrencies, is going through a rough patch as investors focus on last week&rsquo;s lawsuit by the SEC. The lawsuits alleged that the companies provided unregulated securities in the United States. The agency also sued Binance&rsquo;s Chief Executive, Changpeng Zhao, as we wrote&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sec-seeks-alternative-ways-to-serve-changpeng-zhao-after-failing-to-get-him/"><u>here</u></a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">It is stil too early to predict the next outcome of these lawsuits. As we have seen with the ongoing SEC vs Rippple case, the process can last for several years. The most likely outcome will be a settlement between either Binance or Coinbase with the SEC. Alternatively, the two companies could lose the suits, leading to major implications foe the crypto industry.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">For example, if Coinbase loses, it means that the company will be forced to delist thousands of cryptocurrencies. Popular coins like Bitcoin and Litecoin will be safe since they are seen as commodities.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The next key catalyst for the LTC price will be the upcoming interest rate decision by the Federal Reserve scheduled for Wednesday. Analysts believe that the bank will leave interest rates unchanged at between 5% and 5.25%.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">A pause in interest rate hikes will be a positive thing for Litecoin, stocks, and other financial assets. For one, it will be the first time in 10 meetings that the Fed has not hiked interest rates.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The decision will come a day after the US publishes consumer price index (CPI) data. Analysts believe that the headline consumer price index (CPI) dropped to 4.1% in May from the previous 4.9%.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Litecoin price prediction</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/05/12/1686574994713-c00ca613-9236-4ed4-b39d-13ee3217da6d.png" style="width: 693px;height: 337.26px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="693" height="337.26"></p>
<p dir="ltr">Turning to the daily chart, we see that the LTC price has formed a triple-top pattern at $105.70, where it struggled moving above this year. The neckline of this pattern is at about $65.60. The coin has moved below the 50-day and 100-day moving averages.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Relative Strength Index (RSI) has moved below the neutral point at 30. Therefore, I suspect that the LTC price will continue falling as sellers target the key support at $65.60. A move below that level will open the possibility of the coin dropping to $60.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy Litecoin</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>


<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=MTQyODg3&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy LTC with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    CEX.IO</h3>


<p>
    <a href="/visit/cex-crypto?guid=MTQyODg3&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy LTC with CEX.IO today            </a>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/litecoin-price-analysis-ahead-of-the-fomc-decision-us-inflation-data/">Litecoin price analysis ahead of the FOMC decision, US inflation data</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/litecoin-price-analysis-ahead-of-the-fomc-decision-us-inflation-data/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Enhancing Metaverse Integration: My Neighbor Alice Joins The Board of Directors of OMA3</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/enhancing-metaverse-integration-my-neighbor-alice-joins-the-board-of-directors-of-oma3/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/enhancing-metaverse-integration-my-neighbor-alice-joins-the-board-of-directors-of-oma3/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire &#160;]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 07:07:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=142868</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Stockholm, Sweden, June 12th, 2023, Chainwire Riccardo Sibani, Chief Product Officer at My Neighbor Alice, represents the company on the OMA3 Board and contributes to developing a more interconnected metaverse. My Neighbor Alice, the fully-decentralized open-world game, is proud to announce that its Chief Product Officer (CPO) has joined the board of directors of OMA3 [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/enhancing-metaverse-integration-my-neighbor-alice-joins-the-board-of-directors-of-oma3/">Enhancing Metaverse Integration: My Neighbor Alice Joins The Board of Directors of OMA3</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Stockholm, Sweden, June 12th, 2023, Chainwire</strong></p>
<p>Riccardo Sibani, Chief Product Officer at My Neighbor Alice, represents the company on the OMA3 Board and contributes to developing a more interconnected metaverse.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.myneighboralice.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">My Neighbor Alice</a>, the fully-decentralized open-world game, is proud to announce that its Chief Product Officer (CPO) has joined the board of directors of OMA3 (&ldquo;Open Metaverse Alliance for Web3&rdquo;).</p>
<p>OMA3 collaborates with Web3 metaverse platform creators, including renowned members such as Animoca Brands, Alien Worlds, Unstoppable Domains, The Sandbox, Upland, along with many others. OMA3 ensures virtual land, digital assets, ideas, and services are highly interoperable between platforms and transparent to all communities.</p>
<p>My Neighbor Alice is an open world where players can gather and leverage resources to shape their shared digital environment. The team focuses on creating a metaverse where digital items and resources can be shared across various virtual worlds. This focus aligns seamlessly with OMA3&rsquo;s vision of an open and highly interoperable metaverse, marking a significant milestone for both entities.</p>
<p>The collaboration between My Neighbor Alice and OMA3 signifies a significant step forward in ensuring transparency for project communities and the web3 ecosystem. This includes striving for high interoperability of virtual land, digital assets, ideas, and services across platforms.</p>
<p>Riccardo Sibani, with his profound technical expertise and rich blockchain knowledge, is expected to be an invaluable asset to OMA3. Actively involved in creating shared protocols, Sibani will join a board to guide OMA3 to further the collective mission.</p>
<blockquote><p>Commenting on the recent appointment as a board of directors member, Riccardo Sibani said, &ldquo;Joining the board of directors at OMA3 is an exciting opportunity to contribute to the development of a more interconnected metaverse. By fostering collaboration and interoperability across platforms, we aim to create a seamless and transparent experience in the web3 space for all communities. I am thrilled to be part of this collective mission and look forward to shaping the future of decentralization together.&rdquo;</p></blockquote>
<p>By joining OMA3&rsquo;s board of directors, My Neighbor Alice further demonstrates its commitment to establishing shared protocols and shaping an open metaverse. The team is excited about the future of their collaboration with OMA3 and looks forward to creating a more transparent and interconnected virtual landscape.</p>
<h3><strong>About My Neighbor Alice&nbsp;</strong></h3>
<p><a href="https://www.myneighboralice.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">My Neighbor Alice</a> is a groundbreaking multiplayer builder game built on Chromia&rsquo;s Blockchain that offers an engaging and accessible experience on a charming virtual island. My Neighbor Alice represents the future of gaming, combining virtual reality, blockchain, and decentralized finance to redefine how people interact with virtual worlds. Integrating Blockchain technology allows players to own and trade virtual assets (NFTs). The game&rsquo;s marketplace enables players to buy, sell, and trade these NFTs, creating a dynamic and player-driven virtual economy. Players can earn rewards, monetize their creations, and engage in community events, fostering a sense of ownership and collaboration. With different strategic partnerships, MNA underscores the project&rsquo;s dedication to promoting NFT ownership, encouraging a more engaging and interactive gaming community.</p>
<p>or more information and to stay updated, please visit My Neighbor Alice&rsquo;s: <a href="https://www.myneighboralice.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Official website</a> | <a href="https://discord.gg/myneighboralice" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Discord</a>&nbsp;| <a href="https://t.me/MyNeighborAlice" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Telegram</a>&nbsp;| <a href="https://t.me/AliceAnnouncements" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Telegram Announcement</a>&nbsp;| <a href="https://twitter.com/MyNeighborAlice" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Twitter</a>&nbsp;| <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/my-neighbor-alice/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Linkedin</a></p>
<h3>Contact</h3>
<p>Fati Hakim, Fati.Hakim@ChromaWay.com</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/enhancing-metaverse-integration-my-neighbor-alice-joins-the-board-of-directors-of-oma3/">Enhancing Metaverse Integration: My Neighbor Alice Joins The Board of Directors of OMA3</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/enhancing-metaverse-integration-my-neighbor-alice-joins-the-board-of-directors-of-oma3/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance, Binance.US, and Coinbase collectively lose $4B in outflows</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-binance-us-and-coinbase-collectively-lose-4b-in-outflows/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-binance-us-and-coinbase-collectively-lose-4b-in-outflows/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 18:01:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-binance-us-and-coinbase-collectively-lose-4b-in-outflows/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The US SEC has sued both Coinbase and Binance for allegedly violating securities laws. Most of the outflows are occurring through Ethereum Network. Between Monday and Thursday, there was a net outflow of $3.1B through the Ethereum network alone. The US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) started by suing Binance, and its US affiliate that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-binance-us-and-coinbase-collectively-lose-4b-in-outflows/">Binance, Binance.US, and Coinbase collectively lose $4B in outflows</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul class="decimal_type">
<li>The US SEC has sued both Coinbase and Binance for allegedly violating securities laws.</li>
<li>Most of the outflows are occurring through Ethereum Network.</li>
<li>Between Monday and Thursday, there was a net outflow of $3.1B through the Ethereum network alone.</li>
</ul>
<p>The US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) started by suing <a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/binance/">Binance</a>, and its US affiliate that operates Binance.US before casting the net wider to include <a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/coinbase/">Coinbase</a>. The SEC filed a lawsuit against accusing Binance, its American firm Binance.US, and CEO Changpeng &ldquo;CZ&rdquo; Zhao of breaking federal securities laws Monday. It then filed a lawsuit against Coinbase on Tuesday for allegedly selling unregistered securities to the general public.</p>
<p>The SEC lawsuit has spurred panic among investors especially since the SEC argues that several crypto assets listed on the exchanges are securities rather than digital assets. The tokens identified as securities have registered a significant price decline with Binance&rsquo;s BNB, Polygon&rsquo;s MATIC, and Cardano&rsquo;s ADA experiencing the most drops.</p>
<h2>$4 billion in outflows in four days</h2>
<p>According to data from blockchain analytics companies Nansen and Glassnode, Binance, Binance.US, and Coinbase experienced a net outflow of $3.1 billion through the Ethereum network and $864 million in bitcoin (BTC) between Monday and Thursday.</p>
<p>Despite the regulatory difficulties, the exchanges processed the withdrawals promptly throughout the week and no delays have been reported so far.</p>
<p>According to Nansen data, Binance, the biggest cryptocurrency exchange in the world by trading volume, observed a net outflow of $2 billion on the Ethereum blockchain in just four days. This sum includes all Ethereum-based tokens including ETH. According to Glassnode&rsquo;s data, BTC withdrawals were higher than deposits by about 31,868 BTC ($838 million).</p>
<p>Binance saw a sizeable net outflow on Wednesday of 13,953 BTC, the largest daily drawdown since December, when a faulty reserve report and the collapse of a rival exchange, FTX, undermined investor confidence.</p>
<p>Although the outflows seen this week were sizable, according to Binance&rsquo;s crypto wallets, they only account for about 5% of all the assets held on the exchange.</p>
<p>According to Nansen, Binance.US saw net outflows of $75 million from the Ethereum network. The exchange is not tracked by Glassnode, so it is difficult to track the BTC outflows. It has however been met with the full wrath of the SEC, which has sought <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-sec-is-seeking-court-order-to-freeze-binance-uss-assets/">orders to freeze all .Binance.US assets</a>.</p>
<p>For Coinbase, the Ethereum network saw a net outflow of $1 billion from Monday through Thursday according to Nansen. According to Glassnode&rsquo;s data, Coinbase saw $25 million worth of Bitcoin outflows.<a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/binance/">Binance</a></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-binance-us-and-coinbase-collectively-lose-4b-in-outflows/">Binance, Binance.US, and Coinbase collectively lose $4B in outflows</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-binance-us-and-coinbase-collectively-lose-4b-in-outflows/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nigeria&#8217;s SEC orders Binance Nigeria Limited to stop operations</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/nigerias-sec-orders-binance-nigeria-limited-to-stop-operations/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 15:26:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Africa]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/nigerias-sec-orders-binance-nigeria-limited-to-stop-operations/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Nigeria&#8217;s SEC said Binance Nigeria Limited is neither registered nor regulated and its operations in Nigeria are illegal. The order against Binance Nigeria Limited comes days after the US SEC sued Binance and its founder CZ. Nigeria&#8217;s SEC had previously said it viewed all crypto assets to be securities by default. According to a Friday [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/nigerias-sec-orders-binance-nigeria-limited-to-stop-operations/">Nigeria&#8217;s SEC orders Binance Nigeria Limited to stop operations</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Nigeria&rsquo;s SEC said Binance Nigeria Limited is neither registered nor regulated and its operations in Nigeria are illegal.</li>
<li>The order against Binance Nigeria Limited comes days after the US SEC sued Binance and its founder CZ.</li>
<li>Nigeria&rsquo;s SEC had previously said it viewed all crypto assets to be securities by default.</li>
</ul>
<p>According to a Friday circular from Nigeria&rsquo;s Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), <a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/binance/">Binance&rsquo;s</a> Nigerian branch has been told to stop all operations immediately.</p>
<p>The circular stated that Binance Nigeria Limited&rsquo;s operations in Nigeria were unlawful because it was neither registered with nor subject to regulation by the Commission. The <a href="https://sec.gov.ng/circular-on-the-activities-of-binance-nigeria-limited/">circular</a> by the SEC states:</p>
<p><em>&ldquo;Binance Nigeria Limited is neither registered nor regulated by the Commission and its operations in Nigeria are therefore illegal. Any member of the investing public dealing with the entity is doing so at his/her own risk.</em></p>
<p><em>As the regulator with the statutory mandate of investor protection, the Commission urges Nigerians to be wary of investing in crypto-assets, and crypto-asset-related financial products and services if the service provider/its platform is not registered or regulated by the Commission. Nigerian investors are hereby warned that investing in crypto-assets is extremely risky and may result in a total loss of their investment.</em></p>
<p><em>By this circular, Binance Nigeria Limited is hereby directed to immediately stop soliciting Nigerian investors in any form whatsoever.&rdquo;</em></p>
<h2>Binance under siege</h2>
<p>Binance Nigeria is the second Binance branch to be accused of operating unlicensed activities. On Monday, the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sec-sues-binance-and-cz-for-breaking-us-securities-rules/">US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) sued Binance</a>, its US affiliate, and its founder Changpeng Zhao violating the securities laws in the country.</p>
<p>The US SEC has gone further to request for the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-sec-is-seeking-court-order-to-freeze-binance-uss-assets/">assets of Binance.US to be frozen</a>. It is currently looking for <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sec-seeks-alternative-ways-to-serve-changpeng-zhao-after-failing-to-get-him/">an alternative way to serve Changpeng Zhao</a> with the court sermon.</p>
<h2>Nigeria&rsquo;s SEC stand on cryptocurrencies</h2>
<p>While this is the first action taken by Nigeria&rsquo;s SEC against a cryptocurrency exchange platform, the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/nigerias-sec-recognises-cryptocurrencies-as-securities/">SEC had previously stated</a> that it considers all crypto assets to be securities by default.</p>
<p>Bloomberg reported in May that Nigeria&rsquo;s SEC was processing registration applications from crypto firms on a trial basis but would not begin doing so formally until it had reached an agreement with the nation&rsquo;s central bank.</p>
<p>Currently, it is <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/central-bank-of-nigeria-bans-crypto-and-sees-angry-backlash/">against the law</a> for banks in Nigeria to provide services to cryptocurrency platforms.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/nigerias-sec-orders-binance-nigeria-limited-to-stop-operations/">Nigeria&#8217;s SEC orders Binance Nigeria Limited to stop operations</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
