<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 16:58:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Uber Shares Plummet over 5% Following Q2 2023 Operating Earnings Report</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/uber-shares-q2-2023-earnings-report/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/uber-shares-q2-2023-earnings-report/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Marco T. Lanz]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 16:43:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wall Street]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dara khosrowshahi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[uber]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[uber stock]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=265347</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uber-shares-q2-2023-earnings-report/">Uber Shares Plummet over 5% Following Q2 2023 Operating Earnings Report</a></p>
<p>Uber reported record profits and milestones in the second quarter of 2023, with significant improvements in earnings per share, operating income, and EBITDA, as well as a substantial increase in trips and food delivery orders.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uber-shares-q2-2023-earnings-report/">Uber Shares Plummet over 5% Following Q2 2023 Operating Earnings Report</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uber-shares-q2-2023-earnings-report/">Uber Shares Plummet over 5% Following Q2 2023 Operating Earnings Report</a></p>
<p>On August 1st, the shares of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/uber/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Uber Technologies Inc</a> (NYSE: UBER) fell by more than 5.5% after the publication of the financial results for Q2 of 2023. This drop can be attributed to the fact that, despite the company&#8217;s earnings per share (EPS) of $0.18, the revenues were lower than expected by the shareholders.</p>
<p>According to the <a href="https://s23.q4cdn.com/407969754/files/doc_earnings/2023/q2/earnings-result/Uber-Q2-23-Earnings-Press-Release.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a>, UBER&#8217;s earnings per share showed a significant improvement compared to the $1.33 per share loss they experienced during the same period last year.</p>
<h2>Uber Hits Revenue and Profit Milestones in Second Quarter</h2>
<p>Uber&#8217;s revenues rose to 14% during the second quarter, generating $9.2 billion in Q2 2023. This reflects a 14% increase compared to Q2 2022. The company attributed the growth primarily to a 25% increase in trips and a 12% rise in food delivery orders. Additionally, Uber noted substantial user growth globally in Latin America (+30%), Europe, Middle East, and Africa (+31%), and Asia Pacific (+31%).</p>
<p>Another positive aspect for Uber was achieving an operating income of $326 million during the second quarter, compared to an operating loss of $713 million in the same period in 2022.</p>
<p>Using EBITDA, a key financial indicator to measure a company&#8217;s profitability, Uber reached $916 million, representing a 152% year-on-year growth and demonstrating significant improvements in the automotive giant&#8217;s profitability.</p>
<p>Uber&#8217;s CEO, Dara Khosrowshahi, stated that the company&#8217;s new growth initiatives contributed to a 22% increase in trips, helping the workforce of 6 million drivers earn a record $15.1 billion during Q2.</p>
<p>&#8220;Robust demand, new growth initiatives, and continued cost discipline resulted in an excellent quarter, with trips up 22% and a GAAP operating profit, for the first time in Uber’s history, [&#8230;] These results also translated into strong driver and courier engagement, with 6 million drivers and couriers earning a record $15.1 billion during the quarter,&#8221; revealed the company.</p>
<h2>Uber Reports Record Profits in Q2 2023</h2>
<p>Uber achieved a record of $1.1 billion in free cash flow during the quarter, marking a 198% increase compared to Q2 2022. Thanks to this milestone, the company can continue investing in its expansion and service innovation.</p>
<p>Nelson Chai, Uber&#8217;s CFO, highlighted the team effort that led to two significant achievements during the second quarter: record profitability and over $1.1 billion in free cash flow, emphasizing the company&#8217;s commitment and position to &#8220;continue generating value for shareholders&#8221; in the years to come.</p>
<p>Regarding expectations, Uber anticipates gross revenues for the third quarter of 2023 to be between $34 billion and $35 billion. Additionally, they project an EBITDA of between $975 million and $1.025 billion.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/wells-fargo-xrp-price-500/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uber-shares-q2-2023-earnings-report/">Uber Shares Plummet over 5% Following Q2 2023 Operating Earnings Report</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/uber-shares-q2-2023-earnings-report/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Price Can Hit $100-$500 in 4-7 months, Wells Fargo Treasury Manager Says</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wells-fargo-xrp-price-500/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wells-fargo-xrp-price-500/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mercy Tukiya Mutanya]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 13:47:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[kraken]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[wells fargo]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=265300</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/wells-fargo-xrp-price-500/">XRP Price Can Hit $100-$500 in 4-7 months, Wells Fargo Treasury Manager Says</a></p>
<p>Using Liquidity Strength as a key metric, the expert provided a detailed breakdown of her calculations before coming to her prediction. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/wells-fargo-xrp-price-500/">XRP Price Can Hit $100-$500 in 4-7 months, Wells Fargo Treasury Manager Says</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/wells-fargo-xrp-price-500/">XRP Price Can Hit $100-$500 in 4-7 months, Wells Fargo Treasury Manager Says</a></p>
<p>Wells Fargo Treasury manager Shannon Thorp predicts that <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/xrp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">XRP</a> will hit between $100 and $500 over the coming four to seven months. This comes following Ripple Labs’ victory over the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) in a lawsuit alleging that Ripple had conducted an unregistered securities offering through the sale of its XRP tokens worth $1.3 billion. The regulator stated that XRP was a security and as such, falls under its jurisdiction.</p>
<p>Ripple’s partial victory against the SEC has sparked online price predictions. In a lengthy post on social media platform X, Thorp noted that the XRP community seems to be divided in their predictions. She observed that one side was basing their predictions on “past and trends that follow Bitcoin to draw short-term price predictions”. The other side, however, appears to be focused on utility, &#8220;believing that partnerships and the replacement of antiquated systems will drive price”.</p>
<p>Wells Fargo Treasury manager dismissed both techniques as flawed because they rely on traditional securities logic when, according to the recent court ruling, XRP is not a security. Using Liquidity Strength as a key metric, Thorp provided a detailed breakdown of her calculations before coming to her prediction.</p>
<blockquote data-theme="dark"><p>https://twitter.com/thorpshannon87/status/1685427003879522305</p></blockquote>
<p>“My price prediction is anywhere from $100 &#8211; $500 near the short term (4 -7 months) why? It all boils down to LS if XRP is $100 at a supply of say only 50B that makes an LS of $5T and at $500 that gives us an LS of $25T. This gives the market room to breathe, allows for growth, and ensures no one company needs to own billions of XRP to perform day-to-day operations,” she wrote.</p>
<p>On July 13, the court ruled that XRP sold on exchange platforms did not qualify as a security. Following this news, the token’s price spiked by as much as 98% to reach a high of $0.93, with several exchanges reporting a rise in XRP market activity. Several crypto exchanges, including <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase</a> and Kraken, also <a href="https://blog.kraken.com/product/asset-listings/trading-for-ripple-xrp-starts-now-for-the-usa" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announced</a> that they would be re-listing XRP.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Ripple Labs anticipates increased use of its token and On-Demand Liquidity (ODL) product for cross-border payments by US financial institutions following the ruling. Ripple’s general counsel Stu Alderoty stated that he was hopeful that potential clients would reach out to the firm this quarter and that “some of those conversations will actually turn into a real business”.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/terraform-denied-motion-sec/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/wells-fargo-xrp-price-500/">XRP Price Can Hit $100-$500 in 4-7 months, Wells Fargo Treasury Manager Says</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wells-fargo-xrp-price-500/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Terraform Labs Denies Motion Seeking Dismissal of SEC Fraud Allegations</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/terraform-denied-motion-sec/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/terraform-denied-motion-sec/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 13:42:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[do kwon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[luna]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[terra]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[terraform labs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[terrausd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ust]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=265285</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/terraform-denied-motion-sec/">Terraform Labs Denies Motion Seeking Dismissal of SEC Fraud Allegations</a></p>
<p>The implications of this judgment are significant for both Terraform and the broader ecosystem.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/terraform-denied-motion-sec/">Terraform Labs Denies Motion Seeking Dismissal of SEC Fraud Allegations</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/terraform-denied-motion-sec/">Terraform Labs Denies Motion Seeking Dismissal of SEC Fraud Allegations</a></p>
<p>Terraform Labs, and its founder, Do Kwon, are facing a major setback as US District Judge Jed Rakoff has <a href="https://www.zawya.com/en/special-coverage/the-future-of-cryptos/terraform-labs-must-face-us-sec-fraud-allegations-judge-rules-tmor239g" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reportedly</a> ruled against their motion to dismiss fraud allegations brought forth by the US Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>).</p>
<h2>SEC Allegations against Terraforms and Its Ramifications</h2>
<p>The SEC alleges that Terraform and Do Kwon, were involved in fraudulent activities related to the sale of two digital assets. According to the SEC, these assets were sold as investment contracts to the public without registering them as securities, which is a violation of extant Federal laws.</p>
<p>The SEC&#8217;s <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-investigation-terraform-labs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">complaint</a> alleges that Terraform and Kwon engaged in fraudulent practices by misleading investors about the stability of TerraUSD (UST) and making false promises regarding the potential appreciation of the firm&#8217;s crypto tokens.</p>
<p>According to the SEC, Terraform and Kwon misled investors by claiming that UST, the algorithmic stablecoin, would remain pegged to the US dollar at a 1:1 ratio and that the firm&#8217;s crypto token, including LUNA, would appreciate in value over time.</p>
<p>The SEC, however, contends that these commitments were not kept, as UST eventually fell below its peg to the US dollar in May 2022. This failure to sustain the promised stability resulted in considerable <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/terraform-legal-team-resigns/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">losses</a> for investors who had relied on Terraform and its founder&#8217;s promises.</p>
<h2>The Implication of Judges’ Ruling</h2>
<p>Judge Rakoff&#8217;s ruling allowing the SEC to proceed with these allegations signals that the court finds sufficient evidence or merit in the regulator’s complaint to warrant further examination and legal action. The ruling clears the way for the case to proceed, giving the regulatory body the opportunity to present its evidence and argument against Terraform and Kwon in court.</p>
<p>The implications of this judgment are significant for both Terraform and the broader ecosystem. If the SEC successfully establishes its charges in court, it might have far-reaching implications for how algorithmic stablecoins are produced, sold, and regulated in the future.</p>
<p>The verdict may potentially have an influence on investor confidence in the crypto sector, encouraging additional inspection and due research from investors before engaging in similar initiatives.</p>
<h2>The Ongoing Digital Assets Securities Debate</h2>
<p>Meanwhile, the recent court <a href="https://www.courtlistener.com/docket/19857399/874/securities-and-exchange-commission-v-ripple-labs-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ruling</a> involving <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ripple-labs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ripple Labs Inc</a> and the sale of its associated token, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/xrp/">XRP</a>, has sparked a debate between Judge Rakoff and Judge Analisa Torres.</p>
<p>In the Ripple Labs case, Judge Torres ruled that sales of XRP on public crypto exchanges do not constitute securities. However, in the case involving Terraform and its algorithmic stablecoin TerraUSD (UST), Judge Rakoff took a different perspective.</p>
<p>He disagreed with the notion that the identity of the seller, in this case, Terraform, should be a determining factor in deciding whether a reasonable investor would interpret the statements made by the company or its representatives as promises of profit.</p>
<p>According to Rakoff, the focus should be on the content of the statements and the expectations they create among investors, rather than the technical classification of the crypto.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-upgrade-assistant-ai/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/terraform-denied-motion-sec/">Terraform Labs Denies Motion Seeking Dismissal of SEC Fraud Allegations</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/terraform-denied-motion-sec/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Google Plans Major Upgrade to Its Assistant with Generative AI Features</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-upgrade-assistant-ai/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-upgrade-assistant-ai/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 12:56:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alexa]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alphabet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Amazon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[google]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[siri]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=265262</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-upgrade-assistant-ai/">Google Plans Major Upgrade to Its Assistant with Generative AI Features</a></p>
<p>Meanwhile, Google is not alone in its pursuit of enhancing AI-powered virtual assistants.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-upgrade-assistant-ai/">Google Plans Major Upgrade to Its Assistant with Generative AI Features</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-upgrade-assistant-ai/">Google Plans Major Upgrade to Its Assistant with Generative AI Features</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/google/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Google</a> is gearing up for a significant upgrade to its virtual personal assistant, Google Assistant, designed to help users perform simple tasks on their smartphones. The company plans to upgrade the product using advanced generative AI technology to improve its capabilities. According to an internal email seen by <a href="https://www.axios.com/2023/07/26/amazon-alexa-ai-home" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Axios</a>, Google aims to develop a &#8220;supercharged&#8221; version of the assistant powered by the latest large language models (LLM) similar to ChatGPT and Bard chatbots.</p>
<p>The technology would enable the virtual assistant to offer more sophisticated and enhanced responses, making user interactions more engaging and natural. Although specific features are yet to be revealed, the focus is on delivering high-quality user experiences. By tapping into LLM technology, the assistant could answer questions based on information gathered from the web, providing more comprehensive and accurate responses.</p>
<p>&#8220;Hundreds of millions of people use the assistant every month and we&#8217;re committed to giving them high-quality experiences. We&#8217;re excited to explore how LLMs can help us supercharge assistant and make it even better,&#8221; Google spokesperson Jennifer Rodstrom said in a statement to The Verge.</p>
<h2>Google to Restructure Its Assistant Team</h2>
<p>The email sent by Google&#8217;s VP Peeyush Ranjan and Product Director Duke Dukellis on July 31 revealed that the company had begun developing the new Google Assistant in mobile version. As part of the upgrade, the company, owned by American multinational technology conglomerate  <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/alphabet-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Alphabet</a>, is restructuring its assistant team.</p>
<p>While the exact number of employees affected remains unclear, according to Axios, Google has laid off &#8220;dozens&#8221; of workers. Although it is unclear when Google will complete the transformation, Ranjan and Dukellis believe the virtual assistant has the potential to become successful:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We remain deeply committed to the Assistant, and we are optimistic about its bright future ahead.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Amazon Plans to Enhance Alexa</h2>
<p>Meanwhile, Google is not alone in its pursuit of enhancing AI-powered virtual assistants. Other technology-focused firms, such as <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/amazon/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Amazon</a>, are also investing in AI-powered upgrades for its virtual assistant Alexa.</p>
<p>According to reports by <a href="https://www.axios.com/2023/07/26/amazon-alexa-ai-home">Axios,</a> Amazon is anticipating that generative AI will breathe new life into its middle-aged Alexa voice assistant. The tech giant views the AI boom as an opportunity to revitalize the over half a billion Alexa-enabled devices, transforming them into advanced voice-enabled interfaces akin to ChatGPT and beyond. This move aims to provide users with fresh and relevant experiences while leveraging the potential of generative AI technology.</p>
<p>The adoption of generative AI in Assistants marks a significant departure from the current state of virtual assistants. Traditional virtual assistant tools like <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/apple-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Apple</a>&#8216;s Siri and Amazon&#8217;s Alexa primarily operate on rule-based systems, providing straightforward responses to specific commands or queries. In contrast, generative AI models like LLMs can generate language and carry on more dynamic conversations with users, leading to more personalized interactions.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nomura-crypto-services-dubai/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-upgrade-assistant-ai/">Google Plans Major Upgrade to Its Assistant with Generative AI Features</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-upgrade-assistant-ai/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nomura to Launch Crypto Services in Dubai after Obtaining License</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nomura-crypto-services-dubai/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nomura-crypto-services-dubai/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Babafemi Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 12:43:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto.com]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dfsa]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nomura]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[okx]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=265213</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nomura-crypto-services-dubai/">Nomura to Launch Crypto Services in Dubai after Obtaining License</a></p>
<p>Nomura's move to launch virtual assets and brokerage services in Dubai is well-timed. It comes amid a growing interest and demand for digital assets among institutional and retail investors worldwide.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nomura-crypto-services-dubai/">Nomura to Launch Crypto Services in Dubai after Obtaining License</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nomura-crypto-services-dubai/">Nomura to Launch Crypto Services in Dubai after Obtaining License</a></p>

<p>Nomura, one of the largest financial services groups in Asia, <a href="https://www.nomuraholdings.com/news/nr/europe/20230801/20230801.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announced</a> on Monday that it has obtained a full license from Dubai’s Virtual Asset Regulatory Authority (VARA). The license is expected to expand Noruma’s presence in the Middle East.</p>
<p>Established in 2022, Laser Digital is Nomura&#8217;s crypto arm, Laser Digital, which delivers scalable, robust opportunities across trading, asset management, and ventures. With the license,  it will provide Virtual Asset (VA) broker-dealer services and VA Management and Investment Services for institutions and professional investors in Dubai.</p>
<p>Additionally, users will be able to assess over-the-counter crypto trading and other investment products. Likewise, institutional investors will enjoy <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-over-the-counter-otc-trading-and-how-does-it-work/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">OTC trading</a> services and access to a wide range of digital asset investment products and solutions.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.nomuraholdings.com/news/nr/asia/20230720/20230720.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">According to Arif Amiri</a>, CEO of DIFC Authority, they &#8220;are delighted to see Nomura&#8217;s growth plans flourish in DIFC, Dubai, and the region.&#8221;</p>
<h2>Dubai Has Great Potentials: Laser Digital CEO</h2>
<p>CEO of Laser Digital Jez Mohideen expressed his gratitude for the license approval. “VARA’s thorough and consultative process provides institutional investors with the assurance they require to engage in this asset class. With the license now in place, we are looking forward to Laser’s growth over the coming years,” said he.</p>
<p>Nomura&#8217;s move to launch virtual assets and brokerage services in Dubai is well-timed. It comes amid a growing interest and demand for digital assets among institutional and retail investors worldwide. According to a recent <a href="https://triple-a.io/crypto-ownership-data/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report by Triple A</a>, global crypto ownership rates are at an average of 4.2%. There are also over 420 million crypto users worldwide. Likewise, the UAE ranks as one of the most crypto-friendly countries in the world.</p>
<h2>Regulations, Nomura, and the Dubai Market</h2>
<p>This is not Nomura’s first rodeo in Dubai. In 2018, it started a regulated digital asset custody solution through a joint venture with CoinShares and Ledger. In July, the group announced that it was launching an International Wealth Management Business in Dubai. Nomura obtained a Category 4 license from the Dubai Financial Services Authority (DFSA) to manage this business.</p>
<p>Aside from Nomura, several other exchanges are in various stages of obtaining their licenses. Just yesterday, Binance won an operational license in <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-crypto-mvp-license-in-dubai/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Dubai</a>. The exchange is on track to getting full license approval in the city after securing a pre-approval last year Also, Crypto.com and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/okx/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">OKX</a> are in various stages of their application completion as they seek to comply with local regulators.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/british-petroleum-bp-q2-2023/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nomura-crypto-services-dubai/">Nomura to Launch Crypto Services in Dubai after Obtaining License</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nomura-crypto-services-dubai/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>British Petroleum (BP) Reports 70% Drop in Profit in Q2 2023, Raises Dividends by 10%</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/british-petroleum-bp-q2-2023/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/british-petroleum-bp-q2-2023/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 12:40:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[british petroleum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=265255</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/british-petroleum-bp-q2-2023/">British Petroleum (BP) Reports 70% Drop in Profit in Q2 2023, Raises Dividends by 10%</a></p>
<p>With falling commodity prices, BP and other oil giants faced significant headwinds taking a major hit on its profits during Q2 2023. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/british-petroleum-bp-q2-2023/">British Petroleum (BP) Reports 70% Drop in Profit in Q2 2023, Raises Dividends by 10%</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/british-petroleum-bp-q2-2023/">British Petroleum (BP) Reports 70% Drop in Profit in Q2 2023, Raises Dividends by 10%</a></p>
<p>On Tuesday, August 1, oil giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/bp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">British Petroleum</a> (LON: BP) reported a 70% drop in profits for Q2 2023 on the backdrop of weaker fossil fuel prices.</p>
<h2>BP in Q2 2023</h2>
<p>BP, the British energy company, reported a second-quarter underlying replacement cost profit of $2.6 billion. Analysts had anticipated a higher profit of $3.5 billion for the same period, based on estimates from Refinitiv.</p>
<p>In the second quarter, BP made a profit of $2.6 billion, which was lower than the $4.96 billion profit in the previous quarter and the $8.5 billion profit in the same quarter last year. The decrease in earnings was due to lower refining margins, increased maintenance activities, and a weak performance in oil trading.</p>
<p>However, the petroleum and energy giant boosted its dividend by 10% by 7.27 cents per share, during the second quarter. Furthermore, BP has announced a buyback of $1.5 billion worth of its shares over the next quarter. <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/08/01/bp-q2-earnings-2023.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Speaking</a> on the development, BP CEO Bernard Looney told CNBC’s “Squawk Box Europe”:</p>
<blockquote><p>“A very good quarter and that has given the board … the confidence to announce a $1.5 billion buyback program for the quarter and additionally we’ve raised the dividend by 10%. So, all in all, we’re doing what we said we would do which is performing while transforming and we’re very pleased with the results.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>As of press time, the BP stock price is up by 2.01% and is currently trading at 492.70 GBX. Amid weaker commodity prices, oil majors have failed to post bumper profits as they did during Q2 2022.</p>
<p>In 2022, the five largest oil companies in the West made a total profit of almost $200 billion, benefiting from the surge in oil and gas prices after Russia&#8217;s invasion of Ukraine. BP, in particular, achieved a record profit of $27.7 billion for the entire year of 2022.</p>
<h2>BP Dialing Back on Its Promise of Reducing Carbon Emissions</h2>
<p>BP has faced criticism in recent times for weakening its promises on climate action. In 2020, the company had committed to becoming a net-zero company by 2050 or even earlier. However, earlier this year, it revised its plans and decided to reduce its carbon emissions by scaling back its oil and gas production.</p>
<p>Previously, BP had promised to lower emissions by 35% to 40% by the end of this decade. However, in early February, it changed its target to a 20% to 30% reduction instead. When asked why is BP shifting its goalposts, Looney said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“We, actually, in February announced that we’re leaning into our strategy and announced that we were going to put $8 billion more into the energy transition this decade, spending between $55 [billion] and $65 billion. At the same time, we announced that we would increase our investment in oil and gas, and that’s because it’s crucial that we invest in the supply of today’s energy system to meet the demand.”</p></blockquote>
<p>“If we don’t, there’s only one thing that is going to happen and that’s that prices are going to go up. We need a rapid transition and we need to make sure that the transition is orderly,” added he.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-sei-36th-project/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/british-petroleum-bp-q2-2023/">British Petroleum (BP) Reports 70% Drop in Profit in Q2 2023, Raises Dividends by 10%</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/british-petroleum-bp-q2-2023/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Unveils Sei as 36th Project on Its Launchpool</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-sei-36th-project/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-sei-36th-project/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 12:36:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Binance News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance launchpool]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cyberconnect]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEI]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=265232</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-sei-36th-project/">Binance Unveils Sei as 36th Project on Its Launchpool</a></p>
<p>Simultaneously, Binance has introduced CyberConnect (CYBER) as the 37th project on Binance Launchpool.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-sei-36th-project/">Binance Unveils Sei as 36th Project on Its Launchpool</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-sei-36th-project/">Binance Unveils Sei as 36th Project on Its Launchpool</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a>, the world’s biggest crypto exchange has announced the debut of Sei (SEI), a cutting-edge layer 1 blockchain designed for the exchange of digital assets, as the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ieo/sei/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">36th project</a> on Binance Launchpool.</p>
<h2>Binance and the Sei Support</h2>
<p>Binance highlighted in an <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/support/announcement/introducing-sei-sei-on-binance-launchpool-farm-sei-by-staking-bnb-tusd-and-fdusd-b1d3b4df9cb34f679783a4fdb891f643" target="_blank" rel="noopener">official statement</a> that Sei is a revolutionary blockchain protocol designed to address the challenges faced by digital asset exchanges.</p>
<p>With a primary focus on optimizing the exchange of digital assets, Sei aims to revolutionize the way users trade and transact in the crypto space. Its advanced architecture and innovative features set the stage for a seamless and efficient digital asset trading experience.</p>
<p>To celebrate the introduction of Sei, Binance is offering users a unique opportunity to participate in the farming of the tokens through Binance Launchpool. Binance is allocating 300,000,000 SEI tokens as Launchpool rewards.</p>
<p>Users can stake their Binance Coin (BNB), TUSD (TrueUSD), and FDUSD (Frax Dollars) into separate pools for 30 days. The farming process is scheduled to begin on August 2, 2023, at 00:00 (UTC). Notably, users will be required to complete the Know Your Customer (KYC) verification process to participate in the SEI Launchpool and stake their tokens,</p>
<p>By staking their assets in the Binance Launchpool, participants are poised to earn SEI tokens as rewards, contributing to the growth and development of the Sei network while also reaping the benefits of their involvement.</p>
<p>Following the successful farming period, Binance said it will list SEI tokens on its platform on August 15, 2023, at 12:00 (UTC). Trading of SEI will commence with three trading pairs: SEI/BTC, SEI/USDT, and SEI/BNB. Moreover, SEI will be labeled with the <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/support/announcement/introducing-seed-tags-monitoring-tags-for-tokens-with-high-volatility-and-risks-b0f241491d0e4d75aa2f8752b7bf8af5" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Seed Tag</a>, indicating its status as a newly listed project on Binance.</p>
<p>The total supply of SEI tokens is set at 10,000,000,000. At the commencement of the Launchpool, an initial circulating supply of 1,800,000,000 SEI tokens will be available in the market. This portion represents 18% of the total SEI token supply.</p>
<p>According to the announcement, snapshots of user balances and total pool balances will be taken multiple times each hour to calculate users’ hourly average balances and rewards. Rewards will be updated every hour, allowing users to accumulate and claim their rewards directly to their spot accounts at any time.</p>
<h2>Binance to Feature CyberConnect (CYBER) on Its Launchpool</h2>
<p>Simultaneously, Binance has introduced CyberConnect (CYBER) as the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ieo/cyberconnect/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">37th project</a> on Binance Launchpool. CyberConnect is a revolutionary Web3 social network that empowers developers to create cutting-edge social applications on the blockchain.</p>
<p>Binance noted in an official statement that users can stake their BNB, TUSD, and FDUSD into separate pools for a duration of 30 days after which they will earn CYBER tokens in a manner similar to that of SEI. The farming process is also scheduled to begin on August 2, 2023, at 00:00 (UTC).<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/blockchain-verifying-cultural-artifacts/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-sei-36th-project/">Binance Unveils Sei as 36th Project on Its Launchpool</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-sei-36th-project/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Blockchain Will Be Used for Verifying Cultural Artifacts</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/blockchain-verifying-cultural-artifacts/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/blockchain-verifying-cultural-artifacts/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Darya Rudz]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 12:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain cultural artifacts]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[salsal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[verification-as-a-service]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web3]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=265168</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/blockchain-verifying-cultural-artifacts/">Blockchain Will Be Used for Verifying Cultural Artifacts</a></p>
<p>Collections submitted for verification by Salsal end up with a proven factual history of the owners and receive an immutable, permanent record of ownership transfer.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/blockchain-verifying-cultural-artifacts/">Blockchain Will Be Used for Verifying Cultural Artifacts</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/blockchain-verifying-cultural-artifacts/">Blockchain Will Be Used for Verifying Cultural Artifacts</a></p>
<p>Researchers have come up with a blockchain solution to confirm the authenticity of cultural artifacts. Dr. Adel Khelifi, an associate professor at Abu Dhabi University, and Dr. Mark Altaweel, a reader in Near East Archaeology at the Institute of Archaeology, University College London, have developed a blockchain tool called Salsal (also known as Agur). Salsal is a Web3-based verification-as-a-service model for determining and recording the authenticity and provenance of antiquities.</p>
<p>Salsal aims to provide heritage collectors with a platform to verify their collection and track an accurate history of an object&#8217;s ownership. The process of verification is pretty simple. According to the Salsal website, a collector first uploads a collection and submits it for verification. Next, experts in the collection field evaluate the collection and submit their review to the Central Verification Board. Once verified by the Board, the collection can be transformed into a <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-are-non-fungible-tokens-nfts/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">non-fungible token</a> (NFT), with the data stored on the blockchain.</p>
<p>Dr. Mark Altaweel <a href="https://edition.cnn.com/2023/07/31/world/ancient-treasures-are-being-looted-but-blockchain-could-help-protect-them/index.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">commented</a>:</p>
<blockquote>
<p data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/clkqw777k000m356fwtbq2tru@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-analytics-observe="off">&#8220;If you’re a collector, like a museum, you can upload images and descriptions about those objects, then it goes to the verifiers who check the objects are valid. We use the Museums Association certification process where you rate objects on a one to five scale (based on) how secure or how valid a collection is. The idea was that this also becomes a way to pressure those collectors – including museums – to really make sure that the items they are displaying to the public are legal. If they have an object there illegally or obtained in an unethical manner, then they should do something about it.&#8221;</p>
</blockquote>
<p data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/clkqw777k000m356fwtbq2tru@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-analytics-observe="off">Thus, collections submitted for verification by Salsal end up with a proven factual history of the owners and receive an immutable, permanent record of ownership transfer.</p>
<h2 data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/clkqw777k000m356fwtbq2tru@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-analytics-observe="off">Blockchain to Settle Cultural Justice</h2>
<p data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/clkqw777k000m356fwtbq2tru@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-analytics-observe="off">Currently, most regions have specific regulations when it comes to purchasing, collecting, and trading of cultural significance, especially when they are found on public or protected land. However, there is no officially recognized registry that would store the track of cultural artifacts globally. As a result of weak legislation, criminals can illegally move artifacts around, while objects with questionable provenance often become legitimized.</p>
<p data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/clkqw777k000m356fwtbq2tru@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-analytics-observe="off">With blockchain, that might change. The technology has the potential to help significantly reduce fraud in the art and collectables industry.</p>
<p data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/clkqw777k000m356fwtbq2tru@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-analytics-observe="off">Tasoula Hadjitofi, author of &#8220;The Icon Hunter&#8221; and CEO of the non-governmental organization Walk of Truth, said:</p>
<blockquote>
<p data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/clkqw85xr0013356fu377vhyj@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-analytics-observe="off">&#8220;Technology can help activists, volunteers, and researchers shed light and combat art trafficking.&#8221;</p>
</blockquote>
<p data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/clkqw85xr0013356fu377vhyj@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-analytics-observe="off">She has also added that Salsal could create &#8220;armies of students&#8221; to search for illegally acquired antiquities and appeal to &#8220;the conscience of collectors&#8221; to share information about their collections and return any items that are found to have been stolen.</p>
<p><a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-ai-chatbots/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/blockchain-verifying-cultural-artifacts/">Blockchain Will Be Used for Verifying Cultural Artifacts</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/blockchain-verifying-cultural-artifacts/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Meta Platforms to Launch AI-Powered Chatbots with Unique Personalities in September</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-ai-chatbots/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-ai-chatbots/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 12:03:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mark zuckerberg]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Meta]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nintendo]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[snap]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tesla]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[threads]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=265234</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-ai-chatbots/">Meta Platforms to Launch AI-Powered Chatbots with Unique Personalities in September</a></p>
<p>Meta is considering automated checks on the chatbots' outputs to ensure accuracy and compliance with platform rules.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-ai-chatbots/">Meta Platforms to Launch AI-Powered Chatbots with Unique Personalities in September</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-ai-chatbots/">Meta Platforms to Launch AI-Powered Chatbots with Unique Personalities in September</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/meta/">Meta Platforms,</a> the parent company of Facebook and Instagram, is set to unveil a new range of artificial intelligence (AI) chatbots with distinct personalities as early as September.</p>
<p>According to <a href="https://www.ft.com/content/fa76c8ce-cdfd-458c-baec-73dceb2d2ad5" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reports</a> from the Financial Times, citing people familiar with the matter, the tech giant has been developing prototypes for chatbots capable of engaging in human-like discussions with its nearly billion users.</p>
<p>These AI-powered tools, known internally as &#8220;personas&#8221;, will feature various characters, including one modeled after former United States president Abraham Lincoln and another designed to offer travel advice in the style of a laid-back surfer. When launched, the chatbots will provide users with a new and exciting search function with personalized recommendations.</p>
<h2>Meta&#8217;s New Endeavour Raises Questions about Data Protection</h2>
<p>The move comes as the company strives to address challenges related to <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-users-retention-threads/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">user retention.</a> In a recent earnings report for Q2 2023, Meta CEO <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/mark-zuckerberg/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Mark Zuckerberg</a> acknowledged the company&#8217;s focus on its latest product Threads aiming to bring back users who drifted away after its launch.</p>
<p>Recall that Coinspeaker <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-threads-100m-users/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a> last month that the new social media platform achieved an impressive milestone of over 100 million users within a few days of its debut, beating OpenAI&#8217;s ChatGPT. Although the Instagram-inspired app has been experiencing a decline in user registrations, Meta CEO said in the recent earnings call that users are returning to the platform designed to rival Twitter.</p>
<p>With the latest AI products on the way, the company aims to attract more users to Threads to bolster its adoption and strengthen its foothold in the social media sector.</p>
<p>However, it is worth noting that Meta&#8217;s new endeavor is not without challenges. The implementation of AI chatbots raises concerns about data privacy and security. With each user interaction, the chatbots have the potential to collect vast amounts of data. While this data can be valuable for improving content and advertising targeting, it also raises questions about how Meta intends to handle and safeguard user information.</p>
<p>According to the Financial Times report, the company is considering automated checks on the chatbots&#8217; outputs to ensure accuracy and compliance with platform rules. By implementing such measures, Meta aims to reduce the chances of chatbots spreading misinformation, hate speech, or other harmful content.</p>
<p>&#8220;According to a Meta insider, the company will probably build on technology that will screen users&#8217; questions to ensure they are appropriate. The company may also automate checks on the output from its chatbots to ensure what it says is accurate and avoid hate or rule-breaking speech, for example,&#8221; reads the FT report.</p>
<h2>Other Tech Companies apart from Meta Exploring AI Opportunities</h2>
<p>Apart from Meta, other tech giants, including <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/apple-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Apple,</a> are actively exploring AI offerings. Apple&#8217;s proprietary framework, &#8216;Ajax&#8217;, is currently under development to create large language models, and the company is also testing its own AI chatbot, internally referred to as &#8216;Apple GPT&#8217; by engineers.</p>
<p>Furthermore, Facebook and Instagram&#8217;s parent company is not the only tech firm venturing into AI-powered chatbots with unique personalities. Character.ai, backed by Andreessen Horowitz and valued at $1 billion, has successfully developed chatbots that emulate the conversational styles of prominent figures such as Tesla CEO <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/elon-musk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Elon Musk</a> and Nintendo character Mario.</p>
<p>Another tech firm Snap has also developed an AI dubbed &#8220;My AI&#8221; feature that has also garnered substantial user engagement, attracting interactions from 150 million users with its friendly chatbot.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-japan-market-34-tokens/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-ai-chatbots/">Meta Platforms to Launch AI-Powered Chatbots with Unique Personalities in September</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-ai-chatbots/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Reenters Japanese Market with 34 Tokens</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-japan-market-34-tokens/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-japan-market-34-tokens/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Babafemi Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 11:51:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Binance News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance cz]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bnb]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[changpeng zhao]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cz]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=265136</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-japan-market-34-tokens/">Binance Reenters Japanese Market with 34 Tokens</a></p>
<p>With 34 tokens, Binance will offer more coins than any exchange operating in Japan.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-japan-market-34-tokens/">Binance Reenters Japanese Market with 34 Tokens</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-japan-market-34-tokens/">Binance Reenters Japanese Market with 34 Tokens</a></p>

<p>Leading cryptocurrency exchange Binance has unveiled its plan to re-enter the Japanese market. The announcement comes after Binance <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/japan-pm-web3-stance-binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">noted</a> in July that it was making a comeback in Japan.</p>
<p>Binance pulled out of Japan in 2018 after the country&#8217;s financial regulator accused it of operating without regulatory clearance. Following failed attempts to obtain an independent license, Binance acquired the Sakura Exchange Bitcoin (SEBC) in November 2022. This allowed it to obtain the necessary license to operate in Japan.</p>
<p>With its launch imminent, Binance announced it will launch its Japan subsidiary with 34 tokens, including Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a>), Ether (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ETH</a>), Litecoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/litecoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">LTC</a>), <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/xrp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">XRP</a>, and BNB coin. This is also the first time that Binance will be offering BNB coins in Japan.</p>
<p>With 34 tokens, Binance will offer more coins than any exchange operating in Japan. According to Coinpost, major domestic competitors Bitbank, GMO Coin, and Coincheck only offer 30, 26, and 22 assets respectively.</p>
<h2>CZ Excited about Binance Japan</h2>
<p>Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao (CZ) expressed his excitement about the re-entry into Japan, saying that it is a &#8220;strategic market&#8221; for the exchange. CZ noted that Japan has been clear on its regulations for almost a decade. Consequently, he labeled the country as &#8220;a leader in the Web3 regulatory environment&#8221;.</p>
<p>Indeed, Japan is one of the most advanced and regulated markets for cryptocurrencies in the world. The country has about 28 licensed crypto exchanges, <a href="https://www.statista.com/statistics/1276409/japan-number-crypto-exchanges-offering-cryptocurrencies-by-coin/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">according to Statista</a>. It also recognized Bitcoin and other digital assets as a legal form of payment since 2017. Binance&#8217;s re-entry into Japan could bring more opportunities for the crypto sector in the country.</p>
<p>Aside from its crypto asset deposit and withdrawal services, Binance Japan will allow users to access the platform’s spot trading, crypto asset market, and NFT marketplace. The simple earn feature, automatic purchase, and API connection will also be available for use. Outside this list, Binance has stated that any other service would not be available through Binance Japan for now.</p>
<h2>Regulatory Headwinds Threaten Binance Globally</h2>
<p>Elsewhere, Binance continues to battle with regulators and licenses. In the US, Binance is facing accusations of mishandling customer funds and manipulating trades. In France, officials raided the exchange while in Australia, regulators are probing the company’s operations. Combined with the withdrawal of its license in several jurisdictions, Binance is clearly facing regulatory headwinds in many parts of the world. However, CZ remains convinced that this will not stop the exchange.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/palantir-pltr-stock-ai-craze/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-japan-market-34-tokens/">Binance Reenters Japanese Market with 34 Tokens</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-japan-market-34-tokens/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4219 metric#misses=41 metric#hit-ratio=99.0 metric#bytes=1084054 metric#prefetches=214 metric#store-reads=20 metric#store-writes=2 metric#store-hits=221 metric#store-misses=2 metric#sql-queries=34 metric#ms-total=97.89 metric#ms-cache=5.01 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.2384 metric#ms-cache-ratio=5.1 -->