<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
>

<channel>
	<title>CoinCu News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://news.coincu.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://news.coincu.com</link>
	<description>Coin and Crypto Infomation Update</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 02:37:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/cropped-Screen-Shot-2022-05-31-at-14.56.39-32x32.png</url>
	<title>CoinCu News</title>
	<link>https://news.coincu.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>HKMA President Pointed Out The U.S. Had No Clear Regulation For Crypto In The Past</title>
		<link>https://news.coincu.com/196055-hkma-president-u-s-had-no-clear-regulation/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Thana]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 02:37:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[HKMA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[HKMA President]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Yue Wai-man]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.coincu.com/?p=196055</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Yue Wai-man, HKMA President, discusses US crypto regulation and Hong Kong's relaxed stance. HK has moved from strict to clear regulations to reduce regional arbitrage.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>The United States lacked clear regulatory requirements for virtual assets in the past while Singapore and Dubai had regulations on certain virtual currencies, such as anti-money laundering.</em></li>



<li><em>Hong Kong has moved from strict regulations that were close to prohibition to clear regulations to reduce regulatory arbitrage caused by different standards in different regions.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Yue Wai-man, HKMA President, discusses US crypto regulation and Hong Kong&#8217;s relaxed stance. HK has moved from strict to clear regulations to reduce regional arbitrage.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1338.png"><img decoding="async" width="1024" height="683" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1338-1024x683.png" alt="HKMA President Pointed Out The U.S. Had No Clear Regulation For Crypto In The Past " class="wp-image-196056" srcset="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1338-1024x683.png 1024w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1338-300x200.png 300w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1338-768x512.png 768w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1338-750x500.png 750w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1338.png 1098w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="HKMA President Pointed Out The U.S. Had No Clear Regulation For Crypto In The Past 1"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>Yue Wai-man, the President of the Hong Kong Monetary Authority, recently <a href="https://news.mingpao.com/pns/%E7%B6%93%E6%BF%9F/article/20230619/s00004/1687108079446/%E9%87%91%E7%AE%A1%E5%B1%80-%E9%98%BF%E8%81%AF%E9%85%8B%E5%B0%8D%E6%B8%AF%E8%99%9B%E6%93%AC%E8%B3%87%E7%94%A2%E7%9B%A3%E7%AE%A1%E7%B6%93%E9%A9%97%E6%9C%89%E8%88%88%E8%B6%A3" target="_blank" data-type="URL" data-id="https://news.mingpao.com/pns/%E7%B6%93%E6%BF%9F/article/20230619/s00004/1687108079446/%E9%87%91%E7%AE%A1%E5%B1%80-%E9%98%BF%E8%81%AF%E9%85%8B%E5%B0%8D%E6%B8%AF%E8%99%9B%E6%93%AC%E8%B3%87%E7%94%A2%E7%9B%A3%E7%AE%A1%E7%B6%93%E9%A9%97%E6%9C%89%E8%88%88%E8%B6%A3" rel="noreferrer noopener">commented </a>on the United States&#8217; strengthened cryptocurrency regulations and Hong Kong&#8217;s relaxed stance. According to Yue, the United States lacked clear regulatory requirements for virtual assets in the past, while Singapore and Dubai had regulations on certain virtual currencies, such as anti-money laundering. After learning from the experiences of other places, such as the collapse of FTX, Hong Kong has gradually opened up from its strict standards and implemented clear regulations.</p>



<p>Yue also pointed out that Hong Kong had previously imposed strict regulations that were close to prohibition but is now moving towards consistent regulatory levels across various regions. This approach aims to reduce regulatory arbitrage caused by different standards in different regions in the future.</p>



<p>It was rumored that the Hong Kong Monetary Authority questioned why many large banks in Hong Kong did not accept opening accounts for virtual asset exchanges. Yu Weiwen, an official from the authority, responded that the authorities have always communicated with the banks. However, virtual assets are still a new project, and the banking regulatory framework and operational requirements have always been aimed at traditional financial businesses. </p>



<p>Therefore, the industry must constantly update its understanding and clarify its regulatory expectations with the authorities. Once a financial institution is licensed, its operations are reviewed by regulatory agencies, and the authorities have anti-money laundering and customer account verification requirements for banks. Banks must follow the principle of &#8220;risk-based&#8221; and review each customer individually. The program then decides whether to open an account or not.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER:&nbsp;</em></strong><em>The information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>



<p>Join us to keep track of news:&nbsp;<a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Thana</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Coincu</strong>&nbsp;<strong>News</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ban-sao-cua-Ban-sao-cua-Noi-dung-doan-van-ban-cua-ban-40-1024x731.jpg" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/jpeg" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Wormhole Review: The Most Powerful Cross-chain Bridge Protocol</title>
		<link>https://news.coincu.com/196020-wormhole-review/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Harold]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 19:23:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Reviews]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Acala]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Algorand]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Aptos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[aurora]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Avalanche]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNB Chain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Celo]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cross-chain bridge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantom]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Karura]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NEAR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Oasis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Portal Bridge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terra Classic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wormhole]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.coincu.com/?p=196020</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Wormhole is a system that enables dApps and smart contracts to interact, link, and transfer data and assets across blockchains using cross-chain messaging technology.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The difficulty of interoperability is one of the key downsides of the various blockchains on the market. This has resulted in several deficiencies and a failure to satisfy the demands of users. As a result, to maximize and capitalize on the enormous potential of such blockchain enterprises. The Wormhole project was created with the goal of creating a bridge that connects enormous ecosystems.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1333.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="800" height="400" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1333.png" alt="Wormhole Review: The Most Powerful Cross-chain Bridge Protocol" class="wp-image-196046" srcset="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1333.png 800w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1333-300x150.png 300w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1333-768x384.png 768w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1333-360x180.png 360w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1333-750x375.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 800px) 100vw, 800px" title="Wormhole Review: The Most Powerful Cross-chain Bridge Protocol 2"></a></figure></div>


<p>So what is Wormhole? Does the project really have potential? Let&#8217;s find out with Coincu through this article.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">What is Wormhole?</h2>



<p>Wormhole is a system that enables dApps and smart contracts to interact, link, and transfer data and assets across blockchains using cross-chain messaging technology. As a consequence, regardless of which blockchain is used, blockchain apps may function with any form of asset or service.</p>



<p>Wormhole, in particular, is a bridge technology that links various blockchain chains. Ethereum, Solana, Terra, Binance Smart Chain, Polygon, Avalanche, and Oasis are among the coins represented. The chains may interact thanks to the protocol. And instead of being divided, they speak with one another. Wormhole is presently focusing on crypto assets, pricing data, and non-fungible tokens.</p>



<p>The protocol will link and transport crypto assets across different networks in a simple and dependable manner. As a consequence, it is feasible to optimize and capitalize on the enormous potential of projects on several blockchains. It also supports synchronization with reduced latency. Also, the data may be utilized freely and without delay.</p>



<p>This is accomplished via the use of a network of guardian nodes, which aid in the protection of the protocol by watching and verifying events and data on its linked chains. Wormhole&#8217;s TVL now exceeds $1 billion and provides the required backing for the NFT.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Wormholes address what problem?</h2>



<p>One of the biggest challenges that blockchain networks face is the difficulty in interacting with one another. This will create several impediments and render the ecosystem incapable of meeting the demands of consumers. Wormhole was therefore created to handle challenging situations such as:</p>



<p><strong>Difficulties in moving tokens across blockchains</strong></p>



<p>One often-used solution nowadays is to transfer assets through controlled exchanges. To be able to go anywhere you desire. This strategy, however, has several disadvantages because no one wants to entrust their money or possessions to others.</p>



<p><strong>Interoperability issues with smart contracts and blockchain apps</strong></p>



<p>Given the rising popularity of DeFi, smart contracts, and layer 2 apps. Interoperability between smart contracts is difficult. Thus the program unintentionally imposes a constraint on these blockchain networks. So how can it do this?</p>



<p>The Wormhole Core Layer arises in response to these constraints. The Core Layer is the most crucial component, the backbone of the Wormhole project&#8217;s complete ecosystem, and it addresses the entire basic interaction issue. Of course, the Core Layer does not have to be handled by centralization, such as the previously described centralized exchanges. Core Layer is incredibly strong and effective despite its simplicity. It operates by deploying a single contract per blockchain. This is known as a Core Contract. Other Core Contracts may leverage this feature to communicate off-chain or verify the legitimacy of a communication.</p>



<p><strong>Guardians — Validator Nodes</strong></p>



<p>The Guardian Network, however, is the most significant component of the Wormhole Core Layer. Guardian Network was developed to assist in the tracking and validation of messages transmitted from each blockchain through Core Contract.</p>



<p>All 18 Guardians are part of the Guardian Network. Wormhole&#8217;s blockchain will be observed by each unit. A message is not regarded genuine until it has been seen and acknowledged by two-thirds of the total Guardians. When it examines the message&#8217;s validity, they might be termed verification signatures. In particular, 18 Guardians are hand-picked among the world&#8217;s most famous Providers and Validators.</p>



<p><strong>Wormhole Token Bridge</strong></p>



<p>Wormhole&#8217;s most essential and well-known characteristic. It allows crypto-asset transactions across Layer 1 blockchains to be trustless and permissionless. Ethereum, Solana, Terra, Binance Smart Chain, Polygon, Avalanche, and Oasis are among them.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Highlights</h2>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Many popular blockchains supported</strong></h3>



<p>One of them is the diversity of blockchains supported, which allows users to access a broad range of DeFi protocols without relying on centralized solutions. You may, for example, move ERC-20 tokens from Ethereum to other chains and utilize DeFi protocols there. This is a nice answer to an issue that seems to have been there for some time, especially for Ethereum users who are battling with excessive gas prices. Similarly, holders of tokens from other chains may acquire access to the large Ethereum DeFi ecosystem.</p>



<p>Wormhole also supports Solana and Terra, two of the most popular Layer 1 blockchains on the market, with each having a quickly rising number of TVLs due to their own expanding DeFi ecosystems. Wormhole differs from most other bridges in that it supports all three &#8220;major&#8221; DeFi chains.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1335.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="653" height="332" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1335.png" alt="Wormhole Review: The Most Powerful Cross-chain Bridge Protocol" class="wp-image-196048" srcset="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1335.png 653w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1335-300x153.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 653px) 100vw, 653px" title="Wormhole Review: The Most Powerful Cross-chain Bridge Protocol 3"></a></figure></div>


<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>NFT bridges across chains</strong></h3>



<p>Moreover, the Wormhole NFT gateway enables users to transmit NFTs across many blockchains. Likewise, other popular token bridges do not provide this capability.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>DApps are totally based on chains</strong></h3>



<p>Wormhole, in addition to the token bridge, offers decentralized apps developed on top of it. Developers may approach apps from a protocol-first design viewpoint thanks to Wormhole&#8217;s architecture. This may be chain-agnostic or make use of the characteristics of each blockchain. For example, an application may choose Solana to confirm transactions due to its cheap transaction costs, but Ethereum is the ultimate payment layer due to its security.</p>



<p>Wormhole effectively enables apps to leverage multiple Layer 1 blockchains as a Layer 2 solution. Developers may create multi-chain decentralized exchanges, chain-independent wallets, and even multi-chain DAOs.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Ecosystem and development platform</strong></h3>



<p>Wormhole is a developer ecosystem and platform. Developers may construct apps that enable the transfer of assets across the blockchains supported by Wormhole by integrating the Wormhole SDK, considerably enhancing liquidity. Users may, for example, transmit ETH from Ethereum to a Solana application or play games on Solana and collect NFT prizes from Ethereum.</p>



<p>A cluster of 19 nodes known as guardians secure and controls the Wormhole environment. Among the guardian nodes testing this Wormhole on-chain activity are well-known companies such as Everstake, the world&#8217;s biggest staking platform.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Non-EVM chains are supported</strong></h3>



<p>Wormhole is one of the few methods that allow data and assets to be transferred between EVM-incompatible blockchains such as Solana, Aptos, Sui, and Acala and EVM chains like Ethereum and Polygon.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Top TVL on DeFi market</strong></h3>



<p>Portal, Wormhole&#8217;s product, is worth more than $360 million in TVL, ranking fourth in the market&#8217;s Bridge category. Portal&#8217;s TVL used to be more than $4.6 billion, however, it has fallen dramatically since Terra&#8217;s UST collapse and the effect of the $326 million breach.</p>



<p>While it has previously been hacked for a huge sum of money, Wormhole has overcome it and responded fast by developing a bug bounty program for the project. Wormhole evaluates and discovers flaws in smart contracts, adds an extra layer of 2FA protection for users, employs additional technologies to identify aberrant network activity, and so on.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot-2023-06-19-at-01.43.36.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="463" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot-2023-06-19-at-01.43.36-1024x463.png" alt="Wormhole Review: The Most Powerful Cross-chain Bridge Protocol" class="wp-image-196045" srcset="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot-2023-06-19-at-01.43.36-1024x463.png 1024w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot-2023-06-19-at-01.43.36-300x136.png 300w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot-2023-06-19-at-01.43.36-768x348.png 768w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot-2023-06-19-at-01.43.36-1536x695.png 1536w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot-2023-06-19-at-01.43.36-2048x927.png 2048w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot-2023-06-19-at-01.43.36-750x339.png 750w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot-2023-06-19-at-01.43.36-1140x516.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Wormhole Review: The Most Powerful Cross-chain Bridge Protocol 4"></a></figure></div>


<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Infrastructure</h2>



<p>As a user interacts with Dapps, this activity is relayed to the Wormhole blockchain through the following channels:</p>



<ul>
<li>Contracts to accept transactions, interact with xDaap, and deliver services are referred to as xDapp Contracts.</li>



<li>Ecosystem Contracts: Wormhole-administered contracts that offer xDapps developers Wormhole&#8217;s feature set.</li>
</ul>



<p>The Guardian Network validates this information before sending it to Relayers through VAA messages. Wormhole is a multi-signature authentication mechanism that uses VAA to safeguard cross-chain communication.</p>



<ul>
<li>Guardian Network: A validator that monitors Core Contracts on compatible blockchains and produces VAAs (signed notifications) when such contracts are triggered.</li>



<li>Relayers: Relayers use off-chain functionality to decrease gas expenses and improve cross-blockchain interoperability.</li>



<li>VAA (Verifiable Action Approvals): The Wormhole ecosystem&#8217;s core piece of data, comprising information supplied by xDapps as well as contact information via alerts. The VAA is signed by the guardian; authentication requires 13/19 signatures.</li>
</ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Products</h2>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Portal Bridge</strong></h3>



<p>Wormhole&#8217;s Portal Bridge is a cross-chain bridge project. To transfer assets across blockchains, Portal Bridge will use a lock and mint method.</p>



<p>When a user transfers token/coin X from chain A to chain B, Portal employs Wormhole&#8217;s &#8220;lock &amp; mint&#8221; approach, in which they lock the original token in chain A in a smart contract and mint-create (mint) token X&#8217; (wrapped token) in chain B.</p>



<p>The lock and mint mechanism may be easily mimicked as follows:</p>



<ul>
<li>People transfer ETH (Ethereum) using the Portal.</li>



<li>This ETH will be protected by the smart contract.</li>



<li>Locking ETH (wrapped ETH) on Chain B generates a new coin (target blockchain).</li>



<li>The wrapped ETH may then be exchanged for other tokens on chain B.</li>
</ul>



<p>Solana, Ethereum, Terra Classic, BNB Chain, Polygon, Avalanche, Oasis, Algorand, Aurora, Fantom, Karura, Acala, Near, Aptos, Celo….</p>



<p>For exchanging assets associated with Solana, Ethereum, and BNB Chain, Portal Bridge is most often employed.</p>



<p>With EVM Chain, the quantity of assets associated to Acala (a Polkadot parachain) has lately increased somewhat, accounting for roughly 5-9% of total bridge traffic on Portal.</p>



<p>Portal Bridge also operates under the following three entities:</p>



<p><strong>Transfers</strong></p>



<p>Portal must lock the original token on chain A and mint the wrapped token on chain B in order to move tokens from network A to network B. It is critical that the tokens on A first be verified locked. when minting is possible on B. Chain A facilitates this by locking the tokens and emitting a message indicating that the locking is complete.</p>



<p><strong>Attestation</strong></p>



<p>Key information is missing from the message delivery mechanism described above. Notwithstanding the fact that the action on thread B may rely on the cryptographic lock message on thread A. It has no means of knowing what the token that is being locked is. Portal Bridge offers token attestation to address this issue. Chain A sends a message with address information that thread B may use to determine the name, symbol, and decimal precision of the token address.</p>



<p><strong>Relayers</strong></p>



<p>Token bridging must be completed on the destination chain, which will necessitate payment of transaction fees in the native currency of that chain. Wormhole offers a system that enables Relayers to perform the last step and pay the charge on behalf of the user since many users initiating the transfer may not have any cash.</p>



<p>This technique works by enabling the user to define how much of the token they want to transmit as a charge. When a VAA transfer is sent, the contract pays the charge to the Relayers rather than the user.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1337-1024x470.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="470" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1337-1024x470.png" alt="Wormhole Review: The Most Powerful Cross-chain Bridge Protocol" class="wp-image-196050" srcset="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1337-1024x470.png 1024w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1337-300x138.png 300w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1337-768x352.png 768w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1337-1536x705.png 1536w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1337-750x344.png 750w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1337-1140x523.png 1140w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1337.png 1600w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Wormhole Review: The Most Powerful Cross-chain Bridge Protocol 5"></a></figure></div>


<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>NFT Bridge Portal</strong></h3>



<p>NFT Bridge is a location where users may transfer NFTs across chains like Ethereum, Solana, BNB Chain, Polygon, Avalanche, Fantom, Oasis, Karura, Aptos, and Celo.</p>



<p>NFT Portal presently supports the ERC-721 (metadata) token standard and the SPL token standard.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>NativeSwap</strong></h3>



<p>Wormhole created a cross-chain money transfer mechanism using Stablecoin UST in early 2022. Nevertheless, due to the failure of UST in the middle of the year, this idea was scrapped.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1336.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="566" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1336-1024x566.png" alt="Wormhole Review: The Most Powerful Cross-chain Bridge Protocol" class="wp-image-196049" srcset="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1336-1024x566.png 1024w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1336-300x166.png 300w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1336-768x424.png 768w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1336-1536x849.png 1536w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1336-750x414.png 750w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1336-1140x630.png 1140w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1336.png 1600w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Wormhole Review: The Most Powerful Cross-chain Bridge Protocol 6"></a></figure></div>


<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Carrier</strong></h3>



<p>Carrier, which debuted in early March 2023, is a Wormhole-based Bridge created by Automata Network. Carrier is now compatible with 12 blockchains, including prominent chains such as Solana, Ethereum, BNB Chain, and Polygon. Further features, such as swap functionalities and a 2FA protection mechanism to assure bridge security, will be progressively published on the Carrier development roadmap.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Roadmap</h2>



<p>Wormhole V1 was created in October 2020 by Certus One and other developers to connect Ethereum and Solana. Some developers have noticed increased consumer demand over time. Wormhole, a cross-chain communication mechanism that was introduced in August 2021, was the outcome.</p>



<p>As Wormhole progresses toward becoming a protocol that provides information communication solutions for market ventures, the team has restructured it such that it is no longer only a bridge.</p>



<p>Eventually, they decided to deploy Portal in early 2022 as a native bridge based on Wormhole&#8217;s technology.</p>



<p>The Portal Bridge and Wormhole development path is then described as follows:</p>



<ul>
<li>February 3, 2022: Wormhole exploited 120,000 WETH (equivalent to $324 million)</li>



<li>February 4, 2022: Wormhole replenishes lost funds with the help of Jump Trading</li>



<li>February 12, 2022: Open the Bug Bounty Program worth 10 million USD</li>



<li>May 9, 2022: TVL drops from $4.9 billion to $600 million just one month after Terra&#8217;s crash</li>



<li>December 2022: Hashflow partners with Wormhole</li>



<li>March 2023: Integrate native USDC and Circle CCTP</li>
</ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Investors &amp; Partners</h2>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Investors</strong></h3>



<p>Jump Trading is the investment fund that played a vital part in restoring money lost in the previous $325 million assault on Wormhole. Jump Trading, being one of the largest donors to Wormhole at the time, compensated for the losses by purchasing roughly $300 million in ETH on the market.</p>



<p>Prior to Jump Trading, there were a variety of investment funds in Wormhole that could be tracked, including Chorus One, Arrington Capital, Big Brain Holdings, and others.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Partners</strong></h3>



<p>Several projects from other ecosystems have integrated with Wormhole to enable Wormhole token wrap assets, including Solend, Trader Joe, Taiga, Raydium, Klap, and others.</p>



<p>Presently, the list of supporting projects from the 19 chains that Wormhole is integrating includes more than 50 distinct projects. Portal Bridge will thereby profit from the parent company&#8217;s collaborations.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Conclusion</h2>



<p>Wormhole is one of the most popular cross-chain platforms with a big user base. Nonetheless, there are still several security threats.</p>



<p>This may aid in the growth of the Wormhole ecosystem. Transferring assets across blockchains has emerged as a critical need in the cryptocurrency business. The use of cross-chain communications technologies may raise demand for the platform.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER: </em></strong><em>The information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>



<p>Join us to keep track of news:&nbsp;<a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Harold</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Coincu News</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1334-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Weekly Top Crypto News (June 12 &#8211; June 18)</title>
		<link>https://news.coincu.com/196022-weekly-top-crypto-news-june-12-june-18/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Harold]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 14:11:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto Recap]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Atomic Wallet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blackrock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coindesk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[highlights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uniswap]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US CPI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.coincu.com/?p=196022</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The crypto market has seen the development of a slew of significant news impacting the Bitcoin price during the last week]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The crypto market has seen the development of a slew of significant news impacting the Bitcoin price during the last week. First, the US CPI continued to decrease, prompting the Fed to pause interest rate hikes for the first time in ten years. Nevertheless, the biggest cryptocurrency rebounded when BlackRock decided to submit an application with the SEC to create a Bitcoin ETF.</strong> <strong>Here, let&#8217;s review this week&#8217;s top crypto news with Coincu!</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1331.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="683" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1331-1024x683.png" alt="Weekly Top Crypto News (June 12 - June 18)" class="wp-image-196023" srcset="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1331-1024x683.png 1024w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1331-300x200.png 300w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1331-768x512.png 768w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1331-750x500.png 750w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1331-1140x760.png 1140w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1331.png 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Weekly Top Crypto News (June 12 - June 18) 7"></a></figure></div>


<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Fed Doesn&#8217;t Raise Interest Rates</h2>



<p>During today&#8217;s FOMC meeting, the Fed decided not to increase its federal funds&#8217; rate, halting a continuous string of aggressive rises stretching back to March 2022. The central bank needs time to examine the effect of its prior monetary tightening actions on the economy.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-wp-embed is-provider-coincu-news wp-block-embed-coincu-news"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="wp-embedded-content" data-secret="C7Otbpxvwf"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/195238-fed-doesnt-raise-interest-rates/">Fed Doesn&#8217;t Raise Interest Rates, Bitcoin Stabilizes At $26,000</a></blockquote><iframe class="wp-embedded-content" sandbox="allow-scripts" security="restricted" title="&#8220;Fed Doesn&#8217;t Raise Interest Rates, Bitcoin Stabilizes At $26,000&#8221; &#8212; CoinCu News" src="https://news.coincu.com/195238-fed-doesnt-raise-interest-rates/embed/#?secret=19VASVn503#?secret=C7Otbpxvwf" data-secret="C7Otbpxvwf" width="500" height="282" frameborder="0" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no"></iframe>
</div></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">BlackRock To Expand More Bitcoin ETF With New Filing Application</h2>



<p>BlackRock, the world&#8217;s largest asset manager, is on the verge of launching a Bitcoin ETF. With the ETF, the massive asset management will use Coinbase Custody and the crypto exchange&#8217;s spot market data. It was unclear if the ETF would be spot or future.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-wp-embed is-provider-coincu-news wp-block-embed-coincu-news"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="wp-embedded-content" data-secret="JM99mGOtYw"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/195477-blackrock-to-expand-more-bitcoin-etf/">BlackRock To Expand More Bitcoin ETF With New Filing Application</a></blockquote><iframe class="wp-embedded-content" sandbox="allow-scripts" security="restricted" title="&#8220;BlackRock To Expand More Bitcoin ETF With New Filing Application&#8221; &#8212; CoinCu News" src="https://news.coincu.com/195477-blackrock-to-expand-more-bitcoin-etf/embed/#?secret=CpLIrSJscv#?secret=JM99mGOtYw" data-secret="JM99mGOtYw" width="500" height="282" frameborder="0" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no"></iframe>
</div></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">USDT Is Under Selling Pressure As It Loses 0.3% Of The Value</h2>



<p>Tether&#8217;s USDT is currently struggling with market volatility. The Curve 3Pool&#8217;s balance should be 33.33% for each of its three stablecoins, however, Tether&#8217;s balance has risen to well almost 70%. This suggests that traders are selling a lot of USDT for DAI or USDC, causing the stablecoin to de-peg to $0.9975.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-wp-embed is-provider-coincu-news wp-block-embed-coincu-news"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="wp-embedded-content" data-secret="FEdh6ZD3pl"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/195363-usdt-is-under-selling-pressure/">USDT Is Under Selling Pressure As It Loses 0.3% Of The Value</a></blockquote><iframe class="wp-embedded-content" sandbox="allow-scripts" security="restricted" title="&#8220;USDT Is Under Selling Pressure As It Loses 0.3% Of The Value&#8221; &#8212; CoinCu News" src="https://news.coincu.com/195363-usdt-is-under-selling-pressure/embed/#?secret=FSbm9avKkh#?secret=FEdh6ZD3pl" data-secret="FEdh6ZD3pl" width="500" height="282" frameborder="0" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no"></iframe>
</div></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">CoinDesk Obtains Tether’s FOIL Documents Revealing After USDT Lost Its Peg</h2>



<p>Tether’s FOIL documents reveal important information about its banking relationships, asset-backing strategy, and reliance on commercial paper. CoinDesk stands by the integrity of its reporting on Tether, including the release of FOIL documents obtained after a court dispute, which coincided with USDT losing its peg.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-wp-embed is-provider-coincu-news wp-block-embed-coincu-news"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="wp-embedded-content" data-secret="URdh9YENG6"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/195873-coindesk-obtains-tethers-foil-document/">CoinDesk Obtains Tether&#8217;s FOIL Documents Revealing After USDT Lost Its Peg</a></blockquote><iframe class="wp-embedded-content" sandbox="allow-scripts" security="restricted" title="&#8220;CoinDesk Obtains Tether&#8217;s FOIL Documents Revealing After USDT Lost Its Peg&#8221; &#8212; CoinCu News" src="https://news.coincu.com/195873-coindesk-obtains-tethers-foil-document/embed/#?secret=jv1ty8QvR5#?secret=URdh9YENG6" data-secret="URdh9YENG6" width="500" height="282" frameborder="0" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no"></iframe>
</div></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Binance Is Leaving The Netherlands From July 17 After Legal Difficulties</h2>



<p>Binance is departing the Netherlands after failing to get a VASP license from the Dutch regulator. Dutch citizens will only be permitted to withdraw monies from the exchange as of July 17. The company said that it has engaged in a complete registration application procedure with the authorities as a virtual asset service provider.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-wp-embed is-provider-coincu-news wp-block-embed-coincu-news"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="wp-embedded-content" data-secret="VzSV7G3YAO"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/195731-binance-is-leaving-the-netherlands/">Binance Is Leaving The Netherlands From July 17 After Legal Difficulties</a></blockquote><iframe class="wp-embedded-content" sandbox="allow-scripts" security="restricted" title="&#8220;Binance Is Leaving The Netherlands From July 17 After Legal Difficulties&#8221; &#8212; CoinCu News" src="https://news.coincu.com/195731-binance-is-leaving-the-netherlands/embed/#?secret=CgY9TNPPXf#?secret=VzSV7G3YAO" data-secret="VzSV7G3YAO" width="500" height="282" frameborder="0" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no"></iframe>
</div></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Binance Under Investigation In France For Serious Money Laundering</h2>



<p>French authorities are investigating Binance for an &#8220;illegal&#8221; supply of digital asset services and aggravated money laundering. Binance is accused of soliciting French clients via its local branch in violation of French law until 2022. The exchange recently announced its departure from the Netherlands after failing to get an AML license.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-wp-embed is-provider-coincu-news wp-block-embed-coincu-news"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="wp-embedded-content" data-secret="xsLgGv7eaW"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/195767-binance-under-investigation-in-france/">BREAKING: Binance Under Investigation In France For Serious Money Laundering</a></blockquote><iframe class="wp-embedded-content" sandbox="allow-scripts" security="restricted" title="&#8220;BREAKING: Binance Under Investigation In France For Serious Money Laundering&#8221; &#8212; CoinCu News" src="https://news.coincu.com/195767-binance-under-investigation-in-france/embed/#?secret=UKB5ZnmcKj#?secret=xsLgGv7eaW" data-secret="xsLgGv7eaW" width="500" height="282" frameborder="0" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no"></iframe>
</div></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Binance.US Is Separated From Binance Holdings After Court Approved SEC Deal</h2>



<p>Binance.US, Binance and the SEC have come to a mutual agreement. Binance.US will ensure that no authorities from the global exchange, Binance Holdings, have access to private keys for wallets or hardware wallets. The deal was approved by Judge Amy Berman Jackson.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-wp-embed is-provider-coincu-news wp-block-embed-coincu-news"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="wp-embedded-content" data-secret="1klWyqdZfI"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/195953-binanceus-is-separated-from-binance/">Official: Binance.US Is Separated From Binance Holdings After Court Approved SEC Deal</a></blockquote><iframe class="wp-embedded-content" sandbox="allow-scripts" security="restricted" title="&#8220;Official: Binance.US Is Separated From Binance Holdings After Court Approved SEC Deal&#8221; &#8212; CoinCu News" src="https://news.coincu.com/195953-binanceus-is-separated-from-binance/embed/#?secret=BQNidOlCnP#?secret=1klWyqdZfI" data-secret="1klWyqdZfI" width="500" height="282" frameborder="0" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no"></iframe>
</div></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Ripple Lawsuit&#8217;s Hinman Docs Are Disclosed</h2>



<p>Hinman materials and speeches, including Ripple&#8217;s Rule 56.1 declaration, are now accessible to the public. The paper indicated that the SEC sought advice from Vitalik Buterin throughout the process that led to the contentious speech. On June 4, however, then-SEC director Hinman shared a draft of the speech with the commission&#8217;s division chiefs.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-wp-embed is-provider-coincu-news wp-block-embed-coincu-news"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="wp-embedded-content" data-secret="9Ll0XITTZN"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/194782-ripple-lawsuits-hinman-docs-are-disclosed-xrp-rises-over-7/">Ripple Lawsuit&#8217;s Hinman Docs Are Disclosed, XRP Rises Over 7%</a></blockquote><iframe class="wp-embedded-content" sandbox="allow-scripts" security="restricted" title="&#8220;Ripple Lawsuit&#8217;s Hinman Docs Are Disclosed, XRP Rises Over 7%&#8221; &#8212; CoinCu News" src="https://news.coincu.com/194782-ripple-lawsuits-hinman-docs-are-disclosed-xrp-rises-over-7/embed/#?secret=K5aVJDmbin#?secret=9Ll0XITTZN" data-secret="9Ll0XITTZN" width="500" height="282" frameborder="0" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no"></iframe>
</div></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Uniswap Labs Revealing New Version Of Uniswap</h2>



<p>Uniswap Labs has revealed its plans for the next version of its cryptocurrency trading platform, Uniswap v4. The Uniswap community will administer the exchange. The developer intends to improve the DEX&#8217;s coin-swapping capabilities with the v4 update by integrating &#8220;hooks&#8221; and unique liquidity pools.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-wp-embed is-provider-coincu-news wp-block-embed-coincu-news"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="wp-embedded-content" data-secret="wfDxV6IeFV"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/194785-uniswap-labs-revealing-new-version/">HOT: Uniswap Labs Revealing New Version Of Uniswap, UNI Jumps Over 6%</a></blockquote><iframe class="wp-embedded-content" sandbox="allow-scripts" security="restricted" title="&#8220;HOT: Uniswap Labs Revealing New Version Of Uniswap, UNI Jumps Over 6%&#8221; &#8212; CoinCu News" src="https://news.coincu.com/194785-uniswap-labs-revealing-new-version/embed/#?secret=sKoX0PjDYH#?secret=wfDxV6IeFV" data-secret="wfDxV6IeFV" width="500" height="282" frameborder="0" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no"></iframe>
</div></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Atomic Wallet Hack Is Getting More Complicated</h2>



<p>In a recent robbery impacting Atomic Wallet customers, North Korean hackers stole more than $100 million in cryptocurrency. The hackers targeted over 5,500 digital wallets, according to the business, and were members of the North Korean cybercrime ring known as the Lazarus Group. The Atomic Wallet team is also working with the police in Estonia, where the firm is registered.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-wp-embed is-provider-coincu-news wp-block-embed-coincu-news"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="wp-embedded-content" data-secret="JMFLjjDBVq"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/194945-atomic-wallet-hack-more-complicated/">Atomic Wallet Hack Is Getting More Complicated</a></blockquote><iframe class="wp-embedded-content" sandbox="allow-scripts" security="restricted" title="&#8220;Atomic Wallet Hack Is Getting More Complicated&#8221; &#8212; CoinCu News" src="https://news.coincu.com/194945-atomic-wallet-hack-more-complicated/embed/#?secret=DWDjT5EgLZ#?secret=JMFLjjDBVq" data-secret="JMFLjjDBVq" width="500" height="282" frameborder="0" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no"></iframe>
</div></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">EigenLayer Restaking Has Been Deployed On Ethereum Mainnet</h2>



<p>DeFi platform EigenLayer announced it had implemented its reset protocol on the Ethereum mainnet. This protocol allows users to staking ETH by depositing liquidity staking tokens such as Lido stETH (stETH), Rocket Pool ETH (rETH), and Coinbase Wrapped staking ETH (cbETH). To date, the project has received $64.5 million in funding, with a valuation of $500 million.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-wp-embed is-provider-coincu-news wp-block-embed-coincu-news"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="wp-embedded-content" data-secret="tSG5my5tMS"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/195299-eigenlayer-restaking-deployed-ethereum/">Important: EigenLayer Restaking Has Been Deployed On Ethereum Mainnet</a></blockquote><iframe class="wp-embedded-content" sandbox="allow-scripts" security="restricted" title="&#8220;Important: EigenLayer Restaking Has Been Deployed On Ethereum Mainnet&#8221; &#8212; CoinCu News" src="https://news.coincu.com/195299-eigenlayer-restaking-deployed-ethereum/embed/#?secret=85x9lwR5jf#?secret=tSG5my5tMS" data-secret="tSG5my5tMS" width="500" height="282" frameborder="0" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no"></iframe>
</div></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Voyager Allows Users To Withdraw Within 35% Cryptocurrency Limit This Month</h2>



<p>After almost a year of freezing, Voyager allows users to withdraw part of their cryptocurrency for the first time. From June 20 to July 5, creditors can withdraw about 35% of crypto. Initial cryptocurrency distributions will be made to creditors within three to seven calendar days of submitting a withdrawal request.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-wp-embed is-provider-coincu-news wp-block-embed-coincu-news"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="wp-embedded-content" data-secret="1bmiZCtcWh"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/195285-voyager-users-withdraw-35-cryptocurrency/">Voyager Allows Users To Withdraw Within 35% Cryptocurrency Limit This Month</a></blockquote><iframe class="wp-embedded-content" sandbox="allow-scripts" security="restricted" title="&#8220;Voyager Allows Users To Withdraw Within 35% Cryptocurrency Limit This Month&#8221; &#8212; CoinCu News" src="https://news.coincu.com/195285-voyager-users-withdraw-35-cryptocurrency/embed/#?secret=XpoME7q4KE#?secret=1bmiZCtcWh" data-secret="1bmiZCtcWh" width="500" height="282" frameborder="0" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no"></iframe>
</div></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Celsius Suggests New Plan Sell Altcoins For BTC And ETH From July 1</h2>



<p>Celsius intends to convert all altcoins except Bitcoin and Ethereum into this currency with court approval. This will not affect tokens held in withholding or escrow accounts, and the sale will begin on July 1. The filing states that the conversion will not affect any creditor&#8217;s claims.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-wp-embed is-provider-coincu-news wp-block-embed-coincu-news"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="wp-embedded-content" data-secret="HywEva9gvd"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/195538-celsius-suggests-new-plan-sell-altcoins/">Caution: Celsius Suggests New Plan Sell Altcoins For BTC And ETH From July 1</a></blockquote><iframe class="wp-embedded-content" sandbox="allow-scripts" security="restricted" title="&#8220;Caution: Celsius Suggests New Plan Sell Altcoins For BTC And ETH From July 1&#8221; &#8212; CoinCu News" src="https://news.coincu.com/195538-celsius-suggests-new-plan-sell-altcoins/embed/#?secret=53hsiGVA7n#?secret=HywEva9gvd" data-secret="HywEva9gvd" width="500" height="282" frameborder="0" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no"></iframe>
</div></figure>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER: </em></strong><em>The information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>



<p>Join us to keep track of news:&nbsp;<a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Harold</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Coincu</strong> <strong>News</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1332-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bored Ape Kennel Club Review: Unique Collection Based On BAYC</title>
		<link>https://news.coincu.com/195995-bored-ape-kennel-club-review/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Harold]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 11:23:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Reviews]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BAKC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BAYC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bored Ape Kennel Club]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ERC-721]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LooksRare]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mutant Ape Yacht Club]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OpenSea]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Review]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Yuga Labs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.coincu.com/?p=195995</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Since its inception in June 2021, the Bored Ape Kennel Club (BAKC) initiative has made headlines, and its popularity shows no signs of abating. ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>When it comes to crypto collections, not all are made in the same manner. The Bored Ape Yacht Club NFT collection, in particular, is gradually becoming a household brand, not just among those who already know about it but also among the mainstream media. With its expanding popularity, it, like CryptoPunks, is progressively usurping the throne of the leader.</strong></h5>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Since its inception in June 2021, the Bored Ape Kennel Club (BAKC) initiative has made headlines, and its popularity shows no signs of abating. BAKC NFTs, an extension of the Bored Ape Yacht Club project, employ the ERC-721 token standard on the Ethereum blockchain to verify scarcity and monitor NFT ownership.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1329-1024x576.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="576" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1329-1024x576.png" alt="Bored Ape Kennel Club Review: Unique Collection Based On BAYC" class="wp-image-196017" srcset="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1329-1024x576.png 1024w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1329-300x169.png 300w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1329-768x432.png 768w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1329-750x422.png 750w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1329-1140x641.png 1140w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1329.png 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Bored Ape Kennel Club Review: Unique Collection Based On BAYC 8"></a></figure></div>


<p>So, what makes Bored Ape Kennel Club unique? Let&#8217;s find out with Coincu through this article. We&#8217;ll look at the history of BAKC, the project&#8217;s purpose to promote social good, and how to buy BAKC NFTs. We&#8217;ll also give you the lowdown on web3&#8217;s favorite doggos to get you started in the fascinating world of BAKC NFTs.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">What is the Bored Ape Kennel Club?</h2>



<p>The Bored Ape Kennel Club (BAKC) is a collection of 9,602 NFTs developed using dog characters that share features with the Bored Ape Yacht Club (BAYC). Yuga Labs is the company&#8217;s owner. The BAKC set was released in June 2021, barely two months after the BAYC set.</p>



<p>This collection was created so that the monkey owners in the BAYC collection would have a companion character because the Yuga Labs crew adores dogs. As a result, they launched the BAKC collection. Yuga Labs guarantees that no more collections involving dog characters will be released in the future.</p>



<p>The Bored Ape Kennel Club is a novel new idea in the field of non-fungible tokens (NFTs). Every BAYC member may adopt a one-of-a-kind, procedurally created dog from the BAKC, which is held as an ERC-721 token on the Ethereum blockchain and hosted on IPFS. With a total of 9,602 NFTs accessible, each dog in the kennel club is unique and has over 170 potential qualities, some of which are more unusual than others.</p>



<p>Yuga Labs, noted for its high-quality and visually attractive designs, developed the artwork for the BAKC line. The collection includes a range of lovely doggos with distinct and attractive characteristics such as the back, backdrop, paws, hair, lips, and neck.</p>



<p>With a total volume of 262,192 ETH and a floor price of 3.74 ETH, the collection is a huge success. In conclusion, the NFTs from the Bored Ape Kennel Club are a fun, distinctive, and apparently attractive collection that will be highly sought after by NFT collectors and animal lovers alike. The BAKC is a must-have for anybody interested in the field of NFTs, with procedurally created dogs and high-quality artwork.</p>



<p>Overall, the Bored Ape Kennel Club is a novel and humorous idea that will appeal to both NFT collectors and animal enthusiasts. It&#8217;s a very valuable series because of the programmed creation of unique canines, and the artwork is guaranteed to please. The idea of having a companion animal is intriguing, and the fact that it&#8217;s free (you just have to pay for gas fee) is a huge plus for the current community.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1325.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="530" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1325-1024x530.png" alt="Bored Ape Kennel Club Review: Unique Collection Based On BAYC" class="wp-image-196013" srcset="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1325-1024x530.png 1024w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1325-300x155.png 300w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1325-768x398.png 768w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1325-750x388.png 750w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1325-1140x590.png 1140w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1325.png 1224w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Bored Ape Kennel Club Review: Unique Collection Based On BAYC 9"></a></figure></div>


<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Highlights</h2>



<p>BAKC has the following distinguishing features:</p>



<ul>
<li>Inherit the BAYC collection&#8217;s community and prosperity.</li>



<li>BAKC was not for sale and was only airdropped to BAYC holders, yet it nonetheless ranked among the top 20 most valuable NFT collections in the market.</li>



<li>Yuga Labs also gave BAKC holders an ApeCoin (APE) airdrop.</li>
</ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Traits</h2>



<p>The entire NFT collection is made up of over 170 different features ranging from coat color, eye and mouth position as well as various accessories like hats, glasses, shoes, etc. Each NFT is made up of 8 different attributes, including:</p>



<ul>
<li>Back has 16 different types including: Service Vest, Beer Kegs, Basketball Hoop,&#8230;</li>



<li>Background has 5 different types including: Swamp, Outhouse, SS Monke Biz,…</li>



<li>Eyes has 32 different categories including: Closed, Happy, Anime, Sad,…</li>



<li>Feet has 17 different types including: Cast, Rain Boots, Combat Boots,&#8230;</li>



<li>Fur has 16 different types including: Tan, Black, Brown,…</li>



<li>Head has 32 different types including: Sea Captain&#8217;s Hat, Fez, Cowboy Hat,…</li>



<li>Mouth has 36 different types including: Hot Dog, Beer Can, Bone,&#8230;</li>



<li>Neck has 23 different types including: BAYC Collar, Red Collar With Bone, Hawaiian Bandana,…</li>
</ul>



<p>Each attribute has a different number and rarity, of which the NFT with the Head attribute is the rarest Party Hat with only a maximum of 33.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1328.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="576" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1328-1024x576.png" alt="Bored Ape Kennel Club Review: Unique Collection Based On BAYC" class="wp-image-196016" srcset="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1328-1024x576.png 1024w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1328-300x169.png 300w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1328-768x432.png 768w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1328-750x422.png 750w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1328-1140x642.png 1140w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1328.png 1281w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Bored Ape Kennel Club Review: Unique Collection Based On BAYC 10"></a></figure></div>


<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color" id="section-3">Key Metric&nbsp;</h2>



<p>NFT Name: Bored Ape Kennel Club</p>



<ul>
<li>Ticker: BAKC</li>



<li>Blockchain: Ethereum</li>



<li>Token Standard: ERC-721</li>



<li>NFT Contract: 0xba30E5F9Bb24caa003E9f2f0497Ad287FDF95623</li>



<li>Max Supply: 9,602 BAKC</li>
</ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Ultility</h2>



<ul>
<li>Access to the BAYC ecosystem offers the ability to earn awards and get unique access to communities and events.</li>



<li>Using intellectual property (IP) rights, owners may monetize their NFTs by making and selling products that resembles the NFT.</li>



<li>Users will be able to Stake BAKC in the future to earn APE tokens.</li>



<li>Usage as an avatar on social networking sites.</li>



<li>JPEG&#8217;d, NFTfi, Arcade, and other NFT lending services accept it as collateral.</li>



<li>Holders of a Bored Ape Yacht Club NFT at the time of the airdrop received a BAKC NFT for free. The BAKC also airdrop ApeCoin to holders from time to time.</li>



<li>Each BAKC NFT comes with a set of randomized traits, making them unique.</li>



<li>The relative exclusivity of BAKC NFTs has led to a high value on the secondary market.</li>



<li>Compared to other NFTs in the Bored Ape Yacht Club pantheon, BAKC NFTs have a lower cost of entry.</li>



<li>Holders can trade their BAKC NFTs on the secondary market. This allows them to potentially earn a profit or match up with similar traits.</li>
</ul>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1327.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="678" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1327.png" alt="Bored Ape Kennel Club Review: Unique Collection Based On BAYC" class="wp-image-196015" srcset="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1327.png 1024w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1327-300x199.png 300w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1327-768x509.png 768w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1327-750x497.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Bored Ape Kennel Club Review: Unique Collection Based On BAYC 11"></a></figure></div>


<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Allocation &amp; sale schedule</h2>



<p>Yuga Labs decided to appreciate and encourage BAYC holders by gifting them 100% of NFT BAKC. This differs from the typical opening sale procedure used by previous collections.</p>



<p>Nevertheless, the opportunity to mint NFT BAKC for free is only available for one week. The NFT BAKC will never be formed if there are no holders of the BAYC mint at this period. Since 398 BAYC NFTs were not minted as NFT BAKCs, only 9,602 NFT BAKCs were produced.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">How to buy a Bored Ape Kennel Club NFT?</h2>



<p>To own BAKC NFT, users can buy on NFT exchanges such as Opensea, LooksRare, or X2Y2. In addition, there are synthetic NFT exchanges such as Blur, OpenSea Pro, etc., to make it more convenient for users to find and buy.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Team</h2>



<p>Yuga Labs, the company behind the successful Bored Ape Yacht Club (BAYC), Mutant Ape Yacht Club (MAYC), and Otherside collections, constructed and developed BAKC. Yuga Labs also bought two well-known NFT collections, CryptoPunks and Meebits NFT, from Larva Labs in March 2022.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Roadmap</h2>



<ul>
<li>June 17, 2021: Bored Ape Kennel Club officially launched and airdropped for BAYC holders.</li>



<li>July 28, 2021: Each BAKC holder will receive 1 basketball from Round21 company.</li>



<li>March 17, 2022: ApeCoin (APE) is airdropped to the entire BAYC family, including BAKC.</li>



<li>December 21, 2022: Yuga Labs announced that BAYC/MAYC if holding more BAKC will receive additional benefits when minting NFT commemorating the JimmytheMonkey movie.</li>



<li>January 19, 2023: BAYC/MAYC has an additional benefit to upgrade the event ticket limit if holding more BAKC.</li>
</ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Investors and partners</h2>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Investors</strong></h3>



<p>On March 22, 2022, Yuga Labs closed two rounds of investment for a total of $450 million. This transaction was spearheaded by a16z and drew the interest of several other investors, including Animoca Brands, LionTree, and others. Yuga Labs has shown the commercial attractiveness of BAKC. NFTs with a corporate value of up to $4 billion.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Partner</strong></h3>



<p>Currently, BAKC has not disclosed any information about its partners. We will update you as soon as we have the latest information about BAKC&#8217;s partner team.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Conclusion</h2>



<p>Finally, the Bored Ape Kennel Club has had a big influence on the world of NFT. They provide members with one-of-a-kind digital canines while also supporting animal welfare initiatives. The designers of the Bored Ape Yacht Club, Yuga Labs, have built a dedicated community that appreciates innovation, uniqueness, and pragmatism. The BAKC NFTs have offered an access point into the Yuga Labs ecosystem while also increasing the total value of the BAYC brand. BAKC NFTs&#8217; randomized features, exclusivity, and tradability have made them desirable to both traders and collectors.</p>



<p>While it is just a project created by Yuga Labs as an airdrop incentive for BAYC holders, BAKC connects with the community by donating revenues to groups that help dogs. This is still a rather outstanding collection growth, particularly since BAKC is 100% airdropped to BAYC with no mint cost necessary. Several BAYC holders sold them in the early phases, maybe because BAYC is a side collection and was airdropped as a free currency. BAKC, on the other hand, had a strong rebound in early 2022 and reached the ATH price at that time. The collecting price has reduced dramatically as a result of the NFT market&#8217;s collapse in 2023.</p>



<p>The BAKC airdrop, in which qualifying BAYC members got free NFTs to assist with animal welfare issues, was well accepted by the community and contributed to the project&#8217;s reputation. As compared to other NFTs in the Bored Ape Yacht Club collection, the BAKC NFTs feature a reduced entrance fee. Having a BAKC NFT allows you to possess a one-of-a-kind and exclusive digital canine that may gain value over time.</p>



<p>Ultimately, the Bored Ape Kennel Club has proved the ability of NFTs to promote relevant causes while providing its members with unique and valuable digital products. The BAKC collection has shown that digital dogs may be as precious and adored as their real counterparts. The Bored Ape Kennel Club exemplifies the importance of community and innovation in the realm of NFTs.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER: </em></strong><em>The information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>



<p>Join us to keep track of news:&nbsp;<a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Harold</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Coincu News</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1326-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hong Kong Allocates 50 Million Yuan To Foster Growth Of Web3.0 Enterprises At Cyberport</title>
		<link>https://news.coincu.com/195998-hong-kong-50-million-yuan-web3-cyberport/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chubbi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 11:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hong kong]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web 3.0]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.coincu.com/?p=195998</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Hong Kong Financial Secretary, Paul Chan, has announced the allocation of 50 million yuan to promote the development of Web3.0 enterprises at Cyberport. ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>Hong Kong&#8217;s Financial Secretary, Paul Chan, has allocated 50 million yuan to foster the development of Web3.0 enterprises at Cyberport, attracting over 150 companies in the past year.</em></li>



<li><em>Cyberport&#8217;s robust ecosystem includes successful start-ups, significant financing, and intellectual property projects, positioning it as a leading hub for technological innovation in Hong Kong. The government&#8217;s funding aims to accelerate research, development, and application innovations in the Web3.0 space.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Hong Kong Financial Secretary, Paul Chan, has announced the allocation of 50 million yuan to promote the development of Web3.0 enterprises at Cyberport.&nbsp;</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/2-1-1260x710-1-1024x577.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="577" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/2-1-1260x710-1-1024x577.png" alt="Hong Kong Allocates 50 Million Yuan To Foster Growth Of Web3.0 Enterprises At Cyberport" class="wp-image-196008" srcset="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/2-1-1260x710-1-1024x577.png 1024w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/2-1-1260x710-1-300x169.png 300w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/2-1-1260x710-1-768x433.png 768w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/2-1-1260x710-1-750x423.png 750w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/2-1-1260x710-1-1140x642.png 1140w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/2-1-1260x710-1.png 1260w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Hong Kong Allocates 50 Million Yuan To Foster Growth Of Web3.0 Enterprises At Cyberport 12"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>Over the past year, Cyberport has attracted more than 150 companies in the Web3.0 space, showcasing its position as a thriving hub for technological innovation. With significant financing and intellectual property projects, Cyberport aims to accelerate the growth of Web3.0 and blockchain-based ventures.</p>



<p>In an article penned by <a href="https://news.coincu.com/195623-hong-kong-is-poised-to-open-the-floodgates/">Hong Kong</a> Financial Secretary, Paul Chan, it was revealed that Cyberport, the city&#8217;s flagship technology hub, has successfully attracted over 150 companies operating in the Web3.0 sector. This remarkable achievement underscores Cyberport&#8217;s position as a leading center for cutting-edge technological innovation in Hong Kong.</p>



<p>With more than 1,900 community enterprises, Cyberport boasts a cumulative financing figure of over 35.7 billion yuan for start-ups and holds over 480 intellectual property projects. This robust ecosystem has nurtured the growth of various successful ventures, including six &#8220;unicorns&#8221; that have emerged from Cyberport&#8217;s community.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide size-full"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/63f5a93ea31057c4b4b58ff2.jpeg"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="720" height="404" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/63f5a93ea31057c4b4b58ff2.jpeg" alt="Hong Kong Allocates 50 Million Yuan To Foster Growth Of Web3.0 Enterprises At Cyberport" class="wp-image-196009" srcset="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/63f5a93ea31057c4b4b58ff2.jpeg 720w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/63f5a93ea31057c4b4b58ff2-300x168.jpeg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 720px) 100vw, 720px" title="Hong Kong Allocates 50 Million Yuan To Foster Growth Of Web3.0 Enterprises At Cyberport 13"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure>



<p>To further promote the advancement of Web3.0, the Hong Kong government has allocated 50 million yuan in the Financial Budget to Cyberport. This financial injection aims to fuel the growth of the third-generation Internet, which leverages blockchain technology as its underlying foundation. The funding is expected to drive increased research and development, as well as innovative applications in this evolving field.</p>



<p>Cyberport&#8217;s influence extends beyond attracting Web3.0 companies, as it has also fostered groundbreaking advancements in virtual asset trading and other sectors. Last year, one of the community&#8217;s companies became the second licensed virtual asset trading platform recognized by the Securities and Futures Commission in Hong Kong. Moreover, the hub has witnessed successful initial public offerings (IPOs) of tech-driven start-ups, such as a smart logistics company and a travel platform.</p>



<p>The allocation of 50 million yuan by the Hong Kong government to Cyberport underscores the commitment to supporting the growth of Web3.0 enterprises. With over 150 companies already operating in this space, Cyberport&#8217;s thriving ecosystem and strong financial backing will continue to drive technological innovation, research, and application development in the Web3.0 sector.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER: </em></strong><em>The Information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>



<p>Join us to keep track of news: <a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Chubbi</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Coincu News</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ban-sao-cua-Noi-dung-doan-van-ban-cua-ban-3-2-1024x731.jpg" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/jpeg" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Takes Action Against Fraudulent Entity In Nigeria, CZ Warns Users</title>
		<link>https://news.coincu.com/195996-binance-against-fraudulent-entity-nigeria/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chubbi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 11:04:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Changpeng Zhao]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CZ]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[market]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.coincu.com/?p=195996</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In a recent development, Binance founder Changpeng Zhao, known as CZ, took to Twitter to address a fraudulent entity operating under the name "Binance Nigeria Limited." ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>Binance founder CZ issues a suspension notice to &#8220;Binance Nigeria Limited,&#8221; a fraudulent entity operating in Nigeria, urging them to cease their operations immediately.</em></li>



<li><em>Nigerian Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) previously declared the entity as illegal and not registered, leading to Binance&#8217;s swift action against it to protect its reputation and warn users against trusting any information associated with the fraudulent entity.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>In a recent development, Binance founder Changpeng Zhao, known as CZ, took to Twitter to address a fraudulent entity operating under the name &#8220;Binance Nigeria Limited.&#8221;&nbsp;</strong></h5>



<figure class="wp-block-image aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Anh-chup-Man-hinh-2023-06-18-luc-17.52.29-1024x678.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="678" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Anh-chup-Man-hinh-2023-06-18-luc-17.52.29-1024x678.png" alt="Binance Takes Action Against Fraudulent Entity In Nigeria, CZ Warns Users
" class="wp-image-196001" srcset="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Anh-chup-Man-hinh-2023-06-18-luc-17.52.29-1024x678.png 1024w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Anh-chup-Man-hinh-2023-06-18-luc-17.52.29-300x199.png 300w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Anh-chup-Man-hinh-2023-06-18-luc-17.52.29-768x509.png 768w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Anh-chup-Man-hinh-2023-06-18-luc-17.52.29-750x497.png 750w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Anh-chup-Man-hinh-2023-06-18-luc-17.52.29-1140x755.png 1140w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Anh-chup-Man-hinh-2023-06-18-luc-17.52.29.png 1256w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Binance Takes Action Against Fraudulent Entity In Nigeria, CZ Warns Users 14"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure>



<p>CZ stated that Binance has issued a suspension notice to this entity, urging them to cease their operations immediately. Furthermore, he warned users not to trust any information associated with this fraudulent entity, advising them to rely solely on official announcements from the platform.</p>



<p>This action comes after the Nigerian Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) publicly declared that Binance Nigeria Limited is not registered with or regulated by the commission. As a result, the SEC classified the entity&#8217;s operations in Nigeria as illegal. The announcement by the SEC raised concerns regarding the legitimacy and compliance of the entity, prompting the firm to take swift action against it.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Binance have issued cease &amp; desist notice to the scammer entity &quot;Binance Nigeria Limited&quot;.<br><br>Don&#39;t believe everything you read in the news. <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f937-200d-2642-fe0f.png" alt="🤷‍♂️" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>&mdash; CZ <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f536.png" alt="🔶" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Binance (@cz_binance) <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1670369403223900160?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener">June 18, 2023</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>Binance, one of the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency exchanges, is known for its commitment to regulatory compliance and the security of its users. The suspension notice serves as a strong stance against fraudulent entities attempting to operate under the brand in unauthorized ways. By issuing this notice, the platform aims to protect its reputation and prevent potential harm to users in Nigeria.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/609fc160-0773-11ee-b8c1-cdc7c25c1cba.jpeg"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="640" height="360" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/609fc160-0773-11ee-b8c1-cdc7c25c1cba.jpeg" alt="Binance Takes Action Against Fraudulent Entity In Nigeria, CZ Warns Users
" class="wp-image-196002" srcset="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/609fc160-0773-11ee-b8c1-cdc7c25c1cba.jpeg 640w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/609fc160-0773-11ee-b8c1-cdc7c25c1cba-300x169.jpeg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px" title="Binance Takes Action Against Fraudulent Entity In Nigeria, CZ Warns Users 15"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure>



<p>CZ&#8217;s tweet acts as a cautionary message to users, emphasizing the importance of verifying information from official sources and being vigilant against potential scams. Users are advised to exercise caution when engaging with any entity claiming to be associated with the Nigeria Limited and to report any suspicious activities to the appropriate authorities.</p>



<p>As the cryptocurrency industry continues to grow, regulatory compliance remains a crucial aspect. <a href="https://news.coincu.com/195953-binanceus-is-separated-from-binance/">Binance</a>&#8216;s proactive approach in addressing this fraudulent entity demonstrates its commitment to maintaining a secure and trustworthy ecosystem for its users. By taking swift action and issuing a suspension notice, the firm aims to safeguard its reputation and protect users from potential fraudulent activities.</p>



<p>As the situation unfolds, Binance will continue to work closely with relevant authorities and take necessary steps to ensure compliance with regulations and provide a safe environment for its global user base.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER: </em></strong><em>The Information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>



<p>Join us to keep track of news: <a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Chubbi</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Coincu News</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ban-sao-cua-Noi-dung-doan-van-ban-cua-ban-1-2-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mutant Ape NFT Review: The Breakthrough From BAYC</title>
		<link>https://news.coincu.com/195983-mutant-ape-nft-review/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Harold]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 09:52:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Reviews]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BAYC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bored Ape Yacht Club]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MAYC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mutant ape]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Serum M1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Serum M2]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Serum Mega]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Yuga Labs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.coincu.com/?p=195983</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[One of the better instances of the growth of NFT profile images, PFP NFTs, and sets of NFTs is Mutant Ape Yacht Club (MAYC) NFT.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>After its peak in 2021, NFT collections have grown in popularity. One of the better instances of the growth of NFT profile images, PFP NFTs, and sets of NFTs is Mutant Ape Yacht Club (MAYC) NFT. This collection is still in existence today. The MAYC collection is notable for building on the basis of the Bored Ape Yacht Club NFT collection.</strong></h5>



<p>MAYC NFT is the successor to Bored Ape Yacht Club NFT, and the sales volume plainly demonstrates its popularity. The following article offers an overview of the MAYC NFT collection, as well as its history and technological background. You may also learn about the several aspects that influence the value of Mutant Ape NFT. Additionally, you might consider the specifics of the Mutant Apes project&#8217;s likely future trajectory.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1323.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="341" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1323-1024x341.png" alt="Mutant Ape NFT Review: The Breakthrough From BAYC" class="wp-image-195989" srcset="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1323-1024x341.png 1024w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1323-300x100.png 300w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1323-768x256.png 768w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1323-750x250.png 750w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1323-1140x380.png 1140w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1323.png 1500w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Mutant Ape NFT Review: The Breakthrough From BAYC 16"></a></figure></div>


<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">What is Mutant Ape Yacht Club?</h2>



<p>The Mutant Ape NFT collection was completely sold out within hours of its release in August 2021. The Mutant Ape Yacht Club collection (MAYC) was built with long-term aims in mind by Yuga Labs, the company behind the famous Bored Ape Yacht Club or BAYC NFTs. The creators intended to build a media empire purely on NFT, with BAYC NFT being the first product delivered. Moreover, Mutant Ape NFT has been a significant milestone for the Bored Apes ecology, with the explicit purpose of drawing more people to the BAYC community.</p>



<p>MAYC and BAYC are NFTs built on top of Ethereum. This collection&#8217;s primary topic is really distinctive, talking about monkey characters, but now that this monkey has been mutated, the animation will have a lot more sad traits than BAYC. No one Mutant Ape NFT is alike, with distinguishing traits such as various colored accessories, caps, and feathers.</p>



<p>Mutant Apes has also shown promising success, with sales of more than a billion dollars in less than a year. Since its first release, the Mutant Ape Yacht Club NFT collection has grown to become one of the pioneering PFP NFT projects. The Bored Ape environment had just BAYC NFT and the Bored Ape Kennel Club prior to the MAYC collection. Yuga Labs launched these projects in short succession, with BAYC NFT in April 2021 and Bored Ape Kennel Club in June 2021. Yuga Labs offered the Mutant Ape collection using the new method as the NFT market increased.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1321.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="809" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1321-1024x809.png" alt="Mutant Ape NFT Review: The Breakthrough From BAYC" class="wp-image-195987" srcset="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1321-1024x809.png 1024w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1321-300x237.png 300w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1321-768x607.png 768w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1321-750x593.png 750w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1321-1140x901.png 1140w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1321.png 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Mutant Ape NFT Review: The Breakthrough From BAYC 17"></a></figure></div>


<p>MAYC was introduced in August 2021 and is regarded as an essential expansion of BAYC; it was developed to draw more individuals to the BAYC environment. To improve the image of BAYC and attract more people, the developer Yuga Labs had to come up with all types of novel and creative solutions, and the MAYC outcome was created via the unique serum process.</p>



<p>Each MAYC will be created by combining an original BAYC with a procedure described by Yuga Labs as &#8220;Using Mutant Serum to Mutation BAYC.&#8221; To put it another way, there will be three serums available that will enable BAYC holders to &#8220;convert&#8221; their current Bored Apes into the new Mutant Apes.</p>



<p>The Mutant Ape Yacht Club collection of NFTs is tied to the original NFT Ape. The collection has a total of 20,000 NFTs, 10,000 of which are reserved for BAYC holders. Additional 10,000 NFTs were available for purchase through the Dutch auction process. Mutant Apes are developed by injecting a vial of &#8216;Mutant Serum&#8217; into an existing Bored Ape NFT.</p>



<p>Holders of Bored Ape NFT may freely mix their NFT with Serum NFT through smart contract integration. Even after redeeming the NFT Mutant Ape and destroying the Serum token, the pairing mechanism remains operational. Moreover, the coupling produces a unique, mutant-inspired NFT with features comparable to the original NFT Bored Ape. The concatenation has no effect on the initial BAYC NFT, and you now have two distinct NFTs.</p>



<p>The uniqueness of Mutant Ape Yacht Club is determined by numerous Mutant Ape features that distinguish them. Unusual qualities may ensure that an NFT is more valued. The M2 stunt jacket trait, for example, is only present in 0.4% of Mutant Apes species. As a result, Mutant Apes with M2 stunt jacket is more likely than other NFTs in the collection to sell for a greater price.</p>



<p>Under the Mutant Apes details, you can discover information about the different features as well as the rarity of the MAYC NFT as a percentage. In OpenSea, the traits tab for related NFT Mutants or Bored Ape might help you understand the rarity of NFT Ape Bored.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1320.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="576" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1320-1024x576.png" alt="Mutant Ape NFT Review: The Breakthrough From BAYC" class="wp-image-195986" srcset="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1320-1024x576.png 1024w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1320-300x169.png 300w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1320-768x432.png 768w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1320-1536x864.png 1536w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1320-750x422.png 750w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1320-1140x641.png 1140w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1320.png 1600w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Mutant Ape NFT Review: The Breakthrough From BAYC 18"></a></figure></div>


<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Traits</h2>



<p>The Mutant Ape Yacht Club collection will be split into three different mutants by giving BAYCs a serum to drink:</p>



<ul>
<li>Serum M1 is the cheapest, and currently, there are still 4516 NFTs on the market.</li>



<li>Serum M2 is a bit more expensive than M1 and still has 1409 NFT left.</li>



<li>Serum M3, aka Mega Mutant, has only 8 NFTs minted, and currently, there are only 2 NFTs on the market.</li>
</ul>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1324.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="800" height="800" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1324.png" alt="Mutant Ape NFT Review: The Breakthrough From BAYC" class="wp-image-195990" srcset="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1324.png 800w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1324-300x300.png 300w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1324-150x150.png 150w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1324-768x768.png 768w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1324-75x75.png 75w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1324-350x350.png 350w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1324-750x750.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 800px) 100vw, 800px" title="Mutant Ape NFT Review: The Breakthrough From BAYC 19"></a></figure></div>


<p>The identifying features of NFT MAYC are:</p>



<ul>
<li>Background: M1 Yellow, M1 Purple, M1 Orange,.. There are 16 different background colors for M1 and M2.</li>



<li>Clothes: M2 Black T, M1 Hip Hop, M1 Blue Dress,… There are 86 different clothes for M1 and M2 redesigned from the original BAYC.</li>



<li>Earring: M1 Silver Hop, M1 Gold Hoop, M1 Gold Stud,… There are 12 different types of earrings in total.</li>



<li>Eyes: M1 3D, M2 Bloodshoot, M1 Heart,… There are 46 different eye colors with different expressions.</li>



<li>Fur: M1 Dark Brown, M1 Brown, M1 Black,… MAYC has a total of 36 different coat colors.</li>



<li>Hat: M1 Fez, M1 Halo, M2 Cownboy Hat,… there are 72 different hats used by MAYCs.</li>



<li>Mouth: M1 Bored, M2 Grin, M1 Bore Pipe,… there are 68 different mouth styles.</li>



<li>Name: These are MAYCs with special names and only one NFT per name.</li>
</ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color" id="section-3">MAYC NFT Key Metric</h2>



<ul>
<li><strong>NFT Name:</strong>&nbsp;Mutant Ape Yacht Club</li>



<li><strong>Ticker</strong>: MAYC</li>



<li><strong>Blockchain</strong>: Ethereum</li>



<li><strong>Token Standard:&nbsp;</strong>ERC-721</li>



<li><strong>NFT Contract:&nbsp;</strong>0x60E4d786628Fea6478F785A6d7e704777c86a7c6</li>



<li><strong>Circulating Supply:</strong> 19,478 MAYC</li>
</ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Highlights</h2>



<p>MAYC has 3 highlights:</p>



<ul>
<li>MAYC is a mutant version of BAYC after oral administration of the serum.</li>



<li>Like BAYC, MAYC is currently one of the NFTs with good liquidity and reputation in the market alongside Pudgy Penguins, CryptoPunks, Azuki, etc.</li>



<li>MAYC NFT is one of the few NFT collections on the market that shares the same token with BAYC as (Apecoin) APE because it is in the monkey ecosystem.</li>
</ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Ultility</h2>



<p>Owners who possess MAYC will profit from the following:</p>



<ul>
<li>Since MAYC NFTs are Profile Picture NFTs, using them as profile image is the primary use of the MAYC collection.</li>



<li>It is your passport to special Bored Ape Yacht Club offerings and advantages. Special events, products, and ownership of actual assets are examples of these perks.</li>



<li>MAYC may be purchased, traded, lent, or mortgaged in numerous markets as an investment asset.</li>
</ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Development forecasting</h2>



<p>Everyone&#8217;s attention must be drawn to the Mutant Ape Yacht Club minting procedure right now. How is Mutant Ape NFT made, and how do you get one? It is critical to comprehend Mutant Ape NFT&#8217;s mission and operations. These elements might assist you in learning more about the project before selecting an NFT from the collection.</p>



<p>MAYC NFT was inspired by the success of BAYC NFT. Mutant Ape NFT was envisioned by Yuga Labs as the second degree of membership in the Bored Ape ecosystem. Mutant Apes is a useful tool for rewarding Bored Ape owners with a fresh new NFT.</p>



<p>The mutant variation of the original Bored Ape will be the new NFT. The MAYC NFT collection, on the other hand, is aimed at allowing newcomers to join the BAYC ecosystem. Since its inception, the price of Bored Apes has surged by a significant margin, motivating community members to sell up their NFTs in order to meet financial objectives.</p>



<p>As a consequence, several members of the community were forced to quit the club by selling the NFT Bored Ape. At the same time, several NFT community members voiced regret for not joining the Bored Ape ecosystem prior to the steep price spike. The Mutant Ape Yacht Club NFT collection allows you to join the BAYC ecosystem at the most basic level. Presently, the project&#8217;s goal is to increase the utility while also providing rewards to people who have Bored Apes.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">NFT allocation and sale schedule</h2>



<p>Yuga Labs first wanted to donate 20,000 Mutant Ape Yacht Club (MAYC) to the community in a unique method.</p>



<ul>
<li>They airdropped three Mutant serums to BAYC bearers, instructing them to consume the serum to create MAYC.</li>



<li>The remaining 10,000 MAYC were then auctioned off by Yuga Labs in a lively auction.</li>



<li>The MAYC auction was quite active, with the final value of each MAYC reaching around 2.79 ETH. Based on this, we may predict that Yuga Labs will earn around 27,900 ETH (equivalent to $84 million in August 2021) if all 10,000 MAYC are sold in the auction.</li>
</ul>



<p>This demonstrates the huge possibilities of owning and controlling digital assets. Investors and companies must approach this market with caution and a solid investing strategy.</p>



<p>Yet, for those who are just getting started, it is critical to have a solid grasp of the market and auctions. Likewise, investing in digital assets may be quite rewarding, but it can also be extremely hazardous. As a result, before investing in this market, investors should do extensive research.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/QmVcubzUVkPh7r83LjyCCEGntGmQQLEMECxRCAP7TkmmrT-1024x1024.jpeg"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="1024" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/QmVcubzUVkPh7r83LjyCCEGntGmQQLEMECxRCAP7TkmmrT-1024x1024.jpeg" alt="Mutant Ape NFT Review: The Breakthrough From BAYC" class="wp-image-195991" srcset="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/QmVcubzUVkPh7r83LjyCCEGntGmQQLEMECxRCAP7TkmmrT-1024x1024.jpeg 1024w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/QmVcubzUVkPh7r83LjyCCEGntGmQQLEMECxRCAP7TkmmrT-300x300.jpeg 300w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/QmVcubzUVkPh7r83LjyCCEGntGmQQLEMECxRCAP7TkmmrT-150x150.jpeg 150w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/QmVcubzUVkPh7r83LjyCCEGntGmQQLEMECxRCAP7TkmmrT-768x768.jpeg 768w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/QmVcubzUVkPh7r83LjyCCEGntGmQQLEMECxRCAP7TkmmrT-75x75.jpeg 75w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/QmVcubzUVkPh7r83LjyCCEGntGmQQLEMECxRCAP7TkmmrT-350x350.jpeg 350w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/QmVcubzUVkPh7r83LjyCCEGntGmQQLEMECxRCAP7TkmmrT-750x750.jpeg 750w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/QmVcubzUVkPh7r83LjyCCEGntGmQQLEMECxRCAP7TkmmrT-1140x1140.jpeg 1140w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/QmVcubzUVkPh7r83LjyCCEGntGmQQLEMECxRCAP7TkmmrT.jpeg 1201w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Mutant Ape NFT Review: The Breakthrough From BAYC 20"></a></figure></div>


<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Roadmap</h2>



<p>The MAYC roadmap is divided into several stages:</p>



<ul>
<li>26/4/2022: Snapshot of all BAYC owners.</li>



<li>Launch platform.</li>



<li>3/5/2022: Airdrop 10K NFT serum to BAYC holders.</li>



<li>8/5/2022: Open to sell the remaining 10k NFT MAYC.</li>



<li>8/6/2022: 10K NFT MAYC sold out.</li>



<li>9/6/2022: Allows BAYC holders to use the serum.</li>



<li>3/7-8/7/2022: Auction of 7 NFT Mega Mutants.</li>



<li>12/23/2022: Snapshot of the owner of BAYC and MAYC.</li>



<li>28/1/2023: Airdrop Kennels to all BAYC and MAYC holders.</li>
</ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Team</h2>



<p>Yuga Labs created the Mutant Ape Yacht Club collection after releasing one of the most popular NFT collectibles on the market, Bored Ape Yacht Club, with peak prices often reaching hundreds of ETH.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Investors and partners</h2>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Investors</strong></h3>



<p>MAYC NFT has never raised funds on its own. Instead, Yuga Labs, its parent firm, received two rounds of investment. Yuga Labs now has a minimum of $450 million in funding, with a firm value of up to $4 billion, as of March 22, 2022. Animoca Brands and LionTree were among the investors that participated in the transaction, which was headed by a16z.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Partners</strong></h3>



<p>Mutant Ape Yacht Club (MAYC) has teamed with the Farmhouse brand in order to link the NFT and Farmhouse communities. This collaboration allows fans of digital art goods, such as NFT, to engage in the Web3 globe outside their own group.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Conclusion</h2>



<p>Mutant Apes is a variation on the famous NFT Bored Ape Yacht Clubs that adds unique Mutant Mutant Serums to the normal NFT Ape Bored. Mutant Ape NFT is a valuable resource that allows anybody to join the Bored Ape ecology with little boundaries.</p>



<p>But, the original batch of MAYC mints has long ago sold out, and just one may be purchased on the secondary market. At the same time, the value benefits of Mutant Ape NFT cannot be overlooked.</p>



<p>The value that Mutant Ape Yacht Club gives to owners cannot be measured in monetary terms since holding these NFTs exposes them to the class of celebrities, sharks have a lot of money in the market, and the market may then have a lot of knowledge that regular people do not have.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER: </em></strong><em>The information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>



<p>Join us to keep track of news:&nbsp;<a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Harold</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Coincu</strong> <strong>News</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1322-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>CyberKongz Review: One Of The First Solid PFP NFT Projects</title>
		<link>https://news.coincu.com/195974-cyberkongz-review/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Harold]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 06:15:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Reviews]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Baby Kongz]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BANANA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CyberKongz]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genesis CyberKongz]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PFP NFT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Play & Kollect Jungle Adventure]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[VX Kongz]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.coincu.com/?p=195974</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Beginning with the 1,000 genesis CyberKongz, the family of strange apes has since grown and shows no signs of stopping down.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The CyberKongz NFT project is one of the first NFT projects and has grown in popularity over the last year. Beginning with the 1,000 genesis CyberKongz, the family of strange apes has since grown and shows no signs of stopping down. What is special about this project, let&#8217;s find out with Coincu in this article.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1319.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="999" height="389" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1319.png" alt="CyberKongz Review: One Of The First Solid PFP NFT Projects" class="wp-image-195981" srcset="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1319.png 999w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1319-300x117.png 300w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1319-768x299.png 768w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1319-750x292.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 999px) 100vw, 999px" title="CyberKongz Review: One Of The First Solid PFP NFT Projects 21"></a></figure></div>


<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">What is CyberKongz?</h2>



<p>CyberKongz is a set of 1,000 NFTs featuring 34 × 34 pixel pictures of uncommon, distinctive, and randomly created apes. Just 989 of the original 1,000 NFTs were sold on OpenSea, CyberKongz #810 was retained as the project&#8217;s mascot, and 10 CyberKongz Legendary were sold two weeks later.</p>



<p>Despite the lack of a pre-release advertising effort, the project drew a lot of interest from NFT fans, and CyberKongz avatars immediately became popular on social media.</p>



<p>You&#8217;d be hard-pushed to find PFP projects that have been around longer than this one, which was given to the public on March 3rd, 2021. A total of 989 Genesis CyberKongz were made available for purchase at a cost of 0.01 ETH apiece. The concept soon gathered traction in the following weeks. This resulted in the sale of 11 legendary Kongz for a total of 200 ETH.</p>



<p>Everything changed for Kong holders on April 17th. The project switched to a new contract, which allows for the addition of all new utilities for holders. Holders now have the following new features:</p>



<ul>
<li>Breeding (produce BabyKongz and Kong VX).</li>



<li>BANANA Yield.</li>



<li>Custom Biography and Renaming.</li>
</ul>



<p>Throughout time, CyberKongz has grown into a community-focused initiative in which NFT engineers and community specialists devote their talents to the development of community ideas. It evolved from a modest PFP project to a passive income-generating machine over time.</p>



<p>Later on, the project created two further NFT collections: 4,000 Baby CyberKongz and 15,000 CyberKongz VX. The CyberKongz VX 3D collection, in addition to successfully increasing the CyberKongz community, enables owners to utilize their NFTs in multiple metaverses.</p>



<p>&nbsp;When it comes to this universe, there are four keywords to understand:</p>



<ul>
<li>Genesis CyberKongz&nbsp;– The original collection of 2D avatars</li>



<li>Baby Kongz –&nbsp;Result of “breeding” two genesis CyberKongz</li>



<li>CyberKongz VX –&nbsp;3D Voxel-Based avatars</li>



<li>BANANA Token&nbsp;– Native token for CyberKongz owners</li>
</ul>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1318.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1000" height="700" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1318.png" alt="CyberKongz Review: One Of The First Solid PFP NFT Projects" class="wp-image-195980" srcset="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1318.png 1000w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1318-300x210.png 300w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1318-768x538.png 768w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1318-750x525.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" title="CyberKongz Review: One Of The First Solid PFP NFT Projects 22"></a></figure></div>


<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Traits</h2>



<p>Each NFT in the collection is made up of the following 4 properties:</p>



<ul>
<li>Genesis Trait has 62 different types including: Square Sunglasses, Gold Glasses, Eye Patch, ….</li>



<li>Legendary Trait has 10 different types including: Astronaut, Devil, Ghost,…</li>



<li>Type has only one type, Genesis</li>



<li>Birthday is a marker for the birth of each NFT in the collection and is randomly numbered between 1618607943 and 1631762429.</li>
</ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Key metrics</h2>



<ul>
<li>NFT Collection Name: CyberKongz</li>



<li>Classification: PFPs</li>



<li>Total amount of NFTs: 1,000 NFT</li>



<li>Blockchain: Ethereum</li>



<li>Number of features: 4</li>



<li>NFT contract: 0x57a204AA1042f6E66DD7730813f4024114d74f37</li>
</ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">NFT Utility</h2>



<p>The BANANA cryptocurrency, which is the CyberKongz utility token, was created by the team. All Genesis CyberKongz holders will get 10 BANANA tokens every day for the next ten years as a thank-you for their early support of the project. These tokens may be redeemed for cash, used to breed Baby CyberKongz, or burnt to give their special qualities.</p>



<p>Besides that, NFT holders may rename their NFTs by investing in some BANANA tokens. All holders will also get access to a private Discord channel for holders exclusively.</p>



<p>In every choice, the team clearly prioritizes the owners. Owners, for example, have complete NFT commercial rights to the 2D and 3D versions of their CyberKongz. Additionally, the sophisticated tokenomics in the ecosystem were created with the intention of benefiting the owners in the long term. Users may also use NFT as their avatar on social networking sites or Metaverse services like The Sandbox.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1315.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="512" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1315.png" alt="CyberKongz Review: One Of The First Solid PFP NFT Projects" class="wp-image-195977" srcset="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1315.png 1024w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1315-300x150.png 300w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1315-768x384.png 768w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1315-360x180.png 360w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1315-750x375.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="CyberKongz Review: One Of The First Solid PFP NFT Projects 23"></a></figure></div>


<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">How much does CyberKongz generate?</h2>



<p>Each Genesis Kong grows 10 BANANA each day and will continue to do so for the next 9-10 years. When we initially looked at this collection, that amounted to $480 in passive yield every day. At the current pricing of BANANA at $0.46, it is more in the area of $4.6 per day.</p>



<p>Although not insignificant, it represents a big decrease from the previous year. BANANA is currently held by little about 500 wallets. Nonetheless, with additional usefulness on the way, this is a token to keep an eye on.</p>



<p>BANANA may now be used to:</p>



<ul>
<li>Write your bio like 100 BANANA.</li>



<li>10 BANANA is a custom name.</li>



<li>VX Kong name changes cost 2 BANANA.</li>
</ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Play &amp; Kollect</h2>



<p>Apart from Baby and VX Kongz, Play &amp; Kollect Jungle Adventure is their second major deliverable for holders. Holders may participate in the Polygon Network with minimal to no gas expenses or concern about environmental effects.</p>



<p>CyberKongz VX owners may form crews of one to five people and send them on missions to collect Kongium Ore. This ore (or ERC-1155 NFT) may be redeemed for a portion of the season&#8217;s BANANA pool as well as other special incentives. Each season lasts 10 days, so there are plenty of chances for everyone to collect their fair share of the goodies.</p>



<p>To begin with, each crew has one free excursion every day. Holders may acquire resources for free by consuming the fuel rod they obtain for their crew. After that, each further resource collection trip you send your team will cost 0.4 BANANA. Moreover, the pool of excess BANANA that will accrue as a result of holders sending their personnel on extra missions will be returned to the community. 50% will be added to the season&#8217;s prize pool, 10% to a community treasury, and 40% will be burnt.</p>



<p>Deflationary mechanisms, as well as gamified usefulness, may restore BANANA to its former status as a passive generating goldmine.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Roadmap</h2>



<p>The team has already completed numerous milestones on its plan. This covers developing metaverse playable versions, obtaining land in The Sandbox, establishing community governance, and making 3D printable obj files. There are also other ongoing initiatives, such as Play and Kollect and Kongz Tank.</p>



<p>Jungle Adventure, a blockchain game in which holders may gain different in-game incentives, is included in the Play and Kollect. Players will use their CyberKongz VX to collect Kongium and redeem rewards such as BANANA and unique NFTs in this game.</p>



<p>Kongz Tank, on the other hand, is essentially an NFT counterpart of the popular TV show Shark Tank. The team is always looking for new talent to help them create games and interactive experiences using the Play and Kollect technologies. All games will be launched on the Polygon Network and may also be partially off-chain.</p>



<p>The team also works together with organizations such as The Sandbox, MetaKey, Uniqly, Solarbots, and Global Webb. They have also just hired UFC veteran Chuck Liddell.</p>



<p>CyberKongz has informed the community about a 4-tier roadmap as follows:</p>



<ul>
<li>Level 1 (CyberKongz VX Launch): VX was launched in partnership with The Sandbox, and integration as a playable avatar into The Sandbox game is currently in development.</li>



<li>Level 2 (The Banana Shop): Players will also be able to purchase custom VX wearables to give their avatars additional in-game adventures in the community-built Metaverse games. .</li>



<li>Level 3 (Kongz Island): A jungle with multiple zones built into The Sandbox where both CyberKongz and Sandbox aim to create a gaming and social experience related to all CyberKongz NFTs as well as Banana Tokens.</li>



<li>Level 4 (Kongz Extension): Owning one or more grants any user access to the clan.</li>
</ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">How to buy Sappy Seals NFTs?</h2>



<p>You can buy these NFTs on marketplaces like OpenSea and LooksRare.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1316.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="322" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1316-1024x322.png" alt="CyberKongz Review: One Of The First Solid PFP NFT Projects" class="wp-image-195978" srcset="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1316-1024x322.png 1024w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1316-300x94.png 300w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1316-768x241.png 768w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1316-1536x483.png 1536w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1316-2048x644.png 2048w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1316-750x236.png 750w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1316-1140x358.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="CyberKongz Review: One Of The First Solid PFP NFT Projects 24"></a></figure></div>


<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Team</h2>



<p>The team has not been completely doxxed, and numerous team members remain nameless. This project&#8217;s mad scientist and artist is Myoo. They are now hard at work, together with a team of developers and core members, to construct the future.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Community</h2>



<p>CyberKongz has a vast and diversified community on social networking networks. Moreover, CyberKongz formed a Kongz council of active community members who would take the role of the community in project development and orientation activities.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Should you own Sappy Seal NFT?</h2>



<p>When it comes down to it, this debate is becoming more fascinating. Fresh initiatives are being launched on a daily basis. And there are undoubtedly some fresh collections in this discussion among the initiatives that have been minting in recent months.</p>



<p>Yet, CyberKongz and other well-known initiatives give long-term stability. It has maintained its floor price during the bull and bear cycles since last year.</p>



<p>The key qualification of a blue-chip collection should be price consistency, which CyberKongz unquestionably fulfills. Not only was their floor price consistent, but Genesis holders have been raking in BANANA for over a year. Some diamond-hand bearers have earned a good living by clutching their CyberKong.</p>



<p>Customers may invest their Ethereum into this collection with confidence. They are not concerned about their NFTs losing half their value overnight. Holders have no motive to even look at the floor price. They earn a year&#8217;s income passively and continue to receive value from the developers.</p>



<p>CyberKongz is unquestionably a blue-chip collection that will be around for a long time, if not forever.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Conclusion</h2>



<p>Over time, the common vision of advancing CyberKongz as a community-based initiative evolved. Some of the best developers and specialists in the NFT and De-Fi field may be found in the group. Who contributed their talents and effort to the development of the community&#8217;s ideas? The BANANA coin was produced quickly, giving genesis CyberKongz the potential to earn 10 BANANA every day for the following ten years. Owners may give their CyberKongz attributes such as a unique name and biography by burning a particular quantity of BANANA, as well as breed and incubating one of 4,000 randomly created Baby CyberKongz with various qualities and rarities.</p>



<p>From then, CyberKongz VX was seen as the natural next step. With so many people eager to explore the metaverse, the NFT proẹct understood they needed to bring the jungle to life and put the swing into action.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER: </em></strong><em>The information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>



<p>Join us to keep track of news:&nbsp;<a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Harold</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Coincu</strong> <strong>News</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1317-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sound.xyz Minted 150,000 Music NFTs, Impressive Start On Optimism</title>
		<link>https://news.coincu.com/195954-soundxyz-minted-150000-nfts/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Harold]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 14:48:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[NFT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[optimism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sound.xyz]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[V-Buterin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web3]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.coincu.com/?p=195954</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Sound.xyz is tuning in with the major Layer 2 scaling solution, Optimism, to address important Web3 industry challenges.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>Sound.xyz recently announced the addition of support for Ethereum Layer-2 Optimism.</em></li>



<li><em>The music NFT distribution platform minted more than 150,000 music NFTs on Optimism this month.</em></li>



<li><em>The NFT minted on Optimism is almost the same as the number of music NFTs minted on Ethereum over the past year.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Sound.xyz is tuning in with the major Layer 2 scaling solution, Optimism, to address important Web3 industry challenges, such as high gas prices and sluggish transactions connected with Ethereum&#8217;s mainnet.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large is-resized"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1312.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1312-1024x512.png" alt="Sound.xyz Minted 150,000 Music NFTs, Impressive Start On Optimism" class="wp-image-195967" width="1024" height="512" srcset="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1312-1024x512.png 1024w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1312-300x150.png 300w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1312-768x384.png 768w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1312-1536x768.png 1536w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1312-360x180.png 360w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1312-750x375.png 750w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1312-1140x570.png 1140w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1312.png 2000w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Sound.xyz Minted 150,000 Music NFTs, Impressive Start On Optimism 25"></a></figure></div>


<p>The music NFT platform Sound.xyz has acknowledged Vitalik Buterin, a co-founder of Ethereum, with a Eurodisco dance tune nicknamed &#8220;V-Buterin.&#8221; Importantly, the music is free to listen to till June 19 at 7:00 p.m. Sound.xyz, a Web3 music portal, provides it as a free-to-mint NFT for interested investors and NFT aficionados.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1311-1024x542.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="542" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1311-1024x542.png" alt="Sound.xyz Minted 150,000 Music NFTs, Impressive Start On Optimism" class="wp-image-195966" srcset="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1311-1024x542.png 1024w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1311-300x159.png 300w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1311-768x406.png 768w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1311-750x397.png 750w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1311-1140x603.png 1140w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1311.png 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Sound.xyz Minted 150,000 Music NFTs, Impressive Start On Optimism 26"></a></figure></div>


<p>According to <a href="https://dune.com/web3academypro/t4" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Dune analysis</a>, since the announcement of Optimism&#8217;s debut on June 13, the music NFT distribution network Sound.xyz has minted more than 150,000 music NFTs on Optimism this month, which is about the same as the number of music NFTs minted on Ethereum over the last year. The majority of the mining comes from the V Buterin track NFT published by Optimism Collective.</p>



<p>Sound.xyz achieves a phenomenal 90% decrease in gas expenses by using the Optimism Layer 2 technology, which is a major success given that the rates have often surpassed the cost of the music. Moreover, as a result of this collaboration, transaction speeds on the music-centric NFT marketplace have increased sixfold, and collectors now have additional alternatives for paying for records, including credit cards, Mainnet ETH, and Optimism ETH.</p>



<p>Despite of this partnership, die-hard Ethereum supporters may still deploy their contracts on Ethereum&#8217;s Layer 1 mainnet, enabling music enthusiasts to gather and discover music across both chains. They must, however, spend Optimism ETH while purchasing music on Optimism, which is readily obtained by bridging monies with the official Optimism Bridge. Collectors may now pay using Mainnet ETH and get their music NFTs on the Optimism chain.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1314-1024x576.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="576" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1314-1024x576.png" alt="Sound.xyz Minted 150,000 Music NFTs, Impressive Start On Optimism" class="wp-image-195970" srcset="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1314-1024x576.png 1024w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1314-300x169.png 300w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1314-768x432.png 768w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1314-750x422.png 750w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1314-1140x641.png 1140w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1314.png 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Sound.xyz Minted 150,000 Music NFTs, Impressive Start On Optimism 27"></a></figure></div>


<p>Moreover, Cherished artists Rae Isla and Sammy Arriaga will begin off their debut with their song &#8220;Heartbreak Closer.&#8221; Other artists expected to release songs this week include ROHKI, TK the Legend, Bloody White, Reo Cragun, Sara J Phillips, and Daniel Alla.</p>



<p>In a nutshell, Music and Optimism share a goal of supporting ecosystem contributors and innovators. This collaboration is just the beginning of Web3 development. Even better, Sound teases more intriguing upgrades and changes in the works.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER: </em></strong><em>The information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>



<p>Join us to keep track of news:&nbsp;<a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Harold</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Coincu</strong> <strong>News</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1313-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Official: Binance.US Is Separated From Binance Holdings After Court Approved SEC Deal</title>
		<link>https://news.coincu.com/195953-binanceus-is-separated-from-binance/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Harold]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 14:27:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance.US]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Changpeng Zhao]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CZ]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.coincu.com/?p=195953</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Binance, Binance.US, and the SEC entered into an arrangement to guarantee that only the exchange's subsidiary US workers may access client cash in the near term.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>Binance.US, Binance and the SEC have come to a mutual agreement.</em></li>



<li><em>Binance.US will ensure that no authorities from the global exchange, Binance Holdings, have access to private keys for wallets or hardware wallets.</em></li>



<li><em>The deal was approved by Judge Amy Berman Jackson.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>According to court records, Binance, Binance.US, and the US Securities and Exchange Commission entered into an arrangement to guarantee that only the exchange&#8217;s subsidiary US workers may access client cash in the near term.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1308.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="680" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1308-1024x680.png" alt="Official: Binance.US Is Separated From Binance Holdings After Court Approved SEC Deal" class="wp-image-195957" srcset="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1308-1024x680.png 1024w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1308-300x199.png 300w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1308-768x510.png 768w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1308-750x498.png 750w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1308-1140x757.png 1140w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1308.png 1256w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Official: Binance.US Is Separated From Binance Holdings After Court Approved SEC Deal 28"></a></figure></div>


<p>The Securities and Exchange Commission struck an <a href="https://news.coincu.com/195885-binanceus-and-sec-agreement-access/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">agreement</a> with Binance late Friday that would enable the world&#8217;s biggest cryptocurrency exchange to continue operating in the United States and protect client assets while the business fights a federal lawsuit.</p>



<p>According to the latest announcement, the deal has been approved by the federal judge overseeing the case. According to the filings, Binance.US will take steps to ensure that no Binance Holdings officials have access to private keys for its various wallets, hardware wallets, or root access to Binance.US&#8217;s Amazon Web Services tools.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Update: Judge Amy Berman Jackson apparently just approved the Proposed Stipulation and Consent Order,&quot; filing a &quot;Consent Order&quot; which, upon first glance (I have not reviewed it line-by-line) looks the same as the order agreed to by the parties. So the case is off and running . .… <a href="https://t.co/pu30JbAsZz" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/pu30JbAsZz</a></p>&mdash; John Reed Stark (@JohnReedStark) <a href="https://twitter.com/JohnReedStark/status/1670054262750035969?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener">June 17, 2023</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>Funds belonging to Binance.US users would be placed in separate digital vaults accessible exclusively to the US exchange — not to the exchange&#8217;s bigger worldwide company or its creator, Changpeng Zhao. Binance.US is allowed to transfer firm assets solely to make payments for costs or to discharge obligations accrued in the usual course of business, according to the agreement.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1310.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="958" height="606" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1310.png" alt="Official: Binance.US Is Separated From Binance Holdings After Court Approved SEC Deal" class="wp-image-195960" srcset="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1310.png 958w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1310-300x190.png 300w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1310-768x486.png 768w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1310-750x474.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 958px) 100vw, 958px" title="Official: Binance.US Is Separated From Binance Holdings After Court Approved SEC Deal 29"></a></figure></div>


<p>Additional elements in the proposed deal include Binance.US creating new crypto wallets that no workers of the global exchange will have access to, providing extra information to the SEC, and agreeing to an accelerated discovery timeline, according to the documents.</p>



<p>After the filing of fraud allegations against the exchange on June 5, the SEC proceeded to freeze the firm&#8217;s US assets, which the exchange&#8217;s attorneys said would put it out of business in the US.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/sec-building-photo-via-cbs-news-1575973250383720490692.jpg"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="683" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/sec-building-photo-via-cbs-news-1575973250383720490692-1024x683.jpg" alt="Official: Binance.US Is Separated From Binance Holdings After Court Approved SEC Deal" class="wp-image-195961" srcset="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/sec-building-photo-via-cbs-news-1575973250383720490692-1024x683.jpg 1024w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/sec-building-photo-via-cbs-news-1575973250383720490692-300x200.jpg 300w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/sec-building-photo-via-cbs-news-1575973250383720490692-768x513.jpg 768w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/sec-building-photo-via-cbs-news-1575973250383720490692-750x500.jpg 750w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/sec-building-photo-via-cbs-news-1575973250383720490692-1140x761.jpg 1140w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/sec-building-photo-via-cbs-news-1575973250383720490692.jpg 1536w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Official: Binance.US Is Separated From Binance Holdings After Court Approved SEC Deal 30"></a></figure></div>


<p>The exchange&#8217;s US subsidiary ceased dollar deposits last week and offered consumers until June 13 to withdraw their dollar cash after the SEC requested that its assets be frozen.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER: </em></strong><em>The information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>



<p>Join us to keep track of news:&nbsp;<a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Harold</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Coincu</strong> <strong>News</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-1309-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
