<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 17:08:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Gaming Crypto Token Qwan to Launch via Ethereum on May 31 Supported by Horizen Labs Ventures</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/qwan-launch-via-ethereum-may-31-horizen-labs/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/qwan-launch-via-ethereum-may-31-horizen-labs/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 17:08:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[qwan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[qwan foundation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[qwan token]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=257080</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/qwan-launch-via-ethereum-may-31-horizen-labs/">Gaming Crypto Token Qwan to Launch via Ethereum on May 31 Supported by Horizen Labs Ventures</a></p>
<p>The Qwan tokens have a total supply of 1 billion with about 455 million, representing 45.5 percent, being allocated to the ecosystem’s treasury. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/qwan-launch-via-ethereum-may-31-horizen-labs/">Gaming Crypto Token Qwan to Launch via Ethereum on May 31 Supported by Horizen Labs Ventures</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/qwan-launch-via-ethereum-may-31-horizen-labs/">Gaming Crypto Token Qwan to Launch via Ethereum on May 31 Supported by Horizen Labs Ventures</a></p>
<p><a href="http://www.theqwan.io" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">The Qwan</a>, a Web3 crypto token geared towards revolutionizing the gaming industry by involving users, has announced plans to launch on the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a> ecosystem on May 31. Backed by key Web3 investors including Horizen Labs Ventures &#8211; which has backed successful GamiFi projects like Yuga Labs, The Sandbox, and Animoca Brands &#8211; the Qwan token intends to enable a decentralized economy for all gamers globally through incentivizing their activities.</p>
<h2>Closer Look at the Qwan Ecosystem</h2>
<p>Several centralized exchanges including MEXC, AscendEX, and BTSE, among others, will list the Qwan token on Wednesday at a listing price of about $0.15.</p>
<p>“We are excited about QWAN and its potential to positively impact and shape game economies, powering new utilities and a community-led governance that can appeal to existing Web2 gamers,” said Rohan Handa, Founding Member and SVP of Business Development at HLV.</p>
<p>Already, gaming platform and marketplace, Banger has announced plans to integrate with the Qwan token and work closely with the Qwan Foundation. As a result, the Qwan Foundation hopes the Banger integration will work as a magnet to gaming projects without economic incentives to their players.</p>
<p>“We are thrilled for Banger to integrate The QWAN as its key gaming token and offer our gamers the opportunity to enhance their gaming experience. With The QWAN, our offering becomes very unique in the market and allows us to provide gamers with an experience that can&#8217;t be found elsewhere”, said Borja Villalobos, Banger CEO.</p>
<p>As a decentralized network, the Qwan Foundation uses the QWAN DAO to ensure the community has a voice in the governance on matters affecting the protocol.</p>
<h2>Market Outlook</h2>
<p>The tokenomics of a crypto token plays a crucial role in its general market outlook. Crypto market leaders have called out projects that have allocated huge amounts of tokens to initial developers at the expense of secondary investors. As for the Qwan token, the team has set a fixed supply of 1 billion units. Out of which 455 million, which represents about 45.5 percent, is allocated to the ecosystem’s treasury that is governed by the Qwan DAO.</p>
<p>According to Qwan Foundation, the 45.5 percent allocated to the treasury will be used for gaming incentives, enabling partnerships, and grants, among others.</p>
<p>Notably, approximately 25.3 percent of the Qwan supply, amounting to 253 million units, has been to the Qwan partners. The remaining percent has been divided among investors and launch contributors amounting to 168.3 million and 123.6 million respectively. In order to ensure the stability of the Qwan network, the tokenomics are in such a way that every category has its own unlock period, starting from 12-72 months.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/serve-robotics-partnership-uber-eats/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/qwan-launch-via-ethereum-may-31-horizen-labs/">Gaming Crypto Token Qwan to Launch via Ethereum on May 31 Supported by Horizen Labs Ventures</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/qwan-launch-via-ethereum-may-31-horizen-labs/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Serve Robotics Expands Partnership with Uber Eats to Deliver Meal Orders Seamlessly</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/serve-robotics-partnership-uber-eats/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/serve-robotics-partnership-uber-eats/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 16:50:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Deals News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[uber eats]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[walmart]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=257078</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/serve-robotics-partnership-uber-eats/">Serve Robotics Expands Partnership with Uber Eats to Deliver Meal Orders Seamlessly</a></p>
<p>Robotics developer Serve recently deepened its relationship with Uber Eats to deploy 2,000 bots for food deliveries across the US. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/serve-robotics-partnership-uber-eats/">Serve Robotics Expands Partnership with Uber Eats to Deliver Meal Orders Seamlessly</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/serve-robotics-partnership-uber-eats/">Serve Robotics Expands Partnership with Uber Eats to Deliver Meal Orders Seamlessly</a></p>
<p>Serve Robotics has <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2023/05/30/serve-robotics-to-deploy-up-to-2000-sidewalk-delivery-bots-on-uber-eats/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">expanded its partnership</a> with Uber Eats, deploying as many as 2,000 delivery bots across the United States. Reports state that Serve Robotics’ autonomous sidewalk delivery robots would be on hand to deliver goods via Uber’s platform in several US-based markets. The Serve Robotics-Uber Eats partnership would last until early 2026.</p>
<p>Speaking on the joint initiative, Serve co-founder and chief executive officer Ali Kashani pointed out:</p>
<blockquote><p>“We expect our rapid growth on Uber Eats to continue. We currently have a fleet of 100 robots in Los Angeles, and we expect to operate an increasing number of them on Uber Eats as our coverage and delivery volume on Uber increases.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>Serve Robotics-Uber Eats Partnership Mutually Progressive for Both Platforms</h2>
<p>The collaboration between both platforms underscores Serve’s agenda to enhance autonomous delivery with its commercialized robotics. In addition, the Serve and Uber Eats partnership also fuels the food delivery platform’s commitment to autonomous services.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/uber/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Uber</a> (NYSE: UBER) is currently associated with several autonomy-as-a-service deals for its ride-hailing and delivery platforms. For instance, last week, the San Francisco-based company announced the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/waymo-robotaxis-uber-ride-hailing/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">incorporation of Waymo’s self-driving cars</a> into its service feature later this year. According to Uber, the service rollout would begin in Phoenix, Arizona. The package delivery platform is also collaborating with autonomous vehicle technology company Motional to deliver meals in Santa Monica, California. Also, previous reports state the delivery initiative would take place with involvement from Serve Robotics.</p>
<p>The Serve-Uber partnership began as a pilot scheme a year ago before growing more than 30% month-over-month. Presently, Serve’s Uber-aided robotic deliveries boast a network of more than 200 restaurants in Hollywood, West Hollywood, and Fairfax. Furthermore, Kashani said Serve’s delivery robots currently operate all week between 10 am and 9 pm. However, the company shares its robotic fleet with other partners, including 7-Eleven.</p>
<p>Although Serve did not specify its next target markets with the expanded Uber Eats partnership, the company is eyeing San Jose and Dallas. In addition, Serve also reportedly plans to branch out into Vancouver, Canada. The Los Angeles-based robotics company recently wrapped up pilots with Pizza Hut in Vancouver and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/walmart/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Walmart</a> (NYSE: WMT) in Arkansas. Although the companies involved did not reveal the deal’s value, Kashani said Serve runs a delivery-as-a-service business model. This means that the robotics platform receives payment on a per-delivery basis.</p>
<h2>Serve Robotics</h2>
<p>As a designer, developer, and operator of zero-emission public service robots, Serve has a fleet of Level 4 autonomous sidewalk bots. This operational designation means the machines can function adequately with minimal human intervention. Although tasks include driving competently in certain conditions, the bots require remote human supervision when encountering certain cases, including ongoing construction or police tapes. However, Kashani said Serve’s robots are capable of rerouting should they face pathway obstacles. The CEO also added that the robotics could avoid collision autonomously by predicting driver inattention. However, supervisors usually assist with street crossings.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/brc-721e-ethereum-nfts-bitcoin-ordinals/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/serve-robotics-partnership-uber-eats/">Serve Robotics Expands Partnership with Uber Eats to Deliver Meal Orders Seamlessly</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/serve-robotics-partnership-uber-eats/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>BRC-721E Standard to Bridge Gap between Ethereum NFTs and Bitcoin Ordinals</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/brc-721e-ethereum-nfts-bitcoin-ordinals/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/brc-721e-ethereum-nfts-bitcoin-ordinals/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 16:35:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Ordinals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BRC-721E]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nfts]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=257064</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/brc-721e-ethereum-nfts-bitcoin-ordinals/">BRC-721E Standard to Bridge Gap between Ethereum NFTs and Bitcoin Ordinals</a></p>
<p>As the NFT landscape continues to evolve, the integration of Ethereum and Bitcoin ecosystems through the BRC-721E standard paves the way for further innovation and expansion that can even attract more mainstream innovators into the Web 3.0 world.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/brc-721e-ethereum-nfts-bitcoin-ordinals/">BRC-721E Standard to Bridge Gap between Ethereum NFTs and Bitcoin Ordinals</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/brc-721e-ethereum-nfts-bitcoin-ordinals/">BRC-721E Standard to Bridge Gap between Ethereum NFTs and Bitcoin Ordinals</a></p>
<p>The recent introduction of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> (BTC) Ordinals and the unveiling of the BRC-721E protocol is <a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-ordinals-to-bridge-ethereum-nft-with-new-standard" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">aimed</a> at bridging the gap between Bitcoin and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a> (ETH), particularly in the field of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Non-Fungible Tokens</a> (NFTs). According to reports, the BRC-721E standard, jointly launched by the Ordinals market and the Bitcoin Miladys NFT collection, now serves as a crucial bridge between Ethereum NFTs and Ordinals.</p>
<p>Through the BRC-721E protocol, crypto traders will be permitted to move their Ethereum-based NFTs to the Bitcoin blockchain. Additionally, it will enable the translation of immutable and verifiable ERC-721 NFTs to the Ordinals format, allowing users to store and interact with NFTs on the Bitcoin network.</p>
<p>The conversion of ERC-721 NFTs to the Ordinals format is a huge step forward in integrating Ethereum-based NFTs with the Bitcoin network. Previously, these two blockchain ecosystems operated separately, limiting the opportunities for cross-chain NFT interactions.</p>
<p>However, with the release of Bitcoin Ordinals, users can now convert ERC-721 NFTs, which were formerly connected with Ethereum, into a format that can be stored and used on the Bitcoin network.</p>
<p>Notably, the migration process begins with burning ERC-721 NFTs on the Ethereum network. Burning an NFT means permanently removing the token from circulation. This process is accomplished by calling a specific function on the smart contract associated with the NFT. By burning the NFT, the user signals the intent to migrate the asset to the Bitcoin network.</p>
<p>Furthermore, to claim the burned ETH and add the NFT to the Bitcoin network, users must inscribe authentic BRC-721E data on the Bitcoin blockchain. This inscription process entails encoding the relevant information about the NFT onto Bitcoin Ordinals.</p>
<p>Remarkably, the BRC-721E standard defines a standardized interface for encoding and decoding this data, enabling compatibility across the Ethereum and Bitcoin ecosystems.</p>
<h2>The Concept of Bitcoin Ordinals</h2>
<p>BTC Ordinals, a novel concept developed by the Bitcoin community, allows for the direct embedding of data and instructions into the Bitcoin blockchain. This concept utilizes the Bitcoin scripting language to store metadata, making it possible to attach information to Bitcoin transactions beyond mere financial transactions.</p>
<p>As the NFT landscape continues to evolve, the integration of Ethereum and Bitcoin ecosystems through the BRC-721E standard paves the way for further innovation and expansion that can even attract more mainstream innovators into the Web 3.0 world.</p>
<p>By allowing users to store and interact with NFTs on the Bitcoin network, BTC Ordinals open up new avenues for improved security, wider market reach, cross-chain interoperability, and collaborative activities within the NFT ecosystem.</p>
<p>Notably, since its inception earlier this year, Bitcoin Ordinals has elicited a strong response from the crypto community. The demand for Bitcoin Ordinals has increased dramatically. According to a recent <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-ordinals-10m-inscriptions/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">report,</a> the total number of ordinal inscriptions on the blockchain has surpassed the 10 million mark.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ecb-digital-euro-prototype-cbdc/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/brc-721e-ethereum-nfts-bitcoin-ordinals/">BRC-721E Standard to Bridge Gap between Ethereum NFTs and Bitcoin Ordinals</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/brc-721e-ethereum-nfts-bitcoin-ordinals/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>European Central Bank (ECB) Finalizes Digital Euro Prototype Ahead of Potential CBDC Launch</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ecb-digital-euro-prototype-cbdc/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ecb-digital-euro-prototype-cbdc/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 15:40:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital euro]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ecb]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=257058</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ecb-digital-euro-prototype-cbdc/">European Central Bank (ECB) Finalizes Digital Euro Prototype Ahead of Potential CBDC Launch</a></p>
<p>The ECB has finalized its digital euro prototype scheme as it mulls whether to roll out the government-backed token. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ecb-digital-euro-prototype-cbdc/">European Central Bank (ECB) Finalizes Digital Euro Prototype Ahead of Potential CBDC Launch</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ecb-digital-euro-prototype-cbdc/">European Central Bank (ECB) Finalizes Digital Euro Prototype Ahead of Potential CBDC Launch</a></p>
<p>The European Central Bank (ECB) has finalized a digital euro prototype ahead of a development decision. Later this year, the leading central bank would decide whether to develop the fiat euro as a digital variant.</p>
<p>According to a Friday <a href="https://www.ecb.europa.eu/paym/intro/news/html/ecb.mipnews230526.en.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">report</a>, the ECB examined distributed ledger technology and smart contracts as prime components of a potential digital euro. However, the governing bank has reservations about using decentralized-influenced smart contracts.</p>
<p>The ECB’s findings on its digital euro prototype came in two publications, namely <a href="https://www.ecb.europa.eu/paym/digital_euro/investigation/profuse/shared/files/dedocs/ecb.dedocs230526.en.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener">market research</a> and <a href="https://www.ecb.europa.eu/pub/pdf/other/ecb.prototype_summary20230526~71d0b26d55.en.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener">prototyping exercise</a>.</p>
<h2>ECB Executive Board Member Explains Findings of Digital Euro Prototype Scheme in Detail</h2>
<p>Commenting on the broader scope of the eurozone bank’s investigative phase, ECB Executive Board member Fabio Panetta <a href="https://www.ecb.europa.eu/pub/pdf/other/ecb.mepletter230526_Tinagli~4b892cb94f.en.pdf?b354618b3436566fda4b8402d325112c" target="_blank" rel="noopener">explained</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“This exercise shows that it is possible to smoothly integrate the digital euro design choices into the existing payment landscape while leaving ample scope for innovative features and technologies.”</p></blockquote>
<p>In a recent <a href="https://www.ecb.europa.eu/pub/pdf/other/ecb.mepletter230526_Tinagli~4b892cb94f.en.pdf?b354618b3436566fda4b8402d325112c" target="_blank" rel="noopener">letter</a> to Committee on Economic and Monetary Affairs (ECON) Chair Irene Tinagl, Panetta added:</p>
<blockquote><p>“The feedback received has helped the Eurosystem to better understand the current level of knowledge in the market and the existing experience in building solutions and identifying suitable technologies to potentially implement a digital euro.”</p></blockquote>
<p>The ECB Executive Board member concluded that the investigative phase would shape the potential euro’s functionality and design.</p>
<p>“The findings of the prototyping exercise and our market research will serve as input for both the functional and technical design of a digital euro. These reports can be shared under embargo with ECON Members of the European Parliament,” Panetta put it.</p>
<p>The Eurosystem invited several market participants to participate in its “learning experiment,” with the resulting prototypes used as research tools. Nonetheless, the eurozone’s monetary authority said the market research helped it understand industry-specific knowledge. The Eurosystem also said it acquired invaluable experience in developing potential digital euro technical solutions.</p>
<h2>ECB CBDC Prototyping Exercise</h2>
<p>The ECB conducted its digital euro prototyping exercise between July 2022 and February 2023. The investigative phase began nine months after the Governing Council of the ECB greenlit the digital euro project. During this period, the Eurosystem prime component researched various use cases for the central bank digital currency (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-central-bank-digital-currency-cbdc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CBDC</a>).</p>
<p>The exercise entailed the integration of five user interfaces developed by different providers for various experimental causes. In addition, the Eurosystem also created a single settlement system to serve as a back-end prototype. However, the monetary authority said it developed the back-end and front-end (five user interfaces) prototypes solely for research purposes. As a result, neither prototype class processed any personal data during the exercise. Furthermore, the Eurosystem does not intend to use the developed prototypes further following the experiment’s conclusion.</p>
<h2>ECB Executive Board Member Weighs Possibility of Digital Euro Issuance</h2>
<p>The ECB has mulled the possibility of a digital euro issuance as a European payment enhancer since CBDCs exploded in popularity. Panetta addressed the European Parliament in Brussels in March, emphasizing digital euro user optics. At the time, the ECB Executive Board Member said the CBDC would add value for end users.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-ceo-generative-ai-computing/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ecb-digital-euro-prototype-cbdc/">European Central Bank (ECB) Finalizes Digital Euro Prototype Ahead of Potential CBDC Launch</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ecb-digital-euro-prototype-cbdc/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nvidia CEO Says Generative AI Will Birth ‘New Computing Era’</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-ceo-generative-ai-computing/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-ceo-generative-ai-computing/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 14:43:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ai]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[artificial intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[artificial intelligence nvidia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Generative AI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nvidia]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=257024</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-ceo-generative-ai-computing/">Nvidia CEO Says Generative AI Will Birth &#8216;New Computing Era&#8217;</a></p>
<p>Nvidia believes that generative AI might be the most important computing platform of this generation.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-ceo-generative-ai-computing/">Nvidia CEO Says Generative AI Will Birth &#8216;New Computing Era&#8217;</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-ceo-generative-ai-computing/">Nvidia CEO Says Generative AI Will Birth &#8216;New Computing Era&#8217;</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/nvidia/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Nvidia</a> CEO Jensen Huang has shared some of the prospects of generative AI being a form of artificial intelligence technology that will greatly impact the world. He shared his thoughts on Monday while delivering a keynote speech at the Computex forum in Taiwan.</p>
<p>According to Huang, it is the dawn of a “new computing era” where a layman can easily be a programmer. He claims that generative AI gives virtually anyone the capabilities of being a programmer. That is, without the usual hassle and complexity of writing multiple lines of code.</p>
<h2>Nvidia Unveils New Generative AI-based Supercomputer</h2>
<p>In line with its view, Nvidia has now <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-ai-supercomputer-computex-2023/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">launched</a> a new AI supercomputer platform it calls DGX GH200. But its core aim is to build generative AI models with it. Huang <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/30/everyone-is-a-programmer-with-generative-ai-nvidia-ceo-.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“This computer doesn’t care how you program it, it will try to understand what you mean, because it has this incredible large language model capability.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Huang argues that generative AI might be the most important computing platform of this generation. He noted that it bridges the digital gap, citing that there&#8217;s no need to be a professional programmer to be able to say something to the computer. Huang then mentioned how individuals and businesses alike may also begin creating new apps with the help of this generative AI.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, it is not that Nvidia believes that generative AI will only serve the layman. Professionals will also benefit immensely from it as they advance their work, the company said. For example, a programmer can develop applications faster with minimal effort in debugging. An architect may also generate 3D models from 2D floor plans.</p>
<p>Overall, a change in the way things are done is one thing that is common to “every single computing era,” Huang said. And according to him, artificial intelligence is one such thing that is capable of effecting these new possibilities.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/laos-blockchain-4-0/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-ceo-generative-ai-computing/">Nvidia CEO Says Generative AI Will Birth &#8216;New Computing Era&#8217;</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-ceo-generative-ai-computing/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Laos Government Organizes Meeting on Blockchain 4.0 and Digital Economy Development</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/laos-blockchain-4-0/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/laos-blockchain-4-0/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[staff writer]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 14:23:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[metabank]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=257035</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/laos-blockchain-4-0/">Laos Government Organizes Meeting on Blockchain 4.0 and Digital Economy Development</a></p>
<p>Laos has set up a committee to oversee legal compliance and draft appropriate legislation to prepare for the digital economy.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/laos-blockchain-4-0/">Laos Government Organizes Meeting on Blockchain 4.0 and Digital Economy Development</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/laos-blockchain-4-0/">Laos Government Organizes Meeting on Blockchain 4.0 and Digital Economy Development</a></p>
<p>A conference organized by the Laotian government on May 26, 2023, <a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/laos-government-reportedly-prioritizes-blockchain-technology-for-digital-transformation" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">brought</a> together national blockchain and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-web-3-0/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Web3</a> experts. The meeting’s goal was to discuss the implementation of blockchain 4.0 in Laos&#8217; economic sectors.  The conference examined the digital potential of the nation and ways to apply digital technology to various sectors of the economy. According to reports, MetaBank and the government of Laos are working on a system to aid in the study and creation of the blockchain 4.0 initiative.</p>
<p>The Laotian government is actively pursuing the use of digital technology through Blockchain 4.0 in order to, among other things, raise the living standards of its citizens, strengthen its foreign exchange reserves, and create new sources of tax revenue. Prime Minister Sonexay Siphadone emphasized the benefits of implementing blockchain technology in a variety of administrative and public services, emphasizing its significance in achieving the country&#8217;s ninth five-year economic and social development plan.</p>
<p>In order to prepare for the digital economy, it was suggested that a committee be formed to make sure the whole process follows legal processes and also create essential legislation. To further support this vision, MetaBank is collaborating with the Lao Ministry of Technology to set up research and development facilities.</p>
<h2>Laos Previous Moves towards Utilizing Blockchain and Digital Technology</h2>
<p>The May 26 meeting on incorporating blockchain 4.0 into some aspects of the economy is not Laos’ first move towards integrating digital technology into its system. In February, the Laotian central bank also worked with a Japanese blockchain developer to test its digital currency. The plan was to harness the privilege of digital technology to make financial services more accessible since more than 70% of Laotian citizens don’t have a bank account.</p>
<p>The Laos government is also working with Cambodia to develop a cross-border payment system to make digital currencies more attractive.</p>
<h2>Blockchain Technology Could Continue to Get Greater Adoption</h2>
<p>Blockchain technology has been the subject of in-depth study and testing across many industries. Blockchain 3.0 concentrates on solving problems with second-generation blockchains, but Blockchain 4.0 is the next step in the development of the technology with the goal of providing innovative solutions.</p>
<p>Blockchain 4.0 brings many advantages to individuals, the Internet, businesses, and the government. These include enhanced data management capabilities, heightened security measures, and increased transparency in operations and transactions. By leveraging Blockchain 4.0 in many industries, institutions can expect better efficiency in their daily activities.</p>
<p>Apart from Laos, a number of countries like Nigeria, the United States, and Malaysia, among others, are already using blockchain technologies to create digital currencies and solutions for better inclusion in their financial services. Countries like Russia, Australia, and India are also starting to test the solution this year. As countries and industries begin to explore blockchain solutions, we expect to see the technology get more adopted in a short time.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ark-invest-cathie-wood-nvidia/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/laos-blockchain-4-0/">Laos Government Organizes Meeting on Blockchain 4.0 and Digital Economy Development</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/laos-blockchain-4-0/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ark Invest’s Cathie Wood Calls Nvidia Valuations Stretched, Justifies Exit</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ark-invest-cathie-wood-nvidia/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ark-invest-cathie-wood-nvidia/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 12:44:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investors News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ark invest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cathie Wood]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nvidia]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=257016</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ark-invest-cathie-wood-nvidia/">Ark Invest&#8217;s Cathie Wood Calls Nvidia Valuations Stretched, Justifies Exit</a></p>
<p>Cathie Wood stated that NVDA stock is priced ahead of the curve and trading at 25X expected revenue for this year. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ark-invest-cathie-wood-nvidia/">Ark Invest&#8217;s Cathie Wood Calls Nvidia Valuations Stretched, Justifies Exit</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ark-invest-cathie-wood-nvidia/">Ark Invest&#8217;s Cathie Wood Calls Nvidia Valuations Stretched, Justifies Exit</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ark-invest/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ark Invest</a>&#8216;s Cathie Wood, known for taking bold bets on new-age tech companies, has justified their exit from <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/nvidia/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Nvidia</a> (NASDAQ: NVDA) earlier this year. Last Wednesday, May 24, NVDA stock jumped by more than 20% in a single day moving closer to the $400 level. In her tweets on Monday, May 29, the ARK Innovation ETF (ticker ARKK) manager justified the exit from the stock. Wood added that the world&#8217;s most valuable chipmaker has been priced &#8220;ahead of the curve”.</p>
<p>Earlier this year in January 2023, the ARKK fund exited from Nvidia, after which, the stock has more than doubled and is close to hitting a $1 trillion valuation. However, Wood noted that NVDA stock is trading 25 times the estimated sales for the current financial year as investor enthusiasm spikes over Nvidia&#8217;s push in the AI industry. In comparison, this is six times its peers on the Philadelphia Semiconductor Index as well as 12 times that of Microsoft Corp.</p>
<p>However, we see, NVDA stock has been trading at a premium since the pandemic. But after the strong price surge this year, the gap looks more pronounced. On the other hand, some analysts also believe that the outlook for chips isn&#8217;t quite picking up yet amid the tepid demand for consumer electronics.</p>
<p>“Recent results at Nvidia have heightened expectations for AI servers,” SMBC Nikko Securities Inc analysts including Takeru Hanaya <a href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/too-rich-for-cathie-wood-nvidia-shares-stretch-valuation-limits-1.1926327" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">wrote</a> in a note. Still, there is a “contrast between AI expectations and overall market weakness,” demonstrated by inventory adjustments and ongoing price cuts in the chip industry.</p>
<h2>Nvidia&#8217;s Push in the AI Space</h2>
<p>Jensen Huang, who co-founded Nvidia in 1993 is still running the company. Over the years, Nvidia has made a name for itself for being the leading chip manufacturer while catering to different industrial requirements of gaming, cloud computing, etc.</p>
<p>At the Computex trade show on Monday, May 29, Huang unveiled a number of AI products across new robotics design, gaming capabilities, advertising services, and networking technology. Furthermore, Huang also unveiled Nvidia&#8217;s AI supercomputer platform called <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-ai-supercomputer-computex-2023/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">DGX GH200</a> which will help tech companies to create successors to the popular platform ChatGPT. In a note to investors, independent analyst William Keating wrote:</p>
<blockquote><p>“We basically feel that Nvidia’s stock is in bubble territory, regardless of the future potential growth. In other words, we think the train has left the station and we see little point in chasing it down the tunnel at this stage.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Based on how much cash Nvidia generates, the company is far more expensive than its peers. Nvidia&#8217;s cash flow valuation is over 140 times, surpassing its peers Advanced Micro Devices Inc. and Monolithic Power Systems Inc., which have cash flow valuations less than half of Nvidia&#8217;s.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-treasury-yields-congress-debt-ceiling/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ark-invest-cathie-wood-nvidia/">Ark Invest&#8217;s Cathie Wood Calls Nvidia Valuations Stretched, Justifies Exit</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ark-invest-cathie-wood-nvidia/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>US Treasury Yields Slide amid Anticipation for Congress Debt Ceiling Vote</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-treasury-yields-congress-debt-ceiling/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-treasury-yields-congress-debt-ceiling/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 12:39:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[joe biden]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=257037</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-treasury-yields-congress-debt-ceiling/">US Treasury Yields Slide amid Anticipation for Congress Debt Ceiling Vote</a></p>
<p>The 2-year and 10-year Treasury yields dropped Tuesday as investors await the legislative voting outcome on the debt ceiling bill.  </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-treasury-yields-congress-debt-ceiling/">US Treasury Yields Slide amid Anticipation for Congress Debt Ceiling Vote</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-treasury-yields-congress-debt-ceiling/">US Treasury Yields Slide amid Anticipation for Congress Debt Ceiling Vote</a></p>
<p>US Treasury yields slumped today ahead of a Congress on the federal government&#8217;s proposed debt ceiling bill. Treasury yields tumbled Tuesday as markets reopened, with investors bracing themselves for a lawmaker vote on the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/joe-biden/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Biden</a> administration&#8217;s 11th-hour debt ceiling proposal.</p>
<p>Late Sunday, US President Joe Biden and House Speaker Kevin McCarthy <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/biden-debt-ceiling-japanese-market/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">struck a deal</a> to raise the nation&#8217;s debt ceiling, thereby preventing a default. Although both political leaders avoided a potential first-ever government default, the presidency must get Congress on board before a June 5th deadline.</p>
<p>As of early morning Eastern Time, the 10-year Treasury yield traded lower by 10 basis points at 3.719%. The 2-year Treasury yield was also down 7 basis points to 4.514%.</p>
<p>Elsewhere, the recently-released April personal consumption expenditures price index still weighed heavily on investors. Last Friday, the price index came in at 0.4% monthly, which surpassed expectations. Commenting at the time on the May 26th PCE report, Key Private Bank CIO George Mateyo <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/26/inflation-rose-0point4percent-in-april-and-4point7percent-from-a-year-ago-according-to-key-gauge-for-the-fed.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;With [Friday&#8217;s] hotter-than-expected PCE report, the Fed&#8217;s summer vacation may need to be cut short as consumers&#8217; vacations fuel spending. Prior to [Friday&#8217;s] release, we believe that the Fed may have been hoping to take the summer off (i.e., pause and reassess), but now, it seems as if the Fed&#8217;s job of getting inflation down is not over.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Investors to Take Cues From Treasury Yields &amp; Debt Ceiling Voting Outcome in Uncertain Economic Clime Plagued by Rising Interest Rates</h2>
<p>Much uncertainty remains over the Federal Reserve&#8217;s interest rate policy, especially regarding future rate hikes. For now, investors remain on edge and continue to take cues from fiscal data, more of which are expected throughout this week. However, all eyes would also be trained on Congress, with debt ceiling voting expected to occur between now and Friday.</p>
<p>Republicans and Democrats from the upper and lower legislative chambers are currently mulling the bill. According to reports, the House of Representatives could vote by Wednesday, with the Senate following suit later in the week.</p>
<p>Despite the bill&#8217;s perceived unpopularity, Biden remains optimistic that his proposal would secure the necessary bipartisan support for implementation. On Sunday, the US president implored both sides of Congress to come together to swiftly implement the debt ceiling agreement. Furthermore, the commander-in-chief expressed relief at having a deal with the Republican McCarthy. According to Biden, the agreement &#8220;prevents the worst possible crisis&#8221; and &#8220;takes the threat of a catastrophic default off the table&#8221;.</p>
<p>The bill, dubbed the &#8220;Fiscal Responsibility 5 Act of 2023&#8221;, allows the government to borrow more and spend on social welfare schemes. However, the debt ceiling proposal also calls for cuts to other spending excesses in other areas.</p>
<p>Biden&#8217;s US debt ceiling proposal <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-debt-ceiling-crypto-tax-bill/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">struck out a crypto tax bill</a> proposed in March. The Digital Asset Mining Energy (DAME) excise tax sought to impose a 30% levy on mining firms for environmental and societal damage.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/robert-f-kennedy-jr-sec-crypto/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-treasury-yields-congress-debt-ceiling/">US Treasury Yields Slide amid Anticipation for Congress Debt Ceiling Vote</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-treasury-yields-congress-debt-ceiling/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Robert F. Kennedy Jr. Criticizes SEC’s Enforcement Action against Crypto</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/robert-f-kennedy-jr-sec-crypto/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/robert-f-kennedy-jr-sec-crypto/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[staff writer]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 12:30:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=257018</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/robert-f-kennedy-jr-sec-crypto/">Robert F. Kennedy Jr. Criticizes SEC’s Enforcement Action against Crypto</a></p>
<p>US presidential candidate Robert F. Kennedy Jr. shared his disapproval of SEC's enforcement action against the crypto industry and plans to include crypto-friendly members on the board when elected president. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/robert-f-kennedy-jr-sec-crypto/">Robert F. Kennedy Jr. Criticizes SEC’s Enforcement Action against Crypto</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/robert-f-kennedy-jr-sec-crypto/">Robert F. Kennedy Jr. Criticizes SEC’s Enforcement Action against Crypto</a></p>
<p>In an <a href="https://www.thestreet.com/cryptocurrency/news/crypto-rfk-jr-robert-f-kennedy-exclusive-interview" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">exclusive interview</a> with TheStreet, Robert F. Kennedy Jr. (RFK Jr.), an aspiring US presidential candidate, criticized the Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) for taking an enforcement approach to regulating the crypto industry.</p>
<p>Kennedy said such a heavy regulatory strategy might significantly affect the country&#8217;s digital asset ecosystem. When elected as president, he plans to appoint SEC staff with a favorable view of virtual assets to ensure that the US remains a hub for crypto.</p>
<p>&#8220;I don&#8217;t want people on the SEC commission who are anti-crypto,&#8221; Kennedy said. &#8220;At most, they should be neutral, and we should have people on there who are from the crypto community,&#8221; said Kennedy.</p>
<h2>US SEC No Longer Protects the Interest of the American People</h2>
<p>The presidential aspirant contrasted the current SEC system with the original intentions of his grandfather, Joseph P. Kennedy Sr., who aimed to bring transparency and fairness to the financial system during his tenure as the first SEC commissioner.</p>
<p>Kennedy said the financial regulator no longer serves its original purpose of protecting the American people. Instead, he argued that it primarily safeguards the interests of banks, particularly central banks, rather than ensuring transparency and fairness for everyday individuals.</p>
<p>&#8220;SEC&#8217;s function now is not to protect the American people, but to protect the banks &#8211; particularly the central banks and those interests. What they&#8217;re doing is obscure, it&#8217;s not transparent, and it&#8217;s not bringing transparency to our system,&#8221; said Kennedy.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Gives People a Way Out</h2>
<p>Speaking to TheStreet, Kennedy also shared his admiration for Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a>) and its value proposition of trust and transparency in the face of turmoil such as inflation. Although he has not personally invested in Bitcoin, the US presidential aspirant commended its underlying value as a base currency.</p>
<p>He praised its finite supply and infinite divisibility, making it an ideal medium of exchange. He said the virtual asset offers individuals an exit from traditional monetary systems by having intrinsic value and providing an alternative option.</p>
<p>Kennedy further stated that nobody could manipulate the crypto asset. According to him, Bitcoin&#8217;s democratic nature, driven by miners and non-manipulable algorithms, makes it a trustworthy digital currency.</p>
<p>&#8220;The Bitcoin that exists on the Earth is infinitely divisible, so it&#8217;s the perfect currency – it has an intrinsic value and gives people a way out. And nobody can manipulate it. There&#8217;s no human being that can manipulate it,&#8221; said Kennedy.</p>
<p>The presidential aspirant declared his support for the crypto asset last week during the Bitcoin 2023 conference in Miami, where he publicly <a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/breaking-robert-f-kennedy-jr-to-accept-campaign-donations-in-bitcoin" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announced</a> that his campaign would accept BTC donations. He also vowed to protect the digital asset against &#8220;invasive surveillance&#8221;.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/eth-price-11-8k-51k-2030-vaneck/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/robert-f-kennedy-jr-sec-crypto/">Robert F. Kennedy Jr. Criticizes SEC’s Enforcement Action against Crypto</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/robert-f-kennedy-jr-sec-crypto/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>VanEck: ETH Price Can Hit $11.8K with up to $51K in Revenue by 2030</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/eth-price-11-8k-51k-2030-vaneck/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/eth-price-11-8k-51k-2030-vaneck/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 11:16:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vaneck]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=257000</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/eth-price-11-8k-51k-2030-vaneck/">VanEck: ETH Price Can Hit $11.8K with up to $51K in Revenue by 2030</a></p>
<p>VanEck analysts have explained in detail why ETH price could rise above $11K by 2030, with revenue of more than $50 billion.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/eth-price-11-8k-51k-2030-vaneck/">VanEck: ETH Price Can Hit $11.8K with up to $51K in Revenue by 2030</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/eth-price-11-8k-51k-2030-vaneck/">VanEck: ETH Price Can Hit $11.8K with up to $51K in Revenue by 2030</a></p>
<p>According to a VanEck report, the Ethereum (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ETH</a>) price could hit $11.8K by 2030. The global investment manager <a href="https://www.vaneck.com/us/en/blogs/digital-assets/matthew-sigel-ethereum-price-prediction-118k-by-2030/#:~:text=Ethereum%20Price%20Prediction%3A%20%2411.8k%20by%202030" target="_blank" rel="noopener">exposited</a> its ETH price predictions earlier in the month.</p>
<p>On May 9th, VanEck’s Digital Assets Research Head, Matthew Sigel, and Digital Assets Senior Investment Analyst Patrick Bush made the bold claims. The duo provided a detailed valuation methodology incorporating cash flow projections and fully diluted valuation calculations to support their argument.</p>
<p>At the time, Sigel and Bush explained that their Ether price claims were updated following the recent hard fork. According to the VanEck analysts, the projected 2030 ETH price increase could also push annual revenue from $2.6B to $51B. Furthermore, the duo said their price predictions assume a 70% smart contract protocol for the popular digital currency. This projection was discounted to $5.3K at a 12% capital cost derived from Ethereum’s recent beta. Furthermore, Sigel and Bush assessed the altcoin’s market capture across critical sectors. They also explored its store-of-value potential in the crypto space. According to analysts, ETH’s new proof-of-stake status could see the crypto rival US T-bills.</p>
<h2>VanEck Methodology Used to Ascertain ETH 2030 Price</h2>
<p>VanEck’s analysis assessed ETH’s price value by estimating cash flows for the year ending on April 30th, 2030. The crypto’s price valuation methodology also involved a series of calculations to arrive at a cash flow figure. One of these was accounting for global tax rate deductions,</p>
<p>Meanwhile, to get ETH’s 2030 fully diluted valuation, analysts applied a long-term estimated cash flow yield of 7%, subtracting the long-term crypto growth rate of 4%. Lastly, the fully diluted valuation total is divided by the expected number of coins in circulation, with the result discounted by 12% to April 20th, 2030.</p>
<p>VanEck analysts also acknowledged ETH system transaction fees and Maximum Extractable Value (MEV) as a revenue line. Additionally, the firm’s analysts also asserted that the token is evolving beyond its traditional use cases of being a transactional currency or a consumable commodity. Although not quite on <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin’s</a> store-of-value level, Sigel and Bush opined that Ether could still become a store of value for human capital maximization purposes. The VanEck analysts also pointed out the perceived dynamism of ETH’s store-of-value applicability within and outside the Ethereum blockchain. According to the duo, the token’s value is versatile in securing applications, protocols, and ecosystems throughout the crypto space.</p>
<h2>ETH Price Base Case Scenario</h2>
<p>In a base case scenario, VanEck analysts assume Ether will achieve an annual revenue of $51B in the year ending April 30th, 2030. Furthermore, the duo deducted a 1% validator fee from the total and a 15% global tax rate to arrive at a $42.90B cash flow for the same period. Sigel and Bush also noted:</p>
<blockquote><p>“We base these estimates on the thesis that Ethereum becomes the dominant open-source global settlement network that hosts substantial portions of the commercial activity of business sectors with the highest potential to gain from moving their business functions to public blockchains. In a portfolio of similar smart contract platforms, we assume to own a collection of call options, with the dominant platform likely to take a majority market share.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Using the parameters above, VanEck’s analysts asserted that ETH’s base case discounted price, as of May 9th, was $5,359.71. The leading altcoin is currently changing hands at just over $1,900.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/musk-resignation-twitter-dogecoin-doge/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/eth-price-11-8k-51k-2030-vaneck/">VanEck: ETH Price Can Hit $11.8K with up to $51K in Revenue by 2030</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/eth-price-11-8k-51k-2030-vaneck/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4067 metric#misses=42 metric#hit-ratio=99.0 metric#bytes=1005136 metric#prefetches=186 metric#store-reads=20 metric#store-writes=3 metric#store-hits=192 metric#store-misses=3 metric#sql-queries=36 metric#ms-total=95.26 metric#ms-cache=4.66 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.2119 metric#ms-cache-ratio=4.9 -->