<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 00:59:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Is Silvergate stock a &#8216;buy&#8217; after it suspended preferred stock dividend?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/sell-silvergate-stock-suspends-preferred-stock-dividend/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wajeeh Khan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 00:58:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=101245</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Silvergate Capital Corp suspends dividend on its preferred stock. Wedbush Securities analyst reiterates his neutral&#160;rating on &#8220;SI&#8221;. Silvergate stock is currently down over 85% since mid-August. Silvergate Capital Corp ended 5.0% down on Friday after the crypto bank suspended dividend on its preferred stock. Silvergate is trying to preserve capital The embattled digital currency services [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sell-silvergate-stock-suspends-preferred-stock-dividend/">Is Silvergate stock a &#8216;buy&#8217; after it suspended preferred stock dividend?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Silvergate Capital Corp suspends dividend on its preferred stock.</li>
<li>Wedbush Securities analyst reiterates his neutral&nbsp;rating on &ldquo;SI&rdquo;.</li>
<li>Silvergate stock is currently down over 85% since mid-August.</li>
</ul>
<p>Silvergate Capital Corp ended 5.0% down on Friday after the crypto bank suspended dividend on its preferred stock.</p>
<h2>Silvergate is trying to preserve capital</h2>
<p>The embattled digital currency services company is cutting back on the payout to preserve capital. Its <a href="https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20230126006026/en/Silvergate-Suspends-Series-A-Preferred-Stock-Dividend" target="_blank" rel="noopener">press release</a> reads:</p>
<blockquote><p>This decision reflects the Company&rsquo;s focus on maintaining a highly liquid balance sheet with a strong capital position. Company continues to maintain a cash position in excess of its digital asset customer related deposits.</p></blockquote>
<p>The California-based company also confirmed that its Board will re-evaluate the quarterly payment once market conditions improve.</p>
<p>Silvergate stock has lost over 85% since mid-August, related partially to the FTX collapse. Consequently, billionaire investor <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ark-fund-unloads-silvergate-stake-131252888.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Cathie Wood</a> almost entirely pulled out of it at the start of the new year.</p>
<h2>Is Silvergate stock a buy?</h2>
<p>According to a Wedbush Securities analyst, suspending Series A preferred stock dividend will make things more difficult for this financial infrastructure solutions firm in the long run.</p>
<p>Reiterating his &ldquo;neutral&rdquo; rating on the Silvergate stock on Friday, David Chiaverini said:</p>
<blockquote><p>We believe this move could raise Silvergate&rsquo;s cost of capital down the road when Silvergate attempts to tap the capital markets for a future capital raise. Any new fixed income or preferred issuance will require a higher coupon.</p></blockquote>
<p>His $13 price objective on the stock suggests it lacks any upside whatsoever. Earlier in January, Silvergate Capital Corp said average deposits from digital asset customers tanked 39% to $7.3 billion in its fourth quarter as <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/silvergate-plunges-after-crypto-meltdown-triggered-deposit-run/">Coin Journal reported here.</a></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sell-silvergate-stock-suspends-preferred-stock-dividend/">Is Silvergate stock a &#8216;buy&#8217; after it suspended preferred stock dividend?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Moody&#8217;s is building a scoring system for stablecoins: report</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/moodys-is-building-a-scoring-system-for-stablecoins-report/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/moodys-is-building-a-scoring-system-for-stablecoins-report/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 18:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/moodys-is-building-a-scoring-system-for-stablecoins-report/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Moody&#8217;s wants to build a scoring system for stablecoins as the market grows amid increased regulatory attention. The system will provide an rating system for the top stablecoins based on quality of their reserve attestations. The leading stablecoins by market cap today are Tether (USDT), USD Coin (USD) and Binance USD (BUSD). Moody&#8217;s Corporation, a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/moodys-is-building-a-scoring-system-for-stablecoins-report/">Moody&#8217;s is building a scoring system for stablecoins: report</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Moody&rsquo;s wants to build a scoring system for stablecoins as the market grows amid increased regulatory attention.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The system will provide an rating system for the top stablecoins based on quality of their reserve attestations.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The leading stablecoins by market cap today are Tether (USDT), USD Coin (USD) and Binance USD (BUSD).</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Moody&rsquo;s Corporation, a leading global credit-ratings company, is reportedly developing a scoring system for the stablecoin industry.</p>
<p dir="ltr">A <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-01-26/credit-rater-moody-preps-crypto-stablecoins-scoring-system" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">report</a> by Bloomberg that cited sources familiar with the development, noted that Moody&rsquo;s solution will not be an official credit rating. However, the integrated risk assessment giant is looking to deliver a platform that offers a scoring system based on a comprehensive analysis of the world&rsquo;s largest <a href="https://coinjournal.net/glossary/stablecoin/">stablecoins</a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Moody&rsquo;s already has a footprint in the crypto space, with major digital asset companies such as Coinbase getting credit ratings from the US-based provider. The credit rater also has a research unit that offers access to analytic reports touching on various issues in the crypto industry.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to the report, the new system will offer access to ratings for up to 20 stablecoins, with the company utilizing the latest technology to score the asset-backed tokens. Among the most important metrics to consider will be the reserves and quality of attestations for each of the stablecoins.</p>
<p dir="ltr">People familiar with the project say its development is still in the early stages.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Moody&rsquo;s to score major stablecoins</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Stablecoins allow holders to participate in the crypto market, including in value transfer without being overly exposed to potentially high volatility characteristic of cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin, Ethereum and so on. &nbsp;But they are not without risks, particularly liquidity and manipulation.</p>
<p dir="ltr">It&rsquo;s these issues that have seen stablecoins increasingly fall into regulatory spotlight, especially around reserves as they must maintain a 1:1 backing to the issued tokens.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Various issuers have attestation reports to ascertain indeed every stablecoin token is backed. But regulators want to see the sector streamlined to better protect investors. As <em>CoinJournal</em> <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/stablecoin-legislation-may-come-this-year-bitwise-exec-says/">recently reported</a>, Bitwise Chief Compliance Officer Kathrine Dowling believes US stablecoin regulation will be ready before the end of 2023.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">The top stablecoins today</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The US dollar-pegged Tether (USDT) is the largest stablecoin with over $67.3 billion worth of tokens in circulation. USD Coin (USDC), another dollar backed stablecoin, follows with $43.2 billion coins in circulation. Meanwhile, Binance USD (BUSD) is the third largest with just over $15.4 billion worth of the tokens circulating.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/categories/stablecoins" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">data</a> from CoinGecko, the stablecoin market capitalization currently stands at over $137 billion. More than $68 billion was traded in the past 24 hours as of 13:20 pm ET on 27 January, 2023.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/moodys-is-building-a-scoring-system-for-stablecoins-report/">Moody&#8217;s is building a scoring system for stablecoins: report</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/moodys-is-building-a-scoring-system-for-stablecoins-report/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Institutional investors are increasingly bullish on Ethereum: report</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/institutional-investors-are-increasingly-bullish-on-ethereum-report/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/institutional-investors-are-increasingly-bullish-on-ethereum-report/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 17:17:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Institutional investors]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/institutional-investors-are-increasingly-bullish-on-ethereum-report/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>60% of respondents are convinced Ethereum will a better investment in 2023.&#160; Bitcoin is also seen as one with huge potential, while other coins attracting institutional investors are Polkadot, Cardano and XRP. Speculative interest and exposure to distributed ledger technology are main reasons for increased interest. Ethereum is the second largest cryptocurrency by market cap, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/institutional-investors-are-increasingly-bullish-on-ethereum-report/">Institutional investors are increasingly bullish on Ethereum: report</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">60% of respondents are convinced Ethereum will a better investment in 2023.&nbsp;</li>
<li dir="ltr">Bitcoin is also seen as one with huge potential, while other coins attracting institutional investors are Polkadot, Cardano and XRP.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Speculative interest and exposure to distributed ledger technology are main reasons for increased interest.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/">Ethereum</a> is the second largest cryptocurrency by market cap, with its market worth nearly $190 billion.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">While it remains behind <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a>, whose market cap as of 27 January 2023 stood at over $482 billion, institutional investors are reportedly more bullish on the cryptocurrency&rsquo;s prospects in 2023 than was the case going into the third quarter last year.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">60% of institutional investors are bullish on Ethereum</h2>
<p dir="ltr">According to the latest survey results <a href="https://a.storyblok.com/f/155294/x/f076ec53c8/coinshares-quarterly-digital-asset-investor-survey-jan-23-pdf.pdf" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">published</a> by digital assets manager CoinShares, bullish sentiment around the top altcoin by institutional investors has increased by 20% since the last survey in October 2022.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The asset manager&rsquo;s report states that 60% of respondents from major wealth majors, family offices, hedge funds and financial advisors, believe Ethereum has a better growth outlook in 2023. In October, when CoinShares published its previous Digital Asset Quarterly Fund Manager Survey, 40% of respondents had indicated a bullish outlook for the leading smart contracts platform.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Comparatively, 30% of the survey participants were bullish on Bitcoin &ndash; down from 40% in the previous report. But while most of the big money is betting on ETH, CoinShares highlighted that a growing number of investors are invested in both assets.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Other digital assets that institutional investors are eyeing in 2023 are Polkadot, Cardano, XRP, Solana and Polygon.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Why are institutional investors adding crypto to portfolios?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">According to CoinShares, the main reasons behind increased interest and investment in digital assets are speculation and the need to gain exposure to opportunities across the distributed ledger technology ecosystem.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Notably, more clients saw the recent crypto crash (after the collapse of FTX) as an opportunity, with a growing number directing fund managers to add crypto to their positions. Bitcoin and Ethereum are the most popular.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Digital assets are still the playground for hedge funds, but weighting in portfolios has increased from ATL 0.7% to represent 1.1% of portfolios. <a href="https://t.co/cCCogB3l1j">pic.twitter.com/cCCogB3l1j</a></p>
<p>&mdash; CoinShares (@CoinSharesCo) <a href="https://twitter.com/CoinSharesCo/status/1618594673018261506?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 26, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">But the asset manager says crypto&rsquo;s increased correlation to equities might be the reason fewer investors cite diversification as a key factor.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>When asked what reasons prevented investors from investing in digital assets, it is interesting to note that reputational risk saw a significant decline while regulation is still an important consideration</em>,&rdquo; CoinShares noted.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/institutional-investors-are-increasingly-bullish-on-ethereum-report/">Institutional investors are increasingly bullish on Ethereum: report</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/institutional-investors-are-increasingly-bullish-on-ethereum-report/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto bank Silvergate suspends preferred stock dividend</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-bank-silvergate-suspends-preferred-stock-dividend/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-bank-silvergate-suspends-preferred-stock-dividend/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 15:54:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-bank-silvergate-suspends-preferred-stock-dividend/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto-friendly bank Silvergate announced its suspended payment of dividends on its series A preferred stock. The company&#8217;s shares fell more than 11% pre-market after the announcement. Silvergate reported a $1 billion loss in the fourth quarter and also cut its staff by 20% amid the crypto bear market and impact of FTX collapse. Silvergate, a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-bank-silvergate-suspends-preferred-stock-dividend/">Crypto bank Silvergate suspends preferred stock dividend</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Crypto-friendly bank Silvergate announced its suspended payment of dividends on its series A preferred stock.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The company&rsquo;s shares fell more than 11% pre-market after the announcement.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Silvergate reported a $1 billion loss in the fourth quarter and also cut its staff by 20% amid the crypto bear market and impact of FTX collapse.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Silvergate, a crypto-friendly bank that&rsquo;s lately hit a rough stretch following the collapse of crypto exchange FTX, has suspended dividend payment on its preferred stock.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Specifially, the crypto bank says it is suspending payment of dividends on the its 5.375% Fixed Rate Non-Cumulative Perpetual Preferred Stock, Series A. The US-based company is taking the move to help preserve capital following the effects of recent turbulence across the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/">crypto ecosystem</a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>This decision reflects the company&rsquo;s focus on maintaining a highly liquid balance sheet with a strong capital position as it navigates recent volatility in the digital asset industry</em>,&rdquo; the firm said in a <a href="https://ir.silvergate.com/news/news-details/2023/Silvergate-Suspends-Series-A-Preferred-Stock-Dividend/default.aspx" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">press release</a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to the news release, the Board of Directors will re-examine the company&rsquo;s payment of quarterly dividends at a later date, with this dependent on how &ldquo;<em>market conditions evolve</em>.&rdquo;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Silvergate shares fall sharply</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Following Friday&rsquo;s news, shares of parent company Silvergate Capital (NYSE:SI) fell more than 11% in early morning trading, hitting lows of $12.55.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Despite a decent run for crypto in the last few weeks, where Bitcoin broke above $23k, Silvergate&rsquo;s shares have struggled amid negative sentiment.</p>
<p dir="ltr">At the time of writing, the shares were trading at around $12.93, still more than 8% down on the day. The company&rsquo;s stock is down nearly 27% year-to-date, with the losses coming on the back of a brutal bear market for the broader cryptocurrency industry.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As previously <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/silvergate-plunges-after-crypto-meltdown-triggered-deposit-run/">highlighted</a>, Silvergate reported a $1 billion loss during the fourth quarter and moved to slash its workforce by 20% as the negative impact of FTX&rsquo;s implosion hit the company.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The crypto bank also reported that customer digital assets deposits had fallen significantly as uncertainty swept through the crypto market.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-bank-silvergate-suspends-preferred-stock-dividend/">Crypto bank Silvergate suspends preferred stock dividend</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-bank-silvergate-suspends-preferred-stock-dividend/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Leading digital wealth platform Yield App acquires Trofi Group</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/leading-digital-wealth-platform-yield-app-acquires-trofi-group/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/leading-digital-wealth-platform-yield-app-acquires-trofi-group/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 15:21:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/leading-digital-wealth-platform-yield-app-acquires-trofi-group/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Yield App is a digital wealth platform that offers safe custody of digital assets. The platform allows customers to exchange and earn on their assets at market-leading rates. The acquisition adds structured products to the Yield Apps product suite. Digital wealth management platform Yield App yesterday announced it has acquired Trofi Group, a platform that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/leading-digital-wealth-platform-yield-app-acquires-trofi-group/">Leading digital wealth platform Yield App acquires Trofi Group</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Yield App is a digital wealth platform that offers safe custody of digital assets.</li>
<li>The platform allows customers to exchange and earn on their assets at market-leading rates.</li>
<li>The acquisition adds structured products to the Yield Apps product suite.</li>
</ul>
<p>Digital wealth management platform Yield App yesterday announced it has acquired Trofi Group, a platform that offers structured solutions for cryptocurrencies. The acquisition brings four new structured products to the Yiled App product suite.</p>
<p>Besides providing customers with additional products, the move also makes Yield App one of the leading digital wealth platforms.</p>
<h2>What specifically does Trofi Group bring on board?</h2>
<p>The team at Trofi Group boasts of 30 years experience in derivatives desks at JP Morgan and HSBC. Now that they will join hands with Yield App in building best-in-class crypto-structured products means Yield App will provide a superior suite of products.</p>
<p>Commenting on the acquisition, the CEO of Yield App, Tim Frost, said:</p>
<p><em>&ldquo;The acquisition of Trofi Group establishes Yield App as a pioneer within the crypto-structured products arena, making us one of only a few platforms to bridge the gap between traditional finance and crypto. We are grateful to the team at Trofi for trusting us to continue their excellent work in bringing enhanced yield structured products to crypto. We look forward to leveraging the team&rsquo;s vast experience to expand Yield App&rsquo;s suite of digital wealth management solutions.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p>Following the acquisition, Yield App will be launching a beta version of a dedicated investment app duped &ldquo;Trofi, powered by Yield App.&rdquo; The app will allow customers to access Yield App&rsquo;s first crypto-structured products through four different strategies and other products including the dual currency, the range, Sharkfin, and the Target.</p>
<p>Dual currency allows investors to acquire cryptocurrencies at a lower price at a predetermined point in the future, while also earning yield. The Range is a structured product that allows investors to generate yield assuming the markets will remain within a specified price range. Sharkfin allows investors with a moderately bullish view of future prices to earn a guaranteed minimum coupon with the potential to generate a high yield at maturity. The Target product allows investors with a bullish view of the future price of a cryptocurrency to earn a high yield.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/leading-digital-wealth-platform-yield-app-acquires-trofi-group/">Leading digital wealth platform Yield App acquires Trofi Group</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/leading-digital-wealth-platform-yield-app-acquires-trofi-group/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Polygon’s Gains Network DEX volume crosses $1.5B as Polygon price reclaims $1</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/polygons-gains-network-dex-volume-crosses-1-5b-as-polygon-price-reclaims-1/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/polygons-gains-network-dex-volume-crosses-1-5b-as-polygon-price-reclaims-1/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 12:50:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/polygons-gains-network-dex-volume-crosses-1-5b-as-polygon-price-reclaims-1/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>At press time, Polygon (MATIC) was trading at $1.09, up 8.93% in 24 hours. Gains Network DEX was initially released on Polygon before being deployed on Arbitrum. The Gains Network DEX has greatly contributed to the recent rising transactional activity on Polygon. The price of Polygon (MATIC) has been steadily rising in recent weeks and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/polygons-gains-network-dex-volume-crosses-1-5b-as-polygon-price-reclaims-1/">Polygon’s Gains Network DEX volume crosses $1.5B as Polygon price reclaims $1</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul class="decimal_type">
<li>At press time, Polygon (MATIC) was trading at $1.09, up 8.93% in 24 hours.</li>
<li>Gains Network DEX was initially released on Polygon before being deployed on Arbitrum.</li>
<li>The Gains Network DEX has greatly contributed to the recent rising transactional activity on Polygon.</li>
</ul>
<p>The <a href="https://coinjournal.net/polygon/">price of Polygon (MATIC)</a> has been steadily rising in recent weeks and it has regained the $1.0 level as the broader crypto market continues to recover.</p>
<p>In addition to <a href="https://coinjournal.net/polygon/what-is-polygon/">Polygon </a>just following the broader crypto market in the current bullish trend, there is an increased transaction activity on the network mainly because of the Decentralized exchange (DEX) Gains Network which was released on the network. The Gains Network DEX was later deployed on Arbitrum and its daily trading volume on Arbitrum has now crossed $230 million.</p>
<h2>The Gains Network decentralized exchange</h2>
<p>It is now barely a month since the Gains Network was deployed on the Arbitrum blockchain. The DEX allows crypto traders to trade various financial derivatives of various assets including crypto, US stocks, and indices using smart contracts. It also allows stakers to earn as much as 10% interest on their GNS tokens.</p>
<p>The DEX provides an opportunity for global traders who would otherwise not be able to trade US-listed instruments without relying on banks. The DEX has so far processed over $25 million in trading volume.</p>
<p>Earlier this week, the DEX started a <a href="https://twitter.com/GainsNetwork_io/status/1616468328956022784">trading contest</a> with rewards totalling $100,000, which is likely the reason for the recent spike in trading volume.</p>
<p>Besides having a direct impact on the Polygon (MATIC) price, the increased activity on the Gains Network has also resulted in the GNS token price rising by more than 40% over the past week.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/polygons-gains-network-dex-volume-crosses-1-5b-as-polygon-price-reclaims-1/">Polygon’s Gains Network DEX volume crosses $1.5B as Polygon price reclaims $1</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/polygons-gains-network-dex-volume-crosses-1-5b-as-polygon-price-reclaims-1/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Can Metacade Lead a Bear Market Rally?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/can-metacade-lead-a-bear-market-rally/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/can-metacade-lead-a-bear-market-rally/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice Davies]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 12:49:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/can-metacade-lead-a-bear-market-rally/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>After the&#160;madness of the 2021 bull run, the&#160;crypto winter really hit hard in 2022, with difficulty saying how long it will continue. Experienced investors know that while interest in crypto may be a little lower, bear markets are actually the perfect time to accumulate strong projects with utility in order to make the most of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/can-metacade-lead-a-bear-market-rally/">Can Metacade Lead a Bear Market Rally?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">After the&nbsp;<a href="https://edition.cnn.com/2021/05/09/investing/dogecoin-elon-musk-snl/index.html" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>madness</u></a> of the 2021 bull run, the&nbsp;<a href="https://www.banklesstimes.com/news/2022/11/28/62percent-of-investors-defied-the-crypto-winter-to-increase-their-investments-over-the-last-year/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>crypto winter</u></a> really hit hard in 2022, with difficulty saying how long it will continue. Experienced investors know that while interest in crypto may be a little lower, bear markets are actually the perfect time to accumulate strong projects with utility in order to make the most of the next bull run. Even in bear market conditions, there are still gains to be made in a bear market rally.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade</u></a> is a new project that is widely regarded in investment groups as a top pick for success in 2023 and beyond, and with some incredible presale results pouring $3.9 million into the project in just 9 weeks, many are turning to the idea that Metacade just might be a project capable of leading a bear market rally. &nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Metacade?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade is a revolution in Web3 gaming, and the project is well underway on its ambition to build the largest play-to-earn (P2E) arcade in the metaverse. The project has turned a lot of heads as a result of the comprehensive&nbsp;<a href="https://metacade.co/whitepaper.pdf" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>whitepaper</u></a> released ahead of the presale, which details plans to build an extensive ecosystem of functionality around the P2E arcade, driving huge levels of engagement and shaking up gaming in the process.</p>
<p dir="ltr">By leveraging the most expansive set of gaming titles, the project is putting itself in pole position for some serious momentum to build in 2023. This is compounded by the positive impact of a number of other complementary features that make up the core of its ecosystem.</p>
<p dir="ltr">One key feature is a compelling and innovative rewards mechanism. Aside from earning rewards for playing games in the P2E arcade, users are able to benefit across different playing styles, competitive gaming ladders and tournament play.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Casual gamers can still earn an income by making valuable contributions to the platform. This could be through activities such as writing reviews of games or sharing useful alpha in order to reward users for helping improve the platform. This will become an effective driver for user growth, irrespective of whether the markets are experiencing a crypto winter.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How does Metacade work?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade has a range of interlinking features, and in order to get the most out of the platform, the project has created a utility token. The MCADE token enables not only the rewards mechanisms but also serves as a medium of exchange across the platform. Activities like purchasing merchandise or entering tournaments are facilitated by the token, creating its inherent worth.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The utility of the Metacade token has been shaped in such a way as to be investor-friendly, including supporting a staking mechanism that MCADE holders can utilize. This provides an ideal set of investment circumstances for would-be investors. While the token value will inevitably increase over time, they can also earn a passive income in return for supporting the network.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This high level of token utility is just one reason why the project seems to be capable of leading a bear market rally, given that utility will drive a price increase through necessity, whether the crypto space is in the midst of a crypto winter or not.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Finally, the Metagrant initiative is a fascinating feature that is rightly drawing attention. It allows game developers to present their game plans to the Metacade community for a chance to receive funding. MCADE holders will be able to use their tokens to vote on which projects receive treasury funds, ensuring a top-quality gaming lineup as well as solid user retention through an extreme level of engagement.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Is Metacade a good investment?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The project developers have understood the need for long-term self-sufficiency, and as a result, a number of different revenue streams have already been outlined to help drive the project forward over time.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">MCADE itself clearly demonstrates a high level of utility, and its price should be expected to rise in line with the adoption of the platform. Given that so many of the project&rsquo;s features are designed to create positive cycles of engagement, it&rsquo;s no surprise that MCADE has been well-received and has enough potential to drive a bear market rally all on its own.</p>
<p><strong>You can participate in the MCADE presale&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong><u>here</u></strong></a><strong>.</strong></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/can-metacade-lead-a-bear-market-rally/">Can Metacade Lead a Bear Market Rally?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/can-metacade-lead-a-bear-market-rally/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto price predictions: Solana, Theta Network, HOOK</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-predictions-solana-theta-network-hook/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-predictions-solana-theta-network-hook/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 11:39:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[THETA News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-predictions-solana-theta-network-hook/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Solana price has formed a triple-top pattern and a head and shoulders. Theta Network has moved above the cup and handle pattern. Hooked Protocol&#8217;s HOOK has surged above its all-time high. Cryptocurrency prices moved sideways this week as the US dollar index continued its downward trend. Bitcoin rose above $23,000 for the first time in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-predictions-solana-theta-network-hook/">Crypto price predictions: Solana, Theta Network, HOOK</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Solana price has formed a triple-top pattern and a head and shoulders.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Theta Network has moved above the cup and handle pattern.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Hooked Protocol&rsquo;s HOOK has surged above its all-time high.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Cryptocurrency prices moved sideways this week as the US dollar index continued its downward trend. Bitcoin rose above $23,000 for the first time in months while the total market cap of all cryptocurrencies rose to over $1 trillion. In this report, we will provide predictions for some of the top cryptocurrencies, including Solana, Theta Network, and Hooked Protocol.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Solana price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Solana (SOL/USD) price has made a spectacular comeback as investors raise their bets that the blockchain will recover amid FTX woes. It has also been helped by the surge of NFTs traded in the ecosystem, as we wrote&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/solana-could-maintain-bullishness-if-this-happens/"><u>here</u></a>. As such, Solana price soared to a high of $26.53, the highest point since FX imploded.</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, the 4H chart is sending a warning about the coin. A closer look shows that it has formed what looks like a triple-top pattern whose neckline is at $20.48. This pattern also has a close resemblance to a head and shoulders pattern. The two patterns are some of the most bearish patterns in the industry.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, there is a likelihood that Solana will have a bearish breakout in the coming days as sellers target the neckline of the two patterns at $20. This price is about 15% below the current level. It is also slightly below the 23.6% Fibonacci Retracement level.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/00/27/1674819463224-9a6c6a6b-0959-425a-af1a-6e9d21993bc6.png" style="width: 546px;height: 258.44px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="546" height="258.44"></p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/SOLUSD/?exchange=COINBASE"><u>SOL/USD chart by TradingView</u></a></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy Solana</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>

    <p>eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=MTAxMTY3&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=VA&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy SOL with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    Public</h3>

    <p>Public is an investing platform that allows you to invest stocks, ETFs, crypto, and alternative assets like fine art and collectibles&mdash;all in one place.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/public-crypto?guid=MTAxMTY3&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=VA&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy SOL with Public today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptocurrency execution and custody services are provided by Apex Crypto LLC (NMLS ID 1828849) through a software licensing agreement between Apex Crypto LLC and Public Crypto LLC. Crypto trading on Public platforms is served by Public Crypto LLC and offered through APEX Crypto. Please ensure that you fully understand the risks involved before trading." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Theta Network price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Theta Network and TFUEL prices jumped sharply as investors cheered the recent launch of Theta EdgeStore. EdgeStore is a new component of the Theta Edge Node&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/theta-network/theta-edgestore-decentralized-storage-released-in-alpha-version-cc1e9e23ec20"><u>software</u></a> that is run by thousands of people around the world. Once fully launched, the platform will make it possible for people to store their documents and files in a decentralized manner. Some of the files that will be stored in it are NFTs, video, software packages, and metaverse projects among others.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Turning to the 4H chart, we see that the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/theta/"><u>THETA</u></a> price has been in a strong bullish trend in the past few weeks. It managed to cross the important resistance level at $0.9821, the highest level on November 27. This was an important price since it was the upper side of the cup and handle pattern that formed. Therefore, by measuring the distance of the upper and lower sides of the cup, we can show that Theta price has more upside.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/00/27/1674819463353-732b8a9c-0ca3-490c-bce5-a480db283d6a.png" style="width: 656px;height: 310.507px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="656" height="310.507"></p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/THETAUSD/?exchange=BINANCE"><u>THETA/USD chart by TradingView</u></a></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy Theta Network</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>

    <p>eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=MTAxMTY3&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=VA&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy THETA with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    Binance.US</h3>

    <p>Binance.US provides secure and reliable access to the world&rsquo;s most popular cryptocurrencies, with some of the lowest fees in the industry.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/binance-us-crypto?guid=MTAxMTY3&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=VA&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy THETA with Binance.US today            </a>
    </p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Hooked Protocol price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr">HOOK price has been in a spectacular rally in the past few weeks because of the remarkable popularity of Wild Cash. It rose to an all-time high this week, bringing the year-to-date gains to over 200%. The coin has moved above all moving averages and the previous all-time high of $3.40. Therefore, using the trend-following approach, the coin will likely continue rising as buyers target the important resistance point at $4.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/00/27/1674819463166-a0460a33-fe23-44cd-bc22-663b42e4154a.png" style="width: 689px;height: 326.127px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="689" height="326.127"></p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://medium.com/theta-network/theta-edgestore-decentralized-storage-released-in-alpha-version-cc1e9e23ec20"><u>HOOK chart by TradingView</u></a></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy Hooked Protocol</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-predictions-solana-theta-network-hook/">Crypto price predictions: Solana, Theta Network, HOOK</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-predictions-solana-theta-network-hook/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What is the Bitcoin hash rate? And why is at all-time highs?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/what-is-the-bitcoin-hash-rate-and-why-is-at-all-time-highs/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/what-is-the-bitcoin-hash-rate-and-why-is-at-all-time-highs/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dan Ashmore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 10:33:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mining pools]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/what-is-the-bitcoin-hash-rate-and-why-is-at-all-time-highs/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key Takeaways The Bitcoin hash rate is the amount of computing power contributed towards mining It has continued to take new all-time highs This squeezes miners&#8217; profitability, at a time when electricity costs have risen and the Bitcoin price has fallen Overall, a high hash rate implies a healthy and more secure Bitcoin network &#160; [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/what-is-the-bitcoin-hash-rate-and-why-is-at-all-time-highs/">What is the Bitcoin hash rate? And why is at all-time highs?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2><strong>Key Takeaways</strong></h2>
<ul>
<li>The Bitcoin hash rate is the amount of computing power contributed towards mining</li>
<li>It has continued to take new all-time highs</li>
<li>This squeezes miners&rsquo; profitability, at a time when electricity costs have risen and the Bitcoin price has fallen</li>
<li>Overall, a high hash rate implies a healthy and more secure Bitcoin network</li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&ldquo;All-time high&rdquo; is a phrase I haven&rsquo;t used in a while when covering the cryptocurrency space. But if you look, there is something that continues to hit higher highs, and that is the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> hash rate.</p>
<p>Bitcoin&rsquo;s hash rate refers to the amount of computing power that is being contributed to the network through <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/mine/">mining</a>. And as the chart below shows, its inexorable rise during the pandemic does not seem to be slowing down. But what does this mean, and why is it rising?</p>
        <div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/12387083">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<h2><strong>What is the Bitcoin hash rate?</strong></h2>
<p>Gone are the days when anyone could mine on their personal computer. Today, mining is dominated by large mining pools, using specialised computers specifically designed for this purpose.</p>
<p>The practice of mining actually involves these computers solving complex mathematical puzzles. Once this puzzle is solved, the latest block of transactions can be validated and attached to the blockchain, before the process repeats regarding the next block and the next mathematical puzzle. Once a puzzle is solved and a block validated, the miner responsible for this work gets paid in newly created bitcoins.</p>
<p>This is all very complicated, but what is important to understand is that Bitcoin is programmed to release a specific number of Bitcoin over time, with the blockchain coded such that a new block is added (validated) every ten minutes.</p>
<p>But as more computers join the network and the hash rate increases, these puzzles should get solved quicker, meaning quicker block time and more bitcoins released. Right? Well, here is the thing. A <em>difficulty adjustment</em> is coded into Bitcoin &ndash; that means that the more computing power that joins the network, the harder it is to solve those puzzles.</p>
<p>Don&rsquo;t ask me how this works, because I don&rsquo;t even come close to understanding what is under the hood of the mythical beast that is the Bitcoin blockchain, but the main point is that as more miners join, the difficulty goes up.</p>
<p>And as Bitcoin has become more popular (and risen in price), that is exactly what has happened. More miners have joined the network, and today it is a highly advanced process. Ten years ago, when only few miners existed, you and I could have pulled out our laptops and mined to a reasonable degree.</p>
        <div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/12387260">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<h2><strong>Why is at all-time highs?</strong></h2>
<p>There are a number of reasons why hash rate continues to surge to new highs. But the bottom line is that the increase in miners causes the hash rate to climb.</p>
<p>Thus the question really asks why miners are continuing to join, when the price of Bitcoin has been plummeting. There are a couple of potential answers here.</p>
<p>The first is that during the pandemic bull run, mining equipment was scarce and prices for items such as chips were sky-high. Many miners ordered new mining rigs during the bull run, but only received the equipment recently (or some, not even yet).</p>
<p>Additionally, as the price of Bitcoin fell, the profitability of mining also decreased, given miners&rsquo; revenue is denominated in Bitcoin. New mining equipment has been developed and is selling for a lower price than previously, helping to push the number of miners higher.</p>
<p>One other theory is the Ethereum Merge. This took place in September, when Ethereum transitioned from Proof-of-Work to Proof-of-Stake, meaning mining on the network ceased. Hence, some of these out-of-work Ethereum miners transitioned across to Bitcoin mining.</p>
<h2><strong>What does a higher hash rate mean?</strong></h2>
<p>The first consequence of an increasing hash rate is obviously greater pressure on miners. More competition and a higher required hash rate squeeze their profitability, especially at a time when electricity costs have risen and revenue (Bitcoin) has fallen.</p>
<p>The best way to see this is to glance at the share price action throughout 2022 of some of the public mining companies.</p>
        <div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/12387813">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p>On the positive side, the Bitcoin hash rate is considered a security metric for the network. The higher the hash rate, the more secure the network, so in that context, the all-time high represents a good thing.</p>
<p>This is why a high hash rate is generally looked upon favourably, as it implies a healthy network. Only problem is, miners are feeling the squeeze.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/what-is-the-bitcoin-hash-rate-and-why-is-at-all-time-highs/">What is the Bitcoin hash rate? And why is at all-time highs?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/what-is-the-bitcoin-hash-rate-and-why-is-at-all-time-highs/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
