<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 18:39:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Coinbase may be losing retail crypto traders to Robinhood: Mizuho</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-losing-retail-crypto-traders-robinhood-mizuho/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wajeeh Khan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 18:39:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robinhood]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=143409</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Mizuho analyst says Coinbase may be losing share in retail crypto trading. Dan Dolev continues to see downside in the crypto exchange to $27 a share. Coinbase stock is currently down 35% versus its year-to-date high in March. Coinbase Global Inc remains at the risk of having its stock price cut in half, says Dan [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-losing-retail-crypto-traders-robinhood-mizuho/">Coinbase may be losing retail crypto traders to Robinhood: Mizuho</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Mizuho analyst says Coinbase may be losing share in retail crypto trading.</li>
<li>Dan Dolev continues to see downside in the crypto exchange to $27 a share.</li>
<li>Coinbase stock is currently down 35% versus its year-to-date high in March.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/coinbase/">Coinbase Global Inc</a> remains at the risk of having its stock price cut in half, says Dan Dolev. He&rsquo;s a Senior Analyst at Mizuho.</p>
<h2>Coinbase stock could crash to $27</h2>
<p>Dolev maintained his &ldquo;underperform&rdquo; rating on the crypto exchange today. His $27 price objective suggests shares could tank an alarming 50% from here.</p>
<p>The analyst is super bearish on Coinbase stock partially because he suspects that it&rsquo;s losing share in retail trading to peer Robinhood Markets Inc.</p>
<blockquote><p>Our analysis suggests that COIN&rsquo;s share of combined COIN retail + Hood crypto volumes trended lower in April vs. the approx. 65% ratio in the prior three quarters.</p></blockquote>
<p>Part of it may be related to the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-sec-strikes-again-first-binance-now-coinbase/">lawsuit</a> the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission filed against the crypto company last week.</p>
<h2>Coinbase has increased trading fees</h2>
<p>Dan Dolev also cited trading fees as a possible reason why Coinbase Global Inc is losing to Robinhood.</p>
<p>The crypto exchange has resorted to higher fees for small-ticket traders to offset volume declines which may have pushed them to Robinhood as it has refrained from increasing fees so far, the Mizuho analyst told clients in a research note today.</p>
<blockquote><p>If we assume that COIN maintained share and retail take rate held constant at 168bps in April &hellip; this would imply $117 million of retail transactions for April.</p></blockquote>
<p>In comparison, the company recently <a href="https://s27.q4cdn.com/397450999/files/doc_financials/2023/q1/Shareholder-Letter-Q1-2023.pdf?pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a> a lower $110 million of total transaction revenue in April. Coinbase stock is currently down 35% versus its year-to-date high.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-losing-retail-crypto-traders-robinhood-mizuho/">Coinbase may be losing retail crypto traders to Robinhood: Mizuho</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>GamCare Calls For Crypto Trading Self-Exclusion: Will GamStop Take Actions?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/gamcare-calls-for-crypto-trading-self-exclusion-will-gamstop-take-actions/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/gamcare-calls-for-crypto-trading-self-exclusion-will-gamstop-take-actions/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 18:24:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/gamcare-calls-for-crypto-trading-self-exclusion-will-gamstop-take-actions/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>GamCare is the leading provider of information, advice, support, and free referrals to prevent and resolve gambling problems in the UK. To the surprise of many, recently, GamCare equated crypto trading with gambling activities and stressed the&#160;necessity of self-exclusion for traders. The reason for this is the appearance of the first signs similar to gambling [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/gamcare-calls-for-crypto-trading-self-exclusion-will-gamstop-take-actions/">GamCare Calls For Crypto Trading Self-Exclusion: Will GamStop Take Actions?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">GamCare is the leading provider of information, advice, support, and free referrals to prevent and resolve gambling problems in the UK. To the surprise of many, recently, GamCare equated crypto trading with gambling activities and stressed the&nbsp;<a href="https://www.gamcare.org.uk/news-and-blog/news/gamcare-highlights-need-for-self-exclusion-scheme-for-consumers-involved-in-high-risk-and-cryptocurrency-trading/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>necessity of self-exclusion for traders</u></a>. The reason for this is the appearance of the first signs similar to gambling addiction, which has negative consequences.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Cryptocurrency Trading and Gambling: Similarities According To GamCare</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The crypto market appeared relatively recently but has already experienced an uncountable number of ups and downs. The crypto traders and miners lost and earned on fluctuations in cryptocurrency rates literally staggered the imagination. Cryptocurrency trading, compared to ordinary stock trading, is considered a particularly risky activity. Having tools that can&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/gamban-blocks-crypto-platforms-will-gamstop-take-actions/"><u>block crypto trading such as Gamban</u></a> may have a positive influence on both traders and cryptocurrency platforms. The crypto market is highly volatile, and it is often impossible to predict in which direction the price of coins will turn.</p>
<p dir="ltr">GamCare believes that the addiction of traders can be even stronger than that of poker players, for example, especially if we are talking about a lover who gets a dose of adrenaline by betting on the growth of certain coins.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Crypto creates the misconception that coins have a reputation for being high-tech means of payment. This provides constant faith in the growth of quotes and turns investors into gamblers.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In pursuit of profit, a crypto trader must constantly take risks. On the day, he can make many transactions as the price of some small coins rises or collapses at one moment. The conditions under which a trader (or, in this context, a gambler) must constantly be in the &ldquo;game&rdquo; are similar to gambling in an online casino. Based on this and a number of other aspects, GamCare made this decision and added crypto trading to the number of gambling activities.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How GamStop Experience Can Be Applied For Crypto Trading?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">GamStop and GamCare have the same goals, but so far different in that the former does not yet extend its activities to crypto trading. But according to experts and analysts, it may soon do so. The reason for this is the great experience and the availability of the necessary tools used for online casinos, bookmakers, etc., which can be applied in the field of crypto trading.</p>
<p dir="ltr">One obvious tool is the self-exclusion periods that traders can set for themselves. Just like in the case of&nbsp;<a href="https://nonstopcasino.org/not-gamstop-casinos/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>non GamStop casino online</u></a> accepting crypto, when customers exclude themselves from playing casino games, crypto traders could use a piece of software that would force them to take temporary breaks, do things IRL, and analyze everything without making impulsive decisions. Most crypto market players actually understand that they will lose money. But they still decide on super-risk operations &ndash; and miss the moment when the amount of potential loss becomes fatal.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Also, the most important advantage of the GamStop program is the voluntary nature and the company&rsquo;s policy of independent choice. This can also apply to cryptocurrency trading. Traders who feel they need a break can voluntarily make this decision, and no one will force them to do so.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">The Benefits of Crypto Trading Self-Exclusion Software Like GamStop</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/05/15/1686852986867-50f8af71-784e-49ae-9f0c-4caa0a858dfd.png" style="width: 800px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="800" height="307"></p>
<p dir="ltr">The GamStop program has been showing quality and performance since its first launch in April 2018. Many gamblers were sceptical about this, but still, they understood the importance of controlling gambling activity and fighting addiction to gambling, betting, and all that. Similarly to gambling platforms, the possible collaboration of self-exclusion programs like GamStop and crypto platforms could be used to the great advantage of all people involved in high-risk crypto trading operations.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Regulated Environment</h3>
<p dir="ltr">As in gambling, crypto trading is known for various fraudulent and fake platforms. Using self-exclusion programs will create a safe environment and guarantee the protection of traders in all aspects. There is nothing wrong with trading cryptocurrencies if you approach the issue rationally and wisely. But not everyone follows&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/gamstop-crypto-fostering-responsible-gambling-for-a-sustainable-ecosystem/"><u>responsible gambling rules</u></a> and is honest in this business.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Take a Break From Cryptocurrency Trading</h3>
<p dir="ltr">What was mentioned earlier is an important part of any activity. Crypto trading is no exception. Successful traders rely not on luck but on their own calculation, which can only be obtained in a calm and &ldquo;quiet&rdquo; environment.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Learn About Possible Negative Impacts</h3>
<p dir="ltr">Crypto trading is a rather specific and difficult field. But still, at some point, it is difficult to overcome the addiction. Self-exclusion programs have a large knowledge base, advisors, telephone support, and other valuable educational features. This will help traders understand what addiction is and what negative aspects it can bring to life.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Great Budget Control Tool</h3>
<p dir="ltr">Many traders are skilled in money management and budgeting. But this is only before they become addicted, and these actions become systematic and, to a greater extent, lead to the loss of real money. Self-exclusion programs allow you to set budget limits, which will help you control money-related activities.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Conclusion</h2>
<p>According to GamCare,&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/why-is-nobody-talking-about-crypto-trading-addiction/"><u>crypto trading is similar to gambling addiction</u></a>, especially in the case of people who trade crypto on a daily basis, lose large sums of money, and start chasing losses. Self-exclusion programs for gambling platforms familiar to many have demonstrated their effectiveness and usefulness for a long time. GamCare was the first to announce the expansion of the scope of the self-exclusion program. How effective it is and whether other companies will use it, like GamStop, time will tell.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/gamcare-calls-for-crypto-trading-self-exclusion-will-gamstop-take-actions/">GamCare Calls For Crypto Trading Self-Exclusion: Will GamStop Take Actions?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/gamcare-calls-for-crypto-trading-self-exclusion-will-gamstop-take-actions/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Blk DNM Introduces Intelligence Into Clothing With Blockchain, In First Use Of ‘Connected Fashion’</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/blk-dnm-introduces-intelligence-into-clothing-with-blockchain-in-first-use-of-connected-fashion/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/blk-dnm-introduces-intelligence-into-clothing-with-blockchain-in-first-use-of-connected-fashion/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire &#160;]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 16:59:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=143400</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Stockholm, Sweden, June 15th, 2023, Chainwire BLK DNM bridging the Physical and Virtual Worlds of Fashion through Blockchain Innovation Swedish-American fashion brand BLK DNM today unveils the first-ever example of connected fashion (garments that exist both physically and virtually, each aspect &#8216;twinned&#8217; via technology) with the launch of BLK DNM Society and integration of blockchain-powered [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/blk-dnm-introduces-intelligence-into-clothing-with-blockchain-in-first-use-of-connected-fashion/">Blk DNM Introduces Intelligence Into Clothing With Blockchain, In First Use Of ‘Connected Fashion’</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Stockholm, Sweden, June 15th, 2023, Chainwire</strong></p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">BLK DNM bridging the Physical and Virtual Worlds of Fashion through Blockchain Innovation</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Swedish-American fashion brand <a href="https://www.blkdnm.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">BLK DNM</a> today unveils the first-ever example of connected fashion (garments that exist both physically and virtually, each aspect &lsquo;twinned&rsquo; via technology) with the launch of <strong>BLK DNM Society</strong> and integration of blockchain-powered hardware and software into its products.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">BLK DNM Society, built on tech designed by blockchain innovator and BLK DNM owner <a href="https://chromaway.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">ChromaWay</a>, will grant each garment a unique and recordable identity in both the physical and virtual worlds, while also rewarding ethical behaviour and granting brand influence to owners.</p>
<ul>
<li>Blockchain-powered &lsquo;digital garment ID&rsquo; microchips will give each item a unique identity and record of its history</li>
<li>Chips form the hardware element of BLK DNM Society, which launches in tandem and rewards responsible behavior and ownership</li>
<li>Tech will first appear in BLK DNM&rsquo;s FW 2023 collection</li>
</ul>
<h2 class="ql-align-justify">The Hardware: Digital Garment IDs</h2>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Future BLK DNM clothing will be fitted with a &lsquo;digital garment ID&rsquo; &ndash; an undetectable chip that gives each physical item a unique and recordable identity. Some of the first features of the digital garment IDs will include:</p>
<ul>
<li>Authentication of the garment as genuine, eliminating fakes and counterfeiting</li>
<li>Rewarding responsible behaviours of treasuring and caring for clothing long-term, such as refurbs and second-hand purchases</li>
<li>Recording each individual garment&rsquo;s unique history &ndash; owners, events and places worn, repairs and alterations &ndash; enabling the item to accrue emotional and monetary value over time</li>
<li>Acting as a digital ticket for entry to events</li>
<li>Access to and voting rights within BLK DNM Society</li>
</ul>
<h2 class="ql-align-justify">BLK DNM Society</h2>
<p class="ql-align-justify">The digital garment IDs are the first hardware elements of BLK DNM Society, which launches in tandem. The first example of connected fashion, BLK DNM Society is a community of BLK DNM owners, connected virtually by their physical items, who are rewarded for responsible behaviours and are granted voting rights on key brand decisions based on item ownership &ndash; thereby beginning the first ever process of decentralising a fashion brand&rsquo;s stewardship.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Each digital garment ID will create a &lsquo;digital reflection&rsquo; of the physical garment: a twin in the virtual world where the physical item&rsquo;s history and place within BLK DNM Society is recorded. The digital reflection can also be worn in the metaverses, catering especially to younger generations whose identities in virtual worlds are equally as important as in the physical.</p>
<h2 class="ql-align-justify">FW 2023</h2>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Digital garment IDs will be revealed at BLK DNM&rsquo;s FW event in Paris on June 21st. For this first collection, the chips will be embedded in only leather items, with subsequent collections introducing more items to BLK DNM Society through embedded blockchain-enabled hardware.</p>
<blockquote><p>Henrik Hjelte, CEO and Co-founder of ChromaWay, comments: &ldquo;This is totally futuristic. Nothing like this has been attempted in fashion before. It&rsquo;s very exciting for us, after much hard work, to see our technology elevating one of fashion&rsquo;s iconic brands into something completely unique. This has the potential to transform people&rsquo;s relationships with the clothes they wear and the brands they buy. No longer does the relationship with the customer end at the checkout. And each beautiful garment now becomes its own living, evolving piece of history.&rdquo;</p></blockquote>
<p class="ql-align-justify"><img decoding="async" src="https://invezz.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/DSCF4500-3_2_1686842385CWogefXm84.jpg"></p>
<p>Toni Collin, CEO of BLK DNM, and Henrik Hjelte, CEO and Co-founder of ChromaWay</p>
<blockquote><p>Toni Collin, CEO of BLK DNM, comments: &ldquo;BLK DNM&rsquo;s philosophy is one of community, and our clothing is designed, through both its craftsmanship and timeless aesthetic, to be treasured and passed down through generations &ndash; the antithesis of irresponsible fast fashion. Now, with the introduction of BLK DNM Society and the first embedded hardware in our garments, we take those two pillars to a revolutionary new level. By embedding intelligence in every item, we hope we can inspire our industry to join us in using connected fashion to do better.&rdquo;</p></blockquote>
<h3>About BLK DNM</h3>
<p class="ql-align-justify">BLK DNM is a Swedish-American fashion brand that specialises in timeless tailoring, leather, and denim of extraordinary quality. Following its 2023 relaunch as an entry-luxury fashion house under the stewardship of new Creative Director Jessy Heuvelink, BLK DNM&rsquo;s focus on both enduring craftsmanship and aesthetic timelessness encourages customers to love and treasure each item for decades and across generations.</p>
<h3>About ChromaWay</h3>
<p>ChromaWay is an industry leader in blockchain technology and specializes in creating and deploying cutting-edge, scalable blockchain solutions for both businesses and governments. The company, which was established in 2014 and has its headquarters in Stockholm, Sweden, has been at the forefront of driving the widespread adoption of blockchain technology. Its flagship product, relational blockchain Chromia, enables developers to build decentralized applications (dApps) with a relational database model that offers unprecedented scalability and flexibility.</p>
<p><strong>Contact</strong></p>
<p>Fati Hakim, Fati.Hakim@ChromaWay.com</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/blk-dnm-introduces-intelligence-into-clothing-with-blockchain-in-first-use-of-connected-fashion/">Blk DNM Introduces Intelligence Into Clothing With Blockchain, In First Use Of ‘Connected Fashion’</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/blk-dnm-introduces-intelligence-into-clothing-with-blockchain-in-first-use-of-connected-fashion/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase partners with Bitkey Wallet to promote Bitcoin self-custody</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-partners-with-bitkey-wallet-to-promote-bitcoin-self-custody/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-partners-with-bitkey-wallet-to-promote-bitcoin-self-custody/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 15:14:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wallets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-partners-with-bitkey-wallet-to-promote-bitcoin-self-custody/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Coinbase&#8217;s partnership with Bitkey, Block&#8217;s self-custody bitcoin wallet, will span six continents. The platforms will integrate Coinbase Pay to allow users buy/sell or transfer Bitcoin to their Bitkey self-custody wallet. Coinbase said the collaboration will allow customers to easily buy, store and manage their BTC. Coinbase and Bitkey, the self-custody Bitcoin (BTC) wallet built by [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-partners-with-bitkey-wallet-to-promote-bitcoin-self-custody/">Coinbase partners with Bitkey Wallet to promote Bitcoin self-custody</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Coinbase&rsquo;s partnership with Bitkey, Block&rsquo;s self-custody bitcoin wallet, will span six continents.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The platforms will integrate Coinbase Pay to allow users buy/sell or transfer Bitcoin to their Bitkey self-custody wallet.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Coinbase said the collaboration will allow customers to easily buy, store and manage their BTC.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/coinbase/">Coinbase</a> and Bitkey, the self-custody <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">Bitcoin (BTC)</a> wallet built by the Block, Inc., have<a href="https://www.coinbase.com/blog/announcing-a-global-partnership-with-blocks-bitkey-wallet" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">&nbsp;<u>announced</u></a> a global partnership that will see the two companies promote self-custody usage.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The partnership, which will span six continents, will see Bitkey users buy and sell BTC on Coinbase, as well as transfer their holdings to their self-custody Bitkey wallets. The wallet includes a mobile app, hardware device and set of recovery tools, the companies said in a blog announcement on Thursday.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to the announcement, Coinbase and Bitkey will leverage Coinbase Pay to allow customers easy access to fiat-to-crypto onramps, the US-based crypto exchange noted in the blog post. It is a key component to powering the next adoption phase of the Bitcoin economy.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>At Bitkey, we&rsquo;re building a self-custody bitcoin wallet designed to empower the next 100 million people to truly own and manage their Bitcoin &ndash; safely and easily</em>,&rdquo; Lindsey Grossman, Business Lead at Bitkey said.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>Partners play a key role in bringing self-custody to a wider group of people around the world, and we are incredibly proud to have partnered with leading companies like Coinbase to make self-custody both secure and easy to use</em>.&rdquo;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitkey launches global beta program</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The collaboration between Coinbase and Bitkey is kicking off as the self-custody wallet launches its global beta program.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Customers in the beta program will be able to transfer their Bitcoin from centralized exchanges to Bitkey&rsquo;s self-custody wallet. Buying and selling as well as direct transfers between Coinbase and Bitkey will be enabled when the wallet launches to the public later this year.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As noted above, Bitkey and Coinbase will offer the service to customers in six continents. Some of the countries include the US, Canada, the UK, Brazil, and Australia.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-partners-with-bitkey-wallet-to-promote-bitcoin-self-custody/">Coinbase partners with Bitkey Wallet to promote Bitcoin self-custody</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-partners-with-bitkey-wallet-to-promote-bitcoin-self-custody/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance introduces Bitcoin mining cloud services amid regulatory pressure</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-introduces-bitcoin-mining-cloud-services-amid-regulatory-pressure/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-introduces-bitcoin-mining-cloud-services-amid-regulatory-pressure/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 14:19:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-introduces-bitcoin-mining-cloud-services-amid-regulatory-pressure/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways Binance users interested in Bitcoin mining can now subscribe to Binance&#8217;s cloud mining services starting today. The new service comes despite Binance currently facing regulatory pressure in the United States.&#160; Binance launches its Bitcoin mining cloud services The world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency exchange by daily trading volume, Binance, has launched new Bitcoin subscription-based cloud [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-introduces-bitcoin-mining-cloud-services-amid-regulatory-pressure/">Binance introduces Bitcoin mining cloud services amid regulatory pressure</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Binance users interested in Bitcoin mining can now subscribe to Binance&rsquo;s cloud mining services starting today.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The new service comes despite Binance currently facing regulatory pressure in the United States.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr">Binance launches its Bitcoin mining cloud services</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The world&rsquo;s largest cryptocurrency exchange by daily trading volume, <a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/binance/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Binance</u></a>, has launched new Bitcoin subscription-based cloud mining products.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">https://twitter.com/binance/status/1669212701443379201</p>
<p dir="ltr">Starting today, June 15, Binance users interested in Bitcoin mining but who don&rsquo;t have the hardware can subscribe to the cryptocurrency exchange&rsquo;s cloud mining services and purchase hashrates.</p>
<p dir="ltr">At the moment, the cryptocurrency exchange is selling 1 Terahash per second (Th/s) at $10.7280. As a user purchases more hashrate. The probability of higher income in terms of the Bitcoin earned through mining increases.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Binance revealed that its BTC mining subscription service would be active for six months. For each TH/s purchased, users stand a chance to earn 0.0004338 BTC during the 180-day period.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The product is currently available on the Binance global website, which means that it is not available to its users in the United States.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Binance continues to face regulatory pressure</h2>
<p dir="ltr">This latest development comes at a time when Binance is facing regulatory pressure in the United States.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC)&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sec-sues-binance-and-cz-for-breaking-us-securities-rules/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>sued Binance</u></a> earlier this month for allegedly breaking securities laws. The regulatory agency has also filed for a temporary restraining order to&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-sec-is-seeking-court-order-to-freeze-binance-uss-assets/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>freeze Binance.US&rsquo;s assets</u></a>.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Binance.US has already hired former SEC enforcement co-director George Canellos as part of its legal team as it defends itself against the regulatory agency&rsquo;s allegations.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Last week, Binance.US announced the suspension of USD deposits on its platform as it transitions into an all-crypto exchange.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The SEC also&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-sec-strikes-again-first-binance-now-coinbase/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>sued rival cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase</u></a> for failing to register as a broker, national securities exchange or clearing agency.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-introduces-bitcoin-mining-cloud-services-amid-regulatory-pressure/">Binance introduces Bitcoin mining cloud services amid regulatory pressure</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-introduces-bitcoin-mining-cloud-services-amid-regulatory-pressure/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin correlation with stocks at 5-year low as regulatory crackdown takes toll</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-correlation-with-stocks-at-5-year-low-as-regulatory-crackdown-takes-toll/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-correlation-with-stocks-at-5-year-low-as-regulatory-crackdown-takes-toll/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dan Ashmore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 13:51:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-correlation-with-stocks-at-5-year-low-as-regulatory-crackdown-takes-toll/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key Takeaways Our Head of Research, Dan Ashmore, digs into Bitcoin&#8217;s relationship with stocks Correlation between Bitcoin and the Nasdaq is at its lowest point since 2018 The Nasdaq is up 10% in the last month as stocks have surged off softer forecasts around interest rates and the macro climate Bitcoin is down 9% in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-correlation-with-stocks-at-5-year-low-as-regulatory-crackdown-takes-toll/">Bitcoin correlation with stocks at 5-year low as regulatory crackdown takes toll</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>Key Takeaways</h2>
<ul>
<li>Our Head of Research, Dan Ashmore, digs into Bitcoin&rsquo;s relationship with stocks</li>
<li dir="ltr">Correlation between Bitcoin and the Nasdaq is at its lowest point since 2018</li>
<li dir="ltr">The Nasdaq is up 10% in the last month as stocks have surged off softer forecasts around interest rates and the macro climate</li>
<li dir="ltr">Bitcoin is down 9% in the same time frame, the US regulatory crackdown spreading fear about crypto&rsquo;s future in the country&nbsp;</li>
<li dir="ltr">Ashmore writes that the break in correlation surpasses what was seen in November 2022 amid the FTX collapse, when Bitcoin fell to $15,000 while stocks increased off positive inflation readings</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p dir="ltr">After ten consecutive interest rate hikes, the US Federal Reserve this week paused its rate hiking policy. The move was nearly unanimously anticipated by the market and movement after the meeting was relatively minimal. &nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, over the past month, markets have been flying. The S&amp;P 500 is up 6% in the last 30 days, now only 8.8% off an all-time high, despite being 27% below the mark in October. The Nasdaq is up 10% over the same timeframe &ndash; that is 15% below its all-time high from November 2021 but a tremendous resurgence considering it shed a third of its value in 2022. &nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">And yet, something is being left behind: Bitcoin.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin is now trading below $25,000 for the first time in three months. I put together a <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/no-bitcoin-is-still-as-correlated-as-ever-with-the-stock-market-a-deep-dive/"><u>deep dive</u></a> in March analysing the its underlying price movement to show how tightly it trades with the stock market. This was at a time when Bitcoin was rallying and banks were wobbling amid the Silicon Valley Bank fiasco. Suddenly, it was fashionable to declare Bitcoin as decoupling from the stock market. Ultimately, that wasn&rsquo;t true. However, something very interesting has happened in the last month.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">First, take a look at the path of the Nasdaq and Bitcoin since the start of 2022, which roughly coincides with the start of the bear market:&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14142938">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">Clearly, the two have moved in lockstep. But two episodes jump out: the first is November 2022, when Bitcoin fell and the Nasdaq surged. The second is this past month. We discussed the 10% jump in the Nasdaq over the last month. However, Bitcoin has fallen 9% in the same timeframe. This marks a clear departure from what we would expect. Plotting the correlation (using 60-Day Pearson) shows this more directly:</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14143041">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">I touched on November 2022 above, and the swift fall in correlation can be seen on the chart. This was when FTX collapsed, sending the crypto market into a tailspin. At the same time, however, stocks raced upwards as softer inflation numbers were met by lower expectations around the future path of interest rates.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">There were also less dramatic (but equally temporary) decouplings between Bitcoin and stocks in April/May 2022 and June/July 2022. On the chart below, I have pencilled in incidents which occurred during these periods:</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/05/15/1686836790790-e6ad26c9-1132-4a69-b507-7ea8eb63f579.png" style="width: 600px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="600" height="427">Indeed, what is different about November (FTX) and today is that we see a Bitcoin fall happening at the same time as a Nasdaq surge. While the Luna and Celsius incidents hurt crypto immensely, they came as stocks were also struggling and so the effect is not as dramatic in terms of correlation breaks (although is still tangible on the chart). </p>
<p dir="ltr">But today, we are seeing the biggest break in the correlation trend over the last couple of years &ndash; surpassing even FTX. The 60-Day Pearson currently sits at -0.66, whereas the lowest it hit during the FTX crisis was -0.49.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Regulatory crackdown is suppressing prices</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The reason is obvious. The great regulatory crackdown in the US is freaking the market out, and for very good reason. The two biggest crypto companies on the planet, Binance and Coinbase, were both sued last week.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Crypto.com has suspended its institutional exchange, citing weak demand amid the regulatory woes. eToro and Robinhood pulled a bunch of tokens from their platforms following confirmation from the SEC that it viewed them as securities. Liquidity is <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/45-of-stablecoin-balance-has-left-crypto-exchanges-in-4-months-but-where-has-all-the-money-gone-a-deep-dive/"><u>dropping like a stone</u></a>.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">I wrote in-depth about the concern following the announcement of the Coinbase lawsuit last week, so I won&rsquo;t rehash it here (that analysis is <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-and-cryptos-fate-hangs-by-a-string-a-deep-dive/"><u>here</u></a>). While I believe Bitcoin should be able to weather the storm long-term, the picture appears far murkier for other cryptocurrencies.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Make no mistake about it, the crypto industry faces a <em>massive&nbsp;</em>problem as long as lawmakers continue to turn the screw. The crisis very much feels existential for a lot of the crypto market.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Regarding Bitcoin, enthusiasts dream of a day when it can decouple and claim that title of uncorrelated hedge asset, or a store-of-value, akin to gold. I&rsquo;ve done a lot of work around what that hypothetical future could look like, or what could lead the market to that point. But for now this remains just that: <em>hypothetical. &nbsp;</em>Because while the correlation is at its lowest point in five years, it is not being driven by fundamentals and thus will inevitably spike back up. This is nothing more than the market reacting to what is a very bearish development around regulation in the US.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">It&rsquo;s not how investors hoped a decoupling would come. But if anyone doubted the market&rsquo;s fear over the regulatory woes, or questioned why Bitcoin had not fallen more, looking at the break in correlation paints a very clear picture of how detrimental Gary Gensler&rsquo;s games have been to the cryptocurrency industry.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">In truth, it is not hyperbole to say that this is the most out of whack Bitcoin&rsquo;s correlation has ever been whilst trading as a mainstream financial asset. Because back when it last happened in 2018, Bitcoin traded with such thin liquidity that its price action is largely irrelevant to draw conclusions from going forward.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-correlation-with-stocks-at-5-year-low-as-regulatory-crackdown-takes-toll/">Bitcoin correlation with stocks at 5-year low as regulatory crackdown takes toll</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-correlation-with-stocks-at-5-year-low-as-regulatory-crackdown-takes-toll/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto price prediction: XRP, Hedera Hashgraph, Stacks</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-xrp-hedera-hashgraph-stacks/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-xrp-hedera-hashgraph-stacks/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 12:46:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-xrp-hedera-hashgraph-stacks/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrencies plunged hard after the latest Federal Reserve decision. Bitcoin dropped below the key support levels at $25,300 and $25,000. XRP has formed a double-top pattern on the daily chart. Cryptocurrency prices dipped sharply this week amid significant monetary policy and regulatory concerns.&#160;Bitcoin crashed below the important support at $25,000 while most altcoins erased their [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-xrp-hedera-hashgraph-stacks/">Crypto price prediction: XRP, Hedera Hashgraph, Stacks</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Cryptocurrencies plunged hard after the latest Federal Reserve decision.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin dropped below the key support levels at $25,300 and $25,000.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">XRP has formed a double-top pattern on the daily chart.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Cryptocurrency prices dipped sharply this week amid significant monetary policy and regulatory concerns.&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/"><u>Bitcoin</u></a> crashed below the important support at $25,000 while most altcoins erased their 2023 gains. This sell-off accelerated after the&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-consolidates-ahead-of-the-feds-decision-is-it-safe-to-buy-it-here/"><u>Federal Reserve</u></a> pointed to two more rate hikes later this year. In this article, we will explain what to expect in XRP, Hedera Hashgraph, and Stacks.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">XRP price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The XRP price drifted downwards this week after it jumped to a high of $0.5624. Its highest point was an important level since it was also the year-to-date high. This means that the coin has formed a double-top pattern, which is usually a bearish signal. The neckline of this price is at $0.4075, the lowest level on May 11.</p>
<p dir="ltr">At the same time,&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/ripple"><u>Ripple</u></a> price managed to cross the 25-day and 50-day exponential moving averages, signaling that bears are gaining traction. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) crossed the key level st 50 while one line of the Stochastic Oscillator indicator dropped below the oversold level. XRP price also formed a small shooting star pattern.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, the outlook of Ripple is bearish, with the next level to watch being at the neckline of the double-bottom pattern at $0.4075.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/05/15/1686833142708-c0894fcf-6eeb-4ae2-bbc0-7aee7cf600f0.png" style="width: 634px;height: 308.547px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="634" height="308.547"></p>
<h3 dir="ltr">How to buy XRP</h3>
<p dir="ltr">inv-news-table coins=&rdquo;XRP&rdquo; limit=&rdquo;2&Prime;]</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Hedera Hashgraph price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/hedera/"><u>Hedera Hashgraph</u></a> is a major blockchain project that seeks to become a good and faster alternative to Ethereum. It is faster, cheaper, and governed by leading companies like Google, IBM, and LG. Like other cryptocurrencies, the HBAR price has been in a strong downward trend in the past few months. It has erased about 40% from its highest level this year.</p>
<p dir="ltr">HBAR price has dropped below the important support level at $0.0542, the lowest level on March 10th. The token has moved below the 25-period and 50-period moving averages. At the same time, the Relative Strength Index (RSI) has continued falling. Therefore, there is a likelihood that the coin will continue falling as sellers target the next key support level at $0.035, which is about 18.5% below the current level.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/05/15/1686833142705-b7af11b2-7c5f-4f9e-8005-5a16a313192e.png" style="width: 689px;height: 335.697px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="689" height="335.697"></p>
<h3 dir="ltr">How to buy Hedera Hashgraph</h3>
<p dir="ltr">inv-news-table coins=&rdquo;HBAR&rdquo; limit=&rdquo;2&Prime;]</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Stacks price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/stacks/"><u>Stacks</u></a> price has been in a strong bearish trend despite the rising interest of Bitcoin development. STX managed to move below the lower side of the descending channel shown in orange. At the same time, the coin has dropped below the 25-day and 50-day EMA. On the daily chart, it has moved below the 61.8% Fibonacci Retracement level.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Stacks has also moved below the psychological level of $0.50. Therefore, there is a likelihood that the coin will continue falling as sellers target the next level at $0.35.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/05/15/1686833143235-3876a3f7-547a-4c59-a0cc-32334940dd8f.png" style="width: 693px;height: 337.26px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="693" height="337.26"></p>
<h3 dir="ltr">How to buy Stacks</h3>
<p dir="ltr">inv-news-table coins=&rdquo;STX&rdquo; limit=&rdquo;2&Prime;]</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-xrp-hedera-hashgraph-stacks/">Crypto price prediction: XRP, Hedera Hashgraph, Stacks</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-xrp-hedera-hashgraph-stacks/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto lending platform Delio temporarily suspends withdrawals</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-lending-platform-delio-temporarily-suspends-withdrawals/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-lending-platform-delio-temporarily-suspends-withdrawals/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 11:39:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto adoption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[South Korea]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-lending-platform-delio-temporarily-suspends-withdrawals/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Delio&#8217;s move comes amid a heightened crackdown in the US by the SEC. The move follows the recent suspension of deposit and withdrawal of digital assets at Haru Invest. There have also been a sharp increase in market volatility and increased confusion among investors. Due to increased market volatility, Delio, a Korea-owned cryptocurrency lending and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-lending-platform-delio-temporarily-suspends-withdrawals/">Crypto lending platform Delio temporarily suspends withdrawals</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Delio&rsquo;s move comes amid a heightened crackdown in the US by the SEC.</li>
<li>The move follows the recent suspension of deposit and withdrawal of digital assets at Haru Invest.</li>
<li>There have also been a sharp increase in market volatility and increased confusion among investors.</li>
</ul>
<p>Due to increased market volatility, Delio, a Korea-owned cryptocurrency lending and savings company, has temporarily suspended fund withdrawals.</p>
<p>Founded in 2018, Delio offers its customers an annual percentage rate (APR) of up to 10.7% on their <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/what-is-bitcoin/">Bitcoin (BTC)</a>, <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/what-is-ethereum/">Ethereum (ETH)</a>, and <a href="https://coinjournal.net/tether/what-is-tether/">Tether (USDT)</a> holdings.</p>
<p>The company said in a <a href="https://delio.io/notice/noticeDetail?id=376&amp;p=0">statement</a> that it made the decision to halt deposits and withdrawals to protect its customers, who are currently perplexed as a result of the sharp decline in the price of Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies. The translated version of the statement read:</p>
<p><em>&ldquo;In the aftermath of the recent suspension of deposit and withdrawal of digital assets at Haru Invest., situations such as a sharp increase in market volatility and increased confusion among investors are causing. &nbsp;In this situation, in order to safely protect the assets of customers currently in custody, Delio will inevitably suspend withdrawals temporarily as of June 14, 2023, 18:30, until the above situation and its aftermath are resolved.&rdquo;</em></p>
<h2>Crypto market decline</h2>
<p>Since reaching an all-time high (ATH) of $69,000 in 2021, the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">price of Bitcoin</a> has significantly decreased. The price of the leading cryptocurrency has decreased by more than 5% this week, and most altcoin prices have also undergone significant declines.</p>
<p>Without strong capital controls and reserves, the protracted bear market has made it inevitable for centralized cryptocurrency businesses to cease fund withdrawals or go out of business. Only a few of the numerous crypto lending platforms have managed to continue their regular business operations.</p>
<p>The bear market has seen industry heavyweights like Celsius, Voyager, BlockFi, Vauld, and a host of others go under.</p>
<p>One of the very few digital asset lenders that have not suspended fund withdrawal services during these difficult times is Nexo, which reached a <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/nexo-to-pay-45-million-to-settle-sec-charges/">$45 million settlement with the US SEC</a> last January.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-lending-platform-delio-temporarily-suspends-withdrawals/">Crypto lending platform Delio temporarily suspends withdrawals</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-lending-platform-delio-temporarily-suspends-withdrawals/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Astar Network Unveils the ‘Astar 2.0 Vision’ to Deliver Web3 Mass Adoption to Billions of Users</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/astar-network-unveils-the-astar-2-0-vision-to-deliver-web3-mass-adoption-to-billions-of-users/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/astar-network-unveils-the-astar-2-0-vision-to-deliver-web3-mass-adoption-to-billions-of-users/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire &#160;]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 11:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=143313</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Tokyo, Japan, June 15th, 2023, Chainwire Setting the long-term direction, the Astar 2.0 Vision aligns tokenomics, organizational structure, and key pillars of technology to drive Web3 mass adoption Astar Network, the smart contract platform for multichain, is delighted to introduce the &#8216;Astar 2.0 Vision&#8217; as it aims to drive mass adoption of Web3 to billions [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/astar-network-unveils-the-astar-2-0-vision-to-deliver-web3-mass-adoption-to-billions-of-users/">Astar Network Unveils the ‘Astar 2.0 Vision’ to Deliver Web3 Mass Adoption to Billions of Users</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Tokyo, Japan, June 15th, 2023, Chainwire</strong></p>
<h2>Setting the long-term direction, the Astar 2.0 Vision aligns tokenomics, organizational structure, and key pillars of technology to drive Web3 mass adoption</h2>
<p>Astar Network, the smart contract platform for multichain, is delighted to introduce the &lsquo;<a href="https://astar.network/ahttp://astar.network/astar2?utm_source=pr&amp;utm_medium=marketacross&amp;utm_campaign=astar2star2" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Astar 2.0 Vision</a>&rsquo; as it aims to drive mass adoption of Web3 to billions of users. With developers&rsquo; growing interest in base layers that offer scalability, security, and interoperability, Astar Network aims to position itself as the go-to Layer-1 blockchain by providing them with all the tools, resources, and support to help them build unstoppable dApps.</p>
<p>The &lsquo;Astar 2.0 Vision&rsquo; sets the long-term direction for the rapidly-growing Astar ecosystem. It aligns the network&rsquo;s tokenomics, organizational structure, and pillars of technology to achieve its mission of enabling Web3 innovations that empower billions of people worldwide.</p>
<h3>1. Tokenomics</h3>
<p>Astar Network will revamp its current tokenomics to align with the long-term vision and the DAO will make Astar sustainable for the future.</p>
<p>The Astar Foundation is building this with the community in forums to gain their valuable insights. A redesigned ASTR token better serves the needs of network participants, from users and builders to enterprise partners. It&rsquo;s essential to ensuring a sustainable future of growth and success.</p>
<h3>2. Astar Link</h3>
<p>Connects the fragmented layers of the blockchain industry. With customizable options and tailor-made SDKs, developers can create limitless solutions. Astar Link unlocks diverse use cases from gaming to enterprise that is only possible by linking different ecosystems to each other.</p>
<h3>3. Organizations supporting Astar Network</h3>
<ol>
<li>Startale Labs &ndash; The enterprise arm that enables users and businesses to embrace blockchain in Japan. With a focus on Web3 infrastructure, Startale aims to build innovative products to enable the widespread adoption of Web3 technologies.</li>
<li>Astar Foundation &ndash; It is currently the main contributor and maintainer of the Astar Network Source Code. The Foundation deploys resources to expand Astar Network through partnerships, community activities, hiring developers, funding projects, and other initiatives.</li>
<li>Formation of Astar DAO &ndash; Astar is actively working with the community to realize this goal in <a href="https://forum.astar.network/t/the-state-of-astar-governance-and-our-development-plans/4633/8" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Community Forums</a>. The DAO will help create an unstoppable network by embracing decentralization and handing governance to the community. Anyone can use Astar Network anywhere to improve their communities</li>
</ol>
<h3>4. Creating unstoppable dApps</h3>
<p>Improving the developer experience to help them build unstoppable dApps with two pillars of technology:</p>
<ol>
<li>Cross-chain applications &ndash; Astar supports both EVM and WebAssembly (WASM) environments, and interoperability between them using a Cross-Virtual Machine (XVM). With XVM, smart contracts will work seamlessly regardless of the blockchain. Astar 2.0 brings more options and is scalable.</li>
<li>DApp staking &ndash; Improved tokenomics will return more value to builders and stakers via dApp staking. Astar&rsquo;s innovative Build2Earn program empowers developers to get paid through a dApp staking mechanism for the dApps they build. It allows network users to stake their tokens to support their favorite projects.</li>
</ol>
<h3>5. Supernova: Paving the path forward</h3>
<p>Actions speak louder than words. Watch out for our coming updates in the middle of Q3 which will see Astar deliver on its web3 promises. Like a supernova exploding and impacting the universe, Astar aims to have the same impact in the web3 universe. Bringing Astar technology and vision to the masses.</p>
<p>Interested developers and users can explore the <a href="http://astar.network/astar2?utm_source=pr&amp;utm_medium=marketacross&amp;utm_campaign=astar2" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">2.0 Vision here</a>. Moreover, Japan&rsquo;s leading corporations have shown strong belief in Astar&rsquo;s vision and its ability to execute. Astar will share more details later in June and July.</p>
<p>The Astar Foundation and Startale Labs have been working with many of the world&rsquo;s leading global players to achieve the 2.0 Vision. Japan&rsquo;s leading corporations including Toyota Motor Corporation and Sony Network Communications have teamed up with Astar Network to explore the opportunities in Web3.</p>
<p>Sota Watanabe, the Founder of Astar Network, said, &ldquo;We will push the network to unlock Web3 for billions. Each part of Astar 2.0 is being shaped and improved, starting with token economics and developer tooling to ensure the sustainable long-term growth of the network.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Astar Network is the leading Layer-1 in Japan, having been voted the most popular blockchain in the country by the Japanese Blockchain Association. It is the go-to blockchain for developers and enterprises interested in exploring the Japanese Web3 space. Astar is also the first public blockchain from the country to be listed there despite Japan&rsquo;s strict listing regulations. Astar&rsquo;s native token ASTR is registered as a cryptocurrency, not a security, by the Japanese government.</p>
<h3>About Startale Labs</h3>
<p>Startale Labs is a web3 tech company developing multichain applications and infrastructure. We also conduct R&amp;D and incubation activities based on the experience and connections developed in coordination with Astar Network. In addition, a subsidiary, Startale Labs Japan, was established on January 31st 2023 to provide web3 business development and strategic consulting services to corporate enterprises and governments, leveraging the strengths of Japan&rsquo;s most widely-recognized public blockchain.</p>
<h3>About Astar Network</h3>
<p>Astar is Japan&rsquo;s most popular smart contract platform, supporting both EVM and WebAssembly (Wasm) environments, and interoperability between them using a Cross-Virtual Machine. Astar Network is friendly to all kinds of developers, and tools and languages they already know. Backed by the shared security of Polkadot, Astar shines brilliantly on its own within a vibrant and healthy ecosystem, and is a leading star in the blockchain industry overall, driving international corporate adoption, and consumer interest in web3 technologies.</p>
<p>For more information, visit: <a href="https://astar.network/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Website</a> | <a href="https://twitter.com/AstarNetwork" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Twitter</a> | <a href="https://discord.com/invite/Z3nC9U4" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Discord</a> | <a href="https://t.me/PlasmOfficial" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Telegram</a> | <a href="https://github.com/AstarNetwork" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">GitHub</a> |<a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/Astar_Network/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"> Reddit</a> | <a href="https://www.youtube.com/c/AstarNetwork" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">YouTube</a></p>
<h3>Contact</h3>
<p>Sota Watanabe, info@startale.org</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/astar-network-unveils-the-astar-2-0-vision-to-deliver-web3-mass-adoption-to-billions-of-users/">Astar Network Unveils the ‘Astar 2.0 Vision’ to Deliver Web3 Mass Adoption to Billions of Users</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/astar-network-unveils-the-astar-2-0-vision-to-deliver-web3-mass-adoption-to-billions-of-users/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
