<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 15:51:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Do Kwon Lawyers Tells SEC to Back Off Due to Lack of Jurisdictions Over Terra Products</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/do-kwon-lawyers-sec-terra-products/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/do-kwon-lawyers-sec-terra-products/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 15:51:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[do kwon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[lunc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[terra]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[terra luna]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[usdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=251967</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/do-kwon-lawyers-sec-terra-products/">Do Kwon Lawyers Tells SEC to Back Off Due to Lack of Jurisdictions Over Terra Products</a></p>
<p>Do Kwon's lawyers indicated that Coinbase does not list securities, and the SEC has not been granted the powers by Congress to regulate digital assets as securities or commodities.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/do-kwon-lawyers-sec-terra-products/">Do Kwon Lawyers Tells SEC to Back Off Due to Lack of Jurisdictions Over Terra Products</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/do-kwon-lawyers-sec-terra-products/">Do Kwon Lawyers Tells SEC to Back Off Due to Lack of Jurisdictions Over Terra Products</a></p>
<p>The Terra Luna and Do Kwon case could be headed in a different direction after a South Korean court ruled that the rebranded LUNC project is not a security product. As a result, Do Kwon&#8217;s lawyers were motivated to ask the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) to stop pushing with the legal pressure due to lack of jurisdiction. His lawyers noted in a court filing that Terra LUNA was a global currency that never participated in an initial coin offering (ICO).</p>
<p>Additionally, the lawyers argued that sales of LUNA coins were never directed to any of the United States persons. Thereby denying the United States SEC jurisdictions over Do Kwon and Terra  Luna UST.</p>
<p>“TFL conducted no public offerings requiring SEC registration. The AC does not allege that Defendants solicited any sales of digital assets to the general public anywhere. The challenged LUNA and MIR token sales were exempt from registration under multiple exemptions. And Defendants had no involvement in the programmatic minting of mAssets by the Mirror Protocol nor did they solicit transactions on the protocol by US-based persons,” the court filings <a href="https://www.courtlistener.com/docket/66820843/29/securities-and-exchange-commission-v-terraform-labs-pte-ltd/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">noted</a>.</p>
<p>As a result, Do Kwon&#8217;s lawyers have requested the court to dismiss the charges due to insufficient factual statements. The court filings noted that Terraform Labs is a Singaporean open-source software development firm that was serviced by Kwon as the CEO. In its defense, Terra Luna UST noted that it is an algorithmic stablecoin that operated only to adjust the money supply in response to changes in demand.</p>
<p>Additionally, Do Kwon&#8217;s lawyers indicated that <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase</a> does not list securities, and the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a> has not been granted the powers by Congress to regulate digital assets as securities or commodities?</p>
<h2>What Next for Do Kwon and Terra Luna Victims?</h2>
<p>A recent investigation by South Korean law enforcement revealed that Do Kwon does not have physical assets like houses, cars, or lands that can be liquidated in favor of Terra victims. Since Terra Luna&#8217;s clients were global, the case gets even more complicated to identify the victims. Moreover, the Terra protocol provided services to decentralized financial protocols and centralized exchanges of minting and adjusting LUNA and UST.</p>
<p>In return, the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-decentralized-finance-defi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">DeFi</a> and CEX protocols provided Terra Luna and UST tokens to their customers. As a result, the real value of affected users may never be fully understood since some protocols like <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a> have since collapsed.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, Do Kwon remains to be prosecuted for fraud charges after he was arrested trying to flee to Dubai in Montenegro.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/kucoin-loses-22000-twitter-hack/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/do-kwon-lawyers-sec-terra-products/">Do Kwon Lawyers Tells SEC to Back Off Due to Lack of Jurisdictions Over Terra Products</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/do-kwon-lawyers-sec-terra-products/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>KuCoin Loses $22,000 due to Twitter Hack, Exchange Announces Reimbursement</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/kucoin-loses-22000-twitter-hack/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/kucoin-loses-22000-twitter-hack/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 15:45:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cybersecurity News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[kucoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[twitter]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[usdc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[usdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=251927</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/kucoin-loses-22000-twitter-hack/">KuCoin Loses $22,000 due to Twitter Hack, Exchange Announces Reimbursement</a></p>
<p>KuCoin has assured all the impacted users that it would reimburse them the amount lost while also pledging additional security measures. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/kucoin-loses-22000-twitter-hack/">KuCoin Loses $22,000 due to Twitter Hack, Exchange Announces Reimbursement</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/kucoin-loses-22000-twitter-hack/">KuCoin Loses $22,000 due to Twitter Hack, Exchange Announces Reimbursement</a></p>
<p>In the latest development, the hackers managed to briefly breach the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/twitter/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Twitter</a> account of the crypto exchange KuCoin thereby causing the exchange users to lose more than $22,000.</p>
<p>Earlier today on April 24, hackers took over KuCoin&#8217;s Twitter account for 45 minutes, promoting a fake activity. Although the incident was brief, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/kucoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">KuCoin</a> has acknowledged that it identified 22 such transactions in connection with the fraudulent activity, including that of BTC and ETH. The value of the losses totaled 22,628 <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/tether/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">USDT</a>.</p>
<p>KuCoin said that to prevent any further harm to users, it is currently examining and blocking suspicious addresses in this regard. Although KuCoin recovered its Twitter account, the exchange has clarified that it was the only channel affected. Thus, it conveyed that its website and other social handles are doing absolutely fine.</p>
<p>Twitter is the most widely used social media channel for crypto discussions.  Thus, it has been a go-to communication for some of the top crypto personalities as well as crypto firms to communicate their ideas.</p>
<p>However, this also makes Twitter the top choice for hackers to manipulate users by posting fake giveaways and stealing people&#8217;s money. In a similar incident, hackers managed to hijack the Twitter account belonging to Circle’s Chief Strategy Officer Dante Disparte, and thus promoting a fake USDC airdrop.</p>
<p>Using such tricks, hackers have been airdropping several such fake tokens or circulating fake tokens under the name of popular platforms.</p>
<h2>KuCoin Decides to Reimburse the Victims</h2>
<p>Crypto exchange KuCoin has acknowledged the development and stated that it would reimburse the victims of the hack. In a message on Twitter, the crypto exchange <a href="https://twitter.com/kucoincom/status/1650426197497757696" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">noted</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;KuCoin will fully reimburse all verified asset losses caused by the social media breach and the fake activity. If you&#8217;re affected by this incident, please contact KuCoin Support team at support@kucoin.com&#8221;.</p></blockquote>
<p>Furthermore, KuCoin noted that along with Twitter&#8217;s 2FA, they plan to implement additional security measures in order to bolster the protection of its social media accounts. &#8220;We are also conducting a thorough investigation of the incident with Twitter to prevent similar occurrences in the future,&#8221; it added.</p>
<p>As the news of the hack spread, KuCoin&#8217;s native crypto token KCS came under selling pressure. As of press time, the KCS token is trading 0.71% down at a price of $8.05 and a market cap of $781 million.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coca-cola-q1-2023-results/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/kucoin-loses-22000-twitter-hack/">KuCoin Loses $22,000 due to Twitter Hack, Exchange Announces Reimbursement</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/kucoin-loses-22000-twitter-hack/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coca-Cola Releases Q1 2023 Results, Beats Estimates &amp; Doubles Down on Yearly Outlook</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coca-cola-q1-2023-results/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coca-cola-q1-2023-results/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 13:28:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wall Street]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coca cola]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coca cola stock]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=251914</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coca-cola-q1-2023-results/">Coca-Cola Releases Q1 2023 Results, Beats Estimates &#038; Doubles Down on Yearly Outlook</a></p>
<p>According to its Q1 2023 report, beverage giant Coca-Cola realized revenue of $10.96 billion on higher product prices and increased demand. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coca-cola-q1-2023-results/">Coca-Cola Releases Q1 2023 Results, Beats Estimates &#038; Doubles Down on Yearly Outlook</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coca-cola-q1-2023-results/">Coca-Cola Releases Q1 2023 Results, Beats Estimates &#038; Doubles Down on Yearly Outlook</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coca-cola/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coca-Cola</a> (NYSE: KO) published a <a href="https://investors.coca-colacompany.com/news-events/press-releases/detail/1081/coca-cola-reports-first-quarter-2023-results" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Q1 2023 earnings report</a> that beat estimates, largely by benefitting from price increases and higher demand. For the first quarter of 2023, the beverage giant pulled in revenue of $10.96 billion adjusted. This haul compares favorably to the $10.8 billion analysts expected for the same period. For Q1 2023, Coca-Cola also realized earnings per share (EPS) of 68 cents adjusted versus the consensus estimate of 64 cents expected.</p>
<p>Coca-Cola reported a $3.11 billion, or 72 cents per share Q1 net income attributable to shareholders. This haul is a substantial increase from the $2.78 billion, or 64 cents per share, the Atlanta-based corporation got a year earlier. Minus items, the company behind the famous Coke brand earned 68 cents per share.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, net sales for the first three months of the year rose 5% to $10.98 billion. In addition, Coca-Cola’s organic revenue rose 12% in the first quarter. Organic revenue eliminates the impact of acquisitions and divestitures.</p>
<p>Following its commendable quarterly outing, Coca-Cola doubled down on its forecast for the rest of 2023. The company projects a comparable revenue increase of up to 5% for the year alongside earnings per share growth of 4% to 5%.</p>
<h2>Coca-Cola CEO Comments on Company Q1 2023 Performance</h2>
<p>Weighing in on Coca-Cola’s latest quarterly performance, company chief executive James Quincey enthused:</p>
<blockquote><p>“We are encouraged by our first quarter 2023 results, our system alignment is stronger than ever, and our networked organization is allowing us to adapt as needed. We continue to invest for the long term, strengthening our capabilities to drive sustainable value for our stakeholders.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Quincey also pointed out that Coca-Cola’s performance demonstrated its resilience in the marketplace. Emphasizing the leading beverage company’s ability to keep thriving in a dynamic operating environment, the CEO added:</p>
<blockquote><p>“We have the right portfolio, the right strategy, and the right execution to deliver in the marketplace. We are confident in our ability to deliver on our 2023 objectives.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Coca-Cola has been hiking prices on its drink products to counterbalance the effects of inflation. However, the company, whose stock had risen 1% in 2023, experienced a surge in demand despite the price increments.</p>
<p>Coca-Cola shares are currently trading at just over $64 a pop. The Atlanta-based beverage giant has a market value of $277 billion.</p>
<h2>Coca-Cola AI Scheme</h2>
<p>Quincey previously stated that Coca-Cola’s growth culture opened up new ways to drive growth. One such way is venturing into the artificial intelligence (AI) world by engaging digital creatives to be expressive.</p>
<p>Last month, Coca-Cola <a href="https://www.coca-colacompany.com/news/coca-cola-invites-digital-artists-to-create-real-magic-using-new-ai-platform" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">invited digital artists</a> to generate original artwork using iconic creative assets from the company’s archives. The AI initiative, called “Create Real Magic,” is a platform built exclusively for the beverage corporation by OpenAI and Bain &amp; Company. According to Coca-Cola at the time, “Create Real Magic” is a first-of-its-kind AI platform that leverages the capabilities and potential of GPT-4.</p>
<p>Quincey described the AI scheme as improving the company’s operations and capabilities.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/lvmh-500-billion-market-value/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coca-cola-q1-2023-results/">Coca-Cola Releases Q1 2023 Results, Beats Estimates &#038; Doubles Down on Yearly Outlook</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coca-cola-q1-2023-results/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>LVMH Becomes First European Company to Exceed $500B Market Value</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/lvmh-500-billion-market-value/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/lvmh-500-billion-market-value/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 13:24:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bernard arnault]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[lvmh]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=251925</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/lvmh-500-billion-market-value/">LVMH Becomes First European Company to Exceed $500B Market Value</a></p>
<p>As LVMH records new levels in market valuation, its CEO and co-founder of the company is currently the world’s richest person.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/lvmh-500-billion-market-value/">LVMH Becomes First European Company to Exceed $500B Market Value</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/lvmh-500-billion-market-value/">LVMH Becomes First European Company to Exceed $500B Market Value</a></p>
<p>Luxury goods company <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/lvmh/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">LVMH</a> has become the first European company to exceed $500 billion in market value. LVMH, which engages in the design, manufacture, and sale of luxury products globally, is the parent company of Louis Vuitton, Hennessy, and Moet &amp; Chandon. Its other subsidiaries include Dior, Bvlgari, Sephora, Kenzo, Givenchy, etc.</p>
<p>For Q1 2023, LVMH reported a 17% increase in Q1 sales, representing more than X2 of analysts’ expectations. In reaction to the quarterly sales, its shares grew nearly 5%. Sales at the company reached more than $23 billion during the first quarter. The increased sales were triggered by the sharp rebound from the lockdown in China, its key market. At the beginning of the year, LVMH had said it was looking forward to benefiting from China’s reopening from the global health crisis lockdown. It revealed that wealthy Chinese consumers had resumed shopping since the country’s reopening. Hence, CEO <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/bernard-arnault/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bernard Arnault</a> said LVMH has “every reason to be confident, indeed optimistic on China”. When he made the statement, the CEO confirmed that the company’s stores in Macau were already full of shoppers.</p>
<p>According to LVMH, sales in Asia, excluding Asia, popped by 14%, compared to an 8% fall recorded in 2022 Q4. The luxury goods maker’s shares hit an all-time high on Thursday, after which it hit another high on Monday.</p>
<h2>LVMH Hit $500B Market Value</h2>
<p>LVMH, which is now the first European company to surpass $500 billion in market value, reported 79.2 billion euros ($87.1 billion) as revenue for 2022. Also, profit from recurring operations was 21.1 billion euros, marking the company’s second consecutive year of delivering record results. Before the new milestone in market value, Arnault had confidently stated that it would be an excellent year for LVMH. However, chief financial officer Jean-Jacques Guiony said the rebound was nothing compared to the pre-pandemic performance. The CFO noted LVMH is not back to the 2019 levels, adding that the company is “a long way from that”.</p>
<p>In addition, LVMH expects China to drive growth in 2023, which could further push its market value. On the other hand, the demand for European fashion houses in the US decreased, especially among younger shoppers. The new most valued European company said it saw softer demand in the US for fashion and leather goods as business slows down.</p>
<p>As LVMH records new levels in market valuation, its CEO and co-founder of the company, Arnault, is currently the world’s richest person. According to <a href="https://www.forbes.com/real-time-billionaires/#7225e7573d78" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Forbes</a>, Bernard Arnault &amp; Family tops the rank of the world’s richest with a net worth of $243.5 billion. He is about $68.5 billion richer than popular businessman <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/elon-musk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Elon Musk</a>, the second richest in the world, with $175.0 billion as his net worth.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cosmose-ai-near-retail-shopping/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/lvmh-500-billion-market-value/">LVMH Becomes First European Company to Exceed $500B Market Value</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/lvmh-500-billion-market-value/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cosmose AI and NEAR Foundation Partner to Improve Retail Shopping</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/cosmose-ai-near-retail-shopping/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/cosmose-ai-near-retail-shopping/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Babafemi Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 13:16:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[compose ai]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[kaikai]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[near]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[near foundation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=251815</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cosmose-ai-near-retail-shopping/">Cosmose AI and NEAR Foundation Partner to Improve Retail Shopping</a></p>
<p>Through the partnership with NEAR Foundation, Cosmose AI will expand its individualized experiences to its worldwide clientele through several channels.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cosmose-ai-near-retail-shopping/">Cosmose AI and NEAR Foundation Partner to Improve Retail Shopping</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cosmose-ai-near-retail-shopping/">Cosmose AI and NEAR Foundation Partner to Improve Retail Shopping</a></p>

<p>Cosmose AI, a leading AI and retail company, <a href="https://near.org/blog/cosmose-and-near-foundation-set-to-revolutionize-retail-with-web3-and-ai/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">is partnering</a> with NEAR Foundation to bring <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-web-3-0/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Web3</a> personalization to retail shopping. While the strategic investment by the NEAR Foundation was not disclosed, it raised the valuation of Cosmose AI from $100 million to $500 million.</p>
<p>The partnership will leverage the power of AI and blockchain to create hyper-personalized shopping experiences that increase loyalty and happiness. It will also incorporate a new crypto payment system that helps buyers and sellers save money.</p>
<p>Before the investment, Cosmose had served 20 million stores globally and had a team strength of 80 staff. Now, the duo are looking to reach at least one billion users with their AI and Web3-powered payment system.</p>
<h2>How KaiKai Is Changing Retail Shopping</h2>
<p>Cosmose AI&#8217;s flagship mobile application KaiKai offers a unique shopping experience known as Shoppertainment. It combines shopping, retail, and gamification, creating an altogether different experience for the retail shopper.</p>
<p>KaiKai gives users access to exclusive product drops, geolocation features that display available products in the vicinity, and rewards for products purchase and review writing. With its Near-powered payment system, users will save up to 50 times on their transactions when compared to traditional payment systems like Stripe.</p>
<p>According to a Cosmose board member, George Raymond Zage III, founder and CEO of Tiga Investments, “The investment from NEAR Foundation is a testament to Cosmose AI&#8217;s strength and potential to revolutionize e-commerce and the retail industry.”</p>
<h2>How the Web3 Personalization Will Look</h2>
<p>Even more ambitious than the lowering of transaction costs is the decision to pursue a hyper-personalized experience for customers.</p>
<p>While shopper and user personalization are not new in retail shopping, Cosmose approaches it differently. The company’s platform gathers and analyzes user data to produce suggestions and experiences that are personal to each user. It then gives users access to their data who can then determine how they want their data used. It does this while ensuring their privacy and security.</p>
<p>Through the partnership with NEAR Foundation, Cosmose AI will expand its individualized experiences to its worldwide clientele through several channels, including online, in-store, and mobile. It will also help retailers develop stronger customer interactions.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-btc-price-projection-50k-halving/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cosmose-ai-near-retail-shopping/">Cosmose AI and NEAR Foundation Partner to Improve Retail Shopping</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/cosmose-ai-near-retail-shopping/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin (BTC) Price Projections to $50K Grows Ahead of Next Year’s Halving</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-btc-price-projection-50k-halving/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-btc-price-projection-50k-halving/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 12:56:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin halving]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ther]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=251899</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-btc-price-projection-50k-halving/">Bitcoin (BTC) Price Projections to $50K Grows Ahead of Next Year’s Halving</a></p>
<p>Bitcoin price is hinged on the current perception of the macroeconomic outlook and monetary policies from the United States Federal Reserve.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-btc-price-projection-50k-halving/">Bitcoin (BTC) Price Projections to $50K Grows Ahead of Next Year’s Halving</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-btc-price-projection-50k-halving/">Bitcoin (BTC) Price Projections to $50K Grows Ahead of Next Year’s Halving</a></p>
<p>The forthcoming <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> (BTC) halving slated for April 2023 might have a significant impact in helping to push the price of digital currency to a new pedestal. The anticipation of the Bitcoin network event has spurred a renewed bullish projection from the top industry analyst.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-04-23/bitcoin-btc-halving-in-2024-spurs-predictions-of-rally-past-50-000?leadSource=uverify%20wall" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">According</a> to insight from Bloomberg Intelligence and Matrixport, the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-halving-2024-1-year-away/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">upcoming halving</a> event has the potential to help push the price of Bitcoin upward by at least 81%. The digital currency is changing hands at $27,419.85, down by 1.45% over the past 24 hours <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/bitcoin/markets/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">according</a> to data from CoinMarketCap.</p>
<p>Despite the fact that Bitcoin’s current outlook is a bearish one, the premier digital asset has recorded a largely positive performance for the bigger part of the year. Data shows that Bitcoin is up by 65.51% in the Year-to-Date (YTD) and Bloomberg Intelligence Analyst, Jamie Douglas Coutts noted that the upcoming Halving is just 50% price in.</p>
<p>“Bitcoin cycles bottom around 12-18 months prior to the halving and this cycle structure looks similar to the past ones, albeit many things have changed &#8211; while the network is vastly stronger, Bitcoin has never endured a prolonged severe economic contraction,” he said.</p>
<p>According to Jamie, Bitcoin looks very poised to retest the $50,000 price level by April 2024 following the halving event.</p>
<p>Notably, the fundamentals behind Halving back this bullish projection as the rate of Bitcoin production is projected to be cut by half. Riding on the law of demand and supply, the reduced production rate mixed with higher demand from both retail and institutional investors is bound to fuel the imminent growth in the price of digital currency.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin (BTC) Headwinds Projection</h2>
<p>Part of the key projection for Bitcoin price is hinged on the current perception of the macroeconomic outlook and monetary policies from the United States Federal Reserve. While inflation is pegged at approximately 5% for the month of March, the fears of a steady interest rate hike remain a major consideration to embrace risk assets or not.</p>
<p>The regulatory environment in the United States as it concerns the crackdown on top industry players by the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Securities and Exchange Commission</a> (SEC) is also a major headwind for the projected performance in the price of Bitcoin.</p>
<p>While Bitcoin is not exactly the target of the SEC which has named even <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a> (ETH) a security, the outlook emanating from the crackdowns is unhealthy for the industry as a whole. The digital currency ecosystem, with Bitcoin as the main asset, has experienced a lot of battery following the collapse of the FTX derivatives exchange. However, analysts believe the bottom is in and more upside momentum is in view for the cryptocurrency moving forward.</p>
<p>“If the collapse of FTX was indeed the bottom of this cycle, then history would suggest that we still have approximately 350 days of ‘accumulation’ before witnessing the characteristic post-halving breakout price action,” said Jacob Joseph, an analyst at CCData.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-revival-anthony-scaramucci/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-btc-price-projection-50k-halving/">Bitcoin (BTC) Price Projections to $50K Grows Ahead of Next Year’s Halving</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-btc-price-projection-50k-halving/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>FTX Revival Unlikely, Says Skybridge Capital Founder Anthony Scaramucci</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-revival-anthony-scaramucci/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-revival-anthony-scaramucci/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mercy Tukiya Mutanya]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 12:48:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthony Scaramucci]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gary gensler]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sam bankman-fried]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=251874</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-revival-anthony-scaramucci/">FTX Revival Unlikely, Says Skybridge Capital Founder Anthony Scaramucci</a></p>
<p>Scaramucci stated that it was more likely that FTX, once valued at $32 billion, would end up selling its software and licensure before opening under a new brand. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-revival-anthony-scaramucci/">FTX Revival Unlikely, Says Skybridge Capital Founder Anthony Scaramucci</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-revival-anthony-scaramucci/">FTX Revival Unlikely, Says Skybridge Capital Founder Anthony Scaramucci</a></p>
<p>Skybridge Capital founder Anthony Scaramucci does not think the defunct crypto exchange <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a> can be revived any time soon. The financier and former White House communications director explained that many exchanges were not making much money under current market conditions.</p>
<p>“I don&#8217;t see how it&#8217;s possible to restart FTX. Not a lot of money is being made in these exchanges right now, and so a lot of these exchanges are in the red, and they&#8217;re burning off capital that they raised in these private placements, waiting for a new bull market to start and waiting for higher volume,” Scaramucci <a href="https://www.theblock.co/post/227697/scaramucci-ftx-skybridge" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">stated</a> on an episode of The Block&#8217;s The Scoop podcast with Frank Chaparro.</p>
<p>Skybridge Capital is uniquely tied to FTX as it invested in the exchange while FTX bought a large stake in the investment company. Although Scaramucci believes that an FTX revival would be a “net positive” for his investment firm as it would provide an avenue for negotiation with the exchange, it would require a green light from creditors and a bankruptcy judge.</p>
<p>FTX’s legal team has previously stated that will explore the feasibility of a revival and will propose a restructuring plan in July that will have to be reviewed by creditors and voted on in the first half of next year. If approved, the plan would go into effect in the second quarter of 2024. Earlier this month, the legal team announced that the exchange’s new leadership had managed to recover $7.3 billion and was working on a revival plan. News of a possible reboot sent the price of FTX’s FTT token <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftt-surges-ftx-considers-reopening/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">surging over 100%</a> from $1.32 to $2.80. Scaramucci stated that it was more likely that FTX, once valued at $32 billion, would end up selling its software and licensure before opening under a new brand.</p>
<p>The financier also commented on Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) chairman Gary Gensler’s appearance before US Congress last week. He opined that Gensler’s treatment of crypto firms could end up pushing more businesses outside the country.</p>
<p>“Mr. Gensler is a bad faith regulator, and I think he&#8217;ll just delay the process of adoption for the US and it&#8217;s sad, because other countries will take the lead and we&#8217;ll be missing out,” Scaramucci said. “The notion that you would kick crypto out of the country because you got embarrassed by Sam Bankman-Fried I think is an absolute absurdity.”</p>
<p>During his April 18 appearance, Gensler was met with criticism from House Republicans over the SEC’s crackdown on crypto businesses. Among the issues raised was that the watchdog’s regulations were created with traditional markets in mind and did not apply to decentralized currency exchanges. Rep. Patrick McHenry, R-N.C. <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/04/18/gensler-defends-crypto-crackdown.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">stated</a> that the agency’s approach was “driving innovation overseas and endangering American competitiveness.”</p>
<p>“Regulation by enforcement is not sufficient nor sustainable,” said McHenry. “You’re punishing digital asset firms for allegedly not adhering to the law when they don’t know it will apply to them.”<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/philips-shares-q1-2023-results/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-revival-anthony-scaramucci/">FTX Revival Unlikely, Says Skybridge Capital Founder Anthony Scaramucci</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-revival-anthony-scaramucci/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Philips Shares Pop 12% as Company Reports Q1 2023 Results and Expresses Confidence in Fiscal Year</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/philips-shares-q1-2023-results/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/philips-shares-q1-2023-results/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 12:43:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[philips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[philips stock]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=251879</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/philips-shares-q1-2023-results/">Philips Shares Pop 12% as Company Reports Q1 2023 Results and Expresses Confidence in Fiscal Year</a></p>
<p>With Q1 over, the CEO is confident that Philips will deliver on its plan for 2023.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/philips-shares-q1-2023-results/">Philips Shares Pop 12% as Company Reports Q1 2023 Results and Expresses Confidence in Fiscal Year</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/philips-shares-q1-2023-results/">Philips Shares Pop 12% as Company Reports Q1 2023 Results and Expresses Confidence in Fiscal Year</a></p>
<p>Shares of multinational conglomerate corporation <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/philips/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Philips</a> (NYSE: PHG) popped 12.72% at the pre-market trading on Monday as the company <a href="https://www.results.philips.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">released</a> its Q1 2023 financial results. The company recorded gains after reporting higher adjusted EBITA and sales during the first quarter. Adjusted EBITA increased by 8.6% to EUR 359 million. Meanwhile, the company saw EUR 243 million, or 6.2% of sales, in Q1 2022. According to the Q1 2023 quarterly report, group sales soared with 6% comparable sales growth to EUR 4.2 billion. At the same time, there was an improvement in the operating cash flow. While Philips highlighted that the cash flow did better to EUR 202 million in Q1 2023, there was an outflow of EUR 227 million in Q1 2022.</p>
<h2>Philips Posts Q1 2023 Results</h2>
<p>However, Philips said the net loss in Q1 was wider than the previous year&#8217;s first quarter. This is because of the significant litigation provision related to the anticipated resolution of the Respironics recall-related economic loss class action in the US. The multinational company noted that operating income amounted to a loss of EUR 583 million.</p>
<p>The CEO of Royal Philips, Roy Jakobs, said in the Q1 report that the company had a strong start for fiscal 2023. The CEO said:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;I am encouraged that we delivered a solid start to the year, with sales, profitability and operating cash flow improvements in the quarter, a first step to drive progressive value creation. We are executing on our three priorities to enhance patient safety and quality, strengthen our supply chain reliability, and establish a simplified, more agile operating model.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Furthermore, Jakobs said the highest priority is to resolve the Philips Respironics recall for patients. He stated that the Amsterdam-based company recorded a provision of an anticipated resolution in the US, which is crucial in addressing the litigation related to the call. Also, the Royal Philips CEO mentioned &#8220;good growth&#8221; across its Diagnosis &amp; Treatment businesses and in Hospital Patient Monitoring.</p>
<h2>Philips&#8217; Progress on Headcount Reduction</h2>
<p>In addition, Philips was among the multiple companies that dismissed specific percentages of their workforce. The company announced in January that it would be firing another 6,000 employees after saying in October 2022 that it would cut 4,000 jobs. Combined, it planned to let go of 10,000 people or about 13% of its global workforce. While commenting on the Q1 financial performance, Jakobs said that Philips had reduced its employees by approximately 5,400. He applauded the workers&#8217; efforts and commitment to fulfilling the organization&#8217;s purpose. The chief executive also expressed his appreciation to partners and customers for maintaining their trust and support for the company.</p>
<p>With Q1 over, the CEO is confident that Philips will deliver on its plan for 2023. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Looking ahead, based on our solid performance in the quarter, our order book, and the ongoing actions to further improve execution, we are confident in our plan for the year 2023, acknowledging that uncertainties remain.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>On the New York stock exchange, Philips is up 12.72% to $21.45 in the pre-market trading session.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-hit-100000-2024-end/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/philips-shares-q1-2023-results/">Philips Shares Pop 12% as Company Reports Q1 2023 Results and Expresses Confidence in Fiscal Year</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/philips-shares-q1-2023-results/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Standard Chartered: Bitcoin Tipped to Hit $100,000 by 2024 End</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-hit-100000-2024-end/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-hit-100000-2024-end/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 12:29:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price 2024]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price prediction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[standard chartered]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=251882</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-hit-100000-2024-end/">Standard Chartered: Bitcoin Tipped to Hit $100,000 by 2024 End</a></p>
<p>With all the predictions, it appears that Bitcoin may truly be getting ready for a long rally.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-hit-100000-2024-end/">Standard Chartered: Bitcoin Tipped to Hit $100,000 by 2024 End</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-hit-100000-2024-end/">Standard Chartered: Bitcoin Tipped to Hit $100,000 by 2024 End</a></p>
<p>Flagship cryptocurrency <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> could climb as high as $100,000 by the end of next year, according to Standard Chartered. If that level is reached, it would mark a 270% surge from Monday&#8217;s level of just over $27,000 that CoinMarketCap <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">data</a> shows.</p>
<p>According to <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/standard-chartered/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Standard Chartered</a>&#8216;s report, the so-called &#8220;crypto winter&#8221; is over, and from all indications, Bitcoin is set to go on a gaining stretch.</p>
<p>One of the factors that inform this prediction is the fact that the Federal Reserve is about to end its aggressive rate-hiking cycle. According to Geoff Kendrick, head of digital assets research at Standard Chartered, the move could propel Bitcoin to $100,000. However, he admits that other factors may still hinder this expected rally. Kendrick <a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/bitcoin-could-hit-100000-by-end-2024-standard-chartered-says-2023-04-24/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">wrote</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;While sources of uncertainty remain, we think the pathway to the USD 100,000 level is becoming clearer.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Another factor that formed part of the prediction is that, recently, there has been improved profitability in crypto mining operations. That is not to mention the risks of the banking sector that were recently exposed.</p>
<h2>Too Bold Bitcoin Prediction by Standard Chartered?</h2>
<p>Generally, there is now a much more optimistic outlook on cryptocurrencies and other risk assets. This is as central banks round off tightening their monetary policies.</p>
<p>However, sky-high predictions such as this are not exactly uncommon in the crypto sector. A Citi analyst once projected that Bitcoin could hit $318,000 by the end of 2022. While that prediction didn&#8217;t go as planned, there are many more who are bullish on Bitcoin even for the year running. For example, Venture Capitalist Tim Draper holds the opinion that Bitcoin could rise to as much as $250,000 this year. Draper has held this view since 2021 and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tim-draper-250k-price-bitcoin-2023/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reconfirmed his position</a> again last December.</p>
<p>With all the predictions, however, it does appear that Bitcoin may truly be getting ready for a long rally. It has shown some positive signs in the year thus far, rallying above the $30,000 mark this April. Interestingly, that was the first time it crossed that level in ten months.</p>
<p>While Bitcoin has slightly retraced, it is expected that the crypto market in general will continue on the path to recovering from its trillion-dollar losses of 2022.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tech-earnings-q1-reports/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-hit-100000-2024-end/">Standard Chartered: Bitcoin Tipped to Hit $100,000 by 2024 End</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-hit-100000-2024-end/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tech Earnings Dominate Second Week of Q1 Reports with Amazon, Microsoft, Meta &amp; Alphabet Leading Charge</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tech-earnings-q1-reports/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tech-earnings-q1-reports/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 11:37:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wall Street]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alphabet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Amazon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Meta]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[microsoft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tesla]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=251875</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tech-earnings-q1-reports/">Tech Earnings Dominate Second Week of Q1 Reports with Amazon, Microsoft, Meta &#038; Alphabet Leading Charge</a></p>
<p>In this week's Q1 tech earnings reports, investors look for signs of staying power amid a recession-threatened economy. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tech-earnings-q1-reports/">Tech Earnings Dominate Second Week of Q1 Reports with Amazon, Microsoft, Meta &#038; Alphabet Leading Charge</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tech-earnings-q1-reports/">Tech Earnings Dominate Second Week of Q1 Reports with Amazon, Microsoft, Meta &#038; Alphabet Leading Charge</a></p>
<p><a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/amazon-microsoft-meta-alphabet-lead-earnings-rush-what-to-know-this-week-114436466.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Tech earnings</a> will make up a significant portion of corporate Q1 earnings this week, in the second week of quarterly reports. Investors will be paying close attention to <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/amazon/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Amazon</a> (NASDAQ: AMZN), <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/microsoft-corporation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Microsoft</a> (NASDAQ: MSFT), and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/alphabet-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Alphabet </a>(NASDAQ: GOOGL) in a packed week. Investors may also take cues from these corporate reports to determine the fiscal landscape as the Fed battles inflation.</p>
<p>Big tech Q1 earnings this week will also draw attention away from the banking sector, which has dominated earnings reports in the past week. The mainstream financial industry is at its lowest point since the 2008 meltdown, following collapses including Silicon Valley Bank (SVB).</p>
<h2>Projected Tech Q1 Performances Suggest Pared Down Earnings in Light of Bright Start to Year</h2>
<p>Tech stocks surged at the beginning of the year and maxed out last month after becoming a safe haven for investors fleeing the banking crisis. This ascent is also evident in the tech-heavy Nasdaq Composite, which is up by more than 15% this year. However, investors remain restrained in their expectations and believe an underwhelming performance could impact the broader equity market.</p>
<p>Recent <a href="https://insight.factset.com/sp-500-earnings-season-update-april-21-2023?utm_source=Direct&amp;utm_medium=Email&amp;utm_campaign=feedotter-04-21-2023&amp;utm_content=httpsinsightfactsetcomsp500earningsseasonupdateapril212023" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">FactSet data</a> showed quarterly <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-the-sp-500-index/">S&amp;P 500</a> earnings are expected to decline 6.2% through April 21st. This decline is more apparent when combining already reported results with analysts&#8217; expectations. A 6.2% quarterly decline would be the most significant earnings drop since 2020&#8217;s Q2 31.6% setback.</p>
<p>Results from Amazon, Microsoft, Alphabet, and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/meta/">Meta Platforms</a> (NASDAQ: META) could shape investor guidance going forward. Furthermore, most investors will look out for signs that these tech companies can thrive in an economy headed toward a recession. These signs include updates on artificial intelligence (AI) efforts and ongoing cost cuts. Generally tech earnings for Q1 are important as Q2 begins.</p>
<h2>AI Developments &amp; Downsizing Post-Covid</h2>
<p>Tech players have been under increasing pressure to develop their AI units since ChatGPT entered the market last November. The OpenAI chatbot has exploded in popularity, demonstrating its applicability in everyday use cases. However, although tech giants like Microsoft, Meta, Amazon, and Chinese mainstay Tencent look to strengthen their AI visibility, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/tesla/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tesla</a> (NASDAQ: TSLA) harbors some reservations. The electric vehicle manufacturer warns of the &#8216;intrusive&#8217; and &#8216;destructive&#8217; repercussions of sentient AI technology on humankind. Instead, Tesla&#8217;s CEO <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/elon-musk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Elon Musk</a> seeks to <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/elon-musk-launch-truthgpt/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">create an AI tech called TruthGPT</a> that offsets those threats. Musk described the initiative as a &#8220;maximum truth-seeking&#8221; initiative, saying TruthGPT would right the wrongs of the &#8220;politically correct&#8221; ChatGPT. In his assessment of the type of AI technology presently making inroads into numerous sectors and industries, the Tesla boss said:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;AI is more dangerous than, say, mismanaged aircraft design or production maintenance or bad car production in the sense that it has the potential &#8211; however small one may regard that probability, but it is not trivial &#8211; it has the potential of civilizational destruction.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Tech companies have also resorted to downsizing for better earnings. Several of these companies over-expanded during the lockdown to better contain the exponential growth experienced from consumer trends.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ethereum-eth-ico-participant-awakens-after-7-7-years-heres-what-happened/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tech-earnings-q1-reports/">Tech Earnings Dominate Second Week of Q1 Reports with Amazon, Microsoft, Meta &#038; Alphabet Leading Charge</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tech-earnings-q1-reports/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=PhpRedis metric#hits=4747 metric#misses=43 metric#hit-ratio=99.1 metric#bytes=1345357 metric#prefetches=207 metric#store-reads=21 metric#store-writes=16 metric#store-hits=213 metric#store-misses=4 metric#sql-queries=34 metric#ms-total=101.47 metric#ms-cache=6218.67 metric#ms-cache-median=0.00 metric#ms-cache-ratio=6,128.6 -->