<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 11:06:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Binance.US Halts USD Deposits, Blames SEC’s ‘Witch-hunt’</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-us-halts-usd-deposits/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 11:05:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance us]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[changpeng zhao]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=258291</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-us-halts-usd-deposits/">Binance.US Halts USD Deposits, Blames SEC&#8217;s &#8216;Witch-hunt&#8217;</a></p>
<p>Ongoing regulatory pressure has created a difficult working terrain for the banking partners of Binance.US.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-us-halts-usd-deposits/">Binance.US Halts USD Deposits, Blames SEC&#8217;s &#8216;Witch-hunt&#8217;</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-us-halts-usd-deposits/">Binance.US Halts USD Deposits, Blames SEC&#8217;s &#8216;Witch-hunt&#8217;</a></p>
<p>Binance.US has told its customers that they may not be able to buy crypto with their US dollars from June 13. The Thursday announcement follows after the Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-sues-binance-securities-rules/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">filed</a> a lawsuit against the exchange and its founder Changpeng Zhao (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/changpeng-zhao/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CZ</a>) on Monday.</p>
<p>SEC insists that <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a> had violated the country’s securities laws. The exchange, on the other hand, says the regulator is only leveling “unjustified civil claims” against its business.</p>
<p>The official <a href="https://twitter.com/BinanceUS/status/1666996908651323393" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announcement</a> reads in part:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Today we are suspending USD deposits and notifying customers that our banking partners are preparing to pause fiat (USD) withdrawal channels as early as June 13, 2023.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Binance.US to Lose Access to US Banking System</h2>
<p>As it stands, the SEC is looking to freeze Binance.US&#8217; assets. Interestingly, however, the regulator has also considered customers and asked the court to approve a temporary restraining order. This is to allow the exchange to continue processing withdrawal requests in the meantime.</p>
<p>Despite this, the regulatory pressure has created a difficult working terrain for the banking partners of Binance.US. Hence, the reason the so-called banking partners “signalled their intent to pause USD fiat channels”, from as early as next week.</p>
<p>Nonetheless, Binance has encouraged its customers to take appropriate action with their USD. It also assures them that their funds are safe. That is, even if they are unable to withdraw their money by the due date, they could still convert it to a stablecoin such as Tether (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/tether/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">USDT</a>), and then withdraw that. Thereafter, they may then convert the stablecoin back to dollars elsewhere.</p>
<p>The exchange said it had preemptively disabled customers’ ability to buy and deposit US dollars.</p>
<h2>Transition in Progress?</h2>
<p>The proactive measures taken by Binance.US to stop customers from buying and depositing US dollars may have positioned it as a crypto-only exchange. But that may be only until its case with the SEC is cleared up.</p>
<p>Presently, however, Binance.US has taken other measures to ensure that its US-focused platform continues functioning even without the banks. To this end, the exchange has also <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-us-selected-trading-pairs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">announced</a> the de-listing of ten different trading pairs in light of the ongoing lawsuit.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/breakthroughs-generative-ai-meta/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-us-halts-usd-deposits/">Binance.US Halts USD Deposits, Blames SEC&#8217;s &#8216;Witch-hunt&#8217;</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>‘We’ve Seen Some Really Incredible Breakthroughs on Generative AI,’ Meta CEO Mark Zuckerberg Says</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/breakthroughs-generative-ai-meta/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 10:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mark zuckerberg]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Meta]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=258288</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/breakthroughs-generative-ai-meta/">&#8216;We’ve Seen Some Really Incredible Breakthroughs on Generative AI,&#8217; Meta CEO Mark Zuckerberg Says</a></p>
<p>Meta will work towards making these AI capabilities accessible to people. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/breakthroughs-generative-ai-meta/">&#8216;We’ve Seen Some Really Incredible Breakthroughs on Generative AI,&#8217; Meta CEO Mark Zuckerberg Says</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/breakthroughs-generative-ai-meta/">&#8216;We’ve Seen Some Really Incredible Breakthroughs on Generative AI,&#8217; Meta CEO Mark Zuckerberg Says</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/mark-zuckerberg/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Mark Zuckerberg</a> recently revealed that Meta (NASDAQ: META) has been experiencing “incredible breakthroughs&#8221; in its use of generative artificial intelligence (AI). Like many other tech giants, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/meta/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Meta</a> is also in the middle of the AI race, which has become the latest evolution in the market. Not only tech companies, but different organizations across diverse fields have also started adopting AI in the latest developments.</p>
<h2>Meta Records Significant Breakthroughs with Generative AI</h2>
<p>According to a spokesperson, the Meta boss spoke about the areas where the company uses generative AI during a meeting with employees on Thursday. The meeting was held in the Hacker Square Pavilion at the tech company’s headquarters in Menlo Park. Notably, the event was the first that happened at the locations since pre-pandemic days.</p>
<p>In a statement shared with <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/06/08/meta-ceo-mark-zuckerberg-talks-companys-ai-efforts-to-employees.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">CNBC</a>, Zuckerberg said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“In the last year, we’ve seen some really incredible breakthroughs- qualitative breakthroughs- on generative AI and that gives us the opportunity to now go take that technology, push it forward, and build it into every single one of our products.”</p></blockquote>
<p>In addition, he noted that Meta will work towards making these AI capabilities accessible to people. The CEO said the company will bring the technology to people in a unique way, different from others. He and other executives discuss how AI could aid the creation of 3D visuals for the metaverse. Zuckerberg is indeed moving hard on AI as Meta announced that employees now have access to multiple generative AI tools. The purpose is to enable them to develop prototypes while the company organizes a hackathon for them to show off their AI projects.</p>
<p>The plan Meta CEO has includes putting AI text, image, and video generators into its flagship products like Facebook and Instagram. The development will allow Instagram users to modify pictures via text prompts and share them in their Stories feature. Furthermore, Meta is working towards enabling Messenger and WhatsApp users to engage with AI-powered chatbots.</p>
<h2>Instagram is Reportedly Working on AI Chatbot</h2>
<p>Meanwhile, Coinspeaker <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/instagram-ai-chatbot/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a> on Wednesday that Meta-owned Instagram is reportedly working on an AI chatbot. The matter was revealed by app researcher Alessandro Paluzzi who shared some screenshots that suggest that the social media app is on the verge of unveiling an AI chatbot.</p>
<p>Also, Meta addressed the recent layoff at the same event where he spoke about the “breakthroughs” the company has seen in AI. The tech giant began <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-another-round-layoffs-6000/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">another round of layoffs</a> in late May. The new decision means that additional 6,000 employees will lose their jobs in addition to over 20,000 job cuts since November. While other layoffs focused on the engineering and recruitment teams, the latest workers in the business division.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/docu-shares-docusign-q1-2024/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/breakthroughs-generative-ai-meta/">&#8216;We’ve Seen Some Really Incredible Breakthroughs on Generative AI,&#8217; Meta CEO Mark Zuckerberg Says</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>DOCU Shares Up 5% as DocuSign Beats Q1 2024 Earnings Estimate with Strong Guidance</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/docu-shares-docusign-q1-2024/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 08:32:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wall Street]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[docu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[docu stock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[docusign]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[docusign stock]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=258278</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/docu-shares-docusign-q1-2024/">DOCU Shares Up 5% as DocuSign Beats Q1 2024 Earnings Estimate with Strong Guidance</a></p>
<p>DocuSign has given a strong guidance for the second fiscal quarter anticipating revenue of $675 million to $679 million. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/docu-shares-docusign-q1-2024/">DOCU Shares Up 5% as DocuSign Beats Q1 2024 Earnings Estimate with Strong Guidance</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/docu-shares-docusign-q1-2024/">DOCU Shares Up 5% as DocuSign Beats Q1 2024 Earnings Estimate with Strong Guidance</a></p>
<p>On Thursday, June 8, e-signature provider DocuSign (NASDAQ: DOCU) <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/06/08/docusign-docu-q1-earnings-report-2024.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reported</a> strong earnings beating revenue estimates for the fiscal quarter ending April 30 (Q1 2024). In the aftermarket hours on Thursday, the company&#8217;s share price is trading 5% up moving past $61.</p>
<p>DocuSign Inc, based in San Francisco, California, is a company that provides electronic agreement management services. Their flagship product, eSignature, enables electronic signing on various devices as part of the DocuSign Agreement Cloud.</p>
<p>DocuSign reported Q1 2024 earnings at 72 cents per share against the 56 cents per share as per analysts of Refinitiv. Similarly, the company reported a revenue of $661 million against the expected $642 million. This shows that during the first quarter of fiscal 2024, DocuSign&#8217;s revenue surged by a healthy 12%. Interestingly, this double-digit growth comes at a time of uncertain macro environment.</p>
<p>DocuSign reported a 14% spike to $22 million in the “professional services and other” category, on a year-over-year period. The company&#8217;s net income stood at $539,000 against the $27.4 million net loss, a year ago.</p>
<p>Additionally, DocuSign also announced new products and services such as Webforms. Using Webforms, organizations will be able to create, manage and customize their own forms. Thus, it will help in exporting as well as analyzing the data collected.</p>
<p>Since the beginning of the year 2023, the DOCU stock has remained quite volatile underperforming the benchmark indices. However, these strong results might serve as a catalyst for the stock price to rally from here onwards.</p>
<h2>DocuSign User Growth in Q1 2024</h2>
<p>DocuSign has a total of $1.4 million paying users more than 1 billion users as of April 30. The company emphasized on its international focus to investors and offers its service in more than 180 countries. DocuSign has registered 17% international revenue growth year over year.</p>
<p>According to Refinitiv, DocuSign anticipates revenue of $675 million to $679 million for the fiscal second quarter, surpassing analyst estimates of $667 million. For the entire fiscal year, the company predicts revenue ranging from $2.71 billion to $2.73 billion, exceeding analysts&#8217; expectations of $2.7 billion.</p>
<p>Last quarter, DocuSign hired new executives for key positions in its leadership team. They appointed Blake Grayson as the new chief financial officer. Blake previously worked as the CFO at The Trade Desk and held finance roles at <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/amazon/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Amazon</a>.</p>
<p>They also brought on Dmitri Krakovsky as the new chief product officer, who has previous experience at CP4, Google, SAP, and Yahoo. Additionally, Kurt Sauer joined as the new chief information security officer, having previously held the same role at Workday.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-broadcasting-tool-channels-whatsapp/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/docu-shares-docusign-q1-2024/">DOCU Shares Up 5% as DocuSign Beats Q1 2024 Earnings Estimate with Strong Guidance</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Meta Soon to Bring Broadcasting Tool ‘Channels’ for WhatsApp</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-broadcasting-tool-channels-whatsapp/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 12:33:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Meta]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[whatsapp]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=258255</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-broadcasting-tool-channels-whatsapp/">Meta Soon to Bring Broadcasting Tool &#8216;Channels&#8217; for WhatsApp</a></p>
<p>WhatsApp Channels will function as a one-way broadcast tool allowing admins to send photos, texts, videos, stickers, and polls. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-broadcasting-tool-channels-whatsapp/">Meta Soon to Bring Broadcasting Tool &#8216;Channels&#8217; for WhatsApp</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-broadcasting-tool-channels-whatsapp/">Meta Soon to Bring Broadcasting Tool &#8216;Channels&#8217; for WhatsApp</a></p>
<p>Facebook parent <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/meta/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Meta</a> (NASDAQ: FB) has recently confirmed that it will soon debut its broadcasting feature Channels for its most-popular messaging service WhatsApp.</p>
<p>Speaking on the development on Thursday, June 8, Meta said that the new Channels feature is similar to a “private broadcast service” wherein individuals and organizations can send messages as well as updates to followers which are different from the kinds of interpersonal communications that happen between WhatsApp users.</p>
<p>Channels will function as a one-way broadcast tool allowing admins to send photos, texts, videos, stickers, and polls. Besides, Channels will come with a searchable directory wherein users can find their hobbies, sports team, updates, and much more.</p>
<p>Also, the Channels admins won&#8217;t be able to able to add followers to their channels. They can store messages only for a period of 30 days before being deleted automatically.</p>
<p>Another thing that users need to note Channels won&#8217;t come with end-to-end encryption in order to &#8220;reach a wide audience&#8221; said WhatsApp. However, the messaging platform added that they might bring end-to-end encrypted Channels eventually in the future. But WhatsApp will keep this facility limited to nonprofits or health organizations that need to keep their communication secure.</p>
<p>WhatsApp will eventually enable users to find Channels they want to join in a searchable directory. Users will be able to access the Channels they follow through a new &#8220;Updates&#8221; tab. WhatsApp stated that the tab will be &#8220;separate from your chats with family, friends, and communities&#8221;.</p>
<h2>Meta to Debut Channels with Various Groups</h2>
<p>WhatsApp stated that it&#8217;s already working with various groups and nonprofits such as Colombia Check and Singapore Heart Foundation to debut Channels. They are planning for a broader launch in other parts of the world. In the official <a href="https://blog.whatsapp.com/introducing-whatsapp-channels-a-private-way-to-follow-what-matters" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">blog post</a>, WhatsApp noted:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;To kick off Channels, we’re excited to work with leading global voices and select organizations in Colombia and Singapore, where Channels will first be available, to build, learn, and adapt the experience. We’ll bring Channels to more countries and the ability for anyone to create a channel over the coming months.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Eventually, WhatsApp will allow everyone to create a WhatsApp channel. Some of its other launch partners include the International Rescue Committee and the World Health Organization. Meta also said that “there is an opportunity to support admins with a way for them to build a business around their channel using our expanding payment services as well as the ability to promote certain channels in the directory to help increase awareness”.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-sec-boss-advisor-crypto/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-broadcasting-tool-channels-whatsapp/">Meta Soon to Bring Broadcasting Tool &#8216;Channels&#8217; for WhatsApp</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Attorneys Say SEC Boss Offered to Be Advisor to Crypto Company in 2019</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-sec-boss-advisor-crypto/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 10:53:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Binance News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[changpeng zhao]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gary gensler]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=258251</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-sec-boss-advisor-crypto/">Binance Attorneys Say SEC Boss Offered to Be Advisor to Crypto Company in 2019</a></p>
<p>At the time Gensler was offered to be an advisor to Binance, he was teaching at Massachusetts Institute of Technology’s Sloan School of Management. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-sec-boss-advisor-crypto/">Binance Attorneys Say SEC Boss Offered to Be Advisor to Crypto Company in 2019</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-sec-boss-advisor-crypto/">Binance Attorneys Say SEC Boss Offered to Be Advisor to Crypto Company in 2019</a></p>
<p>According to the lawyers of Binance and its CEO <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/changpeng-zhao/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Changpeng Zhao</a>, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a> chair <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/gary-gensler/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Gary Gensler</a> was offered to be an advisor to Binance’s parent company in 2019. Interestingly, Gensler has been spearheading the crackdown against the crypto industry over the past year. Binance and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-sec-coinbase-unregistered-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">other crypto companies</a> are currently under the radar of the US regulator over violations of securities laws. The SEC chair has repeatedly expressed his bearish stance against crypto and crypto companies. He said in March that just because a crypto trading platform claims to be a qualified custodian does not mean that it is.</p>
<h2>SEC Chair Could Become an Advisor to Binance in 2019</h2>
<p>The news of the offer to Gensler to serve as an adviser to <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a> came to light in the wake of the recent filings against the company, which include violations of securities laws, flouting KYC rules, and more. Per the documents filed by the Commission on Wednesday, two law firms representing Binance, Gibson Dunn and Latham &amp; Watkins, alleged that the SEC chair made the offer in several conversations with Binance executives and Zhao in March 2019. The filing added that Gensler also met the Binance CEO in Japan for lunch later in the same month.</p>
<p>At the time Gensler was offered to be an advisor to Binance, he was yet to be a boss at SEC. He was teaching at Massachusetts Institute of Technology’s Sloan School of Management. After then, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/joe-biden/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">President Joe Biden</a> appointed him to head the Commission in 2021. However, Gensler has become hard on the crypto market, targeting numerous companies and slamming them with lawsuits over allegedly selling unregistered securities. It has been a dramatic week for the crypto industry as the SEC filed 13 charges against Binance and Zhao. The regulator claimed the company did not register as an exchange and broker-deal. It also alleged that Binance and Zhao put investors at risk to fund their own pockets.</p>
<h2>Zhao-Gensler Relationship before SEC&#8217;s Crypto Crackdown</h2>
<p>Furthermore, the lawyers said Zhao maintained contact with Gensler after the lunch meeting in March. Also, the Binance chief granted Genlser’s request by granting an interview as part of a crypto course he was teaching at MIT. Later in the year, the future SEC boss shared a copy of his intended <a href="https://www.congress.gov/116/meeting/house/109821/witnesses/HHRG-116-BA00-Wstate-GenslerG-20190717-U1.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener">testimony</a> with Zhao. He was going to testify before the House Financial Services Committee. Testifying before the House over Facebook’s proposed but failed crypto Libra and the Calibra wallet, the MIT professor noted:</p>
<blockquote><p>“I do not advise any financial, technology, blockchain or other companies, nor do I own any cryptocurrencies.”</p></blockquote>
<p>After Gensler proposed the advisor idea in 2019 after which he reportedly met Zhao, SEC investigations and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-sues-binance-securities-rules/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">lawsuits against Binance US</a> and Binance began in 2020 and 2020, respectively.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-zhao-summoned-malta/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-sec-boss-advisor-crypto/">Binance Attorneys Say SEC Boss Offered to Be Advisor to Crypto Company in 2019</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Chief Changpeng Zhao Summoned at Malta Address, Says Won’t Have to Appear</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-zhao-summoned-malta/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 09:22:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance cz]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[changpeng zhao]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cz]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[signature bank]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[silvergate bank]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=258241</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-zhao-summoned-malta/">Binance Chief Changpeng Zhao Summoned at Malta Address, Says Won&#8217;t Have to Appear</a></p>
<p>The filing by the SEC cites Binance's operations in Malta with CZ noting that he won't have to appear in person. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-zhao-summoned-malta/">Binance Chief Changpeng Zhao Summoned at Malta Address, Says Won&#8217;t Have to Appear</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-zhao-summoned-malta/">Binance Chief Changpeng Zhao Summoned at Malta Address, Says Won&#8217;t Have to Appear</a></p>
<p>As per the lawsuit filed by the US Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>), Binance chief Changpeng Zhao has been summoned to Malta. The SEC has accused the exchange of indulging in shady activities in Malta between 2018 and 2019.</p>
<p>Binance chief Zhao cleared the air stating that he won&#8217;t need to appear in person to address the summons. &#8220;I was told this is just part of the SEC-compliant process. Nothing new. Also told I won&#8217;t have to appear in person. No need to FUD,&#8221; he <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1666513302304727059" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">wrote</a>.</p>
<p>The SEC filed the summons on Wednesday in the US District Court for the District of Columbia. However, this is just procedural and nothing special.</p>
<p>Earlier this week, the US SEC slapped a lawsuit on Binance on the count of 13 different charges involving misleading investors, operating as an unregistered broker/trader, and much more.  Binance arrived in Malta in March 2018 and in October of the same year, Malta passed a law allowing crypto companies to apply for licenses to operate there.</p>
<p>From October 2018 to October 2019, Binance operated in Malta. During this time, crypto companies that moved to Malta had a year to seek authorization and comply with regulations. During that period, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a> and others were not required to seek authorization or follow anti-money laundering laws.</p>
<p>The recent court filing by the SEC reveals Binance&#8217;s preference for weak regulations in Malta, which was promoting itself as a blockchain-friendly destination. The upcoming trial will likely put light on Binance&#8217;s questionable activities in Malta, particularly concerning US investors and institutions.</p>
<h2>Binance&#8217;s Partnership with Signature Bank</h2>
<p>The fresh filing by the SEC on Wednesday, June 7, also points out the money trail showing that nearly Binance moved nearly $70 billion through its accounts at now-bankrupt Silvergate Bank and Signature Bank. This total amount moved happened in the period from 2019 until earlier this year.</p>
<p>The SEC filing shows that Silvergate Bank facilitated over $50 billion for Binance and affiliated companies. similarly, Signature Bank facilitated over $19 billion. Citing records of Binance&#8217;s bank statements, deposits, wire transfers and canceled checks, the SEC filing shows that some of the funds also flew out to foreign entities.</p>
<p>The filing noted: “At times the amounts being credited and debited during a single month amounts to movement of more than a billion dollars. For example, in July 2021, one Signature Bank Binance Holdings account shows a starting balance of $468 million, deposits of $1 billion, withdrawals of $1.3 billion, and an ending balance of $179 million.”</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-us-selected-trading-pairs/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-zhao-summoned-malta/">Binance Chief Changpeng Zhao Summoned at Malta Address, Says Won&#8217;t Have to Appear</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance US Removes Selected Trading Pairs Amid SEC Allegations</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-us-selected-trading-pairs/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 08:45:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance us]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=258236</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-us-selected-trading-pairs/">Binance US Removes Selected Trading Pairs Amid SEC Allegations</a></p>
<p>Binance is also pausing its OTC Trading Portal services in the US. The exchange said that it will notify users if and when the portal opens in the coming weeks and months. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-us-selected-trading-pairs/">Binance US Removes Selected Trading Pairs Amid SEC Allegations</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-us-selected-trading-pairs/">Binance US Removes Selected Trading Pairs Amid SEC Allegations</a></p>
<p>The US arm of top crypto exchange <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a> has removed 10 advanced trading pairs from its platform. In an <a href="https://support.binance.us/hc/en-us/articles/15133607064983-Binance-US-Will-Remove-Select-Trading-Pairs-Has-Paused-OTC-Trading" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announcement</a>, the exchange said it would let go of select BTC and BUSD Advanced Trading pairs by 9 am PDT on June 8, 2023. Notably, the company earlier planned to eliminate over 100 crypto assets. The initial decision was supposed to affect USDT, BTC, and BUSD advanced trading pairs for digital assets like Bitcoin Cash, Uniswap, and others. According to the breakdown of the former remover provided by Binance, 95 assets were paired with USDT. In addition, eight cryptos were paired with BTC, while two were with BUSD. However, Binance US updated the press release, noting:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Following community feedback, Binance.US will no longer remove any USDT Advanced Trading pairs. All cryptocurrencies and USDT pairs remain available to trade. Only select BTC and BUSD Advanced Trading pairs below will be removed.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>Binance Eliminates Selected Trading Pairs</h2>
<p>The affected Bitcoin trading pairs are ATOM/BTC, BCH/BTC, DOT/BTC, LRC/BTC, MANA/BTC, UNI/BTC, VET/BTC, and XTZ/BTC. On the other hand, Binance US is halting the following BUSD Advanced Trading pairs: HBAR/BUSD and ONE/BUSD.</p>
<p>As Binance US gets rid of the selected trading pairs, it is also streamlining its Buy, Sell &amp; Convert offering. The updated maximum order for Buy, Sell &amp; Covert is $10,000. Also, Binance is pausing its OTC Trading Portal services in the US. The exchange said that it would notify users if and when the portal opens in the coming weeks and months.</p>
<p>The decision on advanced trading pairs for Binance US came shortly after the SEC slammed the exchange with a lawsuit. On June 5, the Commission <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-sues-binance-securities-rules/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">filed a suit</a> against Binance, its US platform, and CEO Changpeng Zhao over unregistered securities operations. According to the lawsuit in the District Court for the District of Columbia, Binance failed to register as a securities exchange and operated illegally in the US. There were 13 charges against Binance, including its staking program, sales of the BNB and BUSD tokens, and the Simple Earn and BNB Vault products. The US regulator added that Binance and other defendants put investors at risk while enriching their own pockets. Furthermore, the SEC claimed that Binance and its US legal entity BAM Trading did not register Binance US as an exchange broker and clearing agency. The SEC <a href="https://www.sec.gov/files/litigation/complaints/2023/comp-pr2023-101.pdf&amp;ved=2ahUKEwjSiYj0jLP_AhXxiIsKHdeaBMYQFnoECB8QAQ&amp;usg=AOvVaw1AtYRWfeqyVs6rZXkRtmVY" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">wrote</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Defendants have engaged in multiple unregistered offers and sales of crypto asset securities and other investment schemes. Defendants BAM Trading and BAM Management defrauded equity, retail and institutional investors about purported surveillance and controls over manipulative trading on the Binance.US Platform, which were in fact virtually non-existent.”</p></blockquote>
<p>About 24 hours after the attack on Binance, the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-sec-coinbase-unregistered-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC also went after Coinbase</a>, citing similar allegations.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/kim-kardashian-emax-case-proceeds/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-us-selected-trading-pairs/">Binance US Removes Selected Trading Pairs Amid SEC Allegations</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kim Kardashian EMAX Case Proceeds as California Judge Rejects Motion to Dismiss</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/kim-kardashian-emax-case-proceeds/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 15:32:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[EMAX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[kim kardashian]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=258204</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/kim-kardashian-emax-case-proceeds/">Kim Kardashian EMAX Case Proceeds as California Judge Rejects Motion to Dismiss</a></p>
<p>Judge Fitzgerald reject arguments from Kim Kardashian and Paul Pierce's lawyers to dismiss the EMAX class-action lawsuit.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/kim-kardashian-emax-case-proceeds/">Kim Kardashian EMAX Case Proceeds as California Judge Rejects Motion to Dismiss</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/kim-kardashian-emax-case-proceeds/">Kim Kardashian EMAX Case Proceeds as California Judge Rejects Motion to Dismiss</a></p>
<p>A California judge has ruled that Reality TV star and businesswoman Kim Kardashian posted false information on social media while promoting EthereumMax (EMAX). The ruling allows the plaintiffs to proceed with the case against the media personality, retired boxer Floyd Mayweather Jr., and NBA Hall of Famer Paul Pierce. Kardashian’s attorneys had <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/kim-kardashian-ethereummax-lawsuit/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">moved to dismiss</a> the suit, claiming there was no evidence investors bought EMAX tokens based on her posts on Instagram.</p>
<p>Los Angeles District Judge Michael Fitzgerald rejected attorneys’ pleas to dismiss the case because Kardashian’s posts online contained “literally false” information. Judge Fitzgerald also said one such post contained misleading information, which suggested that EMAX tokens were scarce.</p>
<p>The judge also rejected similar arguments brought by Pierce’s legal team. However, Mayweather saw some respite as the ruling declared the boxer’s EMAX promotion simply expressed his belief. The judge also said Mayweather’s statements were “quintessential nonactionable puffery”.</p>
<p>Investors had accused the retired boxer of promoting the EMAX tokens at a Bitcoin conference in 2021. Although it was a Bitcoin event, Mayweather and his entourage arrived at the venue donning EMAX t-shirts.</p>
<h2>The Kim Kardashian and Mayweather EMAX Case</h2>
<p>In January last year, investors <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/kardashian-mayweather-crypto-scam/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">sued</a> Kardashian, Pierce, and Mayweather for their involvement in EMAX promotions. According to the class-action suit, the named celebrities promoted EMAX and influenced fans and followers to buy the tokens.</p>
<p>The investors believe Kim Kardashian and other celebrities worked with EMAX to artificially spike the asset’s price. They were allegedly able to do this by deliberately posting “false or misleading statements”.</p>
<p>Between June 2021 and January 2022, EMAX crashed by about 97%. This irked investors who brought the class-action suit as they all believed it was a pump-and-dump scheme. The suit also claimed that the branding as “EthereumMax” was deliberately misleading because the project has no connection with Ethereum.</p>
<p>At the time, an EthereumMax spokesperson refuted the pump-and-dump claim. In an <a href="https://www.rollingstone.com/culture/culture-news/kim-kardashian-floyd-mayweather-ethereummax-emax-nft-scheme-1282801/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">email statement to RollingStone</a>, the spokesperson said the project is “one of the most transparent and communicative” in the crypto space. The person added that they “look forward to the truth coming out”.</p>
<h2>December’s Tentative Ruling</h2>
<p>Fitzgerald had issued a tentative ruling in favor of Kim Kardashian, Mayweather, and EMAX in December. In the ruling, Fitzgerald admitted that the case brings concerns to light about celebrities influencing “millions of undiscerning followers to buy snake oil with unprecedented ease and reach”. However, he tentatively dismissed the motion regardless. According to him, the plaintiff’s submitted facts were inadequate. Furthermore, Fitzgerald said investors must take necessary precautions before dumping funds into a project regardless of an advertiser’s misconduct. The recent rejection of the motion to dismiss the case is a turnaround from the tentative ruling.</p>
<p>In 2021, the UK’s Financial Conduct Authority (FCA) had <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/kim-kardashian-crypto-ad-uk-watchdog/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">criticized</a> Kardashian’s post. She was also fined by the US Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) for failing to reveal the post was a paid advert. Kim Kardashian allegedly settled the case by paying a $1.26 million fine.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/robinhood-tokens-securities-sec/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/kim-kardashian-emax-case-proceeds/">Kim Kardashian EMAX Case Proceeds as California Judge Rejects Motion to Dismiss</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Robinhood Scrutinizing Tokens Designated as Securities by SEC</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/robinhood-tokens-securities-sec/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 15:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ada]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[matic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[polygon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[robinhood]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sol]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[solana]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=258202</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/robinhood-tokens-securities-sec/">Robinhood Scrutinizing Tokens Designated as Securities by SEC</a></p>
<p>Crypto market prices have tumbled significantly since the news began to make rounds.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/robinhood-tokens-securities-sec/">Robinhood Scrutinizing Tokens Designated as Securities by SEC</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/robinhood-tokens-securities-sec/">Robinhood Scrutinizing Tokens Designated as Securities by SEC</a></p>
<p style="text-align: left;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Altcoins like </span><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/solana/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Solana</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> (SOL), </span><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/cardano/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Cardano</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> (ADA), </span><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/matic-network/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Polygon</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> (MATIC) and many other tokens face the possibility of being </span><a href="https://beincrypto.com/robinhood-reviews-token-listings-sec-lawsuits-crypto-exchanges/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">delisted</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> from </span><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/robinhood/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Robinhood Markets Inc</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> (NASDAQ: HOOD), after the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) charged Binance and </span><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Coinbase Global inc</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> (NASDAQ: COIN) for trading unregistered securities. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">At present, Robinhood is taking another look at the digital assets offerings on its platform to &#8220;determine what, if any, actions to take”, according to Dan Gallagher, a one-time SEC Commissioner and the present Chief Legal Officer at Robinhood.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In the lawsuit which was </span><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-sues-binance-securities-rules/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">filed</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> by the SEC against Binance, the regulator categorized BNB, BUSD, SOL, ADA, MATIC, FIL, ATOM, SAND, MANA, ALGO, AXS, and COTI as securities. Coinbase was not </span><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-sec-coinbase-unregistered-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">left out</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> as the SEC also stated that SOL, ADA, MATIC, FIL, SAND, AXS, CHZ, FLOW, ICP, NEAR, VGX, DASH, and NEXO all fall under the securities class.</span></p>
<h2><b>Robinhood Tokens Scrutiny and Broad Crypto Market Reaction</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">These lawsuits were filed simultaneously against the two prominent digital asset service providers. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Unfortunately, the broad crypto industry has had to bear the brunt of these enforcement actions. Crypto market prices have </span><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-btc-crypto-sec-binance/https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-btc-crypto-sec-binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">tumbled</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> significantly since the news began to make rounds. A few hours after SEC indicted Binance, Bitcoin (BTC) price dipped by 5%, Ethereum (ETH) suffered a similar fate, and other altcoins like SOL, ADA, MATIC, and even Dogecoin (DOGE) also fell in terms of price.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Dune Analytics data showed that Binance experienced huge outflows of up to $635 million after the lawsuit. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Coinbase shares value </span><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-shares-tumble-sec-binance-lawsuit/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">fell</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> by 10.3% and by the end of the trading day, it was down by 9%. Considering the huge effect on the crypto market, Edward Moya, a senior market analyst at foreign exchange Oanda mentioned that it was a reflection of investors&#8217; concerns over the U.S. regulatory crackdown on cryptocurrency. Investors have fears that in the long run, many digital assets would be categorized as securities.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Meanwhile, many crypto heavyweights have pledged support for the crypto exchanges against the SEC. Cardano boss Charles Hoskinson urged top crypto industry players to unite to combat the authoritarianism of the SEC and other regulatory agencies. This is not a far cry from what Coinbase was trying to achieve when it filed a lawsuit against SEC requesting that the regulator </span><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-regulatory-united-states-sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">provide</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> clarity in its regulation framework for crypto.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“The SEC is talking out of both sides of its mouth, and it is wrong at each end. The Chair’s statements cannot provide fair notice of the obligations of regulated parties &#8211; that is the function of rulemaking, which Coinbase’s petition requests. But the SEC’s Chair undoubtedly can and does speak authoritatively for the agency he leads in describing its regulatory agenda,” Coinbase stated at the time.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Looking on the bright side, within the last 48 hours, the top three largest Decentralized Exchanges (DEXs): Uniswap v3 (Ethereum), Uniswap v3 (Arbitrum), and PancakeSwap v3 (BSC) have </span><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-crypto-crackdown-defi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">recorded</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> a 444% jump in median trading volume, according to crypto data aggregator CoinGecko.</span></p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-korea-binance-gopax-sec/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/robinhood-tokens-securities-sec/">Robinhood Scrutinizing Tokens Designated as Securities by SEC</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>South Korea Regulator Delays Binance Acquisition of Gopax Due to SEC Lawsuit </title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-korea-binance-gopax-sec/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 13:51:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Deals News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cftc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gopax]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=258191</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-korea-binance-gopax-sec/">South Korea Regulator Delays Binance Acquisition of Gopax Due to SEC Lawsuit </a></p>
<p>While Binance saw the acquisition of Gopax as a means of re-entering South Korea, it was also meant to be a turning point for the local trading platform.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-korea-binance-gopax-sec/">South Korea Regulator Delays Binance Acquisition of Gopax Due to SEC Lawsuit </a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-korea-binance-gopax-sec/">South Korea Regulator Delays Binance Acquisition of Gopax Due to SEC Lawsuit </a></p>
<p>The SEC’s lawsuit against <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a> has started affecting the company’s operations, particularly its acquisition of Gopax in South Korea. The US Securities and Exchange Commission <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-sues-binance-securities-rules/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">filed</a> a case against Binance for violating securities law. According to the filing with the federal court in Washington, Binance mishandled investors and also misled both investors and regulators. The Commission also alleged that the exchange broke the rules by letting Americans trade in an unsecured and unprotected environment.</p>
<p>The Director of the SEC’s Division of Enforcement, Gurbir S. Grewal, wrote in the filing that Zhao and the Binance entities “consciously chose” to flout the rules. He added that the company put its customers and investors at risk to maximize its profits. The SEC executive said Binance engaged in multiple unregistered offerings. Grewal continued, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>“While at the same time combining the functions of exchanges, brokers, dealers, and clearing agencies, the Binance platforms under Zhao’s control imposed outsized risks and conflicts of interest on investors.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>Binance Faces Challenge with Gopax Acquisition</h2>
<p>Now, the legal case has become a hindrance to the business opportunity Binance has with Gopax. A South Korean <a href="https://m.newspim.com/news/view/20230607000608">report</a> revealed that the Financial Service Committee (FSC), is reviewing the Gopax acquisition by Binance. In light of the SEC allegations, the nation&#8217;s financial watchdog has decided to monitor the case as it progresses. Notably, Binance bought a majority stake in Gopax in February. However, the regulator has postponed the report and acceptance of the business change notification filed by Gopax concerning the Binance deal. The local crypto trading platform filed an executive change report on the 7th of March.</p>
<p>Apart from the US SEC accusations, Binance is also under the radar of the US Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC). The <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/cftc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CFTC</a> sued the exchange in March for violating trading and derivative trading regulations and evading registration obligations. In addition, the company has a case with the US Prosecutors’ Office and the US Internal Revenue Service for breaching anti-money laundering laws.</p>
<p>The FSC finds it difficult to accept the report due to the alleged accusations from the SEC and further requests to seize all assets belonging to the US arm of Binance. Noting that the SEC trend cannot be dismissed, an FSC official said that “it is cautious to say that the report is being reviewed internally”.</p>
<p>While Binance saw the acquisition of Gopax as a means of re-entering South Korea, it was also meant to be a turning point for the local trading platform. Following the collapse of the FTX crypto exchange in November 2022, Gopax halted withdrawals of principal and interest payments from its <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-decentralized-finance-defi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">DeFi</a> service GoFi. Thus, the Binance deal was supposed to reawaken the troubled exchange.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sweat-economy-governance-vote/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-korea-binance-gopax-sec/">South Korea Regulator Delays Binance Acquisition of Gopax Due to SEC Lawsuit </a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=3967 metric#misses=41 metric#hit-ratio=99.0 metric#bytes=985262 metric#prefetches=184 metric#store-reads=19 metric#store-writes=2 metric#store-hits=190 metric#store-misses=2 metric#sql-queries=34 metric#ms-total=103.24 metric#ms-cache=5.13 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.2564 metric#ms-cache-ratio=5.0 -->