<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 15:03:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Eli Lilly Raises Full Year Outlook amid Q2 2023 Profit Surge of 85%</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/eli-lilly-q2-2023-profit/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/eli-lilly-q2-2023-profit/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 15:03:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wall Street]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eli lilly]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eli lilly stock]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266179</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/eli-lilly-q2-2023-profit/">Eli Lilly Raises Full Year Outlook amid Q2 2023 Profit Surge of 85%</a></p>
<p>Eli Lilly’s success can be ascribed in part to its promising medical pipeline and strategic acquisitions.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/eli-lilly-q2-2023-profit/">Eli Lilly Raises Full Year Outlook amid Q2 2023 Profit Surge of 85%</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/eli-lilly-q2-2023-profit/">Eli Lilly Raises Full Year Outlook amid Q2 2023 Profit Surge of 85%</a></p>
<p>American pharmaceutical company <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/eli-lilly-and-company/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Eli Lilly and Co</a> (NYSE: LLY) has reported an impressive surge in profits during the second quarter of 2023, leading to a significant increase in its full-year outlook.</p>
<p>The company’s quarterly financial report, <a href="https://investor.lilly.com/news-releases/news-release-details/lilly-reports-second-quarter-2023-financial-results-highlights" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">released</a> earlier today, reveals an 85% jump in net income, surpassing expectations and demonstrating the company’s resilience and growth in the face of global challenges.</p>
<h2>Eli Lilly’s Q2 Profit and Performance</h2>
<p>During Q2 2023, the company reported adjusted earnings of $2.11 per share, beating analysts&#8217; expectations of $1.98 per share. Also, its revenue for the quarter reached an impressive $8.31 billion, outperforming the estimated $7.58 billion.</p>
<p>Additionally, Eli Lilly booked a net income of $1.76 billion, or $1.95 per share. This notable increase in net income is a substantial improvement from the same period the previous year when the company reported net income of $952.5 million, or $1.05 per share.</p>
<p>To provide a clearer picture of its core operational performance, Eli Lilly reported adjusted income, accounting for charges associated with some intangible assets and losses on securities. The company recorded an adjusted income of $1.9 billion, or $2.11 per share.</p>
<p>This adjusted figure indicates Eli Lilly’s underlying financial strength after adjusting for any one-time or non-operational factors that may have influenced the results.</p>
<p>One of the key drivers behind Eli Lilly’s strong financial performance during Q2 2023 was its outstanding sales figures. The company reported $8.31 billion in sales for the quarter, representing a remarkable 28% increase from the same period the previous year.</p>
<p>Sales of Verzenio, a breast cancer pill, recorded a remarkable 57% increase, reaching $926.8 million in the second quarter. Similarly, Jardiance, a tablet used to lower blood sugar in Type 2 diabetes patients, recorded a substantial 45% sales increase, reaching $668.3 million during the quarter.</p>
<p>Eli Lilly’s newer drug, Mounjaro, an injection for Type 2 diabetes, posted impressive sales of $979.7 million in the quarter. The drug’s approval in the US in May 2022 and subsequent demand surge have fueled its rapid revenue growth. However, intermittent delays in fulfilling orders due to overwhelming demand have been reported.</p>
<h2>Promising Developments</h2>
<p>Eli Lilly’s success can be ascribed in part to its promising medical pipeline and strategic acquisitions. The company’s investment in research and development has yielded positive results, as evidenced by the favorable trial outcomes of donanemab, a drug targeted at Alzheimer&#8217;s disease.</p>
<p>Furthermore, Eli Lilly’s progress in its obesity drug pipeline has also garnered attention from investors and the industry alike. As obesity continues to be a major global health concern, the development of effective drugs to combat this condition presents a substantial market opportunity for the company.</p>
<p>One significant move that has bolstered Eli Lilly&#8217;s position is its recent <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/eli-lilly-2-4b-dice-therapeutics/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">acquisition</a> of biopharma company Dice Therapeutics. Eli Lilly expects that the $2.4 billion deal will help the business develop more medications to treat immunological illnesses.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-xrp-price-rally-1-clarity/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/eli-lilly-q2-2023-profit/">Eli Lilly Raises Full Year Outlook amid Q2 2023 Profit Surge of 85%</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/eli-lilly-q2-2023-profit/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple-backed XRP Price Struggles to Rally towards $1 despite Regulatory Clarity</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-xrp-price-rally-1-clarity/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-xrp-price-rally-1-clarity/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 14:53:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gary gensler]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpprice]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266170</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-xrp-price-rally-1-clarity/">Ripple-backed XRP Price Struggles to Rally towards $1 despite Regulatory Clarity</a></p>
<p>The XRP market is heavily bolstered by the adoption of Ripple payment products including On-Demand Liquidity (ODL) and RipppeNet.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-xrp-price-rally-1-clarity/">Ripple-backed XRP Price Struggles to Rally towards $1 despite Regulatory Clarity</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-xrp-price-rally-1-clarity/">Ripple-backed XRP Price Struggles to Rally towards $1 despite Regulatory Clarity</a></p>
<p>On July 13, the United States judicial system through a ruling by District Judge Analisa Torres declared <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/xrp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">XRP</a> exchanges’ sales as non-security. However, the ruling also tied the XRP institutional sales to investment contracts, thus security under the Howey test. Nonetheless, almost all centralized exchanges led by <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase Global Inc</a> (NASDAQ: COIN) re-listed the digital assets for trading. As a result, XRP’s daily traded volume experienced a sharp uptick in the subsequent days towards $14 billion. Additionally, Ripple-backed XRP price doubled following the ruling from trading around 46 cents to as much as 95 cents.</p>
<p>The recent XRP correction has since eaten away significant gains made after the Ripple case ruling. According to the latest market data, XRP price exchanged around 62 cents, down more than 25 percent from this year’s high. Additionally, XRP’s average daily traded volume was about $1.2 billion, a huge drop from the recent highs of about $14 billion.</p>
<p>According to John E Deaton, founder of Crypto-law.us, the ultimate <a href="https://decrypt.co/151712/xrp-price-falls-week-bullish-sec-hype-fades" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">trigger</a> for a parabolic rally of XRP or any other altcoin lies with Bitcoin. Historically, every major crypto bull rally has been triggered by the Bitcoin halving, which is less than a year away.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="474" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">If I had told you <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/XRP?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#XRP</a> would get regulatory clarity but not hit $1, many wouldn’t have believed it. Likewise, if I had told you PayPal would issue a stable coin on Ethereum but <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/ETH?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#ETH</a> wouldn’t increase at all, many wouldn’t have believed it. Like it or not, <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Bitcoin</a> drives this…</p>
<p>&mdash; John E Deaton (@JohnEDeaton1) <a href="https://twitter.com/JohnEDeaton1/status/1688873607605170176?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 8, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2>Ripple-backed XRP Price and Market Analysis</h2>
<p>The XRP price is heavily bolstered by the adoption of Ripple payment products including On-Demand Liquidity (ODL) and RipppeNet. Additionally, the mainstream adoption of XRPL has helped widen the utility of XRP including NFT minting and DeFi operations. As a result, most experts believe XRP price is on the pathway to trading above $1 in the near term perspective.</p>
<p>However, the ongoing XRP price correction could push the digital asset towards a notable support zone between 53 and 58 cents, which acted as significant resistance levels before last month’s ruling.</p>
<p>The mainstream adoption of digital assets is expected to significantly accelerate the use of XRP in cross-border payments. As the fifth largest digital asset with a market capitalization of about $32 billion and deep trading liquidity in different pairs, XRP is well poised for further growth, more so fueled by institutional adoption.</p>
<p>Worth noting that Ripple is already working with several global central banks in developing interoperable <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-central-bank-digital-currency-cbdc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CBDCs</a>.</p>
<p>Additionally, the XRPL has a private chain that helps in the seamless issuance and burning of stablecoins by institutional investors.</p>
<h2>Bigger Picture</h2>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ripple-labs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ripple</a> is yet to fully settle the case with the SEC despite the recent ruling. Notably, the SEC through Chair Gary Gensler has severally stated that the agency does not agree with Judge Torres ruling and thus is preparing to appeal in the next circuit. As a result, the XRP price could continue to lose upward momentum until the case is completely settled.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/moodys-ratings-us-banks/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-xrp-price-rally-1-clarity/">Ripple-backed XRP Price Struggles to Rally towards $1 despite Regulatory Clarity</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-xrp-price-rally-1-clarity/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Moody’s Reduces Ratings of Several US Banks and Puts More Under Review for Potential Downgrades</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/moodys-ratings-us-banks/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/moodys-ratings-us-banks/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 14:44:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[first republic bank]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[moody's]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pacwest bancorp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[wells fargo]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[western alliance bankcorp]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266147</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/moodys-ratings-us-banks/">Moody’s Reduces Ratings of Several US Banks and Puts More Under Review for Potential Downgrades</a></p>
<p>Moody's is watching the banking sector and has already cut its ratings on several institutions because of ongoing economic headwinds.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/moodys-ratings-us-banks/">Moody’s Reduces Ratings of Several US Banks and Puts More Under Review for Potential Downgrades</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/moodys-ratings-us-banks/">Moody’s Reduces Ratings of Several US Banks and Puts More Under Review for Potential Downgrades</a></p>
<p>Bond credit rating platform Moody’s Investors Service has reduced its ratings of several banks in the US. In addition to the cut in these ratings, Moody’s also put several banks under review for possible rating cuts.</p>
<p>The announced reduction affected multiple small and mid-size banks, including Pinnacle Financial, BOK Financial, Webster Financial, and M&amp;T Bank. Others affected are Citizens Financial, Fifth Third Bancorp, and Capital One.</p>
<p>Explaining the decision, Moody’s analysts Ana Arsov and Jill Cetina <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/08/08/moodys-cuts-ratings-of-10-us-banks-and-puts-some-big-names-on-downgrade-watch.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">wrote</a> in a research note that banks are struggling with several problems, largely caused by official monetary policy:</p>
<blockquote><p>“US banks continue to contend with interest rate and asset-liability management (ALM) risks with implications for liquidity and capital, as the wind-down of unconventional monetary policy drains systemwide deposits and higher interest rates depress the value of fixed-rate assets.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Moody’s also put a few major lenders under review for a possible downgrade but has yet to cut their ratings. The potential downgrades include State Street, Bank of New York Mellon, Northern Trust, US Bancorp, Cullen/Frost Bankers, and Truist Financial.</p>
<p>As part of its explanation, Moody’s adds that many banks are facing “profitability pressures” that will affect how much internal capital they can generate.</p>
<h2>Moody’s Forecast for 2024 amid Rating Cut</h2>
<p>Moody’s expects a mild recession in early 2024. The note also states that banks might face risks in their commercial real estate (CRE) portfolios. In addition, analysts have warned about the public loss of confidence in regional banks. This follows the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nydfs-signature-bank-svb-fails/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">collapse of Signature Bank</a> and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/silvergate-shut-down-liquidate-operations/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Silicon Valley Bank</a> earlier this year. While US authorities like the New York Department of Financial Services (NYDFS) stepped in to allay fears, the sector may still suffer distrust. According to Moody’s, banks with heavy unrealized losses face the highest risks for loss of consumer confidence.</p>
<p>In addition to these problems, Moody’s expects banks to face heightened ALM risks because of the Federal Reserve’s continuous increases in interest rates. Like many analysts, Moody’s believes the Fed will keep interest rates high until inflation is reasonably controlled. Unfortunately, this will negatively affect fixed-rate assets. Other causative factors as described by Moody’s include lower deposits and reduced reserves.</p>
<p>Last month, the Federal Reserve increased interest rates by <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fed-25-basis-point-hike-rates/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">25 basis points to 5.25 &#8211; 5.5%</a>, with a midpoint height not seen since 2001. The 22-year high will likely put pressure on banks, assets, and consumers. Regardless, Fed Chairman Jerome Powell has hinted that another increase is possible in September. According to Powell, economic data at the time of the meeting would inform the apex bank’s decision on whether or not another hike is necessary.</p>
<h2>Bullish on Bank Stocks</h2>
<p>Despite the banking problem in Q1, not everyone is bearish. Investor and hedge fund manager Michael Burry has <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/investor-burry-regional-banks/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">made big purchases in regional banks</a>. In a now-deleted tweet, the ‘Big Short’ investor said he believes the crisis would quickly resolve.</p>
<p>According to securities filings in May, Burry’s Scion Asset Management bought 150,000 First Republic Bank shares and 850,000 shares in New York Community Bancorp (NYSE: NYCB). Scion also bought 250,000 shares in PacWest Bancorp (NASDAQ: PACW), and 125,000 Western Alliance Bancorp (NYSE: WAL) shares. Reportedly, Scion spent $23.4 million on these purchases. There is also a reported $4.6 million purchase of Wells Fargo (NYSE: WFC).</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/brazil-name-cbdc-drex/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/moodys-ratings-us-banks/">Moody’s Reduces Ratings of Several US Banks and Puts More Under Review for Potential Downgrades</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/moodys-ratings-us-banks/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Brazil Gives Name and Logo to Its Central Bank Digital Currency (CBDC) – DREX</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/brazil-name-cbdc-drex/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/brazil-name-cbdc-drex/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 14:14:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[drex]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266158</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/brazil-name-cbdc-drex/">Brazil Gives Name and Logo to Its Central Bank Digital Currency (CBDC) &#8211; DREX</a></p>
<p>The DREX CBDC will utilize distributed ledger technology (DLT) for settling wholesale interbank transactions, and retail access will rely on tokenized bank deposits.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/brazil-name-cbdc-drex/">Brazil Gives Name and Logo to Its Central Bank Digital Currency (CBDC) &#8211; DREX</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/brazil-name-cbdc-drex/">Brazil Gives Name and Logo to Its Central Bank Digital Currency (CBDC) &#8211; DREX</a></p>
<p>The Central bank of Brazil continues to push further with its progress o the central bank digital currency (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-central-bank-digital-currency-cbdc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CBDC</a>). Previously popular as Digital Real, the CBDC gets a new official brand name aka the DREX.</p>
<p>On Monday, August 7, Brazil&#8217;s central bank unveiled the new brand and logo for its CBDC through a press release. As per the central bank, the brand &#8220;DREX&#8221; is an acronym. The press release notes:</p>
<blockquote><p>“‘D’ and ‘r’ allude to Real Digital; the ‘e’ stands for electronic and the ‘x’ conveys the idea of ​​modernity and connection, the use of distributed ledger technology (DLT).”</p></blockquote>
<p>In addition to unveiling the brand name, the central bank also introduced Drex&#8217;s visual identity. The CBDC logo features two arrows within the capital letter &#8220;D,&#8221; symbolizing the progression from the national fiat currency, the real, to its digital counterpart. The color shift from blue to light green represents the completion of transactions.</p>
<p>The Drex CBDC by Brazil is all set to hit the market next year in 2024. Central bank officials had previously forecasted that the Brazilian digital currency&#8217;s adoption would begin by the close of 2024, once the testing phase had been concluded.</p>
<p>However, Fabio Araujo, who leads the initiative at the bank, mentioned that employee strikes seeking improved career opportunities might potentially influence the project.</p>
<h2>The DREX CBDC to Bolster Lending and Investments</h2>
<p>The DREX CBDC will utilize distributed ledger technology (DLT) for settling wholesale interbank transactions, and retail access will rely on tokenized bank deposits.</p>
<p>In a live discussion hosted by the central bank, Araujo emphasized that the main focus of developing DREX is to enhance access to financial services within the country. &#8220;By enabling simple and reliable access to registered values through DLT technology, we reduce costs and democratize access to financial services,&#8221; Araujo stated.</p>
<p>He also pointed out that Brazilians are already actively participating in extensive digital payments using the instant payment platform Pix, which was introduced in late 2021 and has been widely adopted. The anticipation now is that DREX will strengthen lending, investment, and insurance services.</p>
<p>&#8220;We aim to make these financial products accessible to the public and increase financial inclusion in Brazil,&#8221; Araujo <a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/brazil-central-bank-names-its-digital-currency-drex-scheduled-2024-launch-2023-08-07/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">added</a>.</p>
<p>Last month, some developers <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/developer-loopholes-brazil-cbdc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">pointed out</a> the loopholes in the code for the DREX. Thus, the central bank might have to conduct some more tests before introducing DREX into the market.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-usdc-btc-eth-silvergate/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/brazil-name-cbdc-drex/">Brazil Gives Name and Logo to Its Central Bank Digital Currency (CBDC) &#8211; DREX</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/brazil-name-cbdc-drex/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Traded USDC In for BTC and ETH Following Silvergate Collapse</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-usdc-btc-eth-silvergate/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-usdc-btc-eth-silvergate/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mercy Tukiya Mutanya]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 13:51:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Binance News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brian armstrong]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[usd coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[usdc]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266160</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-usdc-btc-eth-silvergate/">Binance Traded USDC In for BTC and ETH Following Silvergate Collapse</a></p>
<p>The exchange’s USDC balance was reduced from $3.4 billion on March 1 to $23.9 million by May 1.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-usdc-btc-eth-silvergate/">Binance Traded USDC In for BTC and ETH Following Silvergate Collapse</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-usdc-btc-eth-silvergate/">Binance Traded USDC In for BTC and ETH Following Silvergate Collapse</a></p>
<p>Cryptocurrency exchange <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a> provided a closer look into its reserves with the August 1 release of its proof-of-reserves (PoR). The move of Binance to dump its USD Coin (USDC) reserves after the collapse of Sivergate Bank has become a major topic of discussion in crypto circles online, particularly on social media platform X.</p>
<p>Overall, the <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/proof-of-reserves" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">PoR report</a> paints a picture of good financial health for the exchange. It shows that Binance has enough crypto and cash reserves to cover user funds. The report includes a snapshot of the ratios of Binance’s net balances to its customers’ net balances for cryptocurrencies Bitcoin, Ethereum, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/binance-coin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BNB</a>, USDT, BUSD, USDC, Litecoin and XRP. The ratio of the exchange’s net balances to user net balances on all crypto assets shown is more than 100%.</p>
<p>A main point of discussion online is the movements of Binance’s USDC reserves following the collapse of crypto-friendly Silvegate Bank in March. The exchange’s USDC balance was reduced from $3.4 billion on March 1 to $23.9 million by May 1. Onchain data suggests that Binance started converting its USDC into Ether following Silvergate’s collapse. Onchain analyst Aleksandar Djakovic pointed out that between March 12 and May 1, Binance bought about 100,000 BTC and 550,000 ETH averaging about $3.5 billion, close to the amount of USDC the exchanged had in surplus on March 1.</p>
<p>The discourse surrounding Binance&#8217;s handling of its USDC holdings was furthered when Coinbase CEO <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/brian-armstrong/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Brian Armstrong</a> stated in jest during the company’s Q2 earnings call that Binance had moved a chunk of their funds from USDC to another stablecoin.</p>
<p>“Binance actually moved some of their funds from USDC into another stablecoin. I think the data we have in the last six or seven weeks, I believe, that the USDC market cap is up net of that. And so that’s an important data point,” said he.</p>
<p>PoR has been an industry standard following the seemingly abrupt collapse of the crypto exchange FTX in November last year. Major exchanges began to share reserve audits with the public in an attempt to quell investors’ worries.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/singapore-blockchain-com-license/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-usdc-btc-eth-silvergate/">Binance Traded USDC In for BTC and ETH Following Silvergate Collapse</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-usdc-btc-eth-silvergate/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Singapore Grants Blockchain.com Major Payment Institution License</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/singapore-blockchain-com-license/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/singapore-blockchain-com-license/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Temitope Olatunji]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 11:53:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain.com]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mas]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266123</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/singapore-blockchain-com-license/">Singapore Grants Blockchain.com Major Payment Institution License</a></p>
<p>The new MPI license makes it possible for Blockchain.com to offer regulated digital payment token services to institutions and accredited investors.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/singapore-blockchain-com-license/">Singapore Grants Blockchain.com Major Payment Institution License</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/singapore-blockchain-com-license/">Singapore Grants Blockchain.com Major Payment Institution License</a></p>
<p>On August 1, the Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS), the Singapore Central Bank, granted Blockchain.com a major payment institution (MPI) license. The crypto exchange is now able to provide accredited customers with digital payment token (DPT) services, thanks to this authorization.</p>
<p>The Monetary Authority of Singapore, the country&#8217;s financial regulator, defines a digital payment token as a digital representation of value that lacks physical form and is securely maintained by a blockchain. With this approval, Blockchain.com becomes the twelfth digital payment token (DPT) service provider in Singapore, alongside companies like <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-com-license-singapore/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Crypto.com</a>, Circle, Paxos, Independent Reserve, and Revolut.</p>
<p>The new MPI license grants the exchange approval to offer regulated digital payment token services to institutions and accredited investors in Singapore. This is coming after the company received in-principle approval from MAS last year.</p>
<p>Peter Smith, the CEO and Co-Founder of Blockchain.com, expressed his excitement about the approval, <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/blockchaincom-receives-major-payment-institution-license-from-monetary-authority-of-singapore-301895088.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">stating</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We are thrilled to receive this license that will allow Blockchain.com to bring our industry-leading products and services to Singapore, we commend the Monetary Authority of Singapore on its transparent regulatory process that prioritizes crypto industry oversight while allowing innovation to thrive.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Blockchain.com, which has issued over 99 million wallets and boasts more than 40 million users, is firmly committed to continuous growth and the expansion of its services. The company is presently registered and holds licenses in various regions, demonstrating its dedication to adhering to regulatory standards in diverse markets. Obtaining the Singapore payment provider license stands as a pivotal step toward realizing the company&#8217;s overarching goal.</p>
<h2>Singapore Seeks to Become the Hub of Web3 Innovation and Development</h2>
<p>Additionally, Ripple has received in-principle approval from the Monetary Authority of Singapore for an MPI license. Notably, after receiving in-principle approval, it took Circle seven months to obtain its MPI license. These developments show Singapore&#8217;s efforts to position itself as a center for cryptocurrency innovation and services.</p>
<p>The nation has shown its dedication to cryptocurrencies and web3 technologies in a number of ways, including by announcing plans to invest S$150 million in FinTech solutions over the next three years as part of its updated Financial Sector Technology and Innovation (FSTI) Scheme.</p>
<p>In order to develop innovative <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-fintech/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FinTech</a> solutions utilizing Web3 technologies, Singapore is also extending support to Web3 projects by offering funding and collaboration opportunities. The bank intends to work with significant industry players to achieve this.</p>
<p>In addition to promoting crypto solutions and services, Singapore introduced <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/singapore-financial-authority-crypto-trust/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">new regulations</a> in July to protect cryptocurrency users. These regulations include plans to prevent cryptocurrency providers from taking part in staking and lending activities for retail users, and they mandate that cryptocurrency services hold customer funds in statutory trust by year&#8217;s end.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-gptbot-web-crawling/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/singapore-blockchain-com-license/">Singapore Grants Blockchain.com Major Payment Institution License</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/singapore-blockchain-com-license/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>OpenAI Rolls Out GPTBot for Enhanced Web Crawling</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-gptbot-web-crawling/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-gptbot-web-crawling/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 11:14:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chatgpt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[openai]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266116</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-gptbot-web-crawling/">OpenAI Rolls Out GPTBot for Enhanced Web Crawling</a></p>
<p>The launch of GPTBot comes a few weeks after OpenAI filed a trademark application for "GPT-5".</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-gptbot-web-crawling/">OpenAI Rolls Out GPTBot for Enhanced Web Crawling</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-gptbot-web-crawling/">OpenAI Rolls Out GPTBot for Enhanced Web Crawling</a></p>
<p>OpenAI, a US-based <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/technology/artificial-intelligence-news/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">artificial intelligence</a> (AI) company, has introduced GPTBot, a groundbreaking web crawling tool designed to enhance future AI models like <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/everything-you-need-to-know-about-chatgpt-ai-chatbot/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ChatGPT</a>. According to the company&#8217;s blog post, the new AI tool serves as a web crawler, a digital explorer navigating the internet to index website content. Unlike traditional search engines like Google and Bing, the tool aims to leverage indexed data to improve the accuracy, versatility, and depth of upcoming AI models, promising a significant leap in user interactions.</p>
<p>GPTBOT&#8217;s primary mission is to gather publicly available data from various online sources across the globe. The company said it is committed to ethical data collection practices, equipping the new web crawlers with the ability to exclude sources that demand payment, collect personal information, or violate content guidelines to ensure responsible data usage.</p>
<h2>Website Owners Can Control the Use of GPTBot</h2>
<p>The company also <a href="https://platform.openai.com/docs/gptbot">said</a> in its announcement that it had built GPTBot to respect the autonomy of website owners. OpenAI introduced a series of security measures alongside GPTBot, which allows website administrators to control GPTBot&#8217;s interactions within their sites.</p>
<p>Website operators can choose to restrict the web crawlers from accessing their content by implementing a &#8220;disallow&#8221; command within a standard file on their servers. The move allows web owners to take control of their content.</p>
<p>As mentioned earlier, OpenAI&#8217;s new web crawlers were designed with a proactive feature that scans collected data, eliminating personally identifiable information (PII) and content violating its policies. However, according to Decrypt, some technology ethicists on Hacker News argued that the opt-out approach still raises concerns about consent and privacy protection.</p>
<p>The <a href="https://decrypt.co/151662/chatgpt-web-crawler-openai-data-scraper-gptbot-gpt-5">report</a> noted that certain users defended OpenAI&#8217;s decision by asserting that comprehensive data gathering is necessary for a capable future AI tool. One user emphasized the importance of current data to prevent GPT models from becoming stagnant in September 2021.</p>
<p>&#8220;They still need current data, or their GPT models will be stuck in September 2021 forever,&#8221; the user said.</p>
<p>Another tech enthusiast focused on privacy criticized OpenAI for not adequately citing sources, thereby obscuring its derivative work.</p>
<h2>OpenAI Files Patent Application for GPT-5 Model</h2>
<p>Meanwhile, the launch of GPTBot comes a few weeks after OpenAI filed a trademark application for &#8220;GPT-5&#8221;. The application, submitted to the US Patent and Trademark Office (USPTO) on July 18, suggests a potential successor to GPT-4.</p>
<p>While filing a trademark application does not guarantee an immediate product launch, in June, the company&#8217;s CEO Sam Altman said the firm was &#8220;nowhere close to beginning training on the GPT-5 model&#8221;. He further noted that multiple safety audits must be completed before implementing the model.</p>
<p>The company recently <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-launches-chatgpt-android-app/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">rolled out</a> an Android version of ChatGPT to increase users&#8217; adoption. The app was immediately made available to users in India, the US, Bangladesh, and Brazil, with plans to expand to other regions in the future.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cathie-wood-bitcoin-etf-sec/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-gptbot-web-crawling/">OpenAI Rolls Out GPTBot for Enhanced Web Crawling</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-gptbot-web-crawling/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cathie Wood Anticipates Multiple Bitcoin ETF Approvals by SEC</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/cathie-wood-bitcoin-etf-sec/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/cathie-wood-bitcoin-etf-sec/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 10:45:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funds & ETFs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blackrock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcetf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cathie Wood]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266117</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cathie-wood-bitcoin-etf-sec/">Cathie Wood Anticipates Multiple Bitcoin ETF Approvals by SEC</a></p>
<p>The approval of spot-Bitcoin ETF remains a hot issue of debate among investors, regulators, and financial institutions.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cathie-wood-bitcoin-etf-sec/">Cathie Wood Anticipates Multiple Bitcoin ETF Approvals by SEC</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cathie-wood-bitcoin-etf-sec/">Cathie Wood Anticipates Multiple Bitcoin ETF Approvals by SEC</a></p>
<p>Cathie Wood, the CEO of ARK Invest has expressed belief that the US Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) may approve multiple spot <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> Exchange-Traded Funds (ETFs) simultaneously.</p>
<h2>Cathie Wood Shifts Perspective on Bitcoin ETF</h2>
<p>Cathie Wood shared her updated <a href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/cathie-wood-says-sec-will-approve-multiple-bitcoin-etfs-at-once-1.1956073#:~:text=Cathie%20Wood%20Says%20SEC%20Will%20Approve%20Multiple%20Bitcoin%20ETFs%20at%20Once,-Emily%20Graffeo%20and&amp;text=(Bloomberg)%20--%20Cathie%20Wood%20said,for%20the%20long-awaited%20product" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">perspective</a> on spot Bitcoin ETF approvals during an interview with Bloomberg TV on Monday, where she stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>“I think the SEC if it&#8217;s going to approve a Bitcoin ETF, will approve more than one at once.”</p></blockquote>
<p>This shift in perception indicates a reversal in the crypto community, as her firm had previously claimed to be at the forefront of the approval process due to its early application submission with the SEC.</p>
<p>In June, ARK Invest made waves when it filed for a spot-Bitcoin ETF. The firm&#8217;s enthusiasm was boosted by its timely filing with the SEC. However, the environment has changed, with Wood speculating that the regulatory body may choose to approve many applications at the same time.</p>
<p>James Seyffart, an ETF analyst at Bloomberg Intelligence, has weighed in on Wood’s recent remarks about the potential approval of multiple spot-Bitcoin ETFs by the SEC. Seyffart believes that Wood’s observations align with the sentiments shared by many in the industry, including analysts like himself.</p>
<p>He points out that the SEC may find it easier to approve several spot Bitcoin funds simultaneously, given the current circumstances surrounding the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/grayscale/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Grayscale Investments</a> LLC lawsuit against the regulator.</p>
<p>Grayscale, a major player in the crypto asset management space, is currently embroiled in a legal battle with the SEC. The company took the SEC to court after the regulator rejected its plan to convert the Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC), which holds around $18 billion worth of Bitcoin, into an ETF.</p>
<p>Should the court rule in favor of Grayscale, it might signal to the SEC that there is a viable path for converting existing Bitcoin investment products into ETFs. As a result, the “path of least resistance” for the SEC, according to Seyffart, would be to approve multiple spot-Bitcoin funds concurrently, potentially following a successful resolution of Grayscale’s lawsuit.</p>
<h2>Spot Bitcoin ETFs: Intense Competition Ahead of Regulatory Approval</h2>
<p>The approval of spot-Bitcoin ETF remains a hot issue of debate among investors, regulators, and financial institutions. While the desire for a regulated Bitcoin ETF has progressively increased, the road to approval has been difficult.</p>
<p>The SEC has been hesitant to grant its blessing for such a product, citing concerns over market manipulation, liquidity, and custody. As a result, no spot Bitcoin ETF currently exists in the US.</p>
<p>However, this has not deterred several leading financial firms, including <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/blackrock/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BlackRock Inc</a> (NYSE: BLK), Fidelity Investment, WisdomTree, VanEck, and Invesco, from submitting their applications for approval, each offering products strikingly similar to the proposal put forth by ARK Invest.</p>
<p>Cathie Wood has noted that with multiple firms competing for approval with similar underlying assets, the success of each ETF will hinge on the issuer’s marketing acumen.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/softbank-loss-vision-fund-profit/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cathie-wood-bitcoin-etf-sec/">Cathie Wood Anticipates Multiple Bitcoin ETF Approvals by SEC</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/cathie-wood-bitcoin-etf-sec/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>SoftBank Announces Surprising Loss as Vision Fund Posts First Profit in Five Quarters</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/softbank-loss-vision-fund-profit/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/softbank-loss-vision-fund-profit/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 10:42:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[softbank]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[uber]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vision fund]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266102</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/softbank-loss-vision-fund-profit/">SoftBank Announces Surprising Loss as Vision Fund Posts First Profit in Five Quarters</a></p>
<p>The SoftBank loss surprised analysts who were expecting the company to report a gain, even though the company's investment arm is up.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/softbank-loss-vision-fund-profit/">SoftBank Announces Surprising Loss as Vision Fund Posts First Profit in Five Quarters</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/softbank-loss-vision-fund-profit/">SoftBank Announces Surprising Loss as Vision Fund Posts First Profit in Five Quarters</a></p>
<p><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/softbank/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">SoftBank Group Corp</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> reported a loss for the quarter ended June, surprising much of the market, which expected better. However, the company’s Vision Fund investment arm posted a gain even as indicators suggested a further loss for the fund.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">SoftBank group posted a net loss of 477.6 billion yen, about $3.3 billion. This is a far cry from the 75 billion Refinitiv analysts expected from the company. However, the figure is a significant improvement from the 3.16 trillion yen recorded in the same quarter last year.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">On the other hand, the SoftBank Vision Fund posted a profit even though analysts expected a loss. After five consecutive losing quarters, the Vision Fund gained 159.8 billion yen, about $1.1 billion, in the quarter ended June. Interestingly, SoftBank lost $32 billion during the last quarter, with significant losses from Indonesian e-commerce and ride-hailing company GoTo, as well as Chinese AI company SenseTime.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The SoftBank Vision Fund lost a cumulative ¥6.9 trillion, about $48 billion, over the last 2 years. It has recently suspended new investments and reduced its Alibaba stake. SoftBank also no longer has any stake in <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/uber/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Uber</a>. It initially invested in Uber in 2018 and then sold nearly a third of the stake. As of Monday, SoftBank </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/08/08/softbank-sells-entire-stake-in-uber-as-vision-fund-losses-mount.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">confirmed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> it offloaded all of its Uber holdings, likely to manage its financial health as losses continuously piled up.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">SoftBank in “Offense Mode” Despite Loss</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Speaking at a June shareholder meeting, SoftBank CEO Masayoshi Son said the company will now leave “defense mode” and enter “offense mode.” He explained that SoftBank now has the cash to be on the offensive:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">“In the past few years, we focused on being [on] ‘defense.’ Three years ago, we didn’t have a lot of cash on hand. But because we have been in defense mode, we have built our cash on hand to five trillion yen ($35.3 billion). We are ready to shift to offense mode. I am excited about that.”</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">SoftBank has faced its fair share of headwinds recently as the value of its investments has not spiked as expected. Last year, a top SoftBank exec Rajeev Misra stepped down from his roles as executive vice president and corporate officer. Misra was also the CEO of SoftBank Global Advisors, which controls Vision Fund 2, one of the funds under the SoftBank Vision Fund. Misra’s decision to step down came amid mounting pressure from the fund’s performance as stocks continued to crash and investments failed to pay off.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The market is now looking to SoftBank’s upcoming initial public offering (</span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-initial-public-offering-ipo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">IPO</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">) for its chip designer subsidiary, Arm Ltd. Arm recently </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/softbank-arm-us-only-listing/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">decided to shun the UK market</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> and opt for a US-only listing after talks with the British government did not yield favorable results. Now, the chip designer is looking at a $70 billion valuation, which would be the largest IPO in 2023.</span></p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitstamp-derivatives-trading-europe/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/softbank-loss-vision-fund-profit/">SoftBank Announces Surprising Loss as Vision Fund Posts First Profit in Five Quarters</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/softbank-loss-vision-fund-profit/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitstamp to Expand Derivatives Trading in Europe amid Fundraise</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitstamp-derivatives-trading-europe/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitstamp-derivatives-trading-europe/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 10:39:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitstamp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fca]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[galaxy digital]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gemini]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266111</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitstamp-derivatives-trading-europe/">Bitstamp to Expand Derivatives Trading in Europe amid Fundraise</a></p>
<p>Bitstamp is also looking to expand its operations in the UK after securing the FCA license earlier this year. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitstamp-derivatives-trading-europe/">Bitstamp to Expand Derivatives Trading in Europe amid Fundraise</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitstamp-derivatives-trading-europe/">Bitstamp to Expand Derivatives Trading in Europe amid Fundraise</a></p>
<p>One of the oldest cryptocurrency exchanges <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/bitstamp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitstamp</a> is looking to expand its footprint and service offerings amid the current talks of raising fresh funding. Jean-Baptiste Graftieaux, global chief executive officer of the exchange appraised the recent developments. As per the company spokesperson, Bitstamp started its fundraising efforts earlier this year in June 2023. Mike Novogratz&#8217;s Galaxy Digital is acting as an adviser in the entire process. Earlier, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/galaxy-digital/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Galaxy Digital</a> served as an adviser to Pantera, which later sold its minority stake in Bitstamp to Ripple in 2023. Bitstamp said that they would be using these funds to launch crypto derivatives trading in the European continent next year.</p>
<p>Additionally, they would also use these funds to expand the number of markets that it serves in Asia. The company spokesperson said that Bitstamp is also looking to expand its operations in the U.K. In a statement to Bloomberg, Graftieaux <a href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/crypto-exchange-bitstamp-in-talks-to-raise-funds-for-expansion-ceo-says-1.1956129" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Bitstamp is not for sale, and we are not actively looking to sell the company. Our current and exclusive priority is to raise money through strategic investors to accelerate Bitstamp’s growth by providing new products and services to retail and institutional crypto customers.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Earlier this year in June, Bitstamp also <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitstamp-fca-exchanges/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">secured</a> approval from UK’s Financial Conduct Authority (FCA) to function as a registered crypto firm in the region. After obtaining the license, Bitstamp stated its dedication to increasing its presence and investments in the UK market.</p>
<h2>Bitstamp&#8217;s Growth Over the Years</h2>
<p>As said, Bitstamp is one of the oldest crypto exchanges established in 2011 and based out of Luxembourg. Back then Bitstamp was among the major competitors to now-defunct Bitcoin exchange Mt. Gox. Now, it&#8217;s the seventh-largest exchange in the world. It had around $126 million worth of trading in a recent 24-hour period.</p>
<p>Bitstamp also has a part in the US entity called Bitstamp USA. The exchange also has a special license called BitLicense, essential to operate in New York state.</p>
<p>More platforms for cryptocurrencies are getting into the derivatives market. This market used to be mostly dominated by FTX and Binance. But after the FTX collapse, Bitstamp seems to be grabbing an opportunity here. Coinbase Global Inc and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/gemini/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Gemini</a>, two other big companies in the cryptocurrency world, started their own derivatives markets outside the US this year. Bitstamp was among the first exchanges to allow <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gemini-kraken-bitstamp-resume-xrp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">XRP trading</a> after the court ruling.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/scammers-pyusd-tokens/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitstamp-derivatives-trading-europe/">Bitstamp to Expand Derivatives Trading in Europe amid Fundraise</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitstamp-derivatives-trading-europe/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4106 metric#misses=42 metric#hit-ratio=99.0 metric#bytes=1063031 metric#prefetches=199 metric#store-reads=20 metric#store-writes=2 metric#store-hits=205 metric#store-misses=3 metric#sql-queries=34 metric#ms-total=95.61 metric#ms-cache=4.76 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.2269 metric#ms-cache-ratio=5.0 -->