<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 11:35:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Top meme coin pumps on X speculation: Does this impact Shiba Memu?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/top-meme-coin-pumps-on-x-speculation-does-this-impact-shiba-memu/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/top-meme-coin-pumps-on-x-speculation-does-this-impact-shiba-memu/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 11:35:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOGE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/top-meme-coin-pumps-on-x-speculation-does-this-impact-shiba-memu/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Dogecoin price rallied to above $0.076 on Tuesday, a day after Elon Musk&#8217;s Twitter rebranded to X. Shiba Memu (SHMU) presale on the other hand has seen $1.14 million raised so far amid huge interest in meme tokens. The launch of the Shiba Memu&#8217;s AI dashboard could have a significant impact on the token&#8217;s performance. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/top-meme-coin-pumps-on-x-speculation-does-this-impact-shiba-memu/">Top meme coin pumps on X speculation: Does this impact Shiba Memu?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Dogecoin price rallied to above $0.076 on Tuesday, a day after Elon Musk&rsquo;s Twitter rebranded to X.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Shiba Memu (SHMU) presale on the other hand has seen $1.14 million raised so far amid huge interest in meme tokens.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The launch of the Shiba Memu&rsquo;s AI dashboard could have a significant impact on the token&rsquo;s performance.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu&rsquo;s presale is on fire with nearly 40 million SHMU sold and over $1.14 million raised within weeks of the revolutionary meme project&rsquo;s token sale launch.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Meanwhile, meme coins have added more than $730 million to their total market cap in the past 24 hours, with most of that down to <a href="https://coinjournal.net/dogecoin/">Dogecoin (DOGE)</a>&rsquo;s latest pump.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Elon Musk&rsquo;s X Payments could add Dogecoin</h2>
<p dir="ltr">DOGE price rose to highs of $0.078 early Tuesday after a spike in positivity since Monday, primarily injected by Twitter&rsquo;s rebranding to X. More than that, the speculation that X could incorporate DOGE in its payment feature sees Dogecoin price on the verge of what could be a mega upside leg.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Elon Musk hinted at the possibility of DOGE becoming a payment currency on the rebranded X platform when he put the meme coin&rsquo;s symbol next to the X logo in his bio on Monday. That action fuelled speculation that the cryptocurrency could soon be part of the &ldquo;everything app&rdquo; that Musk and team envision for X.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Raoul Pal, CEO of Real Vision <a href="https://twitter.com/RaoulGMI/status/1683618358380429312" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">believes</a> this is a possibility even as he sees AI playing a big role in X&rsquo;s future developments.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>Two things I&rsquo;ve said when Elon bought &ldquo;X&rdquo;: &nbsp;Elon bought it for the AI, and the free speech angle is to give it an unbiased model. He needs the AI to train the Optimus robot. He will use crypto to be able to make global payments for creators etc. My guess is he uses Doge</em>.&rdquo;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What makes Shiba Memu different from Dogecoin?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">What sets Shiba Memu apart from Dogecoin and other meme coins is that it integrates blockchain technology and artificial intelligence to create an autonomous marketing powerhouse.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">While most meme coin ecosystems, including Dogecoin, rely on market hype for traction, Shiba Memu is taking the game a notch higher by making this entirely AI-driven.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Its AI technology works via robotastic dashboard &ndash; the marketing genius behind this project and one that could catapult the project above rivals in terms of community traction and adoption. Two narratives likely to put Shiba Memu on top is the increased adoption of crypto and the emergence of AI as a strong narrative.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Visit the Shiba Memu <a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">presale page</a> to learn more.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Dogecoin price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr">While Musk could go for any other coin when he eventually integrates crypto into X Payments, much of the global speculation is that DOGE sits at the top of the list.</p>
<p dir="ltr">If this happens, we could see the price of Dogecoin could skyrocket. The same happens in 2021 when Tesla announced it would accept DOGE as payment method for car purchases. Dogecoin hit its ATH of $0.73 in May 2021, rallying from lows of $0.009 in January for a staggering 362x gain in four months.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In 2023, Dogecoin has fluctuated between $0.10 and $0.06 and currently hovers below $0.08.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Although the immediate target remains the elusive $0.1, bulls are likely to see the all-time high of $0.73 as the barrier that will need to be broken if DOGE has to hit $1. A move by Elon Musk&rsquo;s X could catalyse such a breakout.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Does Dogecoin price impact Shiba Memu?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Dogecoin is the top meme coin by market capitalization, and also the most popular one today thanks to its status as the original meme token. The native DOGE&rsquo;s rally in 2021 and on multiple occasions whenever Musk tweets about it has seen other meme coins pick up some upward momentum.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In fact, it is this scenario that has seen several dog-inspired tokens spawned, particularly in 2023. The likes of PEPE and FLOKI have as a result gained massive traction and are competing to take a chunk of the DOGE market.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu is no different and its trajectory could follow the popular meme tokens&rsquo; recent spectacular price gains.</p>
<p dir="ltr">SHMU will be priced at $0.0244 at the end of its 8-week presale. Per the roadmap, the AI dashboard will go live in Q1, 2024 and SHMU will list on exchanges in Q3 that year.</p>
<p dir="ltr">While Shiba Memu price might not mirror DOGE&rsquo;s 2021 explosion, the meme project&rsquo;s unique model has the potential to fuel a enourmous price rally.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Do you want to join the presale? <a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Click here</a>.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/top-meme-coin-pumps-on-x-speculation-does-this-impact-shiba-memu/">Top meme coin pumps on X speculation: Does this impact Shiba Memu?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/top-meme-coin-pumps-on-x-speculation-does-this-impact-shiba-memu/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gnosis price outlook after the 7 days plunge: is Chancer a better option?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/gnosis-price-outlook-after-the-7-days-plunge-is-chancer-a-better-option/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/gnosis-price-outlook-after-the-7-days-plunge-is-chancer-a-better-option/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 10:47:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/gnosis-price-outlook-after-the-7-days-plunge-is-chancer-a-better-option/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Gnosis (GNO) token has lost 22.5% in the past year. While some predict that GNO has hit the bottom, it has dropped by 2.5% in the past seven days. As Gnosis drops, a new decentralized prediction market token called CHANCER is gaining traction. The decentralized prediction markets have been an industry that has seen [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/gnosis-price-outlook-after-the-7-days-plunge-is-chancer-a-better-option/">Gnosis price outlook after the 7 days plunge: is Chancer a better option?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul class="decimal_type">
<li>The Gnosis (GNO) token has lost 22.5% in the past year.</li>
<li>While some predict that GNO has hit the bottom, it has dropped by 2.5% in the past seven days.</li>
<li>As Gnosis drops, a new decentralized prediction market token called CHANCER is gaining traction.</li>
</ul>
<p>The decentralized prediction markets have been an industry that has seen some tremendous growth in the recent following the increasing decentralized betting platforms. Gnosis was among the first decentralized prediction market to be developed on <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/what-is-ethereum/">Ethereum blockchain</a> and it cleared the way for many more such platforms.</p>
<p>Despite the Gnosis platform being famous, its native token has witnessed a long bear market that has lasted for about a year now. On the contrary, the tokens of other decentralized market platforms like <a href="https://coinjournal.net/augur/what-is-augur/">Augur (REP)</a> and Stox (STX) have enjoyed rapid price surges in the past week.</p>
<h2>Gnosis (GNO) price prediction</h2>
<p>Gnosis (GNO) technical analysis shows that its continuous bearish trend has been accompanied by significant price volatility. However, it currently has a sideways trend signalling a possible short-term price rise in the near future.</p>
<p>The <a href="https://coinjournal.net/gnosis/">GNO price</a> has continuously traded within the range of $95 to $124 in the last three months.</p>
<div class="fr-img-space-wrap"><span class="fr-img-caption fr-fic fr-dib fr-draggable" style="width: 615px"><span class="fr-img-wrap">
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/25/1690281709035-6f8003ff-dbb5-4b2d-a6f7-488da729dedf.jpg" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="615" height="295"><span class="fr-inner" style="background: transparent;position: relative"><em>Gnosis price chart. Source: </em><a href="https://www.geckoterminal.com/eth/pools/0xf56d08221b5942c428acc5de8f78489a97fc5599?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=coingecko&amp;utm_campaign=livechart-btn"><em>Coingecko terminal</em></a></span></p>
<p></p></span></span>
<p class="fr-img-space-wrap2">It recently bounced back downwards after hitting the resistance at $124.19 and it is fast approaching the pivot point level at $113.11. If it goes below the pivot point, it could drop towards the next support level at $107 or further down to $96.</p>
</div>
<h2>Does Chancer offer a better investment opportunity?</h2>
<p>Chancer is a cutting-edge Web3 peer-to-peer (P2P) custom betting platform that features live streaming. It emphasizes transparency among the many betting platforms available worldwide.</p>
<p>The goal of the Chancer platform is to give users the ability to create and customize P2P betting markets in real time based on their interests, knowledge, and social media connections.</p>
<p>Through a decentralized platform, Chancer enables users to create their own unique P2P betting markets without being restricted by what bookmakers offer and their odds.</p>
<p>Chancer is an intriguing project because it allows for wagering on events other than sports or popular ones. Users of Chancer can wager on virtually anything in addition to sporting events like football games, such as the day that a person will set foot on Mars, as well as make private bets with their friends to see if they can complete a task with predetermined requirements.</p>
<p>The CHANCER token will power the ecosystem and the success of the Chancer platform and the markets it supports may depend heavily on token holders. Holders can create markets with the tokens, which also gives them the chance to invest in markets established by other users. If interested, you can purchase the CHANCER token <a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news">here</a>.</p>
<p>Investors are flocking to the new Chancer decentralized prediction markets project, as Gnosis (GNO) token, which has long been a leader among the decentralized prediction markets tokens, struggles with a long bear market.</p>
<p>Just like Gnosis, Chancer offers a decentralized prediction market allowing users to create markets where they can speculate on any event or arbitrary outcome.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/gnosis-price-outlook-after-the-7-days-plunge-is-chancer-a-better-option/">Gnosis price outlook after the 7 days plunge: is Chancer a better option?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/gnosis-price-outlook-after-the-7-days-plunge-is-chancer-a-better-option/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dogecoin up 4% as X payments speculations return</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/dogecoin-up-4-as-x-payments-speculations-return/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/dogecoin-up-4-as-x-payments-speculations-return/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 09:55:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/dogecoin-up-4-as-x-payments-speculations-return/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways DOGE is outperforming the other major cryptocurrencies, up by 4% in the last 24 hours. The positive performance comes as speculations return that DOGE could become a payment option on X (Twitter). DOGE outperforms the broader market DOGE, the native coin of the Dogecoin ecosystem, is the best performer amongst the top 10 [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/dogecoin-up-4-as-x-payments-speculations-return/">Dogecoin up 4% as X payments speculations return</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">DOGE is outperforming the other major cryptocurrencies, up by 4% in the last 24 hours.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The positive performance comes as speculations return that DOGE could become a payment option on X (Twitter).</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr">DOGE outperforms the broader market</h2>
<p dir="ltr">DOGE, the native coin of the Dogecoin ecosystem, is the best performer amongst the top 10 cryptocurrencies by market cap today. The coin has added 4% to its value in the last 24 hours, outperforming Bitcoin and other major cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p dir="ltr">At press time, the&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/dogecoin/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>price of Dogecoin</u></a> stands at $0.0771. The positive performance comes as speculations returned that DOGE could be used for payments on Twitter, which was rebranded to X by Elon Musk earlier this week.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Market analysts believe that DOGE&rsquo;s price could soar higher thanks to this speculation. Kryptomon Chief Marketing Officer Tomer Nuni told CoinDesk that;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;The speculation is that advertisers could be able to pay DOGE for ads and for other uses on Twitter. We saw the same happening when Tesla revealed the ability to pay for its goods with DOGE. So the speculation could be around Musk&rsquo;s businesses and stakeholdings starting to accept crypto, as Tesla does.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p dir="ltr">Dogecoin is currently the seventh-largest cryptocurrency by market cap, behind Circle&rsquo;s USDC stablecoin.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Twitter is reportedly designing a system that would allow users to make payments via the social media platform. However, Elon Musk wants fiat currencies to be supported before Twitter will include cryptocurrencies as payment options.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitcoin drops to the $29k level</h2>
<p dir="ltr">While Dogecoin was rallying, Bitcoin was tanking. Bitcoin is down by more than 2% in the last 24 hours, briefly dropping below the $29k level late on Monday.</p>
<p>At press time, the&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>price of Bitcoin</u></a> stands at $29,255. The poor performance came following the Wall Street Journal&rsquo;s report on Monday, alleging possible wash trading activities by the world&rsquo;s largest cryptocurrency exchange.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/dogecoin-up-4-as-x-payments-speculations-return/">Dogecoin up 4% as X payments speculations return</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/dogecoin-up-4-as-x-payments-speculations-return/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fidelity is bullish on Ethereum for the long term</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/fidelity-is-bullish-on-ethereum-for-the-long-term/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wajeeh Khan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 20:18:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=147448</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Fidelity likes Ethereum as burn rate now exceeds issuance. ETH continues to be the largest holding in investors&#8217; portfolios. Ether is currently up more than 50% versus the start of the year. Ethereum is already up more than 50% for the year at writing but Fidelity Digital Assets still remains bullish on the premier altcoin [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/fidelity-is-bullish-on-ethereum-for-the-long-term/">Fidelity is bullish on Ethereum for the long term</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Fidelity likes Ethereum as burn rate now exceeds issuance.</li>
<li>ETH continues to be the largest holding in investors&rsquo; portfolios.</li>
<li>Ether is currently up more than 50% versus the start of the year.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/ethereum/">Ethereum</a> is already up more than 50% for the year at writing but Fidelity Digital Assets still remains bullish on the premier altcoin for the long term.</p>
<h2>Why does Fidelity like Ethereum?</h2>
<p>The crypto platform that caters to institutional investors is constructive on Ether primarily because its burn rate now exceeds issuance.</p>
<p>Since the &ldquo;Merge&rdquo;, the net supply has declined by more than 700,000 coins, as per the firm&rsquo;s recently published <a href="https://www.fidelitydigitalassets.com/sites/default/files/documents/1096171.1.0%20Fidelity%20Digital%20Assets%20-%20Q2%20Signals%20Report.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Q2 2023 Signals Report</a>.</p>
<p>Fidelity also drives optimism from an increase in active Ethereum validators of 15% in the second quarter. The excitement around EIP-1153 update that promises lower costs and better efficiency will help unlock further upside in ETH, the firm added.</p>
<p>&ldquo;New Address Momentum&rdquo; was among other reasons cited for the positive long-term view on Ether.</p>
<h2>Could ETH ever be bigger than BTC?</h2>
<p>Separately, a recent CryptoVantage survey suggested about 46% of Americans expect Ether to eventually surpass Bitcoin in market capitalisation. The said study saw participation from 1,000 Americans who have had exposure to cryptocurrencies as an investment over the past five years.</p>
<p>Recent data from <a href="https://coinshares.com/research/digital-asset-quarterly-fund-manager-survey-jul-23" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinshares</a> was green as well. In a report over the weekend, the asset manager confirmed that Ethereum continues to be the largest holding in investors&rsquo; portfolios even though it has underperformed Bitcoin this year.</p>
<p>Note that ETH could benefit as the U.S. Federal Reserve signals a pivot as well. That&rsquo;s because a lenient monetary policy tends to boost interest in the risk-on assets. <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-price-prediction-fed-and-options-expiry-in-focus/">Ethereum</a>, though, has been trending down in recent sessions, though, ahead of the central bank&rsquo;s announcement on Wednesday.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/fidelity-is-bullish-on-ethereum-for-the-long-term/">Fidelity is bullish on Ethereum for the long term</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto price outlook: BNB, Dogecoin</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-outlook-bnb-dogecoin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 19:43:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOGE]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-outlook-bnb-dogecoin/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrencies traded largely lower today, with Bitcoin dipping to below $29k. BNB moved above XRP although bulls need to keep prices above $330 to keep bears at bay, otherwise it could dump to $220 or lower. Dogecoin spiked as Twitter rebranded to X. Can DOGE go higher? Crypto news today has been dominated by headlines [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-outlook-bnb-dogecoin/">Crypto price outlook: BNB, Dogecoin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Cryptocurrencies traded largely lower today, with Bitcoin dipping to below $29k.</li>
<li dir="ltr">BNB moved above XRP although bulls need to keep prices above $330 to keep bears at bay, otherwise it could dump to $220 or lower.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Dogecoin spiked as Twitter rebranded to X. Can DOGE go higher?</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/">Crypto news</a> today has been dominated by headlines around the launch of Worldcoin (WLD) token and Elon Musk&rsquo;s Twitter rebrand to X. Meanwhile, the broader crypto market has continued to see a slump for major altcoins, with Bitcoin hovering just above $29k following further weakness on Monday.</p>
<p dir="ltr">While analysts have outlined a potential upward flip after recent consolidation, regulatory uncertainty remains a big negative trigger. Also key this week could be the overall investor reaction to the Federal Reserve&rsquo;s policy decision after their two-day meeting.</p>
<p dir="ltr">So, with these factors in perspective, what&rsquo;s the price outlook for BNB and <a href="https://coinjournal.net/dogecoin/">Dogecoin</a>?</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">BNB price outlook: $330 key support level</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/binance-coin/">BNB</a>, the native coin of the Binance ecosystem, has overtaken XRP as the fourth largest crypto asset by market cap after the Ripple token slumped 6% on Monday. However, BNB price is also down (currently 2%) and trades below its 20-day EMA.</p>
<div class="fr-img-space-wrap"><span class="fr-img-caption fr-fic fr-dib fr-draggable" style="width: 700px"><span class="fr-img-wrap">
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/24/1690227074192-e128df51-81e8-4c51-a345-0710534d9dc7.png" style="width: 700px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="700" height="320"><span class="fr-inner">BNB price chart. Source:&nbsp;<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/UYrbhYPP/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">TradingView</a></span></p>
<p></p></span></span>
<p class="fr-img-space-wrap2">While support is likely at $230, a dip below this buffer could allow bears to target a retest of areas below the lower trendline of the symmetrical triangle.&nbsp;</p>
<p class="fr-img-space-wrap2">It&rsquo;s a scenario that could see BNB price such for fresh footing around $220, an area that provided a breather in June this year and in December 2022.</p>
</div>
<h2 dir="ltr">DOGE price outlook: Another push related to X?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Dogecoin (DOGE) price was an outlier of sorts today in the crypto markets. While all major altcoins dipped, the OG meme coin spiked by 10% to break above $0.075.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">As Elon Musk revealed Twitter&rsquo;s rebranding to X, he put the DOGE symbol next to the X logo.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24DOGE&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$DOGE</a> up almost 10% as Elon Musk adds Doge logo to his profile location <a href="https://t.co/vDYn4KPzq3">pic.twitter.com/vDYn4KPzq3</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Dan Gambardello (@cryptorecruitr) <a href="https://twitter.com/cryptorecruitr/status/1683476882518360066?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 24, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">Bulls took cue to push the coin higher and have succeeded in keeping it above the 20-day and 50-day EMA.&nbsp;</p>
<div class="fr-img-space-wrap"><span class="fr-img-caption fr-fic fr-dib fr-draggable" style="width: 700px"><span class="fr-img-wrap">
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/24/1690227169352-5994b171-44aa-49ad-ba07-700f8fe8c4f0.png" style="width: 700px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="700" height="287"><span class="fr-inner">Dogecoin price chart. Source:&nbsp;<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/PGjgAHuA/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">TradingView</a></span></p>
<p></p></span></span>
<p class="fr-img-space-wrap2">The moving averages could offer a key demand reload zone should DOGE flip lower. However, the daily RSI is trending upwards but not yet overextended into the overbought territory.</p>
</div>
<p dir="ltr">This suggests potential upside moves are still likely, particularly in relation to news around DOGE adoption on X.</p>
<p dir="ltr">If bulls push higher, the area around $0.08 will be a key barrier that would need a convincing retest. &nbsp;$0.09 and $0.11 could be the next bull targets. On the downside, a breakout below $0.07 could risk a dump to $0.057.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-outlook-bnb-dogecoin/">Crypto price outlook: BNB, Dogecoin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Caldera brings decentralized sequencing to OP stack with Espresso</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/caldera-brings-decentralized-sequencing-to-op-stack-with-espresso/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/caldera-brings-decentralized-sequencing-to-op-stack-with-espresso/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 18:22:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/caldera-brings-decentralized-sequencing-to-op-stack-with-espresso/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Caldera developers can leverage Espresso Sequencer for greater scaling and decentralisation. The rollup-as-a-service (RaaS) platform recently partnered with Manta Network and SupraOracles. Caldera, a rollup-as-a-service (RaaS) platform, and blockchain infrastructure company Espresso Systems have announced a partnership that will see them work together towards enabling decentralized sequencing to the OP stack and Caldera chains. The [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/caldera-brings-decentralized-sequencing-to-op-stack-with-espresso/">Caldera brings decentralized sequencing to OP stack with Espresso</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Caldera developers can leverage Espresso Sequencer for greater scaling and decentralisation.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The rollup-as-a-service (RaaS) platform recently partnered with Manta Network and SupraOracles.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Caldera, a rollup-as-a-service (RaaS) platform, and blockchain infrastructure company Espresso Systems have <a href="https://blog.caldera.xyz/caldera-partners-with-espresso-to-bring-decentralized-sequencing-to-the-op-stack/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">announced</a> a partnership that will see them work together towards enabling decentralized sequencing to the OP stack and Caldera chains.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The integration will also be key in allowing Caldera layer 2s to tap into the Espresso Sequencer to improve on scalability and interoperability.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Decentralized sequencing is coming to Caldera!</p>
<p>We're partnering with <a href="https://twitter.com/EspressoSys?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@EspressoSys</a> to make it easy for teams to use the Espresso Sequencer as a plug-in component of our modular rollup stack on their Caldera chains!</p>
<p>Let's dive into the details &#129525; <a href="https://t.co/Ib6qt3ubn1">pic.twitter.com/Ib6qt3ubn1</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Caldera (@Calderaxyz) <a href="https://twitter.com/Calderaxyz/status/1683508651263410180?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 24, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Caldera eyes greater scaling and decentralization</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Sequencers are the nodes tasked with aggregating and ordering transactions as well as executing these transactions on the virtual machine. They are like validators in an L1 network ecosystem and thus crucial to the transaction process of a rollup network.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Layer 2 rollups that offer a scaling solution for <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/">Ethereum</a> have one limitation &ndash; they rely on centralized sequencers that can be impacted by risks such as unreliability and censorship. The Espresso Sequencer offers the utility that not only allows for greater decentralization, but also high throughput, low latency transaction ordering and interoperability. This will help developers on Caldera, the team noted.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>Through this partnership, developers building with Caldera will be able to deploy performant app-specific rollups that utilize the Espresso Sequencer for ordering and fast confirmations, bringing another layer of customizability to our modular stack that should enable teams to build their dream applications without compromises!</em>&rdquo; they wrote.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Developer teams will have the option of easily opting into the Espresso Sequencer, with this designed as a plug-in component of Caldera&rsquo;s modular rollup stack.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The partnership with Espresso Systems comes a few days after Caldera partnered with Web3 privacy hub Manta Network. The platforms are collaborating on a project that targets an L2 EVM execution layer for zero-knowledge applications.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Earlier this month, Caldera integrated blockchain oracles service SupraOracles to bring price feeds and VRF to Caldera.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/caldera-brings-decentralized-sequencing-to-op-stack-with-espresso/">Caldera brings decentralized sequencing to OP stack with Espresso</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/caldera-brings-decentralized-sequencing-to-op-stack-with-espresso/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto investment products saw minor outflows of $6.5M last week &#8211; CoinShares</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-investment-products-saw-minor-outflows-of-6-5m-last-week-coinshares/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-investment-products-saw-minor-outflows-of-6-5m-last-week-coinshares/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 17:04:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Institutional investors]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-investment-products-saw-minor-outflows-of-6-5m-last-week-coinshares/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>About $6.5 million flowed out of funds tracking different cryptocurrencies last week. Bitcoin recorded $13 million in outflows, while Ethereum benefited from XRP-driven sentiment to record $6.6 million in inflows. The minor outflows follow 4 consecutive weeks of inflows. CoinShares&#8217; latest report on digital assets investment products suggests the industry saw minor outflows of $6.5 [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-investment-products-saw-minor-outflows-of-6-5m-last-week-coinshares/">Crypto investment products saw minor outflows of $6.5M last week &#8211; CoinShares</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">About $6.5 million flowed out of funds tracking different cryptocurrencies last week.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Bitcoin recorded $13 million in outflows, while Ethereum benefited from XRP-driven sentiment to record $6.6 million in inflows.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The minor outflows follow 4 consecutive weeks of inflows.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">CoinShares&rsquo; latest report on digital assets investment products suggests the industry saw minor outflows of $6.5 million over the past week. The outflows follow a consecutive four weeks of inflows that saw investors pour $742 million into different crypto investment products.</p>
<p dir="ltr">James Butterfill, Head of Research at CoinShares noted that while <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> recorded the most outflows, data showed sentiment towards Ethereum investment products looks to have flipped positive.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Ethereum and XRP record inflows</h2>
<p dir="ltr">As highlighted in a report published on Monday, funds tracking Bitcoin logged $13 million of outflows and short-bitcoin products recorded $5.5 million in outflows &ndash; its 13th consecutive week.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Meanwhile, <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/">Ethereum</a> products witnessed $6.6 million in inflows, with Butterfill noting that the shift in sentiment around ETH has coincided with the recent court ruling in the Ripple Labs versus US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).</p>
<p dir="ltr">US Judge Analisa Torres <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ripple-wins-sec-case-xrp-not-a-security/">delivered</a> a partial win for <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/ripple/">Ripple</a> in its battle with the SEC when she ruled that XRP was not a security as sold on exchanges.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The price of XRP shot up following the ruling, rising more than 100% to hit highs near the much-coveted $1 level. But while XRP failed to break to the psychological 100 cents mark, it appears investor confidence in the cryptocurrency greatly benefited it.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>XRP, both prior to, and following the conclusion of the recent SEC lawsuit, has seen inflows totalling US$6.8m over the last 11 weeks representing 8% of AuM. This implies investors are increasingly confident in the outlook for XRP</em>,&rdquo; Butterfill <a href="https://blog.coinshares.com/volume-141-digital-asset-fund-flows-weekly-report-38255b443eae" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">wrote</a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The positive sentiment was also replicated in Solana, Uniswap and Polygon that registered inflows of $1.1 million, $0.7 million and $0.7 million respectively.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-investment-products-saw-minor-outflows-of-6-5m-last-week-coinshares/">Crypto investment products saw minor outflows of $6.5M last week &#8211; CoinShares</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-investment-products-saw-minor-outflows-of-6-5m-last-week-coinshares/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum price prediction: Fed and options expiry in focus</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-price-prediction-fed-and-options-expiry-in-focus/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-price-prediction-fed-and-options-expiry-in-focus/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 15:58:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-price-prediction-fed-and-options-expiry-in-focus/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum price drifted downwards as demand for the coin waned. Focus shifts to the upcoming Fed interest rate decision. Ethereum will have options expiry on Friday. Ethereum price retreated to the lowest level since July 7th as demand for cryptocurrencies cooled. The coin slipped to $1,847, which was lower than this month&#8217;s high of $2,025. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-price-prediction-fed-and-options-expiry-in-focus/">Ethereum price prediction: Fed and options expiry in focus</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Ethereum price drifted downwards as demand for the coin waned.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Focus shifts to the upcoming Fed interest rate decision.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Ethereum will have options expiry on Friday.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum"><u>Ethereu</u></a>m price retreated to the lowest level since July 7th as demand for cryptocurrencies cooled. The coin slipped to $1,847, which was lower than this month&rsquo;s high of $2,025. It remains ~15% below the year-to-date high, meaning it has moved into a correction.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Fed and options expiry</h2>
<p dir="ltr">There will be two important catalysts for Ethereum price this week. First, the coin will react to the latest interest rate decision by the Federal Reserve. The committee will start its two-day meeting on Tuesday and then deliver its decision on Wednesday.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The meeting comes at an important time for the American economy. All signs show that the economic growth is slowing. Data published on Monday revealed that the manufacturing PMI number rose to 49 while the services PMI fell to 52.4. While the manufacturing PMI rose, it remains below 50, signaling that the sector is contracting.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Meanwhile, the most recent data revealed that the country&rsquo;s inflation dropped to 3.0% in June this year. It has dropped from a pandemic high of 9.1% and the downward trend continues. Therefore, there is a likelihood that prices will drop to the Fed&rsquo;s target of 2.0% even without further rate hikes.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Economists expect the Fed will raise interest rates by 0.25% in this meeting and then point to a long pause. Further interest rate hikes will likely lead to a strong deterioration of the American economy, commonly known as a hard landing.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The other important catalyst for Ethereum price will be the upcoming options expiry. Data compiled by Coinglass shows that&nbsp;<a href="https://www.coinglass.com/options"><u>there</u></a> are now over 2,206,619 ETH calls and 755,222 puts in the options market. Historically, Ethereum tends to show some volatility ahead of options expiry.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Ethereum price prediction</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/24/1690214260325-29fa7e55-5d58-4d60-88bf-3c6ef0460272.png" style="width: 648px;height: 315.36px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="648" height="315.36"></p>
<p dir="ltr">The daily chart shows that ETH price has come under pressure in the past few days. It has moved below the important resistance level at $2,025, the highest point on July 14th. This resistance was also the upper side of the ascending channel shown in black.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Ethereum also moved slightly below the 25-day and 50-day moving averages. Therefore, the coin will likely continue falling as sellers target the next support level at $1,800. A move above the resistance point at $1,900 will invalidate the bearish view.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy Ethereum</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>

    <p>eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=MTQ3Mzgz&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy ETH with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    Public</h3>

    <p>Public is an investing platform that allows you to invest stocks, ETFs, crypto, and alternative assets like fine art and collectibles&mdash;all in one place.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/public-crypto?guid=MTQ3Mzgz&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy ETH with Public today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptocurrency execution and custody services are provided by Apex Crypto LLC (NMLS ID 1828849) through a software licensing agreement between Apex Crypto LLC and Public Crypto LLC. Crypto trading on Public platforms is served by Public Crypto LLC and offered through APEX Crypto. Please ensure that you fully understand the risks involved before trading." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-price-prediction-fed-and-options-expiry-in-focus/">Ethereum price prediction: Fed and options expiry in focus</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-price-prediction-fed-and-options-expiry-in-focus/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto projects raised over $200M last week, with Chancer’s presale closing in on $1M</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-projects-raised-over-200m-last-week-with-chancers-presale-closing-in-on-1m/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-projects-raised-over-200m-last-week-with-chancers-presale-closing-in-on-1m/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 15:15:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-projects-raised-over-200m-last-week-with-chancers-presale-closing-in-on-1m/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways Cryptocurrency projects raised $201 million from VC firms last week. Chancer&#8217;s presale is currently ongoing, and the project is close to hitting the $1 million mark.&#160; The cryptocurrency market is starting the week in a bearish manner. Bitcoin is down by more than 2% today and could experience further decline in the next [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-projects-raised-over-200m-last-week-with-chancers-presale-closing-in-on-1m/">Crypto projects raised over $200M last week, with Chancer’s presale closing in on $1M</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Cryptocurrency projects raised $201 million from VC firms last week.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Chancer&rsquo;s presale is currently ongoing, and the project is close to hitting the $1 million mark.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">The cryptocurrency market is starting the week in a bearish manner. Bitcoin is down by more than 2% today and could experience further decline in the next few hours. At press time, the&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>price of Bitcoin</u></a> stands at $29,148 per coin.</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, Chancer&rsquo;s presale continues to soar higher, with the team now close to hitting the $1 million mark.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Crypto projects raised $201M in a week</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies have been experiencing ranging markets since the start of the month. However, despite the market&rsquo;s poor performance in July, cryptocurrency projects continue to set new records.</p>
<p dir="ltr">A report by CoinDesk revealed that cryptocurrency projects raised $201.4 million last week. The biggest earners in the market were projects that create developer tools for zero-knowledge proofs.</p>
<p dir="ltr">VC firms continue to invest in cryptocurrency projects despite the bear market, indicating that there is a strong belief about the future of the industry.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Chancer</u></a> is gaining traction despite not going via the VC funding path at the moment. The team&rsquo;s presale event is set to hit the $1 million mark, with more than 11 million tokens sold so far.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What does this mean for Chancer?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Cryptocurrency projects raising huge amounts of money from VC firms is a clear indication that investors are willing to enter the market and invest in the right project.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Strong projects with excellent use cases will gain the attention of investors, both retail and institutional.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Chancer</u></a> is one of the exciting and new projects currently in the cryptocurrency space. Chancer is one of the projects that is gathering momentum amongst retail investors.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The team is developing a unique Web3 peer-to-peer (P2P) custom betting platform that would make it possible for users to live-stream betting events.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">What Chancer seeks to achieve is to decentralise the betting industry. The platform is adopting a decentralised method of betting and online gambling.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">An excellent feature of Chancer is that, unlike traditional betting platforms, it doesn&rsquo;t restrict its users&rsquo; betting opportunities. This means that Chancer users can bet on a wide range of events, beyond traditional sports and casino bets.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Chancer presale is in its first phase, and the team has raised $954,038.02 of the $1,000,000 required. In the first presale, CHANCER is selling for $0.01 USDT but will be increased to $0.011 in the second stage.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The developers will use the funds raised from the various funding rounds to build a P2P betting platform.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">In their whitepaper, the Chancer team said they would grant users access to numerous features, including, betting markets in real-time and based on user interests, social media connections, and expertise.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">In addition to that, Chancer is looking to eliminate the problems associated with using bookmakers when betting by allowing users to set up their custom P2P betting markets.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Perhaps the most important feature of Chancer is that it would allow users to bet on various activities. The bet can be on important sporting or political events or trivial ones like the first to complete a task amongst friends.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">CHANCER to go for $0.011 in the second presale stage</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer&rsquo;s first presale stage will be completed soon, and the team will move to the second phase. In the first phase, the CHANCER token is currently going for $0.01 USDT.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, the team will increase the token price to $0.011 in the second presale round. The&nbsp;<a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Chancer</u></a> team will use the funds to develop its suite of products. There would be 12 presale events, with an accumulated target of $15 million.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">CHANCER will have numerous utilities within the Chancer ecosystem. CHANCER token holders will have the option of creating and investing in markets created by others.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Furthermore, the token will allow holders to create, participate in, and profit from their very own predictive markets.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">At the moment, investors can purchase CHANCER tokens using numerous wallets, including, Trust Wallet, MetaMask, Coinbase Wallet, and Rainbow.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Visit the&nbsp;<a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Chancer website</u></a> to get more information about the presale.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Should you invest in Chancer now?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">As more investors enter the cryptocurrency market, the focus is on excellent projects still in their early stages.&nbsp;<a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Chancer</u></a> could become a big project in the cryptocurrency space due to its unique nature.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">By decentralising the betting ecosystem, Chancer could gain massive adoption within the Web3 space and beyond over the next few months and years.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">A surge in adoption of the Chancer platform could also lead to a rally by its native CHANCER token. Furthermore, if the broader cryptocurrency market embarks on a Bull Run, CHANCER could become one of the biggest winners.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-projects-raised-over-200m-last-week-with-chancers-presale-closing-in-on-1m/">Crypto projects raised over $200M last week, with Chancer’s presale closing in on $1M</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-projects-raised-over-200m-last-week-with-chancers-presale-closing-in-on-1m/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
