<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 14:21:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Macy’s Shares Drop after Reporting Mixed Q1 2023 Earnings and Lowered Its Full-Year Outlook</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/macys-shares-q1-2023-earnings/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/macys-shares-q1-2023-earnings/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 14:21:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wall Street]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[macy's]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[macy's stock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nike]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=257420</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/macys-shares-q1-2023-earnings/">Macy’s Shares Drop after Reporting Mixed Q1 2023 Earnings and Lowered Its Full-Year Outlook</a></p>
<p>Macy's noted that Nike will return to its stores, starting from October this year.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/macys-shares-q1-2023-earnings/">Macy’s Shares Drop after Reporting Mixed Q1 2023 Earnings and Lowered Its Full-Year Outlook</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/macys-shares-q1-2023-earnings/">Macy’s Shares Drop after Reporting Mixed Q1 2023 Earnings and Lowered Its Full-Year Outlook</a></p>
<p>Macy’s Inc (NYSE: M), an American conglomerate holding company that engages in consumer goods, released its first-quarter earnings results on June 01. According to the announcement, Macy’s reported net sales of $4.98 billion during the first three months of the year (Q1 2023), which represented a decline of approximately 7 percent YoY basis. However, analysts surveyed by REFINITIV expected the company to report revenue of about $5.04 billion during the first quarter.</p>
<p>Notably, the company noted that the first quarter’s net income was $155 million, representing 56 cents per share, having dropped from $286 million or 98 cents per share a year ago. As a result, M shares continued with this year’s bearish outlook during Thursday’s pre-market to trade around $13.09, down approximately 4 percent.</p>
<p>According to the latest stock market data, M shares have dropped approximately 40 percent in the last three months, after registering a decline of 42 percent last year.</p>
<h2>Macy’s Q1 2023 Financial Highlights</h2>
<p>The $3.83 billion valued company declared its regular quarterly dividend of 16.54 cents per share on the common stock, which is payable on July 3, 2023, to shareholders snapshot taken on June 15, 2023. This is after reporting its merchandise inventories for the first quarter came in at $4.607 billion. However, the company noted that the remaining part of the year will be lower than expected.</p>
<p>“The company is taking a cautious approach to the remainder of the year and is reducing its annual 2023 sales and earnings guidance to reflect anticipated macroeconomic impacts to the consumer,” Macy’s <a href="https://www.macysinc.com/newsroom/news/news-details/2023/Macys-Inc.-Reports-First-Quarter-2023-Results/default.aspx" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">noted</a>.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, the company’s Chief Executive Officer Jeff Gennette noted that the first quarter beat the expectations in gross margin rate that came in at 40.0 percent, up from 39.6 percent in the first quarter of 2022.</p>
<p>As for the Bluemercury segment, Macy’s noted that comparable sales gained 4.3 percent on an owned basis. Whereby approximately 676,000 active customers shopped the Bluemercury brand, on a trailing twelve-month basis. The company noted that Bloomingdale’s brand reported 4.1 million active customers on a trailing twelve-month basis. Nonetheless, Bloomingdale&#8217;s comparable sales dropped approximately 3.9 percent on an owned basis.</p>
<p>“During the first quarter, we delivered a solid beat on our gross margin rate and bottom line expectations enabled by our disciplined teams, the strength of our inventory management, and operational efficiencies. We planned the year assuming that the economic health of the consumer would be challenged, but starting in late March, demand trends weakened further in our discretionary categories,” Gennette noted.</p>
<p>Forward, the company promised its customers that <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/nike/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Nike</a> is returning to its stores starting in October. As a result, Macy’s anticipates that sales will peak as the festive season kicks in in the second half of the year.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ecb-president-euro-zone-inflation/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/macys-shares-q1-2023-earnings/">Macy’s Shares Drop after Reporting Mixed Q1 2023 Earnings and Lowered Its Full-Year Outlook</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/macys-shares-q1-2023-earnings/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>ECB President Says Euro Zone Inflation Still ‘Too High’ as Rate Falls Lower than Expected to 6.1%</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ecb-president-euro-zone-inflation/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ecb-president-euro-zone-inflation/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 14:17:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[christine lagarde]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ing bank]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=257412</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ecb-president-euro-zone-inflation/">ECB President Says Euro Zone Inflation Still &#8216;Too High&#8217; as Rate Falls Lower than Expected to 6.1%</a></p>
<p>Inflation in the Euro zone has fallen to 6.1% as individual countries are also recording reductions. However, Lagarde plans more rate hikes.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ecb-president-euro-zone-inflation/">ECB President Says Euro Zone Inflation Still &#8216;Too High&#8217; as Rate Falls Lower than Expected to 6.1%</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ecb-president-euro-zone-inflation/">ECB President Says Euro Zone Inflation Still &#8216;Too High&#8217; as Rate Falls Lower than Expected to 6.1%</a></p>
<p>Euro zone inflation has dropped in May, with a steeper plunge than analysts and observers expected. <a href="https://ec.europa.eu/eurostat/documents/2995521/16863926/2-01062023-AP-EN.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Flash figures</a> show that headline inflation, which was 7% in April, fell to 6.1% in May. This is the lowest recorded figure since February 2022. According to a Reuters poll, economics had set the May figure at 6.3%. Core inflation, minus food and energy, also fell from 5.6% to 5.3%.</p>
<p>The general sentiment in specific European countries was favorable as well. Generally, the Euro rose slightly higher against the British pound and the US dollar, as European stocks also saw their values climb. Specifically, news from Italy and Spain shows that inflation in both countries is gradually reducing. France and Germany are also seeing reductions below expected forecasts.</p>
<h2>Lagarde: Euro Zone Inflation Is Still Too High</h2>
<p>Despite inflation falling below expected levels, the President of the European Central Bank (ECB) <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/christine-lagarde/">Christine Lagarde</a> believes it is still too high. Speaking at the Deutscher Sparkassentag 2023 conference, Lagarde said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Today, inflation is too high and it is set to remain so for too long. We are determined to bring it back down to our 2% medium-term target in a timely manner.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Lagarde further explained that fighting inflation is the reason the ECB has “hiked rates at our fastest pace ever”. She also clearly stated that there will be more hikes until the apex bank achieves its target. However, the speech also notes that the ECB is monitoring the effect of all policies on the economy. She said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“So, we need to continue our hiking cycle until we are sufficiently confident that inflation is on track to return to our target in a timely manner. At the same time, we need to carefully assess the strength of monetary policy transmission to financing conditions, the economy and inflation.”</p></blockquote>
<p>In a recent note, Dutch Bank ING senior eurozone economist Bert Colijn said many inflation drivers have improved over the last few months. According to him, as these drivers reflect in the data, inflation should start dropping over the next few months. Regardless, the Deutsche Bundesbank President Joachim Nagel has corroborated Lagarde, stating he expects a few more interest rate hikes.</p>
<h2>Inflation in Member Countries</h2>
<p>Inflation in Spain saw a 2-year low of 2.9% after the government subsidized gas bills. Germany’s inflation fell from 7.6% to 6.3%, while France also recorded a reduction from 6.9% to 6%. However, France also saw an 11% plunge in food purchases. The zone&#8217;s second-largest economy recorded fewer purchases than seen during the COVID pandemic.</p>
<p>According to ING Bank senior economist Charlotte de Montpellier, the figure shows that inflation has bitten quite hard into the economy. The situation has resulted in reduced purchasing power and has forced people to rethink purchases and general consumption.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-two-mac-products/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ecb-president-euro-zone-inflation/">ECB President Says Euro Zone Inflation Still &#8216;Too High&#8217; as Rate Falls Lower than Expected to 6.1%</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ecb-president-euro-zone-inflation/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Apple Likely to Launch Two Mac Products at Upcoming WWDC</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-two-mac-products/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-two-mac-products/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 14:14:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mac]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=257409</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-two-mac-products/">Apple Likely to Launch Two Mac Products at Upcoming WWDC</a></p>
<p>Apple is focused on overhauling the Mac line with the new computer as well as attracting more customers, especially now that there is a static stretch in the computer industry.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-two-mac-products/">Apple Likely to Launch Two Mac Products at Upcoming WWDC</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-two-mac-products/">Apple Likely to Launch Two Mac Products at Upcoming WWDC</a></p>
<p>There are suspicions that American multinational technology giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/apple-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Apple Inc</a> (NASDAQ: AAPL) will be <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-05-31/apple-tests-new-high-end-mac-chips-ahead-of-developer-conference" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">launching</a> two highly anticipated Mac models in the upcoming Worldwide Developers Conference  (WWDC) which will be held next week. These rumors are stemming from the fact that the technology company has begun the testing process of two desktop Macs that are equipped with M2 Max and ‌M2‌ Ultra chips.</p>
<p>The two models are labeled internally as Mac 14,13 and Mac 14,14, running on the M2 Max processor. Notably, the first time the M2 Max chip was mentioned was in January during the debut of the 2023 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro models. On the other hand, the M2 Ultra chip is new and is a replacement for the M1 Ultra which the tech firm has been utilizing in the Mac Studio, Apple&#8217;s high-end desktop which was released a year ago.</p>
<p>There had previously been rumors that the revamped Apple Silicon Mac Pro would include the M2 Ultra chip.</p>
<p>However, the Mac Pro which Apple is working on is labelled internally as &#8220;14,8&#8221;. This, therefore, suggests that the desktop machines that are currently being tested are something else, maybe new versions of the ‌Mac Studio. Very soon, Apple is likely to release new iMacs with M3 chips.</p>
<h2>Apple to Attract Customers with New Mac Products</h2>
<p>Apple is focused on overhauling the Mac line with the new computer as well as attracting more customers, especially now that there is a static stretch in the computer industry. So far, the company has been doing well in that regard. About a month ago, Apple <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-fiscal-q2-2023/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a> earnings for the second fiscal quarter and to the amazement of many, it beat Wall Street&#8217;s expectations.</p>
<p>According to Tim Cook, the Chief Executive Officer (CEO) of Apple, the iPhone sales for the last quarter were “better than we expected”. iPhone sales revenue jumped by 2% amidst a general smartphone market decline of 15%.</p>
<p>At the same time, Apple’s Chief of Finance Luca Maestri said &#8220;We expect our June quarter year-over-year revenue performance to be similar to the March quarter assuming that the macroeconomic outlook does not worsen from what we are projecting today for the current quarter.”</p>
<p>Over time, it has been discovered that the powerful desktop model of Apple devices offers one of the strongest appeals to professional users like graphic designers and video editors.</p>
<p>The first device that Apple has been working on includes an ‌M2‌ Max chip with eight high-performance cores, four efficiency cores, a 30-core GPU, and 96GB RAM. It is worthy of note that the chip is the same as the chip embedded in the ‌M2‌ Max version of the 16-inch MacBook Pro. While the second one has 16 high-performance cores and 8 efficiency cores with the M2 Ultra chip.</p>
<p>Additionally, Apple has <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-broadcom-usa-5g-components/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">bagged</a> a recent partnership with multinational semiconductor and infrastructure software firm <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/broadcom/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Broadcom Inc</a> (NASDAQ: AVGO) to design and produce its 5G components.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/first-digital-stablecoin-hong-kong/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-two-mac-products/">Apple Likely to Launch Two Mac Products at Upcoming WWDC</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-two-mac-products/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>First Digital Group Launches FDUSD Stablecoin amid Hong Kong’s Regulation Move</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/first-digital-stablecoin-hong-kong/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/first-digital-stablecoin-hong-kong/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[staff writer]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 14:03:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fdusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=257407</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/first-digital-stablecoin-hong-kong/">First Digital Group Launches FDUSD Stablecoin amid Hong Kong’s Regulation Move</a></p>
<p>FDUSD will not be used in Hong Kong until its stablecoin regulations are fully in place.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/first-digital-stablecoin-hong-kong/">First Digital Group Launches FDUSD Stablecoin amid Hong Kong’s Regulation Move</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/first-digital-stablecoin-hong-kong/">First Digital Group Launches FDUSD Stablecoin amid Hong Kong’s Regulation Move</a></p>
<p>First Digital Group announced the <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/06/01/first-digital-unveils-usd-stablecoin-as-hong-kong-crypto-rules-kick-in/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">introduction</a> of its USD stablecoin FDUSD. The company, which has its headquarters in Hong Kong, is launching the stablecoin on the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a> and BNB blockchains.</p>
<p>Having a coin on multiple blockchains can facilitate better interoperability and broader adoption. It also heightens the chances of gaining access to a wider community and benefiting from each blockchain&#8217;s advantages. Lastly, this can also reduce the risk of over-dependence on one blockchain. The company’s plan is to list the coin on all the top exchanges.</p>
<p>The coin is regulated in Asia by reputable bodies to provide oversight and ensure transparent operations. First Digital also stated that the coin is backed by cash and other assets that store up cash, constituting what the company regards as &#8220;high-quality reserves&#8221; to ensure currency stability.</p>
<p>The First Digital Group is also registered under the Hong Kong Trust, an organization that emphasizes keeping funds in separate accounts to prevent them from mixing with funds meant for other purposes. These measures can help protect their reserves from co-mingling with other funds and constantly provide a clear picture of the company&#8217;s financial standing.</p>
<p>First Digital’s CEO, Vincent Chok, expressing his thoughts about the crypto mentioned that:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The launch of this stablecoin represents a major stride forward in our mission to provide a secure and efficient digital currency that can be seamlessly integrated into everyday transactions.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Hong Kong Maintains Its Strict Stablecoin Regulations</h2>
<p>With the regulatory imbalances surrounding cryptocurrencies, the coin still has a limit to its use, even in Hong Kong, where First Digital is registered, as the government issued a law against using stablecoins among retail traders. This is because the country&#8217;s regulators are still working on classifying the asset for appropriate regulatory oversight.</p>
<p>Additionally, there are certain rules that crypto and stablecoin service issuers are expected to follow to operate locally. Although they are mostly unclear, Hong Kong authorities are working to ensure that stablecoin and crypto transactions and trading are as safe as possible.</p>
<p>In 2023, it is not far-fetched to believe that stablecoins, though expected to be stable, are also susceptible to crashing. A recent example is TerraUSD, a stablecoin that crashed in 2022. The shockwave of the crash shook the crypto world, and many preferred to stay away from crypto entirely. With FDUSD’s introduction, its successful and transparent operation, and favorable Hong Kong regulations for stablecoins, we can expect to see increased adoption of stablecoins since a trusted service will improve investors&#8217; trust. This, at the same time, may also increase the standard for crypto regulations.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-com-license-singapore/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/first-digital-stablecoin-hong-kong/">First Digital Group Launches FDUSD Stablecoin amid Hong Kong’s Regulation Move</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/first-digital-stablecoin-hong-kong/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto.com Secures License from Monetary Authority of Singapore as Payment Institution</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-com-license-singapore/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-com-license-singapore/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 12:56:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto.com]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mas]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=257366</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-com-license-singapore/">Crypto.com Secures License from Monetary Authority of Singapore as Payment Institution</a></p>
<p>Securing this recent license will allow Crypto.com to offer DPT services to a wide range of customers in Singapore.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-com-license-singapore/">Crypto.com Secures License from Monetary Authority of Singapore as Payment Institution</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-com-license-singapore/">Crypto.com Secures License from Monetary Authority of Singapore as Payment Institution</a></p>
<p>In a major development, Crypto.com announced that it has secured the license of a Major Payment Institution (MPI) from the Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS) for offering Digital Payment Token (DPT) services in the region.</p>
<p>Previously, Crypto.com received its in-principle approval from the MAS last year in June 2022. Having secured the license recently, the platform will be able to offer its DPT services to a wide range of customers in Singapore. Speaking on the development, Kris Marszalek, CEO of Crypto.com <a href="https://crypto.com/company-news/crypto-com-obtains-major-payment-institution-licence-from-monetary-authority-of-singapore" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“The Monetary Authority of Singapore is recognized globally as a regulator that ensures responsible innovation of the digital assets sector. We are proud to receive the licence from a regulator that prioritizes consumer protection, safety, and security. We look forward to continuing to collaborate with MAS and leading at the forefront of crypto in our home market of Singapore.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Chin Tah Ang, General Manager, Singapore of Crypto.com, highlighted Singapore as a thriving hub for blockchain and fintech innovation. He emphasized their commitment to the Web3 community in Singapore, exemplified by obtaining the Major Payment Institution (MPI) license.</p>
<p>Founded in 2016, popular crypto exchange Crypto.com serves more than 80 million customers worldwide and is one of the leading players in regulatory compliance, security, and privacy.</p>
<h2>Crypto.com &#8211; New Developments</h2>
<p>Singapore-based cryptocurrency exchange Crypto.com has <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-com-payment-feature-us/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">introduced</a> a new feature in its mobile app, enabling users in the United States to utilize over 30 cryptocurrencies, including CRO, BTC, ETH, and USDT, for payments at more than 150 renowned companies.</p>
<p>Users can earn up to 10% in Pay Rewards, paid in CRO, with a monthly rewards limit of $100. The feature includes a one-time-use card that can be used at notable brands like Apple, Nike, Walmart, Ray-Ban, and GameStop.</p>
<p>At present, the payment feature is exclusively accessible to users situated in the United States. However, Crypto.com has expressed their intentions to expand its availability to other markets in the near future, without disclosing specific details regarding the next country.</p>
<p>The company emphasizes that it retains the right to make changes to this offer, clarifying that there is no formal partnership between Crypto.com and the participating brands involved in this promotion.</p>
<p>Last month in May 2023, Crypto.com also <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-com-new-tokens-ai-assistant/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">announced</a> support for new tokens on the platform.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-rolls-out-ai-chatgpt-tongyi-qianwen/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-com-license-singapore/">Crypto.com Secures License from Monetary Authority of Singapore as Payment Institution</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-com-license-singapore/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alibaba Rolls Out Its AI ChatGPT Rival Tongyi Qianwen for Public Testing</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-rolls-out-ai-chatgpt-tongyi-qianwen/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-rolls-out-ai-chatgpt-tongyi-qianwen/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 12:47:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ai]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alibaba]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[baidu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chatgpt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ernie]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=257377</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-rolls-out-ai-chatgpt-tongyi-qianwen/">Alibaba Rolls Out Its AI ChatGPT Rival Tongyi Qianwen for Public Testing</a></p>
<p>Public testing of Alibaba's Tongyi Qianwen is now underway in China as the company hopes to finetune the AI and fully release it later.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-rolls-out-ai-chatgpt-tongyi-qianwen/">Alibaba Rolls Out Its AI ChatGPT Rival Tongyi Qianwen for Public Testing</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-rolls-out-ai-chatgpt-tongyi-qianwen/">Alibaba Rolls Out Its AI ChatGPT Rival Tongyi Qianwen for Public Testing</a></p>
<p>Alibaba has started rolling out <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-chatgpt-rival-tongyi-qianwen/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tongyi Qianwen</a>, an artificial intelligence model application that will rival OpenAI’s ChatGPT. Tongyi Qianwen is a large language model (LLM) Alibaba intends to integrate with a digital assistant named Tongyi Tingwu.</p>
<p>According to Alibaba, Tongyi Tingwu is an AI assistant offering users a wide range of services, including multimedia content analysis. Alibaba also says Tongyi Tingwu will let users generate a text summary of uploaded audio or video content.</p>
<p>Alibaba Cloud, a major <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/alibaba-group/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Alibaba Group Holdings Ltd</a> (HKG: 9988) is in charge of <a href="https://www.alibabagroup.com/en-US/document-1582482069362049024" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Tongyi Qianwen</a> and has released the ChatGPT rival for public testing. Alibaba says it will initially integrate the LLM with DingTalk, Alibaba’s enterprise communication and collaboration platform.</p>
<p>In a press release, Alibaba specified that simplifying multimedia content is now necessary because of the high volume of this content available every day. Alibaba Cloud Intelligence CTO Jingren Zhou <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/06/01/alibaba-rolls-out-chatgpt-style-tech-as-china-ai-race-heats-up.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“We live at a time when a growing amount of video and audio content is being consumed in various formats every day. In line with this, Tongyi Tingwu aims to use the large language model to facilitate faster and better comprehension and easier sharing of multimedia content.”</p></blockquote>
<p>“Tongyi Qianwen” is traceable to Chinese Confucian philosopher Mencius, and translates to “Truth from a Thousand Questions”.</p>
<h2>Alibaba will Continue to Finetune Tongyi Qianwen</h2>
<p>Alibaba will continue fixing its AI to improve its services and perform better than the competition. For instance, Alibaba plans that later this year, Tongyi Qianwen will provide real-time multimedia content translation between Chinese and English. The company will release this feature as a plugin on Google Chrome. In addition, CNBC has referenced an Alibaba spokesperson confirming that the company will build specific products tailored to corporate cloud customers.</p>
<p>The Chinese conglomerate hopes that the public testing will help advance AI and feed it more information. Alibaba already has a large user base across several services, including e-commerce platforms Alibaba.com and Taobao. Alibaba wants users to report their findings as they continue to improve AI.</p>
<h2>Artificial Intelligence Services in China</h2>
<p>Since ChatGPT launched late last year, several companies have joined the race to create the first major and widely-accepted rival. While the race may not see a significant victor anytime soon, some of the world’s largest tech companies are working tirelessly.</p>
<p>In China, multinational tech giant Baidu <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/baidu-chatgpt-ernie-bot/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">unveiled</a> its own AI chatbot called the ERNIE Bot. Although Ernie is not fully ready, Baidu revealed ERNIE to interested partners in response to demand. Baidu’s bot uses its own ERNIE LLM, set to serve more than 650 companies that have already signed up. Baidu also says that over 120,000 companies have expressed interest in ERNIE, which is usable for several functions, such as in self-driving cars and smart devices. Recently, Baidu CEO Robin Li said on a call with analysts that the company is awaiting regulatory approval.</p>
<p>ERNIE is an acronym for Enhanced Representation through Knowledge Integration.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tether-usdt-market-cap-ath/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-rolls-out-ai-chatgpt-tongyi-qianwen/">Alibaba Rolls Out Its AI ChatGPT Rival Tongyi Qianwen for Public Testing</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-rolls-out-ai-chatgpt-tongyi-qianwen/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tether (USDT) Hit New Market Cap ATH as Adoption Grows</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tether-usdt-market-cap-ath/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tether-usdt-market-cap-ath/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 12:42:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bsc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[matic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[paolo ardoino]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[polygon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sol]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[solana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tron]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[trx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[usdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=257365</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tether-usdt-market-cap-ath/">Tether (USDT) Hit New Market Cap ATH as Adoption Grows</a></p>
<p>USDT has become the most traded stablecoin, especially after the de-pegging of Circle's USD Coin (USDC) earlier this year. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tether-usdt-market-cap-ath/">Tether (USDT) Hit New Market Cap ATH as Adoption Grows</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tether-usdt-market-cap-ath/">Tether (USDT) Hit New Market Cap ATH as Adoption Grows</a></p>
<p>United States-dollar-backed stablecoin Tether (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/tether/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">USDT</a>) has <a href="https://tether.to/en/tether-usdt-reaches-all-time-high-surpasses-previous-market-cap-high-of-832b/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">hit</a> an all-time high in its market capitalization based on existing market data.</p>
<p>The new milestone has helped Tether exceed its previously set all-time high of $83.2 billion which was announced back in May 2022. USDT is currently the third largest cryptocurrency by market cap which at the time of writing is pegged at $83.23 billion. According to Tether&#8217;s Chief Technology Officer (CTO) Paolo Ardoino, this outstanding jump in market cap is a clear indication that people are interested in having access to financial freedom.</p>
<p>When they eventually get this access, they will make use of it, Paolo explained. In his opinion, Tether tokens are a stable alternative for unbanked individuals, at the same time, it also assists people from emerging markets to maintain their buying power even in the face of devaluation of their national currency.</p>
<p>&#8220;Between our battle-tested resilience in the face of market volatility and our industry-leading transparency practices, Tether has proven that it can be trusted, and customers are responding in kind. We are eager to continue maintaining our laser focus on emerging markets and will not waiver in our efforts to expand access to financial freedom globally,” Paolo added.</p>
<h2>Tether (USDT) Popularity Intensifies amidst USDC Depeg</h2>
<p>In recent times, USDT has become the most traded stablecoin, especially after the de-pegging of Circle&#8217;s USD Coin (USDC) earlier this year.</p>
<p>The dollar-pegged stablecoin runs on more than 10 blockchains including Ethereum (ETH), Binance Smart Chain (BSC), <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/solana/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Solana</a> (SOL), <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/matic-network/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Polygon</a> (MATIC), and Tron (TRX). Compared to the leading cryptocurrency Bitcoin (BTC) which has a daily traded volume of around $16.5 billion, Tether has over $25.57 billion.</p>
<p>Tether&#8217;s endearment to many entities <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tether-usdt-prefered-stablecoin-banking-crisis/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">intensified</a> following the crisis in the United States banking system which involved the now-defunct Silvergate Bank, Silicon Valley Bank, and Signature Bank. In their search for alternatives, investors discovered that self-custody through stablecoins was preferable. That marked the beginning of a revolution for USDT as its market cap began to recover exponentially from $65 billion which it had been relegated to due to the FTX implosion.</p>
<p>Explicitly, the first quarter report of Tether (USDT) showed that its circulation had <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tether-strong-q1-btc-gold/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">skyrocketed</a> by about 20%. As of March 31st, 2023, the stablecoin issuer had total reserve assets of around $81.8 billion with the majority of those being the US Treasury Bills. When the Q1 report was released, Ardoino said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Looking ahead to Q2, we have an extremely positive outlook and remain committed to transparency, which is why we have introduced new categories in the reserves’ breakdown in our quarterly report to provide even greater transparency to our users.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Fast forward to this day, Tether has <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tether-usdt-stablecoin-market-usdc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">overtaken</a> the entire stablecoin market and has gained more users while still remaining pegged to the US dollar. In a new move, the company has declared plans to <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/usdt-tether-bitcoin-purchase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">allocate</a> up to 15% of its net realized operating profits toward purchasing Bitcoin as a reserve currency.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gemini-operational-license-uae/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tether-usdt-market-cap-ath/">Tether (USDT) Hit New Market Cap ATH as Adoption Grows</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tether-usdt-market-cap-ath/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Exchange Gemini Seeks Operational License in UAE After European Expansion</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/gemini-operational-license-uae/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/gemini-operational-license-uae/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[staff writer]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 12:26:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cameron winklevoss]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gemini]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tyler winklevoss]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vasp]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=257363</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gemini-operational-license-uae/">Crypto Exchange Gemini Seeks Operational License in UAE After European Expansion</a></p>
<p>Gemini is looking to expand its business offerings across the UAE as regulators begin to accept applications for VASP licensing. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gemini-operational-license-uae/">Crypto Exchange Gemini Seeks Operational License in UAE After European Expansion</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gemini-operational-license-uae/">Crypto Exchange Gemini Seeks Operational License in UAE After European Expansion</a></p>
<p>Leading cryptocurrency exchange <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/gemini/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Gemini</a> has announced its plans to secure a license in the United Arab Emirates (UAE) to tap into the surging interest in digital assets in the region. The move aligns with the company&#8217;s commitment to catering to the evolving needs of investors and its plans to strengthen its position in the global crypto market.</p>
<p>In a <a href="https://www.gemini.com/blog/gemini-announces-plans-for-uae-crypto-license" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">blog post</a> published on May 31, the American-based exchange, owned by the billionaire twins <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/cameron-winklevoss/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Cameron</a> and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/tyler-winklevoss/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tyler Winklevoss</a>, said it would soon begin the application process. If approved, the company will join other exchanges, such as Binance, Huobi Global, CryptoCom, Kraken, and Bybit which have already received the green light from the appropriate authorities to offer their services in UAE legally.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">1/ We’re coming to the UAE! 🇦🇪</p>
<p>We’re thrilled to announce that Gemini will soon begin the process of acquiring a crypto license to serve customers based in the United Arab Emirates (UAE). <a href="https://t.co/Ycdj9RxMbE">pic.twitter.com/Ycdj9RxMbE</a></p>
<p>— Gemini (@Gemini) <a href="https://twitter.com/Gemini/status/1664107397445550081?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 1, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2>US Regulatory Uncertainties Drive Gemini to Pursue License in UAE</h2>
<p>Gemini cited the growing interest in virtual assets as one of the driving forces behind its decision to expand its regional operations. In addition, the company also highlighted its fruitful discussions with financial regulatory bodies as part of its reasons. The company&#8217;s co-founder and CEO, Tyler Winklevoss, told local news media, The National, that the regulatory uncertainties in America also partly influenced the decision to pursue a license in UAE.</p>
<p>The exchange said it has met with market watchdogs in UAE to learn more about their regulatory requirements and how to better service its customers in the region.</p>
<p>&#8220;This week, as the second leg of Gemini&#8217;s global odyssey tour, we have met with stakeholders throughout the region to learn more about local regulatory requirements and the needs of UAE crypto investors so that we can better serve this rapidly growing and vibrant crypto community,&#8221; Gemini said.</p>
<p>The latest expansion plans come after the exchange <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gemini-europe-headquarters-dublin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">received</a> authorization from the Republic of Ireland to offer its products and services in the country. The firm also intends to open a European headquarters in Dublin.</p>
<h2>UAE Open to Accept License Applications</h2>
<p>Gemini&#8217;s plan to acquire an operating license in the UAE follows a recent <a href="https://www.sca.gov.ae/ar/media-center/news/17/4/2023/sca-announces-the-start-of-receiving-applications-for-licensing-virtual-asset-services.aspx" target="_blank" rel="noopener">announcement</a> from the federal securities regulator. In April, the Securities and Commodities Authority (SCA) revealed that it had started accepting applications from companies seeking authorization from the government to operate in the region.</p>
<p>The UAE requires all corporate entities wishing to provide digital asset services to residents in the area to pass through the SCA for licensing.</p>
<p>The new rule is part of a regulatory framework established by the UAE Council Ministers last December in an attempt to regulate the use of crypto assets as well as those providing such services to people.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/blackrock-ceo-us-debt-ceiling-bitcoin/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gemini-operational-license-uae/">Crypto Exchange Gemini Seeks Operational License in UAE After European Expansion</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/gemini-operational-license-uae/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Blackrock CEO Says US ‘Debt Ceiling Drama’ Is Bad for Dollar, Bitcoin May Benefit</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/blackrock-ceo-us-debt-ceiling-bitcoin/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/blackrock-ceo-us-debt-ceiling-bitcoin/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 12:22:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Currencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blackrock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[deutsche bank]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=257344</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/blackrock-ceo-us-debt-ceiling-bitcoin/">Blackrock CEO Says US ‘Debt Ceiling Drama’ Is Bad for Dollar, Bitcoin May Benefit</a></p>
<p>Laurence Fink described the debt ceiling deliberations as bad for the dollar as the Blackrock CEO predicts further interest rate hikes.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/blackrock-ceo-us-debt-ceiling-bitcoin/">Blackrock CEO Says US ‘Debt Ceiling Drama’ Is Bad for Dollar, Bitcoin May Benefit</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/blackrock-ceo-us-debt-ceiling-bitcoin/">Blackrock CEO Says US ‘Debt Ceiling Drama’ Is Bad for Dollar, Bitcoin May Benefit</a></p>
<p>The CEO of investment management company <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/blackrock/">Blackrock</a> is not excited about the ongoing attempt to raise the US debt ceiling. CEO Laurence Fink recently spoke about the “drama” surrounding the debt ceiling increase while discussing inflation and other issues. Observers believe the ongoing situation may turn out bullish for Bitcoin.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/blackrocks-ceo-says-inflation-remains-sticky-expects-more-rate-hikes-2023-05-31/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Speaking</a> at a financial services conference organized by <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/deutsche-bank/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Deutsche Bank</a>, Fink rightfully predicted on Wednesday that there would be a resolution to the debt ceiling debate. However, the CEO noted that raising the debt ceiling is bad because it reduces global trust in the dollar. Finks said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“I believe we’ll have a resolution, … but let’s be clear, the United States is jeopardizing its reserve currency status.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Fink suggested that the US dollar has remained the leading reserve for a while now. However, he mentioned that the continuous conversations about raising the country’s debt ceiling and the possibility of default are factors that can destabilize the dollar:</p>
<blockquote><p>“We are eroding some of that trust, which in the long run we need to rectify and rebuild.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>Blackrock CEO Worries about Debt Ceiling and Inflation but Downplays Recession</h2>
<p>Speaking at the conference, FInk also discussed inflation and interest rates. Although the US Federal Reserve has raised interest rates at least 10 times since last year, Fink expects two more. According to him, the Fed has to be more observant even though the market is very resilient. However, he believes there will be more increases in interest rates because he doesn’t see any evidence of inflation reducing.</p>
<p>Regardless, Fink is generally bullish on the economy. He thinks the likelihood of a recession in the US is low. According to him, if a recession happens, it may not be ugly.</p>
<h2>Could the Increase in the US Debt Ceiling be Good for Bitcoin?</h2>
<p>The discussions around inflation and the US debt ceiling bring Bitcoin back into the light. The largest cryptocurrency by market cap, Bitcoin is the first choice for many enthusiasts and members of the crypto community looking for a hedge against inflation. Since Bitcoin is independent of government control, investors have and may continue to use it to hedge against uncertain monetary policies.</p>
<p>eToro markets analyst Josh Gilbert believes that Bitcoin’s finite supply and independence showcase the king coin’s utility, especially considering the banking crisis and the debt ceiling deal. However, he says investors should not consider the ongoing problems as catalysts for a <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> spike.</p>
<p>Speaking to Cointelegraph, Gilbert said the general uncertainty in the financial climate has caused “more fear than optimism”. He also believes that these events will cause liquidity issues.</p>
<p>Fineqia International research analyst corroborates Gilbert, as he believes that investor fears in reaction to the debt ceiling deal tanked Bitcoin’s price. According to CoinMarketCap data, Bitcoin is trading at $26,913 after climbing nearly 2.5% over the last 7 days.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/getyourguide-investment-ai/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/blackrock-ceo-us-debt-ceiling-bitcoin/">Blackrock CEO Says US ‘Debt Ceiling Drama’ Is Bad for Dollar, Bitcoin May Benefit</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/blackrock-ceo-us-debt-ceiling-bitcoin/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>GetYourGuide Raises $194M at $2B Valuation, Plans Investment in AI</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/getyourguide-investment-ai/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/getyourguide-investment-ai/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 12:18:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ai]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[GetYourGuide]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tripadvisor]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=257337</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/getyourguide-investment-ai/">GetYourGuide Raises $194M at $2B Valuation, Plans Investment in AI</a></p>
<p>According to GetYourGuide, the funds raised will be used to invest in AI including the integration of Large Language Models (LLMs) into its platform.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/getyourguide-investment-ai/">GetYourGuide Raises $194M at $2B Valuation, Plans Investment in AI</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/getyourguide-investment-ai/">GetYourGuide Raises $194M at $2B Valuation, Plans Investment in AI</a></p>
<p>German online travel experience service provider GetYourGuide has announced it has raised the sum of $194 million from both new and old investors as it looks to double down on growing demand for travel experiences and the new buzz in Artificial Intelligence (AI). As <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/06/01/travel-firm-getyourguide-raises-194-million-at-2-billion-valuation.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reported</a> by CNBC, the company, the funding was pulled in two major ways, equity and debt.</p>
<p>The equity part of the funding saw the firm pull $85 million from investors led by US asset management firm Blue Pool Capital. Other participants in the equity funding include KKR and Temasek, both of whom already have stakes in the company.</p>
<p>GetYourGuide is best described as an investor&#8217;s favorite as the total funding into the company is now pegged at a little over $1 billion. According to sources close to the financing, the company is now valued at $2 billion, up from the $1.4 billion it disclosed not long ago. The debt part of the funding was led by UniCredit and also backed by <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/bnp-paribas/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BNP Paribas SA</a> (EPA: BNP), Citibank, and KfW.</p>
<p>GetYourGuide occupies a very special niche in the travel industry, competing with top firms like TripAdvisor. Rather than sell hotel bookings and flight schedules like its competitors, GetYourGuide is more focused on selling experiences, creating a unique market offering that others are typically not focused on.</p>
<p>Over the past couple of years, GetYourGuide has improved on its offerings, and among the services and experiences it has for its users include the “Originals” with examples including the opportunity to turn on the lights of the Sistine Chapel in the Apostolic Palace, the official residence of the Pope in Vatican City, and visit the Museum of Modern Art in New York an hour before regular opening hours.</p>
<h2>GetYourGuide Investment Use Case: AI and Expansion</h2>
<p>According to GetYourGuide, the funds raised will be used to invest in AI including the integration of Large Language Models (LLMs) into its platform to better customize user experiences. The funding will also be used to finance its expansion plans into the United States.</p>
<p>The company hopes its projected plans for growth and the funding will help it continue on its growth path post-COVID-19 pandemic. Johannes Reck, the company’s CEO recalled the firm plunged to its absolute bottom during the pandemic where it made no remarkable revenue for several quarters.</p>
<p>“We were severely depressed in the pandemic,” Reck told CNBC. “The travel industry was very hard hit within the travel industry. GetYourGuide was probably one of the worst affected. Experiences were shut down. People didn’t go out.”</p>
<p>He said the company started seeing recovery when the Omicron variant was tagged as one that is not as deadly as envisaged. The company recorded a 2x growth in its sales volume in 2022 and it quadrupled its first quarter 2023 volume when compared with that of 2019.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nordstrom-first-quarter-sales/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/getyourguide-investment-ai/">GetYourGuide Raises $194M at $2B Valuation, Plans Investment in AI</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/getyourguide-investment-ai/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4061 metric#misses=41 metric#hit-ratio=99.0 metric#bytes=990638 metric#prefetches=194 metric#store-reads=20 metric#store-writes=2 metric#store-hits=201 metric#store-misses=2 metric#sql-queries=34 metric#ms-total=91.87 metric#ms-cache=4.69 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.2233 metric#ms-cache-ratio=5.1 -->