<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>CoinGape</title>
	<atom:link href="https://coingape.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coingape.com/</link>
	<description>CoinGape - 24*7 Crypto Updates</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 02:06:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/14183030/cropped-CoinGape_logo-32x32.png</url>
	<title>CoinGape</title>
	<link>https://coingape.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>1500 Coinbase Users May Be Granted Amicus Curiae In SEC Lawsuit</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/coinbase-lawsuit-amicus-curiae-crypto-news-xrp/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Anvesh Reddy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 02:06:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin(BTC) News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Xrp Lawsuit]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=151905</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto Market News: What started as a check of interest is likely building up into potentially an Amicus Curiae status granted to Coinbase users in the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) lawsuit. John Deaton, the lawyer representing over 76,000 XRP token holders in the SEC lawsuit, had last week asked if Coinbase and Binance <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/coinbase-lawsuit-amicus-curiae-crypto-news-xrp/" title="1500 Coinbase Users May Be Granted Amicus Curiae In SEC Lawsuit"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/coinbase-lawsuit-amicus-curiae-crypto-news-xrp/">1500 Coinbase Users May Be Granted Amicus Curiae In SEC Lawsuit</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/07204038/coinbase-sec.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Coinbase lawsuit amicus curiae Crypto News XRP" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" /><p><strong>Crypto Market News</strong>: What started as a check of interest is likely building up into potentially an Amicus Curiae status granted to Coinbase users in the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) lawsuit. John Deaton, the lawyer representing over 76,000 XRP token holders in the SEC lawsuit, had last week <a href="https://coingape.com/coinbase-binance-lawsuit-sec-amicus-crypto-news/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">asked</a> if Coinbase and Binance users could unite into a group to fight for themselves. This could go on to be very important development in the history of <a href="https://coingape.com/markets/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">crypto market</a> as the two lawsuits against the crypto exchanges could drag on for a long period. Coinbase and Binance have recently been involved in separate SEC lawsuits over alleged violation of the securities laws.</p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/will-mark-cuban-speak-on-crypto-before-us-senate" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>Will Mark Cuban Speak On Crypto Before US Senate?</strong></a></p>
<p>In the <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/xrp-lawsuit/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ripple Vs SEC lawsuit</a>, as many as 16 companies filed an amicus curiae. The XRP community is awaiting the all important Summary Judgement from Judge Analisa Torres.</p>
<h2>Coinbase Lawsuit Amicus Curiae: More Users To Join?</h2>
<p>The main agenda behind attempting to gain amicus status is to help make user voices heard while the <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/crypto-exchange-2/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">crypto exchange</a> is defending itself in the lawsuit. Since asking for user details for amicus curiae on June 9, Deaton managed to unite around 1,500 users so far in the Coinbase lawsuit. The attorney <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/JohnEDeaton1/status/1669357227352940552" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reiterated</a>,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;This isn’t about helping Coinbase. It’s about speaking up if you believe these regulators aren’t protecting you or you don’t want their type of protection.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Earlier, the Alabama Securities and Exchange Commission (ASC) and authorities of ten other US States charged Coinbase for alleged violation of securities laws. The charges also included alleged operation of staking programs in these states without authoization. Hence, the views of Coinbase users from these states could also be helpful.</p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/mark-cuban-predicts-99-of-tokens-will-go-broke-survivors-will-be-game-changers" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>Mark Cuban Predicts 99% of Tokens will Go Broke, Survivors Will be Game Changers</strong></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/coinbase-lawsuit-amicus-curiae-crypto-news-xrp/">1500 Coinbase Users May Be Granted Amicus Curiae In SEC Lawsuit</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/07204038/coinbase-sec.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Will Mark Cuban Speak On Crypto Before US Senate?</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/will-mark-cuban-speak-on-crypto-before-us-senate/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Anvesh Reddy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 19:11:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin(BTC) News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mark Cuban]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=151901</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto Market News: The unprecedented enforcement actions on crypto businesses in the United States is begging the question as to whether there is need for high level debates between lawmakers and industry experts. That the two of the world’s top crypto exchanges have been targeted in back to back lawsuits by the U.S. Securities and <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/will-mark-cuban-speak-on-crypto-before-us-senate/" title="Will Mark Cuban Speak On Crypto Before US Senate?"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/will-mark-cuban-speak-on-crypto-before-us-senate/">Will Mark Cuban Speak On Crypto Before US Senate?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="2000" height="1330" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/06121535/Mark-Cuban-ETH-2.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Mark Cuban crypto" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" /><p><strong>Crypto Market News</strong>: The unprecedented enforcement actions on crypto businesses in the United States is begging the question as to whether there is need for high level debates between lawmakers and industry experts. That the two of the world’s top <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/crypto-exchange-2/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">crypto exchanges</a> have been targeted in back to back lawsuits by the U.S. Securities and Exchanges Commission shook the crypto market. In this context, John Deaton, the attorney representing XRP holders in the SEC lawsuit, is recommending that Shark Tank investor Mark Cuban should speak on the innovative side of crypto and blockchain before the Senate and House Banking and Financial Services Committees.</p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/european-central-bank-ecb-repeats-interest-rate-decision-bitcoin-price-sees-relief/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>European Central Bank (ECB) Repeats Interest Rate Decision, Bitcoin Price Sees Relief</strong></a></p>
<p>Cuban, however, thinks overhyping crypto also has been an equally big problem as the likes of SEC targeting the industry. He believes it’s time for the Congress to step in to resolve the regulatory deadlock. Overall, attracting political action is key in the near term, as we head to the election year in the United States, where it is becoming increasingly clear that crypto could well become a massive election issue.</p>
<h2>Mark Cuban Before Senate and House Committees</h2>
<p>The Shark Tank investor believes there is need for creating exemptions for the <a href="https://coingape.com/markets/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">crypto market</a>, for it to go mainstream and contribute to the economy. He shared the example of how the Congress stepped in to make exemptions for mainstream financial markets so that it continues to grow. Hence, Mark Cuban’s appearance before the Senate and House Committees would make it a compelling case for crypto’s future prospects. He <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/mcuban/status/1669338225197072387" target="_blank" rel="noopener">explained</a>,</p>
<blockquote><p>“It’s time for Congress to respond again and modify the exemptions available to this technology (crypto) so that registration is obvious and the path for exchanges are doable in a way that protects investors and enables the industry to grow. They are not mutually exclusive.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Interestingly, Cuban predicted that a majority of crypto market companies would be nonexistent in the coming future, just as many in the technology sector.</p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/ripple-to-help-colombia-central-bank-explore-cbdc-use-cases" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>Ripple to Help Colombia’s Central Bank Explore CBDC Use Cases</strong></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/will-mark-cuban-speak-on-crypto-before-us-senate/">Will Mark Cuban Speak On Crypto Before US Senate?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/06121535/Mark-Cuban-ETH-2.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tether (USDT) Depeg FUD May Just be Starting, Here&#8217;s Why</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/tether-usdt-depeg-fud-may-just-be-starting-heres-why/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Godfrey Benjamin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 18:56:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CoinDesk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NYAG]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=151904</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The digital currency ecosystem was riled today following the depegging of the industry’s largest stablecoin, Tether (USDT). The depegging, which has seen the stablecoin plunge to $0.9991 at the time of writing, was attributed to the loan saga on the DeFi platform Curve. New details are, however, emerging with Tether Holdings Ltd issuing a statement <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/tether-usdt-depeg-fud-may-just-be-starting-heres-why/" title="Tether (USDT) Depeg FUD May Just be Starting, Here&#8217;s Why"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/tether-usdt-depeg-fud-may-just-be-starting-heres-why/">Tether (USDT) Depeg FUD May Just be Starting, Here&#8217;s Why</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1600" height="898" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/24234511/tether-coin-crypto-currency-themed-260nw-1968955498.webp" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" /><p><span style="font-weight: 400">The digital currency ecosystem was riled today following the depegging of the industry’s largest stablecoin, Tether (USDT). The depegging, which has seen the stablecoin plunge to $0.9991 at the time of writing, was </span><a href="https://coingape.com/tether-usdt-depegs-after-curve-aave-loan-saga-spooks-crypto-market/"><span style="font-weight: 400">attributed</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> to the loan saga on the DeFi platform Curve. New details are, however, emerging with Tether Holdings Ltd issuing a statement detailing new revelations about the entire ordeal.</span></p>
<h2><b>Tether’s Major Concern</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">As the firm noted, the Office of the New York Attorney General (NYAG) provided materials relating to the first of its quarterly reports to Coindesk who had requested them shortly after Tether and NYAG reached their settlement agreement in 2021.</span></p>
<p><a rel='nofollow'  href="https://tether.to/en/tether-on-FOIL-and-continued-commitment-to-transparency/" rel="nofollow"><span style="font-weight: 400">According</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> to Tether, the documents were released because it dropped its opposition to Coindesk. The stablecoin issuer said it initiated the opposition proceedings in the first place “to prevent the use of sensitive commercial information that could potentially be exploited by malicious actors.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Tether revealed that some of the documents shared with Coindesk include the statements from Tether’s banks showing the full existence of the company’s reserves, how the firm has been approaching its asset management obligations and short-term investments and diversification.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In what appears as a proactive move, Tether said there has been a lot of detraction with respect to the content of the documents and it wishes to state that the financial transactions do not reflect the current realities of the firm. The stablecoin issuer is calling on Coindesk not to reveal any past or current information about its customers despite not counting on the news outlet to adhere to fair coverage.</span></p>
<h2><b>Recalling Alameda Research Saga</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Coindesk has played a very crucial role in the crypto ecosystem as it relates to the uncovering of the most hidden financial details on major companies in the industry. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Back in November last year, the news outlet reported on the financial and transactional impropriety of Alameda Research, the trading firm founded by FTX co-founder, Sam Bankman-Fried. The revelations at the time led to the </span><a href="https://coingape.com/breaking-binance-to-dump-ftx-ftt-token-holdings/"><span style="font-weight: 400">collapse</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> of FTX and a similar fear appears to be brewing in the industry as it concerns Tether.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Though Tether has been controversial as it faces FUD all around, the firm has </span><a href="https://coingape.com/tether-q1-profit-tops-1-5b-as-market-recovers/"><span style="font-weight: 400">survived</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> most of its attacks. The question now remains whether or not it will survive the details that the released documents may uncover. Should the details be controversial, the FUD may just be starting.</span></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/tether-usdt-depeg-fud-may-just-be-starting-heres-why/">Tether (USDT) Depeg FUD May Just be Starting, Here&#8217;s Why</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/24234511/tether-coin-crypto-currency-themed-260nw-1968955498.webp" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mark Cuban Predicts 99% of Tokens will Go Broke, Survivors Will be Game Changers</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/mark-cuban-predicts-99-of-tokens-will-go-broke-survivors-will-be-game-changers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Godfrey Benjamin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 17:37:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mark Cuban]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=151903</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In a recent Twitter conversation with former Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) official John Reed Stark, American businessman and philanthropist Mark Cuban predicted that 90% of blockchain companies will go broke. In the same vein, he also predicted that 99% of tokens will do the same, but that those who get to survive will turn <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/mark-cuban-predicts-99-of-tokens-will-go-broke-survivors-will-be-game-changers/" title="Mark Cuban Predicts 99% of Tokens will Go Broke, Survivors Will be Game Changers"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/mark-cuban-predicts-99-of-tokens-will-go-broke-survivors-will-be-game-changers/">Mark Cuban Predicts 99% of Tokens will Go Broke, Survivors Will be Game Changers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1320" height="742" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/06233444/MW-HE188_cuban__ZG_20190219225226.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="mark cuban jim cramer" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" /><p><span style="font-weight: 400">In a recent Twitter conversation with former Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) official John Reed Stark, American businessman and philanthropist Mark Cuban </span><a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/mcuban/status/1669338225197072387?s=20"><span style="font-weight: 400">predicted</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> that 90% of blockchain companies will go broke. In the same vein, he also predicted that 99% of tokens will do the same, but that those who get to survive will turn out to be &#8220;game changers&#8221; in the tech world. </span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Now we are talking tech.  You are in my space John.  I don’t comment. I do.  My entire career has been people telling me why the companies I started were ridiculous and not needed.  Until they found themselves using them. </p>
<p>Smart contracts are about 6 years old.  Maybe the name… <a href="https://t.co/da2zEvjtHU">https://t.co/da2zEvjtHU</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Mark Cuban (@mcuban) <a href="https://twitter.com/mcuban/status/1669338225197072387?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 15, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Cuban compared his prediction to the collapse of early internet companies. The conversation between Mark and John Reed Stark stems from blockchain and regulation litigation, however, it all started after the ex-SEC official shared a post on the </span><a href="https://coingape.com/breaking-us-sec-sues-crypto-giant-binance-and-ceo-cz/"><span style="font-weight: 400">Binance/SEC</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> court hearing. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">United States District Judge Amy Berman Jackson had </span><a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/JohnReedStark/status/1668971373249658882"><span style="font-weight: 400">explained</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> to both the leading digital asset service provider and the regulator to try and work out an agreement without her interference. She did not want to directly rule on the </span><a href="https://coingape.com/who-will-win-us-sec-or-crypto-giant-binance/"><span style="font-weight: 400">SEC&#8217;s motion</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> for a temporary restraining order which may likely lead to the freezing of Binance U.S assets. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In response to Stark&#8217;s tweet, a cryptocurrency enthusiast identified as @_someone_els suggested that Judge Jackson may not have gotten a clear definition of what crypto assets qualify as securities. But, Stark was quick to correct the notion, pointing the individual to an earlier tweet he posted. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Instantly, Cuban called the former SEC official&#8217;s attention to the fact that he may have misread the impact of what Judge Jackson said.</span></p>
<h2><b>Mark Cuban Reiterates His Pro-Crypto Stance</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Cuban began his argument by first establishing the fact that not all crypto businesses that have tokens or considering using one, are big enterprises. Sadly, there is a general assumption that they all are, per Cuban&#8217;s statement. He highlighted a certain time when someone from a small company had approached the SEC for clarification and guidance in registration. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The response from the SEC was “Here are some cases to review, get a lawyer to help you.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Their conversation went in from there to the point where Stark stated that blockchain can never triumph over traditional databases. However, Cuban was not having it, he emphasized that no matter who gets kicked out in the long run, tech always has a way of providing game-changers. In conclusion, the </span><a href="https://coingape.com/mark-cuban-more-bullish-on-dogecoin-than-this-cryptocurrency/"><span style="font-weight: 400">Dogecoin advocate</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> said,</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">&#8220;While I think many of your criticisms of crypto are very valid, they don&#8217;t invalidate the impact the industry can have on the economy.&#8221;</span></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/mark-cuban-predicts-99-of-tokens-will-go-broke-survivors-will-be-game-changers/">Mark Cuban Predicts 99% of Tokens will Go Broke, Survivors Will be Game Changers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/06233444/MW-HE188_cuban__ZG_20190219225226.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Largest XRP Ledger (XRPL) Account Deletions Recorded, What&#8217;s Happening?</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/largest-xrpl-account-deletions-recorded-whats-happening/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Godfrey Benjamin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 16:07:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[poloniex]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPL]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=151898</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the ever-evolving landscape of crypto and blockchain technology, the XRP Ledger (XRPL) has been a prominent player since its inception.  However, market observers have highlighted a surprising trend of significant XRPL account deletions, constituting one of the largest spikes in its history. This is the biggest spike in account deletions registered till date. pic.twitter.com/TK309hjpfk <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/largest-xrpl-account-deletions-recorded-whats-happening/" title="Largest XRP Ledger (XRPL) Account Deletions Recorded, What&#8217;s Happening?"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/largest-xrpl-account-deletions-recorded-whats-happening/">Largest XRP Ledger (XRPL) Account Deletions Recorded, What&#8217;s Happening?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="630" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/15213704/XRPL.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" /><p><span style="font-weight: 400">In the ever-evolving landscape of crypto and blockchain technology, the XRP Ledger (XRPL) has been a prominent player since its inception. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">However, market observers have </span><a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/xrpscan/status/1669279843593203712" rel="nofollow"><span style="font-weight: 400">highlighted</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> a surprising trend of significant XRPL account deletions, constituting one of the largest spikes in its history. </span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">This is the biggest spike in account deletions registered till date. <a href="https://t.co/TK309hjpfk">pic.twitter.com/TK309hjpfk</a></p>
<p>&mdash; XRPScan (@xrpscan) <a href="https://twitter.com/xrpscan/status/1669279843593203712?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 15, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">T</span><span style="font-weight: 400">his development has sparked curiosity and raised questions about the underlying reasons and potential implications. </span><span style="font-weight: 400">Notably, the spike has been primarily attributed to </span><a rel='nofollow'  href="http://www.coingape.com/tag/poloniex/" rel="nofollow"><span style="font-weight: 400">Poloniex</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">, a well-known crypto exchange, which reportedly deleted around 15,000 old XRP accounts, resulting in the recovery of approximately 275,000 XRP tokens. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Moreover, as the process continues, the number of recovered tokens is increasing, accompanied by more than 30,000 XRP burned in fees. Thomas Silkjær, the head of analytics and compliance at the XRP Ledger Foundation has highlighted this growing trend.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">It is worth noting that the news comes shortly after Poloniex </span><a href="https://coingape.com/crypto-news-poloniex-exchange-pays-settle-charges/"><span style="font-weight: 400">paid</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> $7.6 million to resolve charges of sanctions violations with the US Treasury Department.</span></p>
<h2><b>Poloniex&#8217;s Account Deletion and Token Burn</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Poloniex&#8217;s decision to delete individual accounts and maintain the minimum reserve balance for each user has led to a substantial token burn in fees. With the deletion of 15,000 accounts, a significant amount of XRP tokens has already been burned. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">However, the impact could be even more significant considering the reported total of 84,000 accounts held by the exchange. If all these accounts were to be deleted, it would result in a burn of 168,000 XRP.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">This process involves identifying inactive or abandoned accounts and retrieving the XRP tokens associated with them. The recovered tokens can then be utilized by Poloniex for various purposes, such as improving liquidity or supporting other exchange activities.</span></p>
<h2><b>Understanding XRPL and its Significance</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The XRP Ledger is an open-source, decentralized blockchain protocol that facilitates fast and low-cost transactions. It serves as the backbone for XRP, Ripple’s utility token </span><a href="https://coingape.com/xrp-ledger-gamer-change-hsbc-distributed-ledger-tech-news/"><span style="font-weight: 400">utilized</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> for transactions and remittances. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">XRPL distinguishes itself from other blockchain networks through its consensus algorithm, known as the Ripple Protocol Consensus Algorithm (RPCA), which offers scalability and high throughput.</span></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/largest-xrpl-account-deletions-recorded-whats-happening/">Largest XRP Ledger (XRPL) Account Deletions Recorded, What&#8217;s Happening?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/15213704/XRPL.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dump Alert: Celsius Plans To Sell Altcoins Under Reorganization Plan</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/crypto-dump-news-celsius-altcoin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ashish Kumar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 15:26:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Celsius]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Celsius bankruptcy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=151896</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto News: As the digital asset industry deals with heavy selling pressure, Bankrupt crypto lender Celsius Network LLC rolled out its Reorganization Plan. Court filings depict that the defunct crypto lender is looking to sell all of the altcoins from its customers. Also Read: XRP, Ethereum Leads Sell Off As Crypto Market Bleeds Celsius Looks <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/crypto-dump-news-celsius-altcoin/" title="Dump Alert: Celsius Plans To Sell Altcoins Under Reorganization Plan"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/crypto-dump-news-celsius-altcoin/">Dump Alert: Celsius Plans To Sell Altcoins Under Reorganization Plan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/15205004/crash-crypto.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="crypto Dump News Celsius altcoin" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" /><p><strong>Crypto News:</strong> As the digital asset industry deals with heavy selling pressure, Bankrupt crypto lender <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/celsius/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Celsius Network</a> LLC rolled out its Reorganization Plan. Court filings depict that the defunct crypto lender is looking to sell all of the altcoins from its customers.</p>
<p><strong>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/crypto-crash-xrp-ethereum-sell-off-market-bleeds-news/?utm_source=24hrsupdateall" target="_blank" rel="noopener">XRP, Ethereum Leads Sell Off As Crypto Market Bleeds</a></strong></p>
<h2>Celsius Looks To Dodge Collateral Return</h2>
<p>As per Celsius’s Reorganization Plan, it will sell all customers’ altcoins excluding custody and withhold accounts holdings. It mentioned that the process will start on July 1st, 2023. However, the amount recovered from the altcoin sale will be converted into Bitcoin and Ethereum.</p>
<p>This development comes after the bankrupt crypto lender’s announcement of choosing Fahrenheit’s proposal in a bid to handle a new entity that is decided to be owned by its creditors.</p>
<p>However, David Adler, Bankruptcy Partner at McCarter &amp; English stated that a segment of borrowers represented by him in the case might file an opposition to this plan. It is expected that Celsius might not return their collateral. <a href="https://coingape.com/category/news/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>Read More Crypto News Here&#8230;</strong></a></p>
<p><strong>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/binance-sec-settlement-official-case-prediction-news/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance-SEC Settlement Incoming? Ex-SEC Official Predicts How This Case May End</a></strong></p>
<p>Adler highlighted that the debtors in the case elected to treat the Retail Borrow Claims through the Set Off Treatment. He added that the debtors are demanding repayment of the loans but they have no intention to perform their contractual obligations.</p>
<p>As per the bankruptcy partner, Celsius’s proposed treatment is violating both state and federal consumer lending laws in the country. Thus they will be opposing this plan in court. He added that Celsius was required to extend exclusivity so they filed the plan shortly after filing the motion.</p>
<p>He stated that further extensions of exclusivity aren’t warranted ahead as there has been no such communication conducted from Celsius to the borrower Group for the last 6 or 7 weeks.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/crypto-dump-news-celsius-altcoin/">Dump Alert: Celsius Plans To Sell Altcoins Under Reorganization Plan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/15205004/crash-crypto.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Breaking: Terra&#8217;s Do Kwon Bail Approved By Montenegro High Court, Extradition To South Korea</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/do-kwon-bail-approved-by-montenegro-high-court-extradition-to-south-korea/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Varinder Singh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 14:42:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Do Kwon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[South Korea]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terra]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terra Classic]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=151891</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Terra co-founder Do Kwon and former chief financial officer Han Chang-joon’s bail request is approved by the Montenegro High Court, according to sources familiar with the court proceedings. In addition, the High Court investigation judge ruled that South Korean citizens will remain in prison for extradition to South Korea. Do Kwon Receives Bail, But Remains in <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/do-kwon-bail-approved-by-montenegro-high-court-extradition-to-south-korea/" title="Breaking: Terra&#8217;s Do Kwon Bail Approved By Montenegro High Court, Extradition To South Korea"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/do-kwon-bail-approved-by-montenegro-high-court-extradition-to-south-korea/">Breaking: Terra&#8217;s Do Kwon Bail Approved By Montenegro High Court, Extradition To South Korea</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1280" height="720" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/18210643/do-kwon.webp" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Breaking: Terra&#039;s Do Kwon Bail Approved By Montenegro High Court, Extradition To South Korea" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" /><p>Terra co-founder <strong>Do Kwon</strong> and former chief financial officer <strong>Han Chang-joon’s</strong> bail request is approved by the Montenegro High Court, according to sources familiar with the court proceedings. In addition, the High Court investigation judge ruled that South Korean citizens will remain in prison for extradition to South Korea.</p>
<h2>Do Kwon Receives Bail, But Remains in Extradition Custody</h2>
<p>Montenegro High Court on June 15 rejected <a href="https://coingape.com/terra-founder-do-kwon-bail-appeal-moves-to-montenegro-high-court/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Montenegrin prosecutors&#8217; appeal</a> and upheld the verdict by Montenegro Basic Court Judge Ivana Becic to accept the bail of Terra co-founder Do Kwon and former CTO Han Chang-joon, confirmed court spokesperson Marija Rakovic.</p>
<p>Earlier this month, <a href="https://coingape.com/breaking-terra-founder-do-kwon-bail-request-approved-by-montenegro-court/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Montenegro Basic Court approved</a> Do Kwon and Han Chang-joon&#8217;s bail of 400,000 Euros ($436,000) each for the second time, adding surveillance and other court measures to the bail conditions. The Basic Court sent the prosecutors’ appeal and the passport forgery case files to the Montenegro High Court for judgment.</p>
<p>Montenegro High Court granted bail so that they can defend themselves against charges of documents forgery. However, Do Kwon and Han Chang-joon will remain behind bars as the High Court judge ordered them to be extradited to South Korea.</p>
<p>The High Court investigating judge at the request of South Korea ordered the extradition detention of Do Kwon and Han Chang-joon for six months.</p>
<p><strong>Also Read: </strong><a title="Tether (USDT) Depegs After Curve-Aave Loan Saga; Spooks Crypto Market" href="https://coingape.com/tether-usdt-depegs-after-curve-aave-loan-saga-spooks-crypto-market/" target="_blank" rel="bookmark noopener">Tether (USDT) Depegs After Curve-Aave Loan Saga; Spooks Crypto Market</a></p>
<h2>Terra Founder Political Ties in Montenegro</h2>
<p><a href="https://coingape.com/terra-founder-do-kwon-allegedly-have-political-ties-montenegro-prime-minister/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CoinGape Media reported</a> Do Kwon&#8217;s political ties with former Finance Minister <strong>Milojko Spajic</strong> since 2018. Outgoing Montenegro’s Prime Minister <strong>Dritan Abazovic</strong> claimed he received a letter from Do Kwon regarding his ties with Spajic, president of the Europe Now political party.</p>
<p>The former Finance Minister confirmed that his friends and the company he worked for invested in the Terra project in 2018, where he met Do Kwon. However, they lost all during the Terra-LUNA crisis, “which is why we had the special satisfaction of reporting him to authorities.” Milojko Spajic also has connections with Ethereum co-founder <strong>Vitalik Buterin.</strong></p>
<p><strong>Also Read: </strong><a title="Breaking: Binance’s BNB Chain To Announce Layer 2 Blockchain Solution" href="https://coingape.com/binances-bnb-chain-to-announce-layer-2-blockchain-solution/" rel="bookmark">Binance’s BNB Chain To Announce Layer 2 Blockchain Solution</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/do-kwon-bail-approved-by-montenegro-high-court-extradition-to-south-korea/">Breaking: Terra&#8217;s Do Kwon Bail Approved By Montenegro High Court, Extradition To South Korea</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/18210643/do-kwon.webp" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Breaking: BlackRock Bitcoin ETF To Be Reality Soon</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/breaking-blackrock-bitcoin-etf-to-be-reality-soon/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Anvesh Reddy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 14:26:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin(BTC) News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blackrock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=151895</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto Market News: Less than a year after launching a spot Bitcoin private trust, Blackrock, the world’s largest assets manager, is making moves in the direction of filing for a Bitcoin Exchange Traded Fund (ETF), Reuters reported on Thursday. As and when the Bitcoin Bitcoin ETF will be launched, it will prove to be a <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/breaking-blackrock-bitcoin-etf-to-be-reality-soon/" title="Breaking: BlackRock Bitcoin ETF To Be Reality Soon"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/breaking-blackrock-bitcoin-etf-to-be-reality-soon/">Breaking: BlackRock Bitcoin ETF To Be Reality Soon</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/21123524/BlackRock-launches-metaverse-thematic-ETF.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="BlackRock Bitcoin ETF crypto news" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" /><p><strong>Crypto Market News</strong>: Less than a year after launching a spot Bitcoin private trust, Blackrock, the world’s largest assets manager, is making moves in the direction of filing for a Bitcoin Exchange Traded Fund (ETF), Reuters <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/blackrock-close-filing-bitcoin-etf-coindesk-2023-06-15/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a> on Thursday. As and when the Bitcoin Bitcoin ETF will be launched, it will prove to be a massive move in terms of mainstream <a href="https://coingape.com/markets/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">crypto market</a> adoption. The asset manager&#8217;s initiative comes at a time when the United States regulators are increasingly taking enforcement against crypto businesses.</p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/ethereum-price-dips-amidst-7-84b-yoy-defi-tvl-rout-is-eth-bracing-for-1450" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>Will Ethereum Price Crash to $1,450? ETH DeFi TVL Shrinks by $7.84B in One Year</strong></a></p>
<p>In the third quarter of 2022, the asset manager stitched a <a href="https://coingape.com/after-coinbase-deal-blackrock-launches-bitcoin-private-trust/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">partnership</a> with US based crypto exchange Coinbase, which has recently been dragged into a legal tussle by the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). In the latest initiative, Blackrock is extending the deal for its Bitcoin ETF plans.</p>
<h2>What BlackRock Bitcoin ETF Will Mean For Financial Markets</h2>
<p>Blackrock enjoys widespread influence across all sectors and around the globe, like no other asset manager. This will likely put the BlackRock Bitcoin ETF initiative at a crucial place in terms of taking the crypto adoption to the next level, which needs global level support from various governments. Hence, the ETF plan should be working strategically well for the crypto market growth.</p>
<p>The Blackrock ETF will be using Coinbase Custody and the exchange&#8217;s spot market data, the report said.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Blackrock will be using Coinbase Custody, an offline storage solution for digital assets, for the ETF, and the crypto exchange&#8217;s spot market data for pricing.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/european-central-bank-ecb-repeats-interest-rate-decision-bitcoin-price-sees-relief/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>European Central Bank (ECB) Repeats Interest Rate Decision, Bitcoin Price Sees Relief</strong></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/breaking-blackrock-bitcoin-etf-to-be-reality-soon/">Breaking: BlackRock Bitcoin ETF To Be Reality Soon</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/21123524/BlackRock-launches-metaverse-thematic-ETF.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>On-chain Data Reveals Bitcoin Moving To Illiquid Wallets; Holders &#8220;Not Selling&#8221;</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/on-chain-data-reveals-bitcoin-moving-to-illiquid-wallets-holders-not-selling/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Coingape Staff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 13:49:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin(BTC) News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin vs Altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[HODL]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=151877</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Glassnode data reveals intriguing trends in the Bitcoin market, with the illiquid supply of BTC continuing to expand and Bitcoin dominance on the rise. These developments suggest a strong inclination towards HODLing and a shifting of capital from altcoins to major cryptocurrencies. BTC HODLers Multiply According to Glassnode, the illiquid supply of Bitcoin is steadily <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/on-chain-data-reveals-bitcoin-moving-to-illiquid-wallets-holders-not-selling/" title="On-chain Data Reveals Bitcoin Moving To Illiquid Wallets; Holders &#8220;Not Selling&#8221;"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/on-chain-data-reveals-bitcoin-moving-to-illiquid-wallets-holders-not-selling/">On-chain Data Reveals Bitcoin Moving To Illiquid Wallets; Holders &#8220;Not Selling&#8221;</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="900" height="540" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/26210215/bitcoin-1.png" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="bitcoin core crypto news" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" /><p>Glassnode data reveals intriguing trends in the Bitcoin market, with the illiquid supply of BTC continuing to expand and Bitcoin dominance on the rise. These developments suggest a strong inclination towards HODLing and a shifting of capital from altcoins to major cryptocurrencies.</p>
<h2>BTC HODLers Multiply</h2>
<p>According to Glassnode, the illiquid supply of Bitcoin is steadily increasing at a rate of +119K BTC per month. This indicates that coins are increasingly accumulating in wallets with minimal transaction history, reinforcing the notion that HODLing remains the prevailing market dynamic.</p>
<p>This trend suggests that a significant portion of BTC holders are choosing to retain their coins rather than actively trading or selling them.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-151881" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/15183354/btc-supply.png" alt="" width="4052" height="2334" /></p>
<p>In parallel, Bitcoin dominance has been climbing, currently standing at 47.6%, representing a year-to-date increase of 7.6%. This upward trajectory indicates a consistent rotation of capital from altcoins to major cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>As investors seek liquidity and stability, they are favoring the most established and liquid crypto asset, Bitcoin. This phenomenon highlights the growing preference for the market leader and the continued consolidation of capital in Bitcoin.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-151883" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/15183421/bitcoin-dominance.jpg" alt="" width="4052" height="2334" /></p>
<h3>Bitcoin Price Action</h3>
<p><a href="https://coingape.com/price/bitcoin/">Bitcoin&#8217;s price</a> has seen some fluctuations, with a 0.33% increase in the past hour. However, it has experienced a 4.41% decline over the past 24 hours, dropping below $25K for the first time in 3 months is true.</p>
<p>BTC couldn’t stay in a positive zone after the Fed’s interest rate decision and fell below the $25,500, a new weekly low. This comes in when the <a href="https://coingape.com/us-fed-jerome-powell-speech-live-bitcoin-price-reactionpowell-speech-today-fomc-interest-rate-bitcoin-price/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Federal Reserve pauses rate hikes</a> for the first time in the last 15 months.</p>
<p>Read CoinGape&#8217;s story on <strong><a href="https://coingape.com/crypto-crash-xrp-ethereum-sell-off-market-bleeds-news/">crypto market sell off today</a></strong>, where Ethereum and XRP turned out to be one of the biggest losers in the ongoing sell-off.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/on-chain-data-reveals-bitcoin-moving-to-illiquid-wallets-holders-not-selling/">On-chain Data Reveals Bitcoin Moving To Illiquid Wallets; Holders &#8220;Not Selling&#8221;</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/26210215/bitcoin-1.png" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>European Central Bank (ECB) Repeats Interest Rate Decision, Bitcoin Price Sees Relief</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/european-central-bank-ecb-repeats-interest-rate-decision-bitcoin-price-sees-relief/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Anvesh Reddy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 13:45:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin(BTC) News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ecb]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United Kingdom]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=151879</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto Market News: The European Central Bank (ECB) on Thursday announced its decision to raise the three key ECB interest rates by 25 basis points. The bank&#8217;s Governing Council decision will mean the interest rate on the main refinancing operations and the interest rates on the marginal lending facility and the deposit facility will be <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/european-central-bank-ecb-repeats-interest-rate-decision-bitcoin-price-sees-relief/" title="European Central Bank (ECB) Repeats Interest Rate Decision, Bitcoin Price Sees Relief"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/european-central-bank-ecb-repeats-interest-rate-decision-bitcoin-price-sees-relief/">European Central Bank (ECB) Repeats Interest Rate Decision, Bitcoin Price Sees Relief</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="2048" height="1152" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/02210020/ECB.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="European Central Bank" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" /><p><strong>Crypto Market News</strong>: The European Central Bank (ECB) on Thursday announced its decision to raise the three key ECB interest rates by 25 basis points. The bank&#8217;s Governing Council decision will mean the interest rate on the main refinancing operations and the interest rates on the marginal lending facility and the deposit facility will be increased to 4.00%, 4.25% and 3.50% respectively. These rates will take effect from 21 June 2023. This comes at the back of the <a href="https://coingape.com/markets/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">crypto market</a> taking a slump following the US Federal Reserve&#8217;s hints on chances of raising rates later in 2023.</p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/crypto-crash-xrp-ethereum-sell-off-market-bleeds-news" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>Crypto Crash: XRP, Ethereum Leads Sell Off As Crypto Market Bleeds</strong></a></p>
<p>The ECB reasoned the rate hike decision by citing the possibility of inflation remaining too high for a long time although it has been coming down. In reaction to the ECB rate hike, <a href="https://coingape.com/price/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin price</a> rose on Thursday amid a <span class="sc-f1e838b2-0 dRLonq">4.19% </span>decrease over the last 24 hours. The European Central Bank took a similar <a href="https://coingape.com/european-central-bank-ecb-raises-rate-25-bps-bitcoin-eth/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">decision</a> during its May 2023 meeting, leading to an encouraging crypto market reaction.</p>
<h2>ECB: Inflation Pressures Remain Strong</h2>
<p>The ECB Governing Council forecasted a drop in inflation rate over the next two years. The ECB Council said in a <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://www.ecb.europa.eu/press/pr/date/2023/html/ecb.mp230615~d34cddb4c6.en.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">statement</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;According to the June macroeconomic projections, Eurosystem staff expect headline inflation to average 5.4% in 2023, 3.0% in 2024 and 2.2% in 2025. Indicators of underlying price pressures remain strong, although some show tentative signs of softening.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Going forward, the ECB said will look to take a &#8216;sufficiently restrictive&#8217; stance when it comes to achieve the target of bringing inflation down to the 2% target in medium term.</p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/binances-bnb-chain-to-announce-layer-2-blockchain-solution" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>Binance’s BNB Chain To Announce Layer 2 Blockchain Solution</strong></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/european-central-bank-ecb-repeats-interest-rate-decision-bitcoin-price-sees-relief/">European Central Bank (ECB) Repeats Interest Rate Decision, Bitcoin Price Sees Relief</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/02210020/ECB.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple to Help Colombia&#8217;s Central Bank Explore CBDC Use Cases</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/ripple-to-help-colombia-central-bank-explore-cbdc-use-cases/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Godfrey Benjamin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 13:44:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Peersyst]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=151837</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Blockchain payment company Ripple Labs Inc has entered a strategic partnership deal with Colombia’s Central Bank Banco de la República and together, they intend to explore blockchain technology use cases featuring Central Bank Digital Currency (CBDC).  Notably, the partnership involves the Ministry of Information and Communications Technologies (MinTIC) and a specialized blockchain technology firm known <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/ripple-to-help-colombia-central-bank-explore-cbdc-use-cases/" title="Ripple to Help Colombia&#8217;s Central Bank Explore CBDC Use Cases"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/ripple-to-help-colombia-central-bank-explore-cbdc-use-cases/">Ripple to Help Colombia&#8217;s Central Bank Explore CBDC Use Cases</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="800" height="500" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/15191356/CBDC.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" /><p><span style="font-weight: 400">Blockchain payment company Ripple Labs Inc has </span><a rel='nofollow'  href="https://ripple.com/ripple-press/ripple-and-peersyst-partner-with-colombias-banco-de-la-republica-in-advancing-the-implementation-and-utilization-of-blockchain-technology/?utm_campaign=&amp;utm_medium=organic_social&amp;utm_source=twitter" rel="nofollow"><span style="font-weight: 400">entered</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> a strategic partnership deal with Colombia’s Central Bank Banco de la República and together, they intend to explore blockchain technology use cases featuring Central Bank Digital Currency (CBDC). </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Notably, the partnership involves the Ministry of Information and Communications Technologies (MinTIC) and a specialized blockchain technology firm known as Peersyst Technology. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">According to a Twitter </span><a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/Peersyst/status/1669314979420413952?s=20" rel="nofollow"><span style="font-weight: 400">post</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> by Peersyst, the objective of the alliance is to evaluate the potential efficiencies of a solution using the newly </span><a href="https://coingape.com/breaking-ripple-cbdc-platform-offers-end-to-end-solutions-for-launching-cbdcs-and-stablecoins/"><span style="font-weight: 400">launched</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> Ripple CBDC Platform based on the core technology of the XRPLedger (XRPL) to improve use cases on the high-value payment system. Hence, this pilot phase would be developed as part of the third phase of blockchain experimentation led by MinTIC.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In its entirety, this third phase is focused on sensitising both national and territorial public entities on how payment systems and data management can be revolutionized using blockchain technology&#8217;s speed, scalability, and transparency. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The sensitization process will be carried out through interactive and collaborative real-world application experiments. Also, Ripple&#8217;s CBDC Platform will be tested in a controlled environment which does not jeopardize public resources.</span></p>
<h2><b>Ripple and Colombia Collaboration: The Significance </b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Attempting to explain the significance of the project, Minister Mauricio Lizcano, ICT Minister noted that “potential efficiencies can be evaluated through the results obtained in the development of a solution with blockchain technology, which manages to improve and complement the processes in the entities in a safe and efficient way. In addition, it will provide a technological solution (Prototype), which will allow simulations of different use cases in the high-value payment system.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">James Wallis, the Vice President of Central Bank Engagements and CBDCs also believes that this forward-thinking approach of the Colombia Central Bank and MinTIC will be the birth of an era of innovativeness in the digital space. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Per his statement, onboarding the Ripple CBDC Platform based on the </span><a href="https://coingape.com/xrp-ledger-gamer-change-hsbc-distributed-ledger-tech-news/"><span style="font-weight: 400">XRPL</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> will make way for transformative advancement in the use of blockchain technology in the public sector. The partnership highlights the </span><a href="https://coingape.com/will-central-banks-utilise-xrp-via-ripples-cbdc-platform/"><span style="font-weight: 400">growing recognition</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> of Ripple and the firm’s efforts to be a dominant goto Web3 firm among Central Banks building their own CBDCs</span></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/ripple-to-help-colombia-central-bank-explore-cbdc-use-cases/">Ripple to Help Colombia&#8217;s Central Bank Explore CBDC Use Cases</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/15191356/CBDC.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu News: SHIB Burn Rate Boosts, Price Still In Red Zone</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/shiba-inu-news-shib-burn-rate-boosts-price-still-in-red-zone/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Coingape Staff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 12:35:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[shib burn]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=151838</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In a remarkable display of dedication, Shiba Inu has managed to significantly increase the burn rate of SHIB tokens. After enduring a period of consistent decline, recent data from the Shibburn website reveals an astonishing jump of nearly 1,000% in the burn rate. This surge comes after several consecutive days of SHIB tokens lingering deep <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/shiba-inu-news-shib-burn-rate-boosts-price-still-in-red-zone/" title="Shiba Inu News: SHIB Burn Rate Boosts, Price Still In Red Zone"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/shiba-inu-news-shib-burn-rate-boosts-price-still-in-red-zone/">Shiba Inu News: SHIB Burn Rate Boosts, Price Still In Red Zone</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/07121035/SHIB-as-payment.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Shiba Inu Updates" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" /><p>In a remarkable display of dedication, Shiba Inu has managed to significantly increase the burn rate of SHIB tokens. After enduring a period of consistent decline, recent data from the <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://www.shibburn.com/">Shibburn website</a> reveals an astonishing jump of nearly 1,000% in the burn rate. This surge comes after several consecutive days of SHIB tokens lingering deep in the red zone.</p>
<h2>SHIB Burn Soars Finally</h2>
<p>Over the course of the last 24 hours, the Shiba Inu community has made remarkable progress in reducing the circulating supply of their beloved meme coins. A total of 7,825,621 SHIB tokens were successfully burned, a staggering 945.5% increase compared to the previous day&#8217;s burn of 748,502 coins. These impressive numbers contribute to the cumulative count of burned SHIB tokens, which has now closely approached the 300,000,000 mark for the week.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s worth noting that this figure is notably lower than the burning rates witnessed a few weeks ago when the Shiba Inu community was consistently incinerating between one and two billion SHIB tokens every seven days.</p>
<p>CoinGape <a href="https://coingape.com/shiba-inu-lead-developer-teases-new-product-is-enroute/">reported</a> lately tht Shytoshi Kusama, the lead developer in the Shiba Inu ecosystem has teased the SHIB army that &#8220;Something physical is coming&#8221;</p>
<h3>SHIB Price Remains in the Red Zone</h3>
<p>Despite the relentless efforts of the SHIB community to increase token burns, <a href="https://coingape.com/price/shiba-inu/">the price of Shiba Inu (SHIB)</a> continues to reside in the red zone. The token experienced a significant 30% crash over the weekend, triggered by news of regulatory charges filed by the SEC against prominent crypto exchanges Coinbase and Binance.</p>
<p>In the past 24 hours, SHIB has seen a marginal 0.39% increase in price, offering a glimmer of hope to its loyal investors. However, the broader trend remains unfavorable, as the token has witnessed a 4.03% decrease in the past day and a substantial 17.41% decline over the course of the past week.</p>
<p>Shiba Inu is the second largest memecoin with a market cap of $3,865,979,663.</p>
<p><strong>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/shiba-inu-news-us-politician-buys-shib-token-wellys-announces-new-store/">Shiba Inu Latest Updates&#8230;</a></strong></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/shiba-inu-news-shib-burn-rate-boosts-price-still-in-red-zone/">Shiba Inu News: SHIB Burn Rate Boosts, Price Still In Red Zone</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/07121035/SHIB-as-payment.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Breaking: Binance&#8217;s BNB Chain To Announce Layer 2 Blockchain Solution</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/binances-bnb-chain-to-announce-layer-2-blockchain-solution/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Varinder Singh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 12:21:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance (BNB) Coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNB Chain]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=151826</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The layer-1 blockchain BNB Chain by the world&#8217;s largest crypto exchange Binance on Thursday teases a major announcement coming on June 19. The move comes after BNB Chain successfully implemented the Luban hard fork upgrade introducing fast finality, and enhancing security and transaction reliability. BNB Chain Teases Layer-2 Blockchain Solution BNB Chain on its official <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/binances-bnb-chain-to-announce-layer-2-blockchain-solution/" title="Breaking: Binance&#8217;s BNB Chain To Announce Layer 2 Blockchain Solution"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/binances-bnb-chain-to-announce-layer-2-blockchain-solution/">Breaking: Binance&#8217;s BNB Chain To Announce Layer 2 Blockchain Solution</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/13201306/BNB-Chain-Tokens-Ruling-the-Crypto-Market.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Breaking: Binance&#039;s BNB Chain To Announce Layer 2 Blockchain Solution" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" /><p>The layer-1 <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/blockchain" target="_blank" rel="noopener">blockchain</a> BNB Chain by the world&#8217;s largest <a href="https://coingape.com/blog/binance-exchange-review/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">crypto exchange Binance</a> on Thursday teases a major announcement coming on June 19.</p>
<p>The move comes after BNB Chain successfully implemented the Luban hard fork upgrade introducing fast finality, and enhancing security and transaction reliability.</p>
<h2>BNB Chain Teases Layer-2 Blockchain Solution</h2>
<p>BNB Chain on its official Twitter account on June 15 <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/BNBCHAIN/status/1669253419587227649" target="_blank" rel="noopener">posted</a> a teaser video about the future of BNB Chain, unlocking the power of the chain.</p>
<p>The teaser video shows many clues, with a major hint of &#8220;Layer 2 Blockchain Solution.&#8221; The latest innovation is a high-performance Layer-2 Ecosystem, with high capacity and low-cost transaction processing. It also hints at a gas per second of 100 million.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="und" dir="ltr">19.6.23 <a href="https://t.co/R8ZLTNt4kS">pic.twitter.com/R8ZLTNt4kS</a></p>
<p>&mdash; BNB Chain (@BNBCHAIN) <a href="https://twitter.com/BNBCHAIN/status/1669253419587227649?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 15, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The social media bio is also changed to &#8220;a brand-new way to scale your project with BNB Chain.&#8221; BNB Chain has asked users to make guesses about the reveal on June 19, as few clues are already mentioned in the teaser video.</p>
<p>It follows after BNB Chain completed the Luban network upgrade and hard fork. Luban hard fork incorporates three different Binance Smart Chain (BSC) Evolution Proposals (BEPs): BEP-126, BEP-174, and BEP-221. These aim to make the network faster and more secure.</p>
<p>BEP-126 introduces Fast Finality, making block reorganizations almost impossible. In addition, it enhanced security against double-spend and MEV reorg attacks, irreversible transactions after confirmation, and efficient operations for crypto exchanges and DeFi protocols.</p>
<p><strong>Also Read: </strong><a title="Crypto Community Alleges Prometheum’s US SEC And FINRA Approval Is Controversial" href="https://coingape.com/crypto-community-alleges-prometheums-us-sec-and-finra-approval-is-controversial/" target="_blank" rel="bookmark noopener">Crypto Community Alleges Prometheum’s US SEC And FINRA Approval Is Controversial</a></p>
<h2>BNB Price Falls</h2>
<p><a href="https://coingape.com/price/binance-coin" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BNB price</a> fell 6% in the last 24 hours and 12% in a week. The price is currently trading at $233, with the 24-hour low and high of $231 and $249, respectively. Furthermore, the trading volume has declined by 30% in the last 24hrs, indicating a decrease in interest.</p>
<p>BNB price has been under pressure after the US SEC filed lawsuits against Binance, Binance.US, and CEO Changpeng &#8220;CZ&#8221; Zhao for fraud and violating securities laws. The BNB price is down 25% since then.</p>
<p>According to a price analysis published by <a href="https://coingape.com/markets/heres-why-binance-coin-bnb-price-is-at-risk-of-further-downfall-is-200-next/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CoinGape Markets</a>, BNB price is at risk of further fall.</p>
<p><strong>Also Read: </strong><a title="Tether (USDT) Depegs After Curve-Aave Loan Saga; Spooks Crypto Market" href="https://coingape.com/tether-usdt-depegs-after-curve-aave-loan-saga-spooks-crypto-market/" target="_blank" rel="bookmark noopener">Tether (USDT) Depegs After Curve-Aave Loan Saga; Spooks Crypto Market</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/binances-bnb-chain-to-announce-layer-2-blockchain-solution/">Breaking: Binance&#8217;s BNB Chain To Announce Layer 2 Blockchain Solution</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/13201306/BNB-Chain-Tokens-Ruling-the-Crypto-Market.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Crash: XRP, Ethereum Leads Sell Off As Crypto Market Bleeds</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/crypto-crash-xrp-ethereum-sell-off-market-bleeds-news/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ashish Kumar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 11:58:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=151820</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto Crash: The global cryptocurrency market printed red indexes as selling pressure among traders increased. The cumulative digital asset market cap dropped by a massive 4% over the past day to stand at around $1.02 trillion. This comes in when the Federal Reserve pauses rate hikes for the first time in the last 15 months. <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/crypto-crash-xrp-ethereum-sell-off-market-bleeds-news/" title="Crypto Crash: XRP, Ethereum Leads Sell Off As Crypto Market Bleeds"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/crypto-crash-xrp-ethereum-sell-off-market-bleeds-news/">Crypto Crash: XRP, Ethereum Leads Sell Off As Crypto Market Bleeds</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/15172701/crypto-crash.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Crypto Crash XRP, Ethereum Sell Off Market Bleeds News" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" /><p><strong>Crypto Crash:</strong> The global cryptocurrency market printed red indexes as selling pressure among traders increased. The cumulative digital asset market cap dropped by a massive 4% over the past day to stand at around $1.02 trillion. This comes in when the <a href="https://coingape.com/us-fed-jerome-powell-speech-live-bitcoin-price-reactionpowell-speech-today-fomc-interest-rate-bitcoin-price/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Federal Reserve pauses rate hikes</a> for the first time in the last 15 months.</p>
<p><strong>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/sec-coinbase-crypto-rules-news/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">US SEC Refuses To Commit Deadline in Coinbase Crypto Clarity Case</a></strong></p>
<h2>Crypto Liquidation Breaches $162 Mln</h2>
<p><a rel='nofollow'  href="https://www.coinglass.com/LiquidationData" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Coinglass data</a> depicts that more than 46K traders were liquidated in the last 24 hours, while, the total liquidations recorded stands at around $162.2 million. However, the single largest liquidations order of ETHUSDT valued at $11.57 million was registered on the Binance crypto exchange.</p>
<p>It is important to note that $142.4 million, 87% of the total liquidation over the last 24 hours turned out to be long positions set by the traders. This suggests that the traders were betting on an upward movement in the crypto market. However, Ethereum (ETH) recorded the most of the liquidation (approx worth $60.5 million). <a href="https://coingape.com/category/news/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>Read More Crypto Crash News Here&#8230;</strong></a></p>
<figure id="attachment_151840" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-151840" style="width: 1200px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img decoding="async" class="wp-image-151840 size-full" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/15172553/liq.jpg" alt="crypto liquidation" width="1200" height="800" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-151840" class="wp-caption-text"><strong>Source: Coinglass Data</strong></figcaption></figure>
<h2>Cardano, Solana Drops By Over 20%</h2>
<p>Bitcoin <a href="https://coingape.com/price/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">(BTC) price</a> declined by more than 4% in the last 24 hours as the biggest crypto dropped below the crucial $25K level. Bitcoin is trading at an average price of $24,856, at the press time. BTC dominance decreased to stand around 47.57%. However, a further decline can also be expected ahead.</p>
<p>Ethereum (ETH) and Ripple’s native crypto, XRP turned out to be one of the biggest losers in the ongoing sell-off. ETH and XRP price have dropped more than 6% in the last 24 hours.</p>
<p>Cardano (ADA) and Solana (SOL) emerged as the biggest losers in the last 7 days. ADA and SOL prices declined by 21% and 23%, respectively. This major decline comes in after U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) alleged Binance and Coinbase of multiple charges. However, it also listed ADA, SOL, Sandbox (SAND), Filecoin (FIL), Axie Infinity (AXS), Chiliz (CHZ), Flow (FLOW), Internet Computer (ICP), and Other cryptos as securities.</p>
<figure id="attachment_151849" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-151849" style="width: 1200px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img decoding="async" class="wp-image-151849 size-full" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/15174850/crypto-crash-coins.jpg" alt="" width="1200" height="800" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-151849" class="wp-caption-text">Source: CoinMarketCap</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/crypto-crash-xrp-ethereum-sell-off-market-bleeds-news/">Crypto Crash: XRP, Ethereum Leads Sell Off As Crypto Market Bleeds</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/15172701/crypto-crash.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tether (USDT) Depegs After Curve-Aave Loan Saga; Spooks Crypto Market</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/tether-usdt-depegs-after-curve-aave-loan-saga-spooks-crypto-market/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Varinder Singh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 09:55:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[aave]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Curve (CRV)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tether]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=151796</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Tether (USDT), the leading stablecoin having $83 billion market cap, slightly depegged from the typical 1:1 ratio with the US dollar on Thursday. The move comes as DeFi lending and borrowing protocol AAVE moves to freeze Curve (CRV) use as collateral for loans on Aave. As a result, whales and investors are taking arbitrage opportunities <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/tether-usdt-depegs-after-curve-aave-loan-saga-spooks-crypto-market/" title="Tether (USDT) Depegs After Curve-Aave Loan Saga; Spooks Crypto Market"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/tether-usdt-depegs-after-curve-aave-loan-saga-spooks-crypto-market/">Tether (USDT) Depegs After Curve-Aave Loan Saga; Spooks Crypto Market</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="675" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/10211456/TETHER-e1686822825909.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Tether (USDT) Depegs After Curve-Aave Loan Saga; Spooks Crypto Market" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" srcset="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/10211456/TETHER-e1686822825909.jpg 1200w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/10211456/TETHER-e1686822825909-300x169.jpg 300w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/10211456/TETHER-e1686822825909-768x432.jpg 768w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/10211456/TETHER-e1686822825909-678x381.jpg 678w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/10211456/TETHER-e1686822825909-150x84.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /><p>Tether (USDT), the leading <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/stable-coins" target="_blank" rel="noopener">stablecoin</a> having $83 billion market cap, slightly depegged from the typical 1:1 ratio with the US dollar on Thursday. The move comes as DeFi lending and borrowing protocol AAVE moves to freeze Curve (CRV) use as collateral for loans on Aave.</p>
<p>As a result, whales and investors are taking arbitrage opportunities to swap Tether (USDT) for USDC and DAI stablecoins on exchanges Curve, Uniswap, and 1inch.</p>
<h2>Tether CTO: Ready For Redemptions Amid USDT Depeg FUD</h2>
<p>Tether CTO Paolo Ardoino <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/paoloardoino/status/1669223742831042562" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">took</a> to Twitter to calm rising <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/fud" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FUD</a> surrounding USDT amid negative sentiment in the crypto market. He claims Tether is ready for any amount of redemptions. Tether reserve backing has been a key concern for the community, with critics alleging that Tether does not have money and may default.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Markets are edgy in these days, so it&#39;s easy for attackers to capitalize on this general sentiment.<br />But at Tether we&#39;re ready as always. Let them come.<br />We&#39;re ready to redeem any amount.</p>
<p>&mdash; Paolo Ardoino <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f350.png" alt="🍐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (@paoloardoino) <a href="https://twitter.com/paoloardoino/status/1669223742831042562?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 15, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>According to the latest <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://tether.to/en/transparency/#reports" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Tether reserves data</a>, 84.7% are in cash &amp; cash equivalents, 4.14% in precious metals, and 1.83% in Bitcoin. It holds cash &amp; cash equivalents mostly in U.S. Treasury bills.</p>
<p>Curve 3Pool that should have 33.33% each of USDT, USDC, and DAI stablecoins has imbalanced, with USDT balance surging over 72%. DeFi traders and whales are selling millions of USDT for USDC and DAI, causing the leading stablecoin Tether depegging to $0.996.</p>
<p>A notable Ethereum address czsamsun.eth borrowed 31.5 million USDT from Aave V2 by using 17k ETH and 14k stETH as collateral, swapping all borrowed USDT into USDC. The borrower deposited 10 million USDC and 21 million USDC to V2 and V3, respectively. Moreover, the borrower borrowed 12 million USDT from V3 and deposited it into V2.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/15132254/curve-3pol.png" /></p>
<p><strong>Also Read: </strong><a href="https://coingape.com/breaking-usdt-depegs-again-as-whales-dump-largest-stablecoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">USDT Depegs Again As Whales Dump Largest Stablecoin</a></p>
<h2>How It All Started</h2>
<p>Earlier this week, Curve Finance founder Michael Egorov deposited $24 million worth of Curve DAO (CRV) tokens to Aave to mitigate the liquidation risk of a $65 million stablecoin loan.</p>
<p>According to <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://debank.com/profile/0x7a16ff8270133f063aab6c9977183d9e72835428" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Debank</a>, the wallet linked to Michael Egorov provided $188 million in total collateral on Aave v2, with $64.2 million in USDT borrowed. The health rate is 1.55, the collateral will liquidate automatically if it drops below 1.00.</p>
<p><a rel='nofollow'  href="https://governance.aave.com/t/gauntlet-recommendation-to-freeze-crv-and-set-crv-ltv-0-on-aave-v2/13644" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Gauntlet</a>, which managed risks on Aave, recommends the Aave community freeze CRV collateral and set Curve LTV to 0. It will prevent Michael Egorov from continuing to add CRV and increasing concentration risk, as CRV liquidity has decreased in over the past few months.</p>
<div class="sc-aef7b723-0 sc-8497df48-0 iULUNk" data-sensors-click="true">
<div class="sc-aef7b723-0 sc-8497df48-1 iATetF name-area ">
<p class="sc-4984dd93-0 kKpPOn" data-sensors-click="true">Curve DAO Token (CRV) price fell 12% in the last 24 hours and 25 in a week. The price currently trades at $0.57. Meanwhile, AAVE price is trading at $49.56, down 11% in the last 24 hours and 16% in a week.</p>
<p data-sensors-click="true"><strong>Also Read: <a title="Crypto Community Alleges Prometheum’s US SEC And FINRA Approval Is Controversial" href="https://coingape.com/crypto-community-alleges-prometheums-us-sec-and-finra-approval-is-controversial/" target="_blank" rel="bookmark noopener">Crypto Community Alleges Prometheum’s US SEC And FINRA Approval Is Controversial</a></strong></p>
</div>
</div>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/tether-usdt-depegs-after-curve-aave-loan-saga-spooks-crypto-market/">Tether (USDT) Depegs After Curve-Aave Loan Saga; Spooks Crypto Market</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/10211456/TETHER-e1686822825909.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Will Ethereum Price Crash to $1,450? ETH DeFi TVL Shrinks by $7.84B in One Year</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/ethereum-price-dips-amidst-7-84b-yoy-defi-tvl-rout-is-eth-bracing-for-1450/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[John Isige]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 08:32:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Defi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TVL]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=151805</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Federal Open Market Committee (FOMC) decision to pause hikes on the benchmark interest rates has left many investors counting losses. Ethereum invalidated the positive market sentiment that had been building following reports of easing inflation in the US with losses amounting to 5.8% in 24 hours, to trade at $1,638 on Thursday. Ethereum Price <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/ethereum-price-dips-amidst-7-84b-yoy-defi-tvl-rout-is-eth-bracing-for-1450/" title="Will Ethereum Price Crash to $1,450? ETH DeFi TVL Shrinks by $7.84B in One Year"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/ethereum-price-dips-amidst-7-84b-yoy-defi-tvl-rout-is-eth-bracing-for-1450/">Will Ethereum Price Crash to $1,450? ETH DeFi TVL Shrinks by $7.84B in One Year</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1140" height="596" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/15135244/ETHUSD_2023-06-15_09-33-14.png" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Ethereum Price Dips Amidst $7.84B YoY DeFi TVL Rout: is ETH Bracing for $1,450?" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" /><p>The Federal Open Market Committee (FOMC) decision to pause hikes on the benchmark interest rates has left many investors counting losses. Ethereum invalidated the positive market sentiment that had been building following reports of easing inflation in the US with losses amounting to 5.8% in 24 hours, to trade at $1,638 on Thursday.</p>
<h2>Ethereum Price Downtrend Seems Unstoppable</h2>
<p>The daily chart shows bears aggressively working to validate another drop below the lower ascending trendline. <a href="https://coingape.com/price/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum price has been vulnerable to declines</a> since early last week when the US regulator, the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) launched a series of attacks on crypto entities and tokens – <a href="https://coingape.com/binance-sec-settlement-official-case-prediction-news/?utm_source=24hrsupdateall" target="_blank" rel="noopener">suing Binance and Coinbase</a>.</p>
<figure id="attachment_151806" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-151806" style="width: 1140px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/15135244/ETHUSD_2023-06-15_09-33-14.png"><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-151806" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/15135244/ETHUSD_2023-06-15_09-33-14.png" alt="Ethereum Price Dips Amidst $7.84B YoY DeFi TVL Rout: is ETH Bracing for $1,450?" width="1140" height="596" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-151806" class="wp-caption-text">ETH/USD daily chart | Source Tradingview</figcaption></figure>
<p>If ETH price sustains movement below the lower ascending trend line or support at $1,600, it would be an uphill task for bulls to arrest declines before they reach $1,450. Already the On Balance Volume (OBV) indicator, which measures the inflow and outflow of volume in the market, shows sellers resolutely holding the reins.</p>
<p>All the applied moving averages including the 50-day Exponential Moving Average (EMA), the 100-day EMA, and the 50-day EMA hold above <a href="https://coingape.com/ethereum-price-prediction-as-eth-sits-on-1700-support-how-to-stay-profitable-this-week/?utm_source=24hrsupdatealtcoin" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum price</a>. A death cross pattern may come into the picture if losses extend into the weekend, with the 50-day EMA (red) crossing below the 100-day EMA (blue).</p>
<p>Traders considering buying the dip must wait for a confirmed rebound from the short-term support at $1,630, reinforced by the lower ascending trendline. Another buyer congestion holds at $1,600 as the last line of defense to prevent all hell from breaking lose to $1,450.</p>
<h2>Ethereum DeFi Total Value Locked Dips</h2>
<p>Ethereum, the time-tested pioneer in the DeFi realm, has experienced a tumultuous journey with regard to its Total Value Locked (TVL). Though it has shown resilience in the face of shifting market tides, Ethereum&#8217;s position has faced formidable challenges from rising stars in the space like Optimism (OP), Tron (TRX), Solana (SOL), and Polygon (MATIC) among others.</p>
<p>Since June 2022, Ethereum&#8217;s dominance in the DeFi sector has been increasingly contested. Layer-2 solutions like Polygon have seen a considerable surge in TVL, thanks in large part to their ability to provide faster and cheaper transactions.</p>
<p>This has inevitably impacted Ethereum&#8217;s position, prompting a reevaluation of its supremacy in the DeFi landscape. According to the latest data on the DeFi space by DefiLlama, the network’s TVL has since June 15 lost $7.84 billion.</p>
<figure id="attachment_151808" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-151808" style="width: 983px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/15135531/Ethereum-TVL-DefiLlama.jpg"><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-151808" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/15135531/Ethereum-TVL-DefiLlama.jpg" alt="Ethereum Price Dips Amidst $7.84B YoY DeFi TVL Rout: is ETH Bracing for $1,450?" width="983" height="547" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-151808" class="wp-caption-text">Ethereum DeFi TVL | Source DefiLlama</figcaption></figure>
<p>If the rout continues, the TVL may drop further from the current $24.36 billion, thus fading in comparison to Ethereum’s all-time high of approximately $108 billion in November 2021.</p>
<p>Liquid staking platform Lido accounts for the highest TVL in Ether’s ecosystem at $12.65 billion. MakerDAO comes in second place with less than half of Lido’s at $5.47 billion, while Aave, Curve Finance, and Uniswap fill the rest of the top five positions in that order.</p>
<p>The extensive crypto winter is the biggest challenge to investors in DeFi. As the market wobbles they are forced to pull their staked holdings to diversify their portfolios. Unfortunately, this situation increases overhead pressure for DeFi protocols like Ethereum.</p>
<p>Ethereum price is bound to stay vulnerable until resistance at $1,800 is reclaimed for a continued upswing to $2,000 and beyond.</p>
<h3>Related Articles:</h3>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://coingape.com/federal-reserve-rate-halt-sends-bitcoin-price-tumbling-will-btc-hit-20k-or-30k-next/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Federal Reserve Rate Halt Sends Bitcoin Price Tumbling: Will BTC Hit $20K or $30K Next? </a></li>
<li><a href="https://coingape.com/breaking-usdt-depegs-again-as-whales-dump-largest-stablecoin/?utm_source=24hrsupdateall" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Breaking: USDT Depegs Again As Whales Dump Largest Stablecoin </a></li>
<li><a href="https://coingape.com/crypto-community-alleges-prometheums-us-sec-and-finra-approval-is-controversial/?utm_source=24hrsupdateall" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Crypto Community Alleges Prometheum’s US SEC And FINRA Approval Is Controversial </a></li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/ethereum-price-dips-amidst-7-84b-yoy-defi-tvl-rout-is-eth-bracing-for-1450/">Will Ethereum Price Crash to $1,450? ETH DeFi TVL Shrinks by $7.84B in One Year</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/15135244/ETHUSD_2023-06-15_09-33-14.png" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Breaking: USDT Depegs Again As Whales Dump Largest Stablecoin</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/breaking-usdt-depegs-again-as-whales-dump-largest-stablecoin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Coingape Staff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 08:05:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Curve]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether FUD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether UsdT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=151786</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Whales have been selling off significant amounts of Tether (USDT), the largest stablecoin in the cryptocurrency market, leading to a surge in its dominance within the Curve 3pool liquidity pool. The unusual influx of USDT has triggered concerns about the stablecoin&#8217;s stability and caused apprehension surrounding USDT&#8217;s depegging. Tether Reserves in Curve 3pool Miles Deutscher <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/breaking-usdt-depegs-again-as-whales-dump-largest-stablecoin/" title="Breaking: USDT Depegs Again As Whales Dump Largest Stablecoin"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/breaking-usdt-depegs-again-as-whales-dump-largest-stablecoin/">Breaking: USDT Depegs Again As Whales Dump Largest Stablecoin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/17162051/tether1.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Breaking: USDT Depegs Again As Whales Dump Largest Stablecoin" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" /><p>Whales have been selling off significant amounts of <a href="https://coingape.com/price/tether/">Tether (USDT)</a>, the largest stablecoin in the cryptocurrency market, leading to a surge in its dominance within the <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://curve.fi/#/ethereum/pools/3pool/deposit/" rel="nofollow">Curve 3pool liquidity pool</a>. The unusual influx of USDT has triggered concerns about the stablecoin&#8217;s stability and caused apprehension surrounding USDT&#8217;s depegging.</p>
<h2>Tether Reserves in Curve 3pool</h2>
<p>Miles Deutscher took to <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/milesdeutscher/status/1669234677205569537?s=20" rel="nofollow">Twitter</a> to share rising concerns on USDT. He highlighted-</p>
<blockquote><p>Whales have been dumping $USDT, resulting in USDT now comprising 50%+ of the Curve 3pool.</p></blockquote>
<p>The recent dumping of USDT by whales has significantly impacted the composition of the Curve 3pool. USDT now comprises 73.17% of the liquidity pool, with over 13% each. This is the highest it has been since November 2022 (FTX collapse).</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-151795" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/15132254/curve-3pol.png" alt="" width="686" height="275" /></p>
<p>He is unclear if this sudden surge in USDT inflows is merely the result of FUD, or if there is insider knowledge driving these actions. A bulk of the scrutiny towards USDT comes from its de-peg in the wake of the Terra crash.</p>
<p>CoinGape <a href="https://coingape.com/is-tether-usdt-following-terras-ust-in-losing-its-dollar-peg/">reported</a> on May 12, 2022, that the token is down 4.8% to 0.9508- its lowest level since the 2017 crypto crash. Again on June 6, 2022, Tether (USDT) experienced a significant depegging event, trading at $0.18 per USD Coin (USDC) on ValleySwap.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-151803" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/15134209/USDT-CHART-.png" alt="" width="1427" height="690" /></p>
<h3>Whale Shorts USDT</h3>
<p>Lookonchain, a blockchain explorer, has shed further light on the situation by identifying specific addresses associated with the pump and dump activities surrounding USDT.</p>
<p><strong>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/how-stable-is-tether-data-shows-usdt-at-massive-liquidity-imbalance/">How Stable Is Tether?</a>..</strong></p>
<p>One notable player in the USDT depegging scenario is CZSamSun, who <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1669228147265662976?s=20" rel="nofollow">reportedly</a> shorted USDT on Aave V2 after its depegging. CZSamSun borrowed a substantial amount of USDT, specifically 31,544,278 USDT, from Aave V2 and exchanged it for 31,475,408 USDC at a rate of $0.9978. Furthermore, CZSamSun deposited 10 million USDC back onto Aave V2, suggesting a calculated strategy to exploit the depegging situation.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-151804" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/15134447/WHALE-tether-usdt-aave.jpg" alt="" width="1806" height="1362" /></p>
<p>The recent dumping of USDT by whales and its subsequent impact on the Curve 3pool have once again raised concerns about Tether&#8217;s stability and trustworthiness. Tether is currently trading at $0.9973, experiencing a slight 0.25% decrease in value over the past 24 hours. With a market capitalization of approximately 83 billion, USDT continues to be one of the largest and most widely used stablecoins in the cryptocurrency market.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/breaking-usdt-depegs-again-as-whales-dump-largest-stablecoin/">Breaking: USDT Depegs Again As Whales Dump Largest Stablecoin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/17162051/tether1.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Community Alleges Prometheum&#8217;s US SEC And FINRA Approval Is Controversial</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/crypto-community-alleges-prometheums-us-sec-and-finra-approval-is-controversial/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Varinder Singh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 07:08:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Charles Hoskinson]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Custodian]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Securities and Exchange Commission]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=151768</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>At a time when top crypto exchanges Binance and Coinbase face wrath from US regulators such as the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). A lesser-known crypto firm Prometheum gaining approval from the SEC and FINRA has caused a furor in the crypto community. New York-based Prometheum came into the spotlight during the US House <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/crypto-community-alleges-prometheums-us-sec-and-finra-approval-is-controversial/" title="Crypto Community Alleges Prometheum&#8217;s US SEC And FINRA Approval Is Controversial"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/crypto-community-alleges-prometheums-us-sec-and-finra-approval-is-controversial/">Crypto Community Alleges Prometheum&#8217;s US SEC And FINRA Approval Is Controversial</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/09001807/sec-gensler1.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Crypto Community Alleges Prometheum&#039;s US SEC And FINRA Approval Is Controversial" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" /><p>At a time when top <a href="https://coingape.com/blog/binance-exchange-review/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">crypto exchanges Binance</a> and Coinbase face wrath from US regulators such as the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). A lesser-known crypto firm Prometheum gaining approval from the SEC and FINRA has caused a furor in the crypto community.</p>
<p>New York-based Prometheum came into the spotlight during the <a href="https://coingape.com/us-house-releases-stablecoin-bill-bring-clarity-giving-fed-authority/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">US House Financial Services Committee hearing</a> “<strong>The Future of Digital Assets: Providing Clarity for the Digital Asset Ecosystem</strong>” held on June 13. Prometheum co-CEO Aaron Kaplan was announced as a witness in the hearing at the very end, which raised questions.</p>
<h2>Prometheum&#8217;s US SEC And FINRA Approval Are &#8220;Nonsense&#8221;</h2>
<p>During the US House Financial Services Committee hearing, Representative Mike Flood calls Prometheum&#8217;s US SEC and FINRA approval as &#8220;nonsense&#8221; as the firm doesn&#8217;t offer trading in top crypto assets Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH).</p>
<p>However, co-CEO Aaron Kaplan said the clear path forward for the digital asset industry in the U.S. is through the current regulatory frameworks set up by the US SEC. The crypto community claims Aaron Kaplan was reading off pre-written notes with narratives of Democratic members of Congress or the SEC.</p>
<p>In a series of tweets, Castle Island Ventures partner Matt Walsh shared some bizarre facts about Prometheum, its investors Wanxiang Blockchain and Hashkey Capital, and paying $1.5 million in sales commissions to Network 1 Financial Securities.</p>
<p>Aaron Kaplan was mentioning similar narratives of Gary Gensler-led SEC regarding preferred crypto market structure. Gensler argues most crypto are securities and as per him a regulated crypto exchange can operate, as long as it doesn’t actually enable the purchase or sale of crypto.</p>
<p>The crypto community including Cardano co-founder <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/IOHK_Charles/status/1669083769259671554" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Charles Hoskinson</a> has no idea who is Prometheum. Gemini co-founders <span class="account-inline txt-ellipsis">Tyler Winklevoss and </span><span class="account-inline txt-ellipsis">Cameron Winklevoss </span><span class="account-inline txt-ellipsis">have also blasted the US SEC and Prometheum on their view of crypto.</span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">The moral of the story: If you have a fake business you will get approved by the <a href="https://twitter.com/SECGov?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@SECGov</a>, if you have a real business you will get sued by the SEC. <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f602.png" alt="😂" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f921.png" alt="🤡" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <a href="https://t.co/L9Yf4VnF5f">https://t.co/L9Yf4VnF5f</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Tyler Winklevoss (@tyler) <a href="https://twitter.com/tyler/status/1669159238940397568?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 15, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p><span class="account-inline txt-ellipsis">In May, subsidiary Prometheum Ember Capital became the first SEC-qualified firm to offer custody of digital assets after receiving FINRA approval to operate as a special purpose broker-dealer (SPBD) for digital assets.</span></p>
<p><a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/adamscochran/status/1669143092274888704" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Adam Cochran</a> argues the approval is controversial as many <span class="account-inline txt-ellipsis">Prometheum employees </span>are former SEC and FINRA staffers. He has also shared details about the firm and its under-the-radar operations.</p>
<p><strong>Also Read: <a title="Breaking: Terra Classic Biggest v2.1.1 Parity Upgrade Goes Live, LUNC Price Rally 8%" href="https://coingape.com/terra-classic-biggest-v2-1-1-parity-upgrade-goes-live-lunc-price-rally-8/" target="_blank" rel="bookmark noopener">Terra Classic Biggest v2.1.1 Parity Upgrade Goes Live, LUNC Price Rally 8%</a></strong></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/crypto-community-alleges-prometheums-us-sec-and-finra-approval-is-controversial/">Crypto Community Alleges Prometheum&#8217;s US SEC And FINRA Approval Is Controversial</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/09001807/sec-gensler1.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pepecoin Dumped By Another Whale, Is PEPE Craze Over?</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/pepe-tokens-dumped-by-another-whale-is-pepe-craze-over/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Coingape Staff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 06:29:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insider Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PEPE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pepe News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Whale transaction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=151773</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>On-Chain Analysis platform, Lookonchain has reported another whale transaction around once trending PEPE memecoin. Causing speculations about potential insider trading, a whale has sold its entire holdings of 972.84 billion PEPE tokens. Additionally, the token&#8217;s value has experienced a significant decline over the past week. Whale&#8217;s PEPE Token Dump According to Lookonchain, address 0x1497 recently <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/pepe-tokens-dumped-by-another-whale-is-pepe-craze-over/" title="Pepecoin Dumped By Another Whale, Is PEPE Craze Over?"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/pepe-tokens-dumped-by-another-whale-is-pepe-craze-over/">Pepecoin Dumped By Another Whale, Is PEPE Craze Over?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/20165329/pepe_green.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="pepe tokens" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" /><p>On-Chain Analysis platform, Lookonchain has reported another whale transaction around once trending <a href="https://coingape.com/price/pepe-coin/">PEPE</a> memecoin. Causing speculations about potential <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/insider-trading/">insider trading</a>, a whale has sold its entire holdings of 972.84 billion PEPE tokens. Additionally, the token&#8217;s value has experienced a significant decline over the past week.</p>
<h2>Whale&#8217;s PEPE Token Dump</h2>
<p>According to Lookonchain, address 0x1497 recently sold its entire holdings of 972.84 billion PEPE tokens. The sale was executed for 514 ETH, equivalent to approximately $848,000. The selling price was recorded at $0.0000008718 per token. This transaction has led some individuals to question whether the seller might be engaged in insider trading.</p>
<p>Further investigation reveals that the aforementioned address received 0.58 ETH from FixedFloat and promptly used a portion of it, approximately 0.027 ETH (equivalent to $58), to purchase a staggering 2.27 trillion PEPE tokens. Notably, this transaction occurred within <strong>just 10 minutes</strong> of PEPE&#8217;s trading commencement.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-151782" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/15113640/pepe-whale.jpg" alt="" width="2692" height="1246" /></p>
<p>CoinGape <a href="https://coingape.com/whale-sold-over-400-billion-pepe-tokens-at-52-loss/">reported</a> a separate incident from five days ago, a whale incurred a significant loss while trading PEPE. The whale sold 468.5 billion PEPE tokens for 109 ETH (approximately $190,000) and 237.5 thousand USDT. This transaction resulted in a 52% loss for the whale.</p>
<h3>Bearish Outlook For PEPE?</h3>
<p><a href="https://coingape.com/price/pepe-coin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Pepecoin price</a> rose steadily in late April and went on to explode on May 5, when<a href="https://coingape.com/binance-expands-support-for-pepe-and-floki-price-to-rally/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"> Binance announced listing</a> of the meme coin.</p>
<p>But these recent whale-induced token dump has compounded the bearish sentiment surrounding PEPE. The high-volume sale by whales has intensified the downward pressure on the token&#8217;s value. The impact of the whale&#8217;s token dump on PEPE&#8217;s price has been evident in recent market movements. In the aftermath of the sale, PEPE&#8217;s value has continued to decline, reflecting the negative sentiment surrounding the token.</p>
<p>Over the past week, PEPE has experienced a notable decline in value. The token&#8217;s price has decreased by 1.12% within the last hour, 5.48% over the past 24 hours, and a substantial 17.06% in the span of seven days. These price movements indicate a bearish trend for PEPE and may be indicative of wider market sentiment.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/pepe-tokens-dumped-by-another-whale-is-pepe-craze-over/">Pepecoin Dumped By Another Whale, Is PEPE Craze Over?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/20165329/pepe_green.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin and Crypto Enter Steep Correction, Next BTC Price Stop at $23,500?</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/bitcoin-and-crypto-enter-steep-correction-next-btc-price-stop-at-23500/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 05:43:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin(BTC) News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC Price Correction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=151757</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In hours following Jerome Powell&#8217;s announcement of keeping interest rates unchanged, Bitcoin and the broader cryptocurrency market have entered a steep correction. The Bitcoin (BTC) price is down over 3.5% in the last 24 hours and has moved closer to the $25,000 level. Similarly, the broader cryptocurrency market has eroded over $40 billion of investors&#8217; <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/bitcoin-and-crypto-enter-steep-correction-next-btc-price-stop-at-23500/" title="Bitcoin and Crypto Enter Steep Correction, Next BTC Price Stop at $23,500?"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/bitcoin-and-crypto-enter-steep-correction-next-btc-price-stop-at-23500/">Bitcoin and Crypto Enter Steep Correction, Next BTC Price Stop at $23,500?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="900" height="540" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/26210215/bitcoin-1.png" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="bitcoin core crypto news" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" /><p>In hours following Jerome Powell&#8217;s announcement of <a href="https://coingape.com/us-fed-keeps-interest-rate-unchanged-bitcoin-goes-sideways/?utm_source=24hrsupdateall" target="_blank" rel="noopener">keeping interest rates unchanged</a>, Bitcoin and the broader cryptocurrency market have entered a steep correction. The Bitcoin (BTC) price is down over 3.5% in the last 24 hours and has moved closer to the $25,000 level.</p>
<p>Similarly, the broader cryptocurrency market has eroded over $40 billion of investors&#8217; wealth and is on the verge of falling under the $1 trillion mark.</p>
<p>As of now, $25,000 stands as a strong support level for Bitcoin (BTC), and any fall under this could push it further down to $23,500 and below.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">There we go on <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Bitcoin</a>.</p>
<p>The lows are getting swept.</p>
<p>Heavily interested to see response at the $25K region. <a href="https://t.co/0ekuDdRptL">pic.twitter.com/0ekuDdRptL</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Michaël van de Poppe (@CryptoMichNL) <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoMichNL/status/1669075316701003776?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 14, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Popular crypto analyst Ali Martinez <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/ali_charts/status/1668907558763913216" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a>: &#8220;Bitcoin <span class="css-901oao css-16my406 r-poiln3 r-bcqeeo r-qvutc0">sits on thing ice! Notice the most important support zone is between $22,785 and $23,595 where 1.34 million wallets hold 450,000 </span><span class="r-18u37iz">$BTC</span><span class="css-901oao css-16my406 r-poiln3 r-bcqeeo r-qvutc0">. On the flip side, </span><span class="r-18u37iz">#BTC</span><span class="css-901oao css-16my406 r-poiln3 r-bcqeeo r-qvutc0"> faces stiff resistance between $26,000 and $28,250 where 5.18 million wallets bought 2.1 million BTC&#8221;.</span></p>
<figure id="attachment_151759" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-151759" style="width: 2346px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-151759" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/15103856/Bitcoin-BTC-Support-Areas.jpeg" alt="" width="2346" height="880" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-151759" class="wp-caption-text">Courtesy: IntoTheBlock</figcaption></figure>
<p>As we have seen, so far in 2023, the correlation between Bitcoin and US equities has divulged to a great extent. After the Powell speech on Tuesday, the US equities ended flat as the US Fed Chair hinted at the possibility of two more rate hikes ahead this year.</p>
<p>Bitcoin and the crypto market have reacted quickly to this since the market is already facing liquidity challenges in the wake of the SEC lawsuits on crypto exchanges Binance and Coinbase. Already several banking partners have been <a href="https://coingape.com/binance-us-signals-cutting-off-from-banking-partners-liquidity-crisis-ahead/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reconsidering their ties</a> with the crypto exchange in the wake of the current developments.</p>
<h3>Altcoins Face Deeper Correction Than Bitcoin</h3>
<p>Along with Bitcoin, the correction seems more pronounced in the altcoins space. The world&#8217;s second-largest crypto Ethereum (ETH) has tanked by more than 5.5% and has currently slipped under the $1,650 levels.</p>
<p>Other top ten altcoins such as BNB, XRP, Cardano ADA, and Polygon MATIC, have all corrected over 6%. The bears seem to have taken a clear hold of the markets over the bulls and it remains to be seen how far the market can correct further from here.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/bitcoin-and-crypto-enter-steep-correction-next-btc-price-stop-at-23500/">Bitcoin and Crypto Enter Steep Correction, Next BTC Price Stop at $23,500?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/26210215/bitcoin-1.png" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
