<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 21:46:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>FTX Japan to Refund Customers &amp; Shut Down Operations in Q1 2023</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-japan-refund-customers-q1-2023/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-japan-refund-customers-q1-2023/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 14:41:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx japan]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=231031</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-japan-refund-customers-q1-2023/">FTX Japan to Refund Customers &#038; Shut Down Operations in Q1 2023</a></p>
<p>FTX Japan has created systems to refund crypto assets to customers after suspending withdrawals in the previous month.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-japan-refund-customers-q1-2023/">FTX Japan to Refund Customers &#038; Shut Down Operations in Q1 2023</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-japan-refund-customers-q1-2023/">FTX Japan to Refund Customers &#038; Shut Down Operations in Q1 2023</a></p>
<p>According to <a href="https://decrypt.co/118162/ftx-japan-refund-customers-starting-february-2023" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reports</a>, FTX Japan looks to refund customers from February next year following the spectacular <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a> crash. In a <a href="https://help-jp.ftx.com/hc/ja/articles/14007851154201" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">statement</a>, the exchange&#8217;s Japanese subsidiary explained that it is developing a process that facilitates customer recovery of stuck assets.</p>
<p>Local crypto exchange Liquid Japan would be instrumental in this fund recovery phase. FTX had previously acquired Liquid Japan in an undisclosed deal in the spring.</p>
<p>The FTX Japan refund announcement read:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;For the assets entrusted to us by our customers at FTX Japan and Liquid Japan, we are proceeding with system development so that [withdrawals] will be possible from the Liquid Japan web version.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Furthermore, the FTX Japanese subsidiary provided customers with a three-step process to recover their crypto assets. This system entails customers opening accounts with Liquid Japan by mid-January and undergoing balance checks. Eventually, those who satisfy all requirements would be eligible for withdrawals which would open in mind-February. According to FTX Japan, withdrawals would occur on Liquid&#8217;s webpage or mobile app.</p>
<h2>FTX Japan Refund Process Comes 1 Month after Withdrawal Suspension</h2>
<p>FTX Japan previously suspended services last month due to its parent company&#8217;s bankruptcy filing. However, the subsidiary was never at risk of an insolvency crisis and pledged to create a new system different from FTX&#8217;s. At the time, FTX Japan said that its new system would enable its user base to access their funds on its platform. In light of the welcome fund recovery announcement, FTX Japan issued an apology to users for its prior account suspension. The statement read:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We deeply apologize for the big trouble caused by the prolonged suspension of services for the withdrawal of legal currency as well as crypto assets.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>FTX Japan also stated that it would shut down its operations once all users reclaim their assets. This decision follows a direct order from Kanto Local Finance Bureau for FTX Japan to exit the market by March 2023. FTX Japan had earlier halted some of its services, including withdrawals, on orders from the Financial Services Agency (FSA). In addition, the FSA previously mandated that the Japanese subsidiary retain its assets domestically. The federal regulator also implored FTX Japan to periodically update total liabilities on its balance sheet.</p>
<h2>Japan Customers&#8217; Investment Stake Is Not Part of Broader Subsidiary Sale Plans</h2>
<p>Earlier in the month, FTX Japan confirmed that its customers&#8217; cash and digital asset stake should not be part of FTX Japan&#8217;s estate. Citing the law firm representing FTX&#8217;s Chapter 11 bankruptcy proceedings, FTX Japan said:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The fiat currency and crypto assets of our customers are not included in the assets covered by Chapter 11 after considering the method of depositing and storing these assets and the property rights under the laws of Japan.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>FTX Japan is up for sale alongside three other independently-operated solvent subsidiaries in the US and Europe. New FTX chief executive John Ray III approved the bidding procedures for these subsidiaries via a <a href="https://decrypt.co/117412/ftx-files-sell-four-independently-operated-subsidiaries" target="_blank" rel="noopener">court motion</a>.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/treasury-yields-better-market-2023/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-japan-refund-customers-q1-2023/">FTX Japan to Refund Customers &#038; Shut Down Operations in Q1 2023</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-japan-refund-customers-q1-2023/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Treasury Yields Climb as Investors Anticipate Better Market in 2023</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/treasury-yields-better-market-2023/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/treasury-yields-better-market-2023/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 13:09:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FOMC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jerome powell]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[treasury yield]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=231007</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/treasury-yields-better-market-2023/">Treasury Yields Climb as Investors Anticipate Better Market in 2023</a></p>
<p>The 2-year and 10-year Treasury yields increased as investors continue to monitor cues to set the pace for 2023.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/treasury-yields-better-market-2023/">Treasury Yields Climb as Investors Anticipate Better Market in 2023</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/treasury-yields-better-market-2023/">Treasury Yields Climb as Investors Anticipate Better Market in 2023</a></p>
<p>US Treasury yields rose on Friday, December 30th, as investors look ahead to the potential developments and headwinds of 2023. The benchmark 10-year Treasury yield was up nearly 2 basis points to 3.8520% during the early session. In addition, the 2-year Treasury yield climbed more than 3 basis points to 4.4009% as of 5:00 am Eastern Time.</p>
<h2>Treasury Yields Previously Expected to Climb as 2023 Beckons</h2>
<p>Exactly a week ago, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/10-year-treasury-yield-personal-consumption/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reports</a> also suggested that Treasury yields could rise ahead of 2023. At the time, the 10-year Treasury yield was up by a basis point to 3.6856%, with the 2-year yield remaining unchanged.</p>
<p>With 2020 winding down, talks of a looming recession continue to weigh heavy on investor sentiment. In addition, analysts and observers are also constantly paying attention to the Federal Reserve’s moves regarding inflation policies. The apex bank increased interest rates by 75 basis points four consecutive times this year but recently indicated it would cut back.</p>
<p>According to the Federal Reserve, tapering interest rate hikes is necessary to avert an inadvertent recession. In addition, key consumer price index (CPI) data suggested that inflationary pressure was over the hill and was decreasing.</p>
<h2>Consensus Suggests that Interest Rate Hikes Could Taper</h2>
<p>In November, the Federal Open Market Committee (FOMC) released <a href="https://www.federalreserve.gov/monetarypolicy/files/fomcminutes20221102.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener">minutes</a> from its fiscal meeting, suggesting a hike slowdown. The document read in part:</p>
<blockquote><p>“A number of participants observed that, as monetary policy approached a stance that was sufficiently restrictive to achieve the Committee’s goals, it would become appropriate to slow the pace of increase in the target range for the federal funds rate.”</p></blockquote>
<p>However, earlier this month, Fed Chair <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/jerome-powell/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Jerome Powell </a>still called for caution, explaining that the economy was not out of the woods yet. In Powell’s opinion, although CPI optics seemed positive, the Fed still had a role to play in reining in runaway inflation. As the Fed Chair put it:</p>
<blockquote><p>“The inflation data received so far for October and November show a welcome reduction in the monthly pace of price increases. But it will take substantially more evidence to have confidence that inflation is on a sustained downward path.”</p></blockquote>
<p>As it stands, the Fed is widely expected to increase interest rates by 50 basis points heading into the new year. However, the US central bank also previously suggested maintaining higher interest rates throughout the following year. According to the members of the FOMC, there would likely not be any reductions until 2024.</p>
<h2>Investors Ready to Get Behind Any Indication of Waning Inflation</h2>
<p>Despite the Fed’s skeptical stance on inflation, investors and analysts warmly took to talks of reduced rate hikes. The reason is that any signs of tapered hikes reinforce investors’ belief that inflation could be receding. The Chicago Purchasing Managers’ Index, due Friday, should also garner investor attention. This is because the index reflects business activity in the region and could also provide further insight into 2023.</p>
<p>Bond markets are set to close early today and will not reopen until after the New Year’s break.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/5-economic-predictions-for-2023/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/treasury-yields-better-market-2023/">Treasury Yields Climb as Investors Anticipate Better Market in 2023</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/treasury-yields-better-market-2023/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>5 Economic Predictions for 2023</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/5-economic-predictions-for-2023/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/5-economic-predictions-for-2023/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andy Watson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 12:37:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[imf]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=231003</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/5-economic-predictions-for-2023/">5 Economic Predictions for 2023</a></p>
<p>Following periods of badly managed economic policies, including external factors such as Russia’s invasion of Ukraine, the price of crucial commodities has skyrocketed in Europe.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/5-economic-predictions-for-2023/">5 Economic Predictions for 2023</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/5-economic-predictions-for-2023/">5 Economic Predictions for 2023</a></p>
<p>Following a rather turbulent couple of years for many world economies, investors and analysts are looking to next year and trying to forecast some economic changes we may experience. It cannot be easy to calculate predictions over 12 months as it is an incredibly long time for economies. A lot can happen, however, based on what we have seen during the last 12 to 18 months, we will make five economic predictions that may prove true next year, and give you our reasoning for each.</p>
<h2>Deflation</h2>
<p>Following consecutive periods of inflation across Western economies, it is likely that we will see inflation return to normal, or in some cases, we may even see deflation. But <a href="https://admirals.com/financial-events/what-is-deflation" target="_blank" rel="noopener">what is deflation</a> and how does it work? Deflation is an economic mechanism where the cost of services and everyday products decreases. Longer periods of deflation can lead to rising unemployment, less demand, and economic activity stagnating or reducing. It is not considered something that affects an entire economy and is most likely after a period of high inflation. <a href="https://www.imf.org/en/Publications/WEO/Issues/2022/10/11/world-economic-outlook-october-2022" target="_blank" rel="noopener">The IMF expects</a> to see inflation slow down in 2023, which is some good news at least.</p>
<p>Following periods of badly managed economic policies, including external factors such as Russia’s invasion of Ukraine, the price of crucial commodities has skyrocketed in Europe. These countries used Russian oil and gas to fuel homes and businesses throughout the region. When Russia decided to limit this supply due to sanctions imposed on them, inflation entered the double digits in the United Kingdom for the first time in over 35 years. <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/personal-finance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Personal finances</a>, such as savings and investments for retail investors, take the biggest hit with inflation, so deflation may be something we see next year if the situation improves.</p>
<h2>Don’t Get Your Hopes Up</h2>
<p>Sorry to be the bearer of bad news – it appears as though the economic situation is here to stay for at least another 6-12 months. This is due to a combination of factors, including what we have mentioned above. As well as a lack of business investment, stagnation or negative growth will likely remain on the horizon for quite some time. If there is a governmental change in Western countries, that enacts different policies, alongside a ceasefire in Ukraine, this prediction may be more manageable in the following months.</p>
<h2>The R-word – Recession</h2>
<p>It feels like we are bringing nothing but negativity to this piece today. Economic growth is a given for those who grew up in the West in the early 2000s, but given the fine balance of disappointing market factors, do not be surprised to see another recession grip America, the UK, and the rest of Europe, at least at some point in 2023.</p>
<p>The UK, the US, and many European nations are generally considered the most affluent nations that regularly operate at the top of the growth rankings. However, given the current economic market sentiment, that focus has now swung away. Although many other countries are feeling the pinch, some economies in Asia are considered to be green shoots that can be used to insulate investments against the poor economic outlook.</p>
<h2>The United States will Remain at the Top</h2>
<p>Over the last decade, economists have predicted that China will overtake the US in the global economic superpower charts. There was mass agreement that this transition would take place at some point between 2020 and 2030. However, following China’s recent zero-Covid policies, the economy is expected to retract. With the American economy finding its feet again following the 2020 mega shock, these predictions have now been pushed back.</p>
<h2>Guyana will Rise</h2>
<p>Rising out of economic obscurity, Guyana has never really been considered a country with serious economic potential. That was until a recent oil discovery caused the country to fly to the top of every GDP growth chart. Most economists have put their annual growth somewhere in the region of 50% per year, due to the mega discovery of immense reserves of oil.</p>
<p>Their production of this scarce commodity is expected to spiral over the next few years as oil companies begin to set up in the country and plough vast resources and profit into drilling. Only time will tell whether this will be a good or bad thing for Guyana. Venezuela currently has the greatest amount of oil in the world, but it is one of the world’s weakest economies and one of the most volatile countries, so it all depends on how well this huge discovery is managed.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microstrategy-shares-lowest-bitcoin-sale/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/5-economic-predictions-for-2023/">5 Economic Predictions for 2023</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/5-economic-predictions-for-2023/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>MicroStrategy Shares Sink to Lowest Level Since 2020 Following Bitcoin Sale Revelation</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/microstrategy-shares-lowest-bitcoin-sale/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/microstrategy-shares-lowest-bitcoin-sale/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 12:30:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[microstrategy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=230987</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microstrategy-shares-lowest-bitcoin-sale/">MicroStrategy Shares Sink to Lowest Level Since 2020 Following Bitcoin Sale Revelation</a></p>
<p>MicroStrategy saw its shares plummet to their lowest level for more than two years after a recent BTC filing.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microstrategy-shares-lowest-bitcoin-sale/">MicroStrategy Shares Sink to Lowest Level Since 2020 Following Bitcoin Sale Revelation</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microstrategy-shares-lowest-bitcoin-sale/">MicroStrategy Shares Sink to Lowest Level Since 2020 Following Bitcoin Sale Revelation</a></p>
<p>Shares of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/microstrategy-incorporated/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">MicroStrategy Inc</a> (NASDAQ: MSTR) recently hit their lowest level since August 2020 following its first-ever <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin sale</a>. MicroStrategy’s stock dropped 1.1% to $136.63 Thursday and is at a 75% drawdown year-to-date (YTD).</p>
<p>In a recent filing, the cloud-based business intelligence company disclosed that it <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microstrategy-bitcoin-holdings-selling-units/">sold</a> 704 BTC on December 22nd for $11.8 million. According to MicroStrategy, it sold the Bitcoin for tax purposes but re-purchased 810 more two days later. Altogether, the cloud computing company said it bought roughly 2,395 Bitcoin between November and December 21st. This acquisition took place through MicroStrategy’s subsidiary MacroStrategy, costing approximately $42.8 million in cash.</p>
<p>Miller Tabak + Co chief market strategist Matt Maley weighed in on the MicroStrategy BTC development. According to him, the company’s reputation as a devoted token buyer amid crypto winter is worrisome to investors. As Maley <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2022-12-29/microstrategy-mstr-hits-lowest-since-2020-after-bitcoin-sale-announcement?srnd=technology-vp" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">put</a> it:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Investors seem to be concerned about their announcement that they’re still a net buyer of crypto. Most people have been hoping that MSTR might scale back their holdings after Michael Saylor stepped down as CEO. This news means they don’t seem to want to do that anytime soon.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Jefferies analyst Brent Thill also suggested that MicroStrategy may be overleveraged with its current Bitcoin position. According to Thill:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Given MicroStrategy’s $2.4 billion in leverage, we believe the company may have too much leverage for Bitcoin and could face some liquidity risk.”</p></blockquote>
<p>As of December 27th, MicroStrategy held around 132,500 Bitcoin worth more than $4 billion. The digital-servicing company paid an average purchase price of $30,397 per token.</p>
<h2>MicroStrategy Stock Lowest Level Comes After Prosperous 2020/2021</h2>
<p>During the pandemic, MicroStrategy became widely known for its BTC acquisitions, primarily led by co-founder and former CEO <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/michael-saylor/">Michael Saylor</a>. Although Saylor stepped down as CEO to take on the role of executive chairman earlier this year, he still leads MicroStrategy’s Bitcoin strategy. The company’s stock traded at roughly $120 before its first BTC purchases in 2020 and hit an all-time high of $1,315 in early 2021.</p>
<p>The latest lowest level of MicroStrategy stock reflects the severity of the crypto winter that has gripped an underwhelming year. However, despite its recent BTC selloff, many crypto devotees still believed that Bitcoin could end the year on a promising note.</p>
<h2>Lightning Network Enterprise Plugins</h2>
<p>In other recent MicroStrategy news, the company plans to <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microstrategy-plugins-lightning-network/">launch</a> enterprise plugins on Lightning Network next year. According to Saylor, the delays associated with credit card usage for such transactions would not affect the network’s speed.</p>
<p>Speaking at a Twitter Spaces event, Saylor also disclosed that MicroStrategy was working to introduce new services. These include marketing solutions, cybersecurity, and e-commerce that would benefit enterprise users. According to Saylor, MicroStrategy already has teams concurrently developing the different products of its agenda. The cloud-based company intends to unveil these products in the first quarter of next year and launch them sometime later.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-stocks-2022-bearish/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microstrategy-shares-lowest-bitcoin-sale/">MicroStrategy Shares Sink to Lowest Level Since 2020 Following Bitcoin Sale Revelation</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/microstrategy-shares-lowest-bitcoin-sale/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>European Stocks Closes 2022 on Bearish Sentiment Fueled by Macroeconomic Factors</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-stocks-2022-bearish/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-stocks-2022-bearish/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 12:25:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftse 100]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stoxx europe 600]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=231001</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-stocks-2022-bearish/">European Stocks Closes 2022 on Bearish Sentiment Fueled by Macroeconomic Factors</a></p>
<p>The European stocks have experienced more headwinds in the past few months after the Kremlin imposed an indefinite oil cut-off to Eurozone countries.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-stocks-2022-bearish/">European Stocks Closes 2022 on Bearish Sentiment Fueled by Macroeconomic Factors</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-stocks-2022-bearish/">European Stocks Closes 2022 on Bearish Sentiment Fueled by Macroeconomic Factors</a></p>
<p>European stocks are set to close 2022 on a bearish sentiment as global markets prepare to close trading later today. Fueled by the ongoing Russia-Ukraine war, record high inflation, and tightening monetary policy, the Euro economic zone is set to experience more headwinds in 2023 and forward. Moreover, the Euro to US dollar derivative has been below the ratio of 1 for the first time since the 2008 financial crisis in 2022.</p>
<p>Nonetheless, European stocks are not secluded from global sell pressure that has sustained in 2022. Furthermore, cryptocurrency and big tech companies from the United States have been on a falling trend in the past twelve months.</p>
<p>Notably, the STOXX Europe 600 Index Continuous Contract is down approximately 12 percent in the past twelve months. During the mid-London trading session, the FTSE 100 exchanged at 7,497.01, down approximately 0.21 percent.</p>
<p>The poor stock performance has, however, coincided with rising food, oil, and gas prices fueled by the Russia-Ukraine war and subsequent sanctions.</p>
<p>As such, market strategists expect the developed economies to struggle in posting growth during the next decade.</p>
<p>“I think that we are probably going to move into a decade of very, very poor growth in which developed economies are going to find themselves lucky with 1% growth per annum if they are able to achieve it…” Daniel Lacalle, author and chief economist at Tressis Gestion.</p>
<h2>Closer Look at European Stocks in 2022</h2>
<p>The European stocks have experienced more headwinds in the past few months after the Kremlin imposed an indefinite oil cut-off to Eurozone countries. The European stand-off is expected to continue long after the White House recently announced $1.85 billion in military assistance for Ukraine, including a transfer of the Patriot Air Defense System.</p>
<p>As the war escalates, market strategists are concerned it may escalate to World War III.</p>
<p>The situation has not been made any better after Covid restrictions significantly disrupted the global supply. As sanctions affect individual companies, analysts forecast next year’s growth will be determined by fundamental factors.</p>
<p>“Next year I think it’s not going to be the Fed determining the market, I think it’s going to be companies, fundamentals, companies that can grow earnings, defend their margins, probably move higher,” Patrick Armstrong, chief investment officer at Plurimi Wealth LLP, <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/12/30/european-stocks-set-to-log-worst-year-since-2018.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">told</a> CNBC’s “Squawk Box Europe” on Friday.</p>
<p>The UK Brexit continues to be a hectic maneuver for most companies in relation to their supply chain management. Moreover, obligations formerly set by the European Parliament on member states have significantly changed.</p>
<p>Notably, the European Union is readying to <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/digital-euro-transaction-limit/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">launch</a> its digital Euro to bolster its struggling economy.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cathie-wood-5m-coinbase-stock/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-stocks-2022-bearish/">European Stocks Closes 2022 on Bearish Sentiment Fueled by Macroeconomic Factors</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-stocks-2022-bearish/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cathie Wood Stacks Up Additional $5M Worth of Coinbase Stock</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/cathie-wood-5m-coinbase-stock/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/cathie-wood-5m-coinbase-stock/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 12:19:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investors News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ark invest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cathie Wood]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[grayscale]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=230973</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cathie-wood-5m-coinbase-stock/">Cathie Wood Stacks Up Additional $5M Worth of Coinbase Stock</a></p>
<p>Many investors on Wall Street are increasingly becoming bullish about the crypto ecosystem and the technology powering the different digital assets.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cathie-wood-5m-coinbase-stock/">Cathie Wood Stacks Up Additional $5M Worth of Coinbase Stock</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cathie-wood-5m-coinbase-stock/">Cathie Wood Stacks Up Additional $5M Worth of Coinbase Stock</a></p>
<p>Prominent fund manager, Cathie Wood has <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2022/12/30/cathie-wood-continues-buying-coinbases-dip-with-5-million-stock-purchase/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">acquired</a> an additional 158,000 shares of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase Global Inc</a> (NASDAQ: COIN) worth a total of $5 million as the trading platform’s stock continues to take a beating when compared to its spot price earlier in the year. Despite the 6.92% close on Thursday pushing the stock to a price of $34.78, Coinbase (COIN) is still trading around its lowest, having dropped as much as 86% in the year-to-date period.</p>
<p>While the selloffs show that investors are notably shunning the shares of the trading behemoth, Cathie Wood is increasingly becoming bullish on it. The latest acquisition was made through her company’s ARK Fintech Innovation ETF (ARKF) and it comes off as the fourth time Ark Invest will be injected capital into the firm’s stock.</p>
<p>Earlier in December, a total of $3.2 million of the exchange’s stock was acquired by the company as it looks to solidify its bag at this time when most shares are adjudged to be close to their bottom.</p>
<p>Cathie Wood gained her reputation by backing promising stocks that later go on to outperform the general market. Her early bets in Coinbase paid off until the crypto winter sets in that defied all expert’s bullish permutations. This so-called crypto winter has not deterred her interests in Coinbase or other <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> (BTC) focused investments.</p>
<p>As she is gorging up COIN, so also is she stacking up shares from the Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC), a product on offer by Grayscale Investments, a subsidiary of the Digital Currency Group. In November, Cathie Wood purchased a total of 176,945 shares for a cumulative price of $1.5 million. These investments are currently down as the shares of GBTC are changing hands at a 48% discount to the net asset value of BTC.</p>
<h2>Cathie Wood and the Stock Acquisition Motive</h2>
<p>Many investors on Wall Street are increasingly becoming bullish about the crypto ecosystem and the technology powering the different digital assets. While many are Bitcoin maximalists who would like to gain exposure to the coin, the acquisition of Coinbase Inc’s stock is a subtle but safe attempt by Cathie Wood to gain exposure to the nascent asset class.</p>
<p>Coinbase provides a platform for crypto trading and custody for both retail and institutional investors. Its business is directly impacted by the events in the broader market which is largely determined by Bitcoin. The low trading values of the exchange’s stock are complementary to the <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/bitcoin" target="_blank" rel="noopener">more than 65% drop</a> in the value of the digital currency in the year-to-date period.</p>
<p>For Cathie Wood&#8217;s Ark Invest and its associated investment funds, buying shares of Coinbase and Grayscale is an indirect way to expose its clients to the growing world of crypto without the associated risks involved in holding the physical digital currency.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/vaneck-russia-etfs-russia-invasion-ukraine/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cathie-wood-5m-coinbase-stock/">Cathie Wood Stacks Up Additional $5M Worth of Coinbase Stock</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/cathie-wood-5m-coinbase-stock/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>VanEck Suspends Russia ETFs Due to Prolonged Inactivity after Russia’s Invasion of Ukraine</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/vaneck-russia-etfs-russia-invasion-ukraine/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/vaneck-russia-etfs-russia-invasion-ukraine/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 12:09:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blackrock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[erus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vaneck]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=230958</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/vaneck-russia-etfs-russia-invasion-ukraine/">VanEck Suspends Russia ETFs Due to Prolonged Inactivity after Russia&#8217;s Invasion of Ukraine</a></p>
<p>Investment firm VanEck recently suspended two Russia ETFs as Western sanctions bite hard on profitability.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/vaneck-russia-etfs-russia-invasion-ukraine/">VanEck Suspends Russia ETFs Due to Prolonged Inactivity after Russia&#8217;s Invasion of Ukraine</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/vaneck-russia-etfs-russia-invasion-ukraine/">VanEck Suspends Russia ETFs Due to Prolonged Inactivity after Russia&#8217;s Invasion of Ukraine</a></p>
<p>New York-based asset manager VanEck is liquidating its Russia exchange-traded funds (ETFs) following a lack of Western investment interest. According to VanEck, since the Russian-Ukraine strife began, US investment in Russia has effectively dried up. The Russian market has taken a hit since the country invaded neighboring Ukraine, with Moscow&#8217;s stock market closing temporarily. Furthermore, the ongoing Western sanctions against Russia essentially prohibit its major stocks, including Gazprom, from trading in the West. This unsavory development is causing liquidity issues for the funds.</p>
<p>Touching on the decision to wind down its Russia ETFs due to inactivity, VanEck explained in a press release Wednesday:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The Funds&#8217; inability to buy, sell, and take or make delivery of Russian securities has made it impossible to manage the Funds consistent with their investment objectives. The Funds will not engage in any business or investment activities except for the purposes of winding up their affairs.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The investment management firm&#8217;s two Russia ETFs, the VanEck Russia ETF (RSX) and VanEck Russia Small-Cap ETF (RSX), effectively froze after March 4th. At the beginning of 2022, the RSX fund had over $1.3 billion in assets under management (AUM).</p>
<p>Presently, VanEck put fund redemptions on hold while it liquidates the positions. The firm also suggested that redemption remains suspended pursuant to a Securities Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) order. Furthermore, VanEck said it would distribute any liquidation proceeds to investors on January 12th next year.</p>
<h2>VanEck Unwinding of Russia ETFs Follows Similar Franklin Templeton, BlackRock Moves</h2>
<p>VanEck&#8217;s move to unwind its Russia ETFs comes on the heels of a similar announcement by Franklin Templeton. <a href="https://www.franklintempleton.com/press-releases/etfs/2022/update-on-franklin-ftse-russia-etf-flru" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Last week</a>, the leading asset management firm suspended its FTSE Russia ETF (FLRU) shares redemption pursuant to an SEC-exemptive order.</p>
<p>However, Franklin Templeton also stated that FLRU will remain in existence until at least December 31st, 2023. The reason is to allow the ETF to sell the securities if conditions allow. The fund could terminate sooner upon selling all Russian securities before the end of next year. The Franklin Templeton FTSE Russia ETF could also terminate if its funds no longer represent valid interests in their issuers.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20220803005961/en/BlackRock-Update-on-the-iShares-MSCI-Russia-ETF-ERUS" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">In early August</a>, the world&#8217;s largest asset manager, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/blackrock/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BlackRock</a>, also suspended its iShares MSCI Russia ETF (ERUS). In a press statement at the time, the New York-based multinational investment company explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Russia&#8217;s invasion of Ukraine has prompted a range of sanctions and other capital controls that prevent BlackRock and other non-Russian investors from buying and selling Russian securities. As a result, ERUS&#8217; current holdings of Russian equity securities cannot immediately be liquidated.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>BlackRock also said that it would start liquidating ERUS later that month. According to the firm, it would distribute its current liquid assets to shareholders minus the amount of a reserve estimation. This reserve could cover ERUS&#8217; anticipated transaction costs associated with the liquidation.</p>
<p>BlackRock also stated back in August that the fund&#8217;s liquidation could take an extended period.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/doj-classify-mngo-commodity/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/vaneck-russia-etfs-russia-invasion-ukraine/">VanEck Suspends Russia ETFs Due to Prolonged Inactivity after Russia&#8217;s Invasion of Ukraine</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/vaneck-russia-etfs-russia-invasion-ukraine/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Did DOJ Just Classify MNGO as Commodity?</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/doj-classify-mngo-commodity/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/doj-classify-mngo-commodity/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 12:01:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Avraham Eisenberg]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cea]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[doj]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fbi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mango markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mngo]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[us doj]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[usdc]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=230946</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/doj-classify-mngo-commodity/">Did DOJ Just Classify MNGO as Commodity?</a></p>
<p>The arrest of Mango Markets exploiter has  drawn reactions from the crypto community, particularly regarding the terms of the charges he faces.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/doj-classify-mngo-commodity/">Did DOJ Just Classify MNGO as Commodity?</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/doj-classify-mngo-commodity/">Did DOJ Just Classify MNGO as Commodity?</a></p>
<p>Mango (MNGO) markets exploiter, Avraham Eisenberg, was recently arrested in Puerto Rico on charges bordering on market manipulation and fraud. The <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/mango-markets-attacker-arrested-puerto-rico/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">arrest</a> followed after the crypto investor took advantage of a loophole on the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-decentralized-finance-defi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">DeFi</a> trading platform Mango Markets. The mid-October exploit saw Eisenberg making away with $110 million worth of crypto, eventually causing the platform to become insolvent.</p>
<p>Eisenberg, however, insists that he and his team had only “operated a highly profitable trading strategy.” He also maintains that they only carried out market actions that were legally permitted by the protocol.</p>
<p>While his claims will be determined by relevant authorities, his arrest on Monday has expectedly drawn reactions from the crypto community, especially regarding the terms of the charges.</p>
<h2>Eisenberg Slammed with Commodities Fraud Charges in MNGO Case</h2>
<p>It is particularly noteworthy that in such a case involving a coin such as Mango Markets’ native token MNGO, commodities fraud charges are being pressed. Count one of the charges read in part:</p>
<blockquote><p>“AVRAHAM EISENBERG, the defendant, willfully and knowingly, directly and indirectly, used and employed, and attempted to use and employ, in connection with a swap, a contract of sale of a commodity in interstate and foreign commerce.”</p></blockquote>
<p>In further clarification of the terms, however,  US Federal Bureau of Investigation special agent Brandon Racz <a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.nysd.591629/gov.uscourts.nysd.591629.1.0.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener">wrote</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“I understand that virtual currencies, such as USDC, are ‘commodities’ under the Commodity Exchange Act.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Considering this line of thought, the DoJ and FBI appear to be saying that USDC is a commodity, and so MNGO/USDC futures fit the statutory definition of a swap, which must be based on the value of at least one commodity.</p>
<p>Recall, Eisenberg&#8217;s actions involved manipulating the price of the exchange’s MNGO coin against that of the USDC stablecoin. This was before he then took out loans against his collateral.</p>
<p>For what it&#8217;s worth,  there wouldn&#8217;t be so much controversy around claims that USDC is a commodity. At least, not as much as there would be uproars if the same was claimed for a coin like MNGO. However, it seems DoJ consciously chose its words to prosecute the case based on the Commodity Exchange Act (CEA). At least, for the sake of convenience, and the fact that the CEA directly tackles price manipulation.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/baidu-beijing-driverless-robotaxi-tests/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/doj-classify-mngo-commodity/">Did DOJ Just Classify MNGO as Commodity?</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/doj-classify-mngo-commodity/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Baidu Secures License for Its Beijing-based Driverless Robotaxi Tests</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/baidu-beijing-driverless-robotaxi-tests/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/baidu-beijing-driverless-robotaxi-tests/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 11:55:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Transportation News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[baidu]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=230972</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/baidu-beijing-driverless-robotaxi-tests/">Baidu Secures License for Its Beijing-based Driverless Robotaxi Tests</a></p>
<p>Baidu believes that its Robotaxis should eventually cost half of the cost incurred in a commercial car with a driver. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/baidu-beijing-driverless-robotaxi-tests/">Baidu Secures License for Its Beijing-based Driverless Robotaxi Tests</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/baidu-beijing-driverless-robotaxi-tests/">Baidu Secures License for Its Beijing-based Driverless Robotaxi Tests</a></p>
<p>Earlier today on Friday, December 30, China&#8217;s largest search engine and tech giant Baidu said that it has <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/baidu-gets-license-driverless-robotaxi-050648787.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">secured</a> the first license to test driverless vehicles on the roads of Beijing. As a result, the company is planning to add an additional 200 Robotaxis to its wide network across China over the coming year 2023.</p>
<h2>Baidu Conducts Robotaxi Tests in Beijing</h2>
<p>Headquartered in Beijing, Baidu generates most of its revenue from search engine services. However, it now wants to diversify its business operations and has been experimenting with self-driving technologies over the last five years.</p>
<p>Earlier this year in August 2022, Baidu <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/baidu-robotaxis-beijing-ride-hailing/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">said</a> that its Robotaxis have already captured 10% ride-hailing market in the suburbs of Beijing city. By then, the company was operating more than 100 robotaxis in the Beijing suburb of Yizhuang. For the first time, Baidu began offering free robotaxi rides in Yizhuang back in October 2020.</p>
<p>However, last year in 2021, Baidu started charging fees for its robotaxi service Apollo Go. As per Baidu&#8217;s predictions, Robotaxis should eventually cost half of the cost incurred in a commercial car with a driver. The Apollo Go service from Baidu currently operates in Wuhan and Chongqing without the need for a safety driver. By the end of the third quarter of 2022, Baidu said that it has delivered a total of 1.4 million driverless rides.</p>
<h2>Further Plans Ahead for Baidu</h2>
<p>In a step towards offering commercial Robotaxi services in china&#8217;s capital, Baidu is planning to start testing 10 fully autonomous vehicles in a technology park developed by the government of Beijing. Baidu has a major advantage since other companies from outside of China have pulled back their plans of launching their fully autonomous vehicles.</p>
<p>Even Tesla&#8217;s “Full Self Driving” system still requires a human behind the wheel in order to take control anytime when required. Even in the United States, Tesla has been facing a criminal investigation over their claims that the company&#8217;s electric vehicles can drive themselves.</p>
<p>General Motors Co&#8217;s robotaxi unit Cruise is also planning to bring several hundred autonomous vehicles onto the streets of San Francisco and other US cities in the coming year of 2023. Earlier this month, US auto safety regulators stated that they are planning to open a safety probe of the autonomous driving system introduced by Cruise amid reports that the vehicles braked inappropriately.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cbrt-payment-digital-turkish-lira-test/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/baidu-beijing-driverless-robotaxi-tests/">Baidu Secures License for Its Beijing-based Driverless Robotaxi Tests</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/baidu-beijing-driverless-robotaxi-tests/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>CBRT Announces Successful First Payment of Digital Turkish Lira with More Test Scheduled for Q1 2023</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/cbrt-payment-digital-turkish-lira-test/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/cbrt-payment-digital-turkish-lira-test/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 10:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cbrt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital lira]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=230967</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cbrt-payment-digital-turkish-lira-test/">CBRT Announces Successful First Payment of Digital Turkish Lira with More Test Scheduled for Q1 2023</a></p>
<p>According to CBRT, the Digital Turkish Lira needs vigorous testing to ensure that the underlying distributed ledger technology does not fail after rollout.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cbrt-payment-digital-turkish-lira-test/">CBRT Announces Successful First Payment of Digital Turkish Lira with More Test Scheduled for Q1 2023</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cbrt-payment-digital-turkish-lira-test/">CBRT Announces Successful First Payment of Digital Turkish Lira with More Test Scheduled for Q1 2023</a></p>
<p>BBThe Central Bank of the Republic of Türkiye (CBRT) has announced a successful first payment transaction using the Digital Turkish Lira. As the county grapples with high inflation under President Tayyip Erdogan, CBRT intends to scale up its pilot test program in 2023 with selected financial institutions. Notably, Turkey is conducting the viability use case for the Digital Turkish Lira until 2025.</p>
<p>According to a press release shared on December 29, the findings of the Digital Lira pilot test program will be shared with the public in a comprehensive report. Moreover, the CBRT intends to find out how digital identification will affect the Digital Lira program.</p>
<p>“In 2023, the CBRT will expand the Digital Turkish Lira Collaboration Platform to involve selected banks and financial technology companies, and will unveil advanced phases of the pilot study that will further widen the participation,”  CBRT <a href="https://www.tcmb.gov.tr/wps/wcm/connect/EN/TCMB+EN/Main+Menu/Announcements/Press+Releases/2022/ANO2022-55" target="_blank" rel="noopener">noted</a> in the press release.</p>
<p>According to CBRT, the Digital Turkish Lira needs vigorous testing to ensure that the underlying distributed ledger technology does not fail after rollout. Furthermore, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-central-bank-digital-currency-cbdc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CBDCs</a> are meant to complement the fiat system on a global scale. Additionally, the digital asset economy is expected to heavily rely on CBDCs to thrive in the future.</p>
<p>“The CBRT will continue to run tests for authentic architectural setups designed in areas such as the use of distributed ledger technologies in payment systems and the integration of these technologies with instant payment systems,” the bank added.</p>
<h2>More Details on the Digital Turkish Lira</h2>
<p>Following the boom of cryptocurrency and blockchain technology in the past decades, governments worldwide are researching ways to expand their economies via digital assets. Turkey &#8211; strategically located between Europe and Asia -is well poised to benefit from the digital economy through its Digital Turkish Lira.</p>
<p>Furthermore, all G7 economies and 18 out of the G20 countries are in the development stage for their CBDCs, as of December 2022, according to atlanticcouncil.org. Reportedly, Australia, Thailand, Brazil, India, South Korea, and Russia intend to continue or begin pilot testing in 2023.</p>
<p>The sanctioning of Russia and other countries from the US dollar payment system has motivated most nations to develop their independent infrastructure. Moreover, 11 countries, including Jamaica and Nigeria, have fully launched their CBDC.</p>
<p>As such, the republic of Turkey is keen to develop a highly competitive and interoperable Digital Lira. The launch of the CBDC comes at a time the economy of Turkey is struggling with high inflation.</p>
<p>Nonetheless, Ali Babacan, a founding member of DEVA &#8211; Turkey’s opposition party &#8211; is not convinced that the Digital Lira will solve the country’s economic crisis.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/solana-2022-drops-crypto-list/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cbrt-payment-digital-turkish-lira-test/">CBRT Announces Successful First Payment of Digital Turkish Lira with More Test Scheduled for Q1 2023</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/cbrt-payment-digital-turkish-lira-test/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>