<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 11:48:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>TABOO Pushes Its Valuation to $250M Following $10M Funding Round</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/taboo-valuation-250m-10m-funding/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/taboo-valuation-250m-10m-funding/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 11:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funding News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TABOO]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=254594</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/taboo-valuation-250m-10m-funding/">TABOO Pushes Its Valuation to $250M Following $10M Funding Round</a></p>
<p>The TABOO token was designed to serve as a major utility token to help every user of the platform to get the most utility from using the services. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/taboo-valuation-250m-10m-funding/">TABOO Pushes Its Valuation to $250M Following $10M Funding Round</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/taboo-valuation-250m-10m-funding/">TABOO Pushes Its Valuation to $250M Following $10M Funding Round</a></p>
<p>TABOO, an adult entertainment platform, has raised a sum of $10 million in funding as it seeks expansion of its service offering using the power of blockchain technology. According to a press release shared with Coinspeaker, TABOO is now valued at $250 million following the funding round.</p>
<p>According to the announcement, the funding round for TABOO was led by a private family office headed by a former senior executive from American multinational investment banking giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/jpmorgan-chase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">JPMorgan Chase &amp; Co</a> (NYSE: JPM). The funding will serve multiple purposes in helping to reposition TABOO as the high-growth platform that it is designed to be.</p>
<p>The cash injection will be specifically pushed to boost the platform’s growth, improve its products, and enhance security measures. Additionally, it will be used to boost marketing efforts and pursue strategic acquisitions that can help in expanding the brand of the adult content platform.</p>
<p>That blockchain technology can be used to revitalize any industry is a fact that has been proven with many innovative decentralized applications that have been launched over the past few years. TABOO is designed to take care of a rather less penetrated industry in Web 3.0.</p>
<p>As a content creation platform, TABOO uses blockchain and<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/#:~:text=A%20non%2Dfungible%20token%20refers,proofs%20of%20authenticity%20and%20ownership." target="_blank" rel="noopener"> Non-Fungible Tokens</a> (NFT) to redefine curation and distribution. With the right capital base that it now boasts of, TABOO will explore new innovations that will help it expand its global market share while competing favorably.</p>
<p>The support for the digital currency and project by investors is a recognition of the unique fundamentals driving the platform which also translates to a viable stake in a protocol that has a ready market.</p>
<p>“We are excited to partner with TABOO and support its growth in the adult entertainment industry. We see tremendous value in the platform and the doors it will open for TABOO to get listed on all top exchanges and create a global legacy,” a spokesperson for the Family office said.</p>
<h2>TABOO Funding: a Boost for the Token</h2>
<p>The TABOO token was designed to serve as a major utility token to help every user of the platform to get the most utility from using the services. TABOO as a digital currency is set to benefit more from the funding round as the publicity the capital raise has introduced has made it gain more popularity among Web 3.0 users.</p>
<p>While it remains one of the digital currencies that has been well battered by the crypto winter, having touched a high of $600 million valuation at its peak, investors can be assured of the stability and long-term prospects for growth for the digital currency. With the target market and unending demand for its products, the founding team is optimistic the project can live up to its expectations in the long term.</p>
<p>“We are thrilled to have secured this funding, which will enable us to take TABOO to the next level,” said James, the CEO of TABOO further emphasized: “We believe that blockchain and NFTs are the future of adult entertainment, and we are determined to lead the way. This investment allows us to do just that and become a household name.”</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/blockfi-custodial-300m-repayment/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/taboo-valuation-250m-10m-funding/">TABOO Pushes Its Valuation to $250M Following $10M Funding Round</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/taboo-valuation-250m-10m-funding/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>BlockFi Custodial Customers to Receive $300M in Repayment, While BIA Holders Risk Losing Investment to Company’s Creditors</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/blockfi-custodial-300m-repayment/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/blockfi-custodial-300m-repayment/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 10:33:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockfi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=254626</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/blockfi-custodial-300m-repayment/">BlockFi Custodial Customers to Receive $300M in Repayment, While BIA Holders Risk Losing Investment to Company&#8217;s Creditors</a></p>
<p>A judge has approved repayment for BlockFi custodial wallet holders but said interest-bearing funds still belong to the bankrupt company. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/blockfi-custodial-300m-repayment/">BlockFi Custodial Customers to Receive $300M in Repayment, While BIA Holders Risk Losing Investment to Company&#8217;s Creditors</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/blockfi-custodial-300m-repayment/">BlockFi Custodial Customers to Receive $300M in Repayment, While BIA Holders Risk Losing Investment to Company&#8217;s Creditors</a></p>
<p>BlockFi custodial wallet users could receive a massive $300 million repayment from the bankrupt digital asset lender. On Thursday, a New Jersey judge ruled that the assets locked in BlockFi&#8217;s custodial accounts belong to clients rather than the company&#8217;s estate. However, the judge further ruled that another $375 million that users sought to transfer from interest-bearing accounts following November&#8217;s withdrawal suspension still belong to BlockFi.</p>
<p>As Judge Michael Kaplan <a href="https://en.ethereumworldnews.com/blockfi-custodial-account-300-million/amp/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">put</a> it:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The court finds that all digital assets held by the debtors in custodial omnibus wallets are indeed client property and not the property of the bankruptcy estates, subject, of course, to possible avoidance and clawback rights.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Meanwhile, Judge Kaplan&#8217;s less-than-welcome address to BlockFi interest-bearing (BIA) holders <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/05/11/blockfi-customers-can-be-repaid-300m-held-in-custodial-accounts-judge-says/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">read</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;No transfer requests by customers between the BIA and the custodial wallet accounts initiated after 8.15 pm on November 10th, 2022, were effectuated and completed. BIA account holders deposited their assets into these accounts with the full knowledge that they were undertaking certain risks in exchange for the chance of greater returns.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Details of BlockFi Bankruptcy Case</h2>
<p>Kaplan stressed his BIA ruling despite BlockFi&#8217;s user front-end seemingly confirming the successful transfer of funds back to customers. The bankruptcy judge spared custodial wallet holders from the same fate as BIA customers because [custodials] &#8220;did not share this risk or return.&#8221; As a result, custodial ownership of non-estate property should not be diluted by &#8220;those who took on such risks&#8221;.</p>
<p>Bankruptcy laws support the immediate return of funds belonging to customers rather than having said funds divided up among the company&#8217;s estate&#8217;s creditors. In BlockFi&#8217;s case, custodial repayment was delayed by a dispute over funds held in the company&#8217;s interest-bearing accounts. Customers had attempted to liquidate these funds after November 10th following the suspension of withdrawals and transfers. BlockFi&#8217;s BIA holders also tried another transfer on November 18th when the crypto lender instituted corresponding changes in the app.</p>
<p>In early November, BlockFi froze the funds in its interest-bearing accounts as ripples from the collapse of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a> permeated the crypto ecosystem. The New Jersey-based digital asset lender ultimately <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/blockfi-chapter-11-bankruptcy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy</a> on November 28th – a few weeks after the FTX crash.</p>
<h2>BIA Customer Attorney Argues for Same Favorable Repayment Treatment of Clients as Custodial Wallet Holders</h2>
<p>Meanwhile, before BlockFi&#8217;s present bankruptcy court BIA ruling, an attorney representing the affected customers had disapproved of perceived repayment optics.</p>
<p>At a Monday hearing, Deborah Kovsky-Apap of Troutman Pepper argued for including her BIA clients in any repayment schemes. Kovsky-Apap pointed out that her clients all attempted to transfer BIA holdings during the interim period between November 10th and 18th. The attorney said disregarding the &#8220;plain language of the terms of service&#8221; that promises instant transactions would be unfair. In addition, Kovsky-Apap suggested that BlockFi was discriminatory in its treatment of customers who all faced the same situation.</p>
<p>BlockFi trial lawyer and representative Michael B. Slade said the company had yet to complete its assets&#8217; sales in other developments. Slade&#8217;s revelation came amid reports that some clients received email confirmation validating said assets&#8217; sales.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-27000-us-regulatory/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/blockfi-custodial-300m-repayment/">BlockFi Custodial Customers to Receive $300M in Repayment, While BIA Holders Risk Losing Investment to Company&#8217;s Creditors</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/blockfi-custodial-300m-repayment/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin (BTC) Price Tanks Under $27,000 amid Rising US Regulatory Pressures</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-27000-us-regulatory/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-27000-us-regulatory/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 09:43:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bictoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[federal reserve]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jane street group]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jump crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[matic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[polkadot]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[polygon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=254550</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-27000-us-regulatory/">Bitcoin (BTC) Price Tanks Under $27,000 amid Rising US Regulatory Pressures</a></p>
<p>Amid the US regulatory crackdown and the fall of the crypto-friendly banks recently, the lack of liquidity has become a major issue currently in the market. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-27000-us-regulatory/">Bitcoin (BTC) Price Tanks Under $27,000 amid Rising US Regulatory Pressures</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-27000-us-regulatory/">Bitcoin (BTC) Price Tanks Under $27,000 amid Rising US Regulatory Pressures</a></p>
<p>The world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a>) continues to face more and more selling pressure as US regulatory crackdown mounts further. In the last 24 hours, the BTC price has dropped by over 2.98% and is currently trading at a price of $26,654 with a market cap of $516 billion.</p>
<p>The latest drop in the Bitcoin price comes along with a market-wide correction with the entire crypto market cap dropping to $1.1 trillion. Along with BTC, altcoins have also entered a correction of a similar magnitude.</p>
<p>The world&#8217;s second-largest crypto Ethereum (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ETH</a>) is down by 3.31% and is trading at $1,769 with a market cap of above $212 billion. Furthermore, altcoins like Polygon (MATIC), Polkadot (DOT), and others have also corrected by 3% and more, as of press time.</p>
<p>The US regulatory crackdown has recently forced more crypto firms to move out of the market. Earlier this week, two of the world&#8217;s top market-making firms &#8211; Jane Street Group and Jump Crypto &#8211; announced a pullback from the US market citing regulatory uncertainty and the difficulty of doing business.</p>
<p>Although both these firms announced an exit from the US market, they will continue their operations in the international market. However, as we know, the US is the biggest market when it comes to offering crypto liquidity. David Wells, CEO of Enclave Market <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/11/bitcoin-falls-below-27000-as-crypto-market-makers-step-back-from-us-trading.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">told</a> CNBC:</p>
<blockquote><p>“In general, we’re going to see much larger swings in price both ways since so many large market makers have significantly reduced providing. Larger market makers create more stability in prices due to the liquidity they provide,” he added. “You’ll see more frequent gaps up and down since order books are thinner in general.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>US Regulatory Crackdown Intensifies</h2>
<p>Following the collapse of the crypto exchange FTX in November 2022, the US regulatory crackdown has intensified. On the other hand, the regulators have also blamed the recent banking crisis in the US on the crypto market.</p>
<p>Earlier this year in February,  the Federal Reserve, the Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation and the Office of the Comptroller of the Currency issued a joint warning to banks over the risks associated with banking crypto firms.</p>
<p>The regulators have also been going after some of the top crypto exchanges including the giants like Coinbase and Binance. Earlier this week, crypto exchange Bittrex announced bankruptcy amid strong regulatory action by the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>.</p>
<p>Following the closure of crypto-friendly banks like Silvergate Capital and Signature Bank, the illiquidity in the market has shot up significantly. After a strong rally to $30,000 last month, Bitcoin is facing selling pressure. It is still trading at more than 65% gains year-to-date.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/metamask-us-eth-paypal/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-27000-us-regulatory/">Bitcoin (BTC) Price Tanks Under $27,000 amid Rising US Regulatory Pressures</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-27000-us-regulatory/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>MetaMask Adds Support for US-based Users to Purchase ETH via PayPal</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/metamask-us-eth-paypal/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/metamask-us-eth-paypal/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 09:39:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[metamask]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[paypal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=254578</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/metamask-us-eth-paypal/">MetaMask Adds Support for US-based Users to Purchase ETH via PayPal</a></p>
<p>MetaMask has been focused, primarily, on expanding its reach and boosting global crypto adoption.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/metamask-us-eth-paypal/">MetaMask Adds Support for US-based Users to Purchase ETH via PayPal</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/metamask-us-eth-paypal/">MetaMask Adds Support for US-based Users to Purchase ETH via PayPal</a></p>
<p>Crypto wallet MetaMask has begun rolling out PayPal-powered Ether (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ETH</a>) purchases to all its US-based users. Although it <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-metamask-crypto-services/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">added the PayPal integration</a> to its software wallet last December, the feature was not immediately available to all users in the US.</p>
<p>However, the latest reports suggest that all users in the United States may now seamlessly purchase and transfer ETH directly from their MetaMask mobile apps.</p>
<p>The rollout has been confirmed by MetaMask to be a first of its kind. According to the company, it is the first Web 3.0 wallet to offer ETH transactions via <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">PayPal</a>.</p>
<h2>MetaMask Continues Striking Partnership Deals Focused on Bolstering Crypto Adoption</h2>
<p>MetaMask has been focused, primarily, on expanding its reach and boosting global crypto adoption. To this end, it has been pushing for strategic integrations and partnerships in recent times.</p>
<p>Recall, the crypto wallet already enjoys partnerships with multiple payment providers. Some of them include MoonPay, Coinbase Pay, Transak and Wyre, and Sardine among others. Therefore, PayPal is only the latest payment firm to join its fast-growing community of payment providers.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, MetaMask also recently introduced a new feature it calls “Buy Crypto”. The feature allows users to purchase crypto with fiat currency directly from its Portfolio DApp. With the feature, users may purchase cryptocurrencies via various payment means including bank transfers and debit or credit cards.</p>
<p>Similarly, PayPal also does not come into the partnership empty-handed. The partners appear to have their goals aligned considering that PayPal has also been keen on crypto adoption. According to a Q1 <a href="https://d18rn0p25nwr6d.cloudfront.net/CIK-0001633917/195d9afa-779f-4932-b227-90f0a170923e.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a> it filed with the US Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>), PayPal now has a total of $943 million in crypto assets. And that represents about a 56% jump from what it had in the previous quarter.</p>
<p>The report, without a doubt, is proof of its efforts toward crypto adoption and MetaMask is sure to help advance those aims. MetaMask will also seek to take advantage of PayPal&#8217;s wide user base to expand its reach and offer on-ramps for its customers. As of publication, PayPal has no less than 429 million users globally.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-ai-services-ad-campaigns/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/metamask-us-eth-paypal/">MetaMask Adds Support for US-based Users to Purchase ETH via PayPal</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/metamask-us-eth-paypal/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Meta Reveals New AI Services for Ad Campaigns</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-ai-services-ad-campaigns/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-ai-services-ad-campaigns/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 09:08:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ai]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Meta]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meta ai]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=254568</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-ai-services-ad-campaigns/">Meta Reveals New AI Services for Ad Campaigns</a></p>
<p>Meta explained that AI Sandbox and Advantage service offerings would ensure enhanced and seamless ad campaigns. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-ai-services-ad-campaigns/">Meta Reveals New AI Services for Ad Campaigns</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-ai-services-ad-campaigns/">Meta Reveals New AI Services for Ad Campaigns</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/meta/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Meta Platforms Inc</a> (NASDAQ: META) recently uncovered several new artificial intelligence (AI) resources and services for advertisers. On Thursday, the Menlo Park-based tech giant announced a veritable AI “testing playground” called AI Sandbox to help advertisers build campaigns.</p>
<p>By trying out new generative AI-powered ad tools in the Meta-enabled AI Sandbox, advertisers will have access to several tools. These include text variation (generating multiple text versions for emphasis), background creation (generating background images from text inputs), and image cropping (adjusting creative assets across various surfaces).</p>
<p>Meta also announced other AI services, including updates to its collection of automated tools and services called <a href="https://www.facebook.com/business/help/733979527611858" target="_blank">Meta Advantage</a>. The company disclosed that it is working with a sample group of advertisers to test-run its new offerings and gather feedback for enhancements. Speaking on how Meta’s new offerings would ultimately enhance ad performance, the company’s vice president of monetization John Hegeman <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/11/meta-announces-ai-sandbox-and-updates-to-meta-advantage.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“The aim here, again, is really to quickly test and learn and figure out which parts of these new capabilities are turning out to be most helpful for businesses to achieve their goals.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>Meta to Roll Out New AI Services in The Summer</h2>
<p>Starting in July, Meta plans to allow advertisers to integrate some of the new AI features into existing product offerings. The company also explained that the gradual rollout of its new services is deliberate to ensure quality value proposition to its millions of ad clients.</p>
<p>As Hegeman put it:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Overall, the generative AI space is developing incredibly quickly right now, and it’s a very exciting time. Our unique opportunity is to integrate these features over time into our products.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Meta’s ‘AI Sandbox’ and ‘Advantage’ reflect the company’s ongoing efforts to secure its position at the helm of metaverse adaptation. Furthermore, the multinational technology conglomerate also seeks to stoke investor and advertiser interest in the AI space amid slowing ad growth.</p>
<p>In Meta’s <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-q1-2023-results/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">latest earnings call</a>, chief financial officer Susan Li put the company’s full-year capital expenditure between $30 billion and $33 billion. Li explained that Meta’s outlay reflected its “ongoing build-out of AI capacity to support ads, Feed, and Reels.” Furthermore, she added that the company exercised an increased investment capacity for its generative artificial intelligence initiatives.</p>
<p>Leveraging AI tech across all its apps and platforms remains Meta’s core aim as it seeks to improve end-user experience.</p>
<h2>Meta Advantage</h2>
<p>Meta recently improved Advantage to enable swifter and more innovative ad campaigns and optimized results. The company pointed out that it strengthened its Meta Advantage automated products in 2022 and has seen business adoption grow. For example, Meta noted that three times as many advertisers use Advantage+ shopping campaigns compared to 6 months ago.</p>
<p>New Meta Advantage features include deploying video creative in catalog ads and rolling out performance comparisons. In addition, users can now switch manual campaigns to Advantage+ shopping at the click of a button. This transformation allows such businesses to leverage artificial intelligence quickly and seamlessly.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/elon-musk-steps-down-twitter-ceo/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-ai-services-ad-campaigns/">Meta Reveals New AI Services for Ad Campaigns</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-ai-services-ad-campaigns/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Elon Musk to Step Down as Twitter CEO in Six Weeks</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/elon-musk-steps-down-twitter-ceo/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/elon-musk-steps-down-twitter-ceo/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Darya Rudz]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 08:52:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon musk twitter]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon musk twitter ceo]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[linda yaccarino]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[twitter]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[twitter ceo]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=254563</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/elon-musk-steps-down-twitter-ceo/">Elon Musk to Step Down as Twitter CEO in Six Weeks</a></p>
<p>During Elon Musk's leadership, Twitter suffered a few technical errors and outages.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/elon-musk-steps-down-twitter-ceo/">Elon Musk to Step Down as Twitter CEO in Six Weeks</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/elon-musk-steps-down-twitter-ceo/">Elon Musk to Step Down as Twitter CEO in Six Weeks</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/elon-musk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Elon Musk</a> has finally found a new CEO for <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/twitter/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Twitter Inc</a> after a few months of searching. Within the next six weeks, Elon Musk will step down from his position, and a new CEO whose name has not been disclosed will take over the company. Notably, Musk will remain Twitter&#8217;s executive chairman and chief technology officer, which means he will continue to oversee the company.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="474" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Excited to announce that I’ve a new CEO for X/Twitter. She will be starting in ~6 weeks!</p>
<p>My role will transition to being exec chair &amp; CTO, overseeing product, software &amp; sysops.</p>
<p>&mdash; Elon Musk (@elonmusk) <a href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1656747082571722753?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank">May 11, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Back in December 2022, Musk announced his decision to step down as Twitter CEO as soon as a replacement would be found. At that time, the billionaire published a poll asking his followers to decide whether he should stay on or quit as the CEO of the company. As we <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/elon-musk-twitter-ceo-replacement/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a>, the results of the poll that saw more than 17.5 million participants were in favor of finding another chairman, with 57.5% votes for Musk stepping down.</p>
<p>While Elon Musk has not revealed the name of the next Twitter CEO, The Wall Street Journal has <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/linda-yaccarino-in-talks-new-twitter-ceo-elon-musk-7a006bb5" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reported</a> about <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/linda-yaccarino/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Linda Yaccarino</a> being the one. Linda Yaccarino is Chairman of Global Advertising and Partnerships at NBCUniversal – one of the world&#8217;s leading media and entertainment companies in the development, production, and marketing of entertainment, news, and information. She has been with the company since 2011. Recently, there have been reports about Linda Yaccarino being in talks with Elon Musk regarding the role.</p>
<h2>Twitter Under Elon Musk&#8217;s Guidance</h2>
<p>Under Elon Musk&#8217;s leadership, Twitter has significantly transformed. Since he closed a $44 billion deal to acquire the platform, Twitter has seen mass layoffs of employees, account suspensions, content policy changes, revamp of subscription services, and more.</p>
<p>Firstly, the billionaire had slashed the company’s workforce from a high of about 7,500 to a low of 2,000 in one of the most drastic job cuts, with the aim to reduce the operational cost of the company. Notably, cutting the workforce by around 75% has raised concerns about Twitter&#8217;s capacity to maintain its platform.</p>
<p>Secondly, Twitter launched a new version of its subscription service, Twitter Blue, which allowed users to access verification if they pay a monthly fee of $8. The initiative did not work as planned. Many celebrities and high-profile figures like <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/bill-gates/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bill Gates</a>, Oprah Winfrey, Justin Bieber, Katy Perry, Kim Kardashian, and others lost their verified blue check marks as they did not subscribe to the service. As a result, the removal of blue ticks provoked confusion, many users found it rude and objected to the changes amid fears that such a system would encourage the spread of misinformation and fake news.</p>
<p>A few days after the removal of the blue ticks, Twitter started giving them back to high-profile accounts with over one million followers.</p>
<p>During Elon Musk&#8217;s leadership, Twitter also suffered a few technical errors and outages. One of them took place in February, it lasted for hours and required an emergency fix, prompting an apology from the company.</p>
<h2>Tesla Shares Affected by Musk&#8217;s Resignation</h2>
<p>Notably, Musk&#8217;s announcement about stepping down as Twitter CEO has had a positive impact on shares of <a href="https://www.google.com/search?client=safari&amp;rls=en&amp;q=tesla+coinspeaker&amp;ie=UTF-8&amp;oe=UTF-8" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tesla Inc</a> (NASDAQ: TSLA). Apparently, Tesla investors are happy about the move, as Tesla stock added 2.10% to its price and closed at $172.08 per share following the announcement. After hours, Tesla shares jumped by another 1.55% to $174.75.</p>
<p>Earlier, Tesla investors were saying that Musk was distracted by running Twitter and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/spacex/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SpaceX</a>, which affected the performance of the EV maker.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/dorsey-bluesky-musk-twitter/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/elon-musk-steps-down-twitter-ceo/">Elon Musk to Step Down as Twitter CEO in Six Weeks</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/elon-musk-steps-down-twitter-ceo/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Jack Dorsey-Backed Bluesky Goes Head-to-Head with Musk’s Twitter</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/dorsey-bluesky-musk-twitter/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/dorsey-bluesky-musk-twitter/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 07:53:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluesky]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[john dorsey]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mastodon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tesla]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[twitter]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=254560</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/dorsey-bluesky-musk-twitter/">Jack Dorsey-Backed Bluesky Goes Head-to-Head with Musk’s Twitter</a></p>
<p>While it remains unclear how the emerging decentralized social projects will generate profit, they keep getting more attention.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/dorsey-bluesky-musk-twitter/">Jack Dorsey-Backed Bluesky Goes Head-to-Head with Musk’s Twitter</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/dorsey-bluesky-musk-twitter/">Jack Dorsey-Backed Bluesky Goes Head-to-Head with Musk’s Twitter</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/jack-dorsey/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Jack Dorsey</a>-backed decentralized communications app Bluesky has positioned itself as a major rival to the popular social networking service <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/twitter/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Twitter</a>. Bluesky, which has the support of the former Twitter co-founder, was founded in 2021 and hired its first employees in the same year. How is an established app with seasoned past and existing leadership and a massive user base facing new competition with Bluesky, which came to light about two years ago?</p>
<p>Twitter has faced multiple backlash since <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/elon-musk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Elon Musk</a> acquired the company in October 2022, after which he made it a private company. The billionaire has been restructuring Twitter, and the company’s makeover has triggered new interest in decentralized social networks. As opposed to companies with CEOs, decentralized social media platforms like what Bluesky is purporting have no owners or leaders. They also do not have obligations concerning commercial or financial interests. According to advocates of decentralized social networks, these projects are less likely to collect and sell users’ data and less susceptible to censorship. As for Bluesky, the app runs on the AT protocol, a decentralized networking technology.</p>
<p>Basically, Musk’s Twitter is different from Dorsey’s Twitter. Starting with including subscription-only features to major layoffs and giving back access to controversial users, the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/twitter/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tesla</a> CEO has fundamentally changed what Twitter used to be under the former leadership.</p>
<h2>Bluesky Gains Popularity over Twitter</h2>
<p>Citing data from market intelligence firm Sensor Tower, Bluesky has gained massive popularity over the past few months. However, its total download volume is still far below Twitter’s. Data provided by the intelligence firm shows that the social messaging app recorded a whopping 606% surge in monthly mobile downloads in April. There were 628,000 mobile downloads in the month following its <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jack-dorsey-bluesky-android/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">availability on Android</a> and iOS.</p>
<p>On the other hand, Twitter had 14.9 million app downloads in April. Despite the margin between Twitter and Bluesky, Twitter’s mobile downloads only grew 2% from the previous month. The company accumulated 14.6 million downloads in March. As a matter of fact, the Elon Musk-owned social networking service saw a decline in mobile app downloads in February. The figures dropped from January&#8217;s 17.2 million to 14.05 million in the second month of the year. Besides rivaling Twitter, Bluesky is gaining more attention than the decentralized messaging app Mastodon. While many grew interested in the messaging app in November, the buzz seems to have dropped. Mastodon had just 90,000 downloads last month.</p>
<p>Members of the Bluesky project <a href="https://blueskyweb.xyz/blog/2-7-2022-overview" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announced</a> the formation of its Public Benefit LLC in February 2022. In the announcement, the team named Dorsey as one of the board members. A couple of months later, the company revealed that it got $13 million in funding and emphasized Jack’s position as a board member.</p>
<p>While it remains unclear how the emerging decentralized social projects will generate profit, they keep getting more attention. Other examples, in addition to Bluesky and Mastodon, are Lens and Farcaster.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alphabet-google-ai-venture/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/dorsey-bluesky-musk-twitter/">Jack Dorsey-Backed Bluesky Goes Head-to-Head with Musk’s Twitter</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/dorsey-bluesky-musk-twitter/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alphabet (GOOGL) Shares Aim to Revisit ATH as Wall Street Remains Bullish on Google’s AI Venture</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/alphabet-google-ai-venture/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/alphabet-google-ai-venture/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 07:46:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wall Street]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alphabet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[google]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Meta]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[microsoft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[openai]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sundar pichai]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=254561</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alphabet-google-ai-venture/">Alphabet (GOOGL) Shares Aim to Revisit ATH as Wall Street Remains Bullish on Google’s AI Venture</a></p>
<p>From a stock index perspective, Alphabet shares are among the best-performing equities with a gain of about 33% YTD.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alphabet-google-ai-venture/">Alphabet (GOOGL) Shares Aim to Revisit ATH as Wall Street Remains Bullish on Google’s AI Venture</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alphabet-google-ai-venture/">Alphabet (GOOGL) Shares Aim to Revisit ATH as Wall Street Remains Bullish on Google’s AI Venture</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/alphabet-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Alphabet Inc</a> (NASDAQ: GOOGL) shares have strongly rebounded from 2022 lows YTD. As a well-diversified tech company that has invested billions of dollars in different economic sectors, its stock market is well-poised to revisit its ATH and beyond. However, it is the artificial intelligence (AI) venture through one of its subsidiaries Google LLC that has convinced its shareholders to remain bullish. During this year’s Google <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ai-google-i-o-2023-conference/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">annual I/O Developers conference</a> held on Wednesday, it was evident that Alphabet is keen on AI development.</p>
<p>According to the latest market data provided by TradingView and MarketWatch, GOOGL shares gained approximately 11 percent in the past five days to trade around $116.63 during Thursday’s after-hours session. The recent gains materialized following a 4.32 percent pump on Thursday. Notably, GOOGL shares have ranged between 83.34 &#8211; 122.43 in the past 52 weeks with an average volume of about $38.46 million.</p>
<p>From a stock index perspective, Alphabet shares are among the best-performing equities with a gain of about 33 percent YTD.</p>
<p>“We remain bullish and view I/O as a clearing event that will help erode the heavily debated ‘AI overhang’ … and narrow GOOGL’s current valuation gap vs. peers,” <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/morgan-stanley/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Morgan Stanley</a> analyst Brian Nowak wrote.</p>
<h2>Alphabet Market Outlook</h2>
<p>According to a study conducted by MarketWatch, 52 ratings gave GOOGL shares an average target price of 129.21 with an average recommendation of Buy.</p>
<p>For instance, a <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/quote/GOOGL/analyst-ratings" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a> on May 11 by JMP Securities issued a price target of $132.00 expecting GOOGL shares to rise within 12 months, which could mean a possible 13.24 percent upside from current levels. Other analysts from B of A Securities, and Citigroup have maintained their ratings Buy on Alphabet shares.</p>
<p>The American multinational technology conglomerate holding company is, however, expecting stiff competition from <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/microsoft/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Microsoft Corporation</a> (NASDAQ: MSFT), <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/meta/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Meta Platforms Inc</a> (NASDAQ: META), and OpenAI in the artificial intelligence (AI) sector.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, the company has continued to integrate its subsidiaries through AI and cloud computing. During the 2023 first quarter financial results, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/sundar-pichai/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Sundar Pichai</a>, CEO of Alphabet and Google, noted that the company&#8217;s cloud computing sector has attracted huge global momentum to assure future growth prospects.</p>
<p>“…With Search performing well and momentum in Cloud. We introduced important product updates anchored in deep computer science and AI. Our North Star is providing the most helpful answers for our users, and we see huge opportunities ahead, continuing our long track record of innovation,” Pichai <a href="https://abc.xyz/investor/static/pdf/2023Q1_alphabet_earnings_release.pdf?cache=0924ccf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">noted</a>.</p>
<p>The introduction of AI and cloud computing has helped Alphabet reduce expenses through workforce cuts.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/emirates-record-annual-profit-3b/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alphabet-google-ai-venture/">Alphabet (GOOGL) Shares Aim to Revisit ATH as Wall Street Remains Bullish on Google’s AI Venture</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/alphabet-google-ai-venture/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Emirates Group Reports Record Annual Profit of $3B after Prior Devastations of Covid-19 Restrictions</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/emirates-record-annual-profit-3b/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/emirates-record-annual-profit-3b/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 16:45:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[emirates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[emirates group]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=254504</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/emirates-record-annual-profit-3b/">Emirates Group Reports Record Annual Profit of $3B after Prior Devastations of Covid-19 Restrictions</a></p>
<p>Emirates Group announced global freight expansion to different destinations including Tanzania, Germany, Canada, and Brazil.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/emirates-record-annual-profit-3b/">Emirates Group Reports Record Annual Profit of $3B after Prior Devastations of Covid-19 Restrictions</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/emirates-record-annual-profit-3b/">Emirates Group Reports Record Annual Profit of $3B after Prior Devastations of Covid-19 Restrictions</a></p>
<p>Emirates Group, a state-owned Dubai-based international aviation holding company, released its 2022-2023 financial results. According to the announcement, Emirates achieved a record annual profit of AED 10.9 billion, approximately $3 billion. The airline service company was impressed with the financial year 2022-2023, after posting a huge decline in operations during the prior year due to Covid-19-related constraints.</p>
<h2>Emirates and Its Record Results</h2>
<p>The Emirates Group announced its yearly revenue grew by approximately 81 percent to AED 119.8 billion or about $32.6 billion. As a result, the Emirates Group ended the financial year with the highest-ever cash balance of AED 42.5 billion or about $ 11.6 billion.</p>
<p>In this regard, the Emirates Group has since declared a dividend of AED 4.5 billion, or about $1.2 billion to its owner Investment Corporation of Dubai (ICD). The airline has attributed its success to the leadership of HH Sheikh Ahmed bin Saeed Al Maktoum, Chairman and Chief Executive, of Emirates Airlines and Group.</p>
<p>“The Group is the biggest player in the UAE’s aviation sector, which supports over 770,000 jobs and generates an estimated contribution to GDP of over US$ 47 billion (AED 172.5 billion),” the Emirates Group’s CEO noted.</p>
<p>As a state-owned organization, the Emirates Group enjoyed tremendous support in debts to sustain its huge fleet and employees through the Covid pandemic.</p>
<p>“Our ongoing investments in our brand, and our products and services, helped drive customer preference and position us favorably in the market,” Sheikh Ahmed <a href="https://www.emirates.com/media-centre/emirates-group-announces-2022-23-results/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">noted</a>.</p>
<h2>Emirates Group Market Outlook</h2>
<p>The Emirates Group continued to restructure its airline operations to attract more passengers and cargo transportation. For the financial year that ended 31 March 2023, Emirates Group announced global freight expansion to different destinations including Tanzania, Germany, Canada, and Brazil. As a result, the Group anticipates reporting even better results for the financial year ahead as all the Covid-19 restrictions have already been removed.</p>
<p>“We go into 2023-24 with a strong positive outlook and expect the Group to remain profitable. We will work hard to hit our targets while keeping a close watch on inflation, high fuel prices, and political and economic uncertainty,” Sheikh Ahmed added.</p>
<p>Following increased business operations, the Group announced its total workforce increased by 20 percent to 102,379 employees from different nationalities.  The Emirates Group also plans to continue its professional hiring spree as it intends to add more multi-billion dollar aircraft.</p>
<p>According to the announcement, the Dubai-based airline received two new 777 freighter aircraft and intends to add five additional Boeing 777-300ER. Furthermore, the airline announced that it carried 43.6 million passengers during the financial year 2022-2023, representing an uptick of 123 percent.</p>
<p>Other business news can be found <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/business/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/pacwest-shares-decline-deposits/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/emirates-record-annual-profit-3b/">Emirates Group Reports Record Annual Profit of $3B after Prior Devastations of Covid-19 Restrictions</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/emirates-record-annual-profit-3b/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>PacWest (PACW) Shares Plunge 23% after Revealing 9.5% Decline in Deposits</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/pacwest-shares-decline-deposits/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/pacwest-shares-decline-deposits/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 16:42:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wall Street]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pacwest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PacWest Bancorporation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=254506</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/pacwest-shares-decline-deposits/">PacWest (PACW) Shares Plunge 23% after Revealing 9.5% Decline in Deposits</a></p>
<p>There are various choices accessible to PacWest Bancorp that could assist the business overcome the present shares devaluation.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/pacwest-shares-decline-deposits/">PacWest (PACW) Shares Plunge 23% after Revealing 9.5% Decline in Deposits</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/pacwest-shares-decline-deposits/">PacWest (PACW) Shares Plunge 23% after Revealing 9.5% Decline in Deposits</a></p>
<p>PacWest Bancorp (NASDAQ: PACW), a regional bank based in California, is seeing its shares plummet by 23%, days after <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/11/pacwest-shares-tumble-20percent-after-regional-bank-says-deposits-fell-9point5percent-last-week.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reporting</a> a 9.5% drop in deposits for the week ending May 4, 2023.</p>
<p>Notably, the decline in deposits was attributed to media reports that the regional bank was considering several strategic options in the wake of the current banking chaos in the US. Interestingly, stocks of PacWest were already down by 50% this month, and over 70% for the year.</p>
<p>The fact that PacWest&#8217;s stock price tumbled by 20% in response to the news highlights the level of concern among investors. When a bank&#8217;s deposits decline, it can be a sign of broader financial troubles that could ultimately threaten the bank&#8217;s long-term viability. As a result, shareholders might be more inclined to sell their bank shares, which could cause the stock price to drop significantly.</p>
<p>The regional banking sector has experienced a major contagion with Western Alliance Bancorporation (NYSE: WAL) stock <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/pacwest-shares-western-alliance-collapse/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">plunging by down</a> last week. The stock has shed more than 38% and changing hands at a price of $18.20. Similarly, shares of Zions Bancorporation (NASDAQ: ZION) also dropped by 2.7%, while the SPDR S&amp;P Regional Banking ETF (KRE) were down 1.9%.</p>
<p>Since the beginning of March, regional banks in the US have been facing regulatory actions due to concerns about their financial health. As a result, Silicon Valley Bank, Signature Bank, and were finally seized by regulators. <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/first-republic-bank/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">First Republic Bank</a> (OTCMKTS: FRCB) was also taken over and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/first-republic-bank-shares-q1-2023/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">sold</a> to <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/jpmorgan-chase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">JPMorgan Chase &amp; Co</a> (NYSE: JPM).</p>
<p>It is worth noting that the failure of a bank can have serious consequences for the broader economy. It can lead to job losses, financial market instability, and damage to confidence in the banking system.</p>
<h2>PacWest Shares Recovery Options</h2>
<p>There are various choices accessible to PacWest Bancorp that could assist the business overcome the present shares devaluation. Firstly, the regional bank could improve consumer confidence by talking openly about the bank&#8217;s financial health, emphasizing its strengths, and laying out strategies to rectify any weaknesses.</p>
<p>Secondly, PacWest may consider merging with or acquiring another bank in order to gain scale and improve its competitiveness. This could also help the bank diversify its operations and expand into new markets. Meanwhile, the bank has previously announced that it is considering <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/pacwest-sale-stock-drawdown/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">selling</a> its assets after efforts to raise capital remain afloat.</p>
<p>In addition, PacWest could cut its operating expenses to boost its profitability and financial health. This could entail laying off employees or closing branches, renegotiating contracts with suppliers, or establishing more efficient processes. Markedly, the bank has established to <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/pacwest-dividend-regional-banks/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">cut down</a> shareholders&#8217; dividends.</p>
<p>Finally, PacWest may also resort to repurchasing its own stock to bolster the stock price. This could indicate to investors that the bank believes its shares are undervalued and is optimistic about its long-term prospects.</p>
<p>Ultimately, the bank will need to thoroughly assess its condition and identify the best course of action to enhance its financial performance and restore investor trust.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/circle-usdc-reserves-us-default/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/pacwest-shares-decline-deposits/">PacWest (PACW) Shares Plunge 23% after Revealing 9.5% Decline in Deposits</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/pacwest-shares-decline-deposits/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4758 metric#misses=43 metric#hit-ratio=99.1 metric#bytes=1338174 metric#prefetches=212 metric#store-reads=23 metric#store-writes=16 metric#store-hits=220 metric#store-misses=4 metric#sql-queries=34 metric#ms-total=249.63 metric#ms-cache=32.36 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.8516 metric#ms-cache-ratio=13.0 -->