<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 16:50:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Securities Designation: Cardano, Solana, and Algorand Plummet to New Lows</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/cardano-solana-algorand-securities-designation/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/cardano-solana-algorand-securities-designation/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Babafemi Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 16:50:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ada]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[algo]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[algorand]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fil]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[filecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[flow]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[matic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[polygon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sol]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[solana]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=258380</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cardano-solana-algorand-securities-designation/">Securities Designation: Cardano, Solana, and Algorand Plummet to New Lows</a></p>
<p>While the SEC’s designation of some cryptocurrencies as securities has shaken the market, the development companies behind these assets have strongly rejected the regulator’s characterization.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cardano-solana-algorand-securities-designation/">Securities Designation: Cardano, Solana, and Algorand Plummet to New Lows</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cardano-solana-algorand-securities-designation/">Securities Designation: Cardano, Solana, and Algorand Plummet to New Lows</a></p>

<p>The United States Securities and Exchange Commission’s (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) lawsuit against Binance and Coinbase has resulted in widespread volatility in the crypto market.</p>
<p>As part of its legal actions, the regulator identified <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-crypto-market-tokens-securities/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">19 new cryptocurrencies as securities</a>. According to the SEC, “Coinbase makes these crypto assets available for trading without restricting transactions to those who might treat the asset as anything other than as an investment.” </p>
<h2>Market Turmoil as Securities Designation Takes Effect</h2>
<p>Following the classification, several of these digital assets experienced a sharp decline, hitting their lowest prices to date. These assets include Cardano (ADA), Solana (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/solana/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SOL</a>), Algorand (ALGO), Polygon (MATIC), and Filecoin (FIL) to name a few.</p>
<p>According to CoinGecko data, ADA and SOL witnessed a significant drop in value. Each token lost 20% and 18% respectively. ALGO, MATIC, FIL, FLOW, BNB, SUI, and ARB also saw a dip in their prices, as investors grappled with the implications of potential regulatory restrictions.</p>
<p>Within days of the lawsuit, crypto traders had lost over $320 million in liquidations, <a href="https://www.coinglass.com/LiquidationData" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">according to data from CoinGlass</a>. Meanwhile, trading app Robinhood <a href="https://robinhood.com/us/en/support/articles/cardano-polygon-solana-update/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announced</a> it would cease its support for some of the crypto assets from June 27.</p>
<h2>Development Companies Defend Token Status</h2>
<p>While the SEC’s designation of these cryptocurrencies as securities has shaken the market, the development companies behind these assets have strongly rejected the regulator’s characterization.</p>
<p>Input Output Global, the company behind Cardano, refuted the SEC’s allegations. The firm said:</p>
<blockquote>
<p>“Under no circumstances is ADA security under US securities laws. It never has been.”</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Similarly, the Solana Foundation disputed the characterization of SOL as security. The company further stressed its commitment to working with regulators in pursuit of regulatory clarity within the nation. On its part, Polygon Labs also noted that its actions had never specifically targeted the US, pointing to its global community in the process.</p>
<p>Following these clarifications, ADA, SOL, and MATIC all made a partial comeback, recovering some of the losses incurred in the past week. ALGO and FLOW also recovered over 12.5% and 10.5% respectively, to bring a smile to the faces of their holders. Bitcoin has also experienced an uptick in demand, asserting its market dominance, as the altcoins struggle. </p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nasdaq-deal-adenza/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cardano-solana-algorand-securities-designation/">Securities Designation: Cardano, Solana, and Algorand Plummet to New Lows</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/cardano-solana-algorand-securities-designation/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nasdaq Inks $10.5B Deal to Acquire Software Firm Adenza</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nasdaq-deal-adenza/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nasdaq-deal-adenza/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 16:29:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Deals News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FinTech News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adenza]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nasdaq]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thoma Bravo]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=258495</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nasdaq-deal-adenza/">Nasdaq Inks $10.5B Deal to Acquire Software Firm Adenza</a></p>
<p>For Adenza, the acquisition represents a significant milestone in the company’s growth trajectory.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nasdaq-deal-adenza/">Nasdaq Inks $10.5B Deal to Acquire Software Firm Adenza</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nasdaq-deal-adenza/">Nasdaq Inks $10.5B Deal to Acquire Software Firm Adenza</a></p>
<p>Just recently, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/nasdaq/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Nasdaq Inc</a> (NASDAQ: NDAQ), the leading US-based technology firm serving the global financial system <a href="https://www.nasdaq.com/press-release/nasdaq-accelerates-its-transformation-as-a-leading-technology-provider-to-the-global" target="_blank" rel="noopener">announced</a> the acquisition of Adenza, a software application provider. The deal, which is valued at $10.5 billion in cash and common stock, will see the complete takeover of the firm by Nasdaq from Thoma Bravo, an American private equity and growth capital firm.</p>
<p>Interestingly, the acquisition is set to have significant implications for both Nasdaq and Adenza. For Nasdaq, the acquisition is a strategic move aimed at expanding its offerings in the financial technology space. Also, Adenza’s cloud-based solutions will complement Nasdaq’s existing suite of products and services, including its trading and market surveillance platforms.</p>
<h2>Implications of the Acquisition for Nasdaq and Adenza</h2>
<p>In addition to expanding its product offerings, the acquisition will also help Nasdaq to diversify its revenue streams. With the growth of digital banking and the increasing demand for financial technology solutions, Nasdaq is well-positioned to capitalize on the opportunities presented by Adenza’s cloud-based offerings.</p>
<p>For Adenza, the acquisition represents a significant milestone in the company’s growth trajectory. Since its founding, Adenza has established itself as a leading provider of cloud-based solutions for financial institutions. With Nasdaq’s backing, Adenza will be able to accelerate its growth and expand its reach into new markets.</p>
<p>Another key benefit of the acquisition is Adenza’s access to Nasdaq’s extensive customer base. The technology company’s global reach and established relationships with financial institutions will provide Adenza with a platform to showcase its solutions to a wider audience. This will help the firm to increase its market share and drive revenue growth.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the acquisition is a clear signal that the industry is continuing to evolve and consolidate with larger players looking to expand their offerings and gain a competitive edge. Also, Didier Bouillard, Chief Executive Officer at Adenza noted that the acquisition will enable both companies to be in a stronger position to ensure customers are provided with expanded solutions to solve their most difficult problems.</p>
<h2>Nasdaq Pursues Crypto Ambitions</h2>
<p>Despite the high-handed regulatory action in the United States, Nasdaq remains optimistic about <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nasdaq-adoption-crypto-growing/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">securing approval</a> for offering crypto custodial services. The exchange operator is working assiduously to offer crypto custodial and trading services to its clients, a move that is being stalled by the wait for approval from the New York Department of Financial Services (NYDFS).</p>
<p>Likewise, Nasdaq has shown its intentions to enter the crypto space after the collapse of Three Arrows Capital in July 2022. The company has continued to push ahead with its crypto ambitions even after major bankruptcies soiled sentiments across the board.</p>
<p>In all, Nasdaq has been waiting for some regulatory clarity to drive its emergence in the crypto market of the US. The company is also planning to offer liquidity services and also build its anti-financial crimes so it can monitor its ecosystem.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hsbc-innovation-banking-silicon-valley-bank/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nasdaq-deal-adenza/">Nasdaq Inks $10.5B Deal to Acquire Software Firm Adenza</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nasdaq-deal-adenza/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>HSBC Unveils HSBC Innovation Banking with Expertise Help from Its Silicon Valley Bank UK (SVB UK)</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/hsbc-innovation-banking-silicon-valley-bank/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/hsbc-innovation-banking-silicon-valley-bank/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 16:20:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hsbc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[svb uk]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=258519</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hsbc-innovation-banking-silicon-valley-bank/">HSBC Unveils HSBC Innovation Banking with Expertise Help from Its Silicon Valley Bank UK (SVB UK)</a></p>
<p>The HSBC Innovation Banking unit has more than 650 employees in the UK, over 40 members in the US, and hiring more in Hong Kong and Tel Aviv.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hsbc-innovation-banking-silicon-valley-bank/">HSBC Unveils HSBC Innovation Banking with Expertise Help from Its Silicon Valley Bank UK (SVB UK)</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hsbc-innovation-banking-silicon-valley-bank/">HSBC Unveils HSBC Innovation Banking with Expertise Help from Its Silicon Valley Bank UK (SVB UK)</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/hsbc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">HSBC Holdings PLC ADR</a> (NYSE: HSBC), a British universal bank and financial services group with more than $10 trillion in assets under custody (AUC), has launched a new banking tech unit dubbed HSBC Innovation Banking with the help of expertise from former Silicon Valley Bank UK (SVB UK).</p>
<h2>Closer Look at the HSBC Innovation Banking Unit</h2>
<p>According to the announcement, the primary focus of the HSBC Innovation Banking unit is to enable businesses focused on innovation to compete globally. Additionally, the banking giant noted that the new unit will mostly involve tech and life sciences, and their investors.</p>
<p>“Sometimes, high-growth start-ups need a helping hand to capture global opportunities and our new proposition will enable them to navigate the challenges of growing across borders,” the bank noted.</p>
<p>Similar sentiments have been echoed by UK Prime Minister <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/rishi-sunak/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Rishi Sunak</a>, who noted that the country is home to global tech companies involving life sciences. Sunak added that the HSBC Innovation Banking will be a huge boost to innovative businesses and in turn, cement the country as a life science innovation hub.</p>
<p>Notably, HSBC Group Chief Executive Noel Quinn welcomed the new innovative banking unit as it will help showcase the importance of SVB UK in its ecosystem.</p>
<p>“We will protect this specialism and take it to the next level by combining these capabilities with our financial strength and global reach. Our innovation teams will be there to support our client’s international growth at every step,” Quinn <a href="https://www.hsbc.com/news-and-media/media-releases/2023/hsbc-innovation-banking-launches-at-london-tech-week" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">noted</a>.</p>
<p>Notably, the launch of HSBC Innovation Banking coincided with London Tech Week which brought together senior leaders. According to the bank, HSBC Innovation Banking UK has more than 650 employees, including team members from Denmark and Sweden. The HSBC Innovation Banking US, on the other hand, has more than 40 members from across the Bay Area, Boston, and New York City. The bank is in the process of hiring more team members from Hong Kong and Tel Aviv.</p>
<h2>Market Outlook</h2>
<p>The launch of HSBC Innovation Banking comes a few months after the banking giant acquired SVB UK for only £1. This was after the UK government intervened to stop further bank runs earlier this year. Notably, the HSBC stock market gained about 22 percent YTD to trade around $38.15 on Monday. The $152.06 billion valued banking giant reported a revenue of about $20.2 billion, up approximately 64 percent YoY basis. As the market indicators point to profitable quarters ahead, the company issued a positive outlook for the remaining part of the year.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/reddit-communities-private-api/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hsbc-innovation-banking-silicon-valley-bank/">HSBC Unveils HSBC Innovation Banking with Expertise Help from Its Silicon Valley Bank UK (SVB UK)</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/hsbc-innovation-banking-silicon-valley-bank/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Reddit Communities to Go Private in Protest against Proposed API Changes</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/reddit-communities-private-api/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/reddit-communities-private-api/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 11:48:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apollo]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[reddit]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=258489</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/reddit-communities-private-api/">Reddit Communities to Go Private in Protest against Proposed API Changes</a></p>
<p>In a group statement, the moderators of the thousands of subreddits participating in the protest stated that the potential impact of these changes goes beyond the inconvenience caused to users who prefer third-party apps.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/reddit-communities-private-api/">Reddit Communities to Go Private in Protest against Proposed API Changes</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/reddit-communities-private-api/">Reddit Communities to Go Private in Protest against Proposed API Changes</a></p>
<p>In a remarkable show of solidarity, numerous <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/reddit/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Reddit</a> communities have united to take collective action against an imminent change that threatens users’ ability to freely access APIs and tools. Starting today to June 14, these communities, which include popular crypto subreddits, will temporarily go private or switch to read-only mode to voice their strong opposition and highlight the significance of open access on the platform.</p>
<p>According to <a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2023/jun/11/reddit-communities-to-go-dark-in-protest-over-third-party-app-charges" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reports</a> from The Guardian, more than 3,000 subreddits have joined forces in protest against the proposed changes to restricted access on the Reddit platform. Starting on Monday, these communities will effectively block anyone outside of their respective communities from accessing their posts.</p>
<p>Markedly, several prominent Reddit forums have pledged their participation in the ongoing protest against restricted access to APIs and tools. Notable communities such as r/todayilearned, r/funny, and r/gaming, each boasting more than 30 million subscribers, have committed to joining the campaign.</p>
<p>The ongoing protest by Reddit communities, which has resulted in the temporary closure of numerous subreddits, is centered around a series of forthcoming <a href="https://www.redditinc.com/blog/2023apiupdates" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">changes</a> bordering on access to the platform&#8217;s Application Programming Interface (API).</p>
<p>The API allows other companies and developers to utilize Reddit&#8217;s data in their own products and services, fostering innovation and creating a rich ecosystem beyond the Reddit platform itself.</p>
<h2>Reddit Communities Defending Open Access</h2>
<p>By limiting or restricting access to the API, the communities claim these forthcoming changes threaten to stifle the vibrant ecosystem that has flourished around Reddit.</p>
<p>Additionally, the communities noted that the changes would impose huge fees for “premium access”, ultimately wiping out popular third-party Reddit apps like Apollo, which allows users to surf the site with a customizable interface.</p>
<p>Notably, Christian Selig, the sole developer behind Apollo, estimates that in order to meet Reddit&#8217;s increased fees, such apps would need to charge users around $5 (£4) per month.</p>
<p>In a group statement, the moderators of the thousands of subreddits participating in the protest stated that the potential impact of these changes goes beyond the inconvenience caused to users who prefer third-party apps. They hinted that it also affects the broader ecosystem of developers who have contributed to the growth and diversity of Reddit&#8217;s platform.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the moderators revealed that some communities will return after 48 hours while others will go private permanently unless the issue is effectively solved, as many moderators are unable to put in the job they do with the inadequate tools provided by the official app.</p>
<h2>Reddit CEO’s Response to Differing Views</h2>
<p>On the other hand, Reddit’s CEO Steve Huffman has replied in a <a href="https://mashable.com/article/reddit-steve-huffman-ceo-ama-third-api-backlash?taid=6486ad74db776900011809ea&amp;utm_campaign=trueAnthem%3A+Trending+Content&amp;utm_medium=trueAnthem&amp;utm_source=twitter" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">blog post</a> that Reddit will not back down on its API changes. Huffman highlighted that Reddit needs to be a self-sustaining business, and therefore, can no longer subsidize commercial entities that require large-scale data use.</p>
<p>While the community&#8217;s pushback and protest against the proposed changes to the Reddit API continues, it&#8217;s vital to highlight that the platform has also made progress in other areas. One such area is the achievement of a new milestone in terms of collectible avatar holders on Reddit.</p>
<p>Currently, Reddit has <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/reddit-collectible-avatars-10m-users/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">recorded</a> 10 million collectors of its collectible avatars in less than a year after debuting “Reddit NFTs.”<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sturdy-finance-exploit-800000/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/reddit-communities-private-api/">Reddit Communities to Go Private in Protest against Proposed API Changes</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/reddit-communities-private-api/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sturdy Finance Hit in Fresh Exploit, Loses Over $800,000</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sturdy-finance-exploit-800000/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sturdy-finance-exploit-800000/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 11:36:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cybersecurity News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[decentralized finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[defi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[defi hack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[euler finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[flash loan attack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[price manipulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ronin attack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sturdy finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=258456</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sturdy-finance-exploit-800000/">Sturdy Finance Hit in Fresh Exploit, Loses Over $800,000</a></p>
<p>DeFi hacks have gone through the roof in recent times and many will argue that the DeFi ecosystem has proven time and again that it is indeed an exploiter’s paradise.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sturdy-finance-exploit-800000/">Sturdy Finance Hit in Fresh Exploit, Loses Over $800,000</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sturdy-finance-exploit-800000/">Sturdy Finance Hit in Fresh Exploit, Loses Over $800,000</a></p>
<p>Decentralized finance (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-decentralized-finance-defi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">DeFi</a>) protocol Sturdy Finance is the latest victim in a long list of DeFi hacks. The Sturdy Finance platform has reportedly lost 442 <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ETH</a> (worth a little above $800,000 as of publication), to a daring security exploit.</p>
<p>Blockchain security firm PeckShield was the first to notice what appeared to be a price manipulation by the attacker before it then <a href="https://twitter.com/peckshield/status/1668067645638299648" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">alerted</a> the lending platform to the bogus transaction on Monday.</p>
<p>It, however, took Sturdy Finance nearly an hour to respond to the claims by immediately halting all their markets. The DeFi protocol then confirmed the attack before assuring users that everything was under control. According to the platform, it has immediately taken necessary steps to ensure that no additional funds are at risk of being drained.</p>
<p>Despite Sturdy Finance&#8217;s seemingly fast response, however, the attacker was still able to cart away $800,000 in ETH and has since transferred the ill-gotten funds to the crypto mixer Tornado Cash, completing the faulty price oracle exploit.</p>
<h2>Sturdy Finance, Not &#8216;Sturdy&#8217; Security?</h2>
<p>With the latest development, it might be easy to fault the victim platform. But it is also worth noting that the hack is only a further validation of the overall proneness of DeFi protocols to such attacks. DeFi hacks have gone through the roof in recent times and many will argue that the DeFi ecosystem has proven time and again that it is indeed an exploiter’s paradise.</p>
<p>There was the $625 million loss in the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ronin-attackers-bitcoin-network/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ronin Bridge</a>, then the $80 million theft that happened to Qubit Finance. More recently, Euler Finance also lost $196 million to a flash loan attack in March. So, it is clear that security challenges persist in the sector. But the reason for the challenges is not exactly unknown.</p>
<p>Recall that DeFi allows for financial transactions to occur on the blockchain without intermediaries. The decentralization bit and lack of clear regulation are what make DeFi vulnerable to various types of hacks to date.</p>
<p>However, DeFi generally has continued to evolve, showing impressive growth nonetheless. And so too must its security, if it is to enable a safer environment for users to navigate the ecosystem.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-ceo-sam-altman-optimism-ai/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sturdy-finance-exploit-800000/">Sturdy Finance Hit in Fresh Exploit, Loses Over $800,000</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sturdy-finance-exploit-800000/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>OpenAI CEO Sam Altman Unveils Optimism about Global Coordination on AI</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-ceo-sam-altman-optimism-ai/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-ceo-sam-altman-optimism-ai/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[staff writer]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 11:34:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[openai]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sam altman]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=258486</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-ceo-sam-altman-optimism-ai/">OpenAI CEO Sam Altman Unveils Optimism about Global Coordination on AI</a></p>
<p>OpenAI CEO Sam Altman expresses his positive outlook on the prospects of global AI coordination, emphasizing the need for collaboration and cooperation among nations.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-ceo-sam-altman-optimism-ai/">OpenAI CEO Sam Altman Unveils Optimism about Global Coordination on AI</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-ceo-sam-altman-optimism-ai/">OpenAI CEO Sam Altman Unveils Optimism about Global Coordination on AI</a></p>
<p>Sam Altman, the CEO of the trendy OpenAI chatbot, ChatGPT, in a series of recent interviews, has <a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/openai-ceo-says-optimistic-global-ai-coordination-2023-06-12/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">shared</a> his optimism regarding the global coordination of artificial intelligence (AI) efforts. Serving as the prominent representative of this innovative startup, supported by the influential Microsoft Corp, the CEO has embarked on a captivating expedition, seizing opportunities to leverage the growing interest in generative AI and shape the regulations governing this burgeoning technology.</p>
<p>During his remarkable journey, OpenAI CEO Altman addressed an audience of students in Tokyo, confessing that he initially approached the trip with a sense of skepticism, doubting the feasibility of achieving immediate global cooperation to mitigate existential risks. However, as the trip draws to a close, his outlook has transformed into one of cautious optimism, now believing that such cooperation is indeed attainable.</p>
<p>Deducing from his survey, Altman noted that in the midst of this rapidly evolving landscape, regulators find themselves in a race against time, striving to adapt existing regulations while formulating novel guidelines to govern the utilization of generative AI. Thus he believes that the groundbreaking technology, capable of generating text and images, simultaneously fuels anticipation and apprehension due to its potential to reshape a wide array of industries.</p>
<h2>OpenAI CEO Altman Highlights the Significance of Collaboration to Curtail AI Vulnerabilities</h2>
<p>Altman&#8217;s positive stance on global AI coordination stems from the belief that working together will not only help avoid potential risks and pitfalls but also harness the full potential of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/technology/artificial-intelligence-news/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">AI</a> for societal progress. He acknowledges the rapid advancements in AI technology and the need for countries to come together to establish common frameworks and guidelines.</p>
<p>According to reports, Altman had acknowledged the challenges associated with global AI coordination, such as differing national interests and policy approaches. However, he remains optimistic that by engaging in constructive dialogue and finding common ground, countries can navigate these obstacles and collectively steer the course of AI development.</p>
<p>As such, Altman emphasized the importance of international collaboration and cooperation to ensure the responsible and beneficial development of AI technology. Altman highlights the significance of collaboration and cooperation in addressing the challenges posed by AI development. Therefore, he explained that AI has the potential to bring about transformative changes in various sectors, including healthcare, transportation, and education. However, to ensure that AI benefits everyone and avoids potential harm, global coordination is essential.</p>
<p>Furthermore, addressing concerns about the potential misuse of AI, Altman stresses the importance of establishing trust among nations. He believes that transparency in AI research and development is key to fostering cooperation. OpenAI has been actively promoting openness and accessibility by sharing research findings and collaborating with other institutions to advance the field.</p>
<p>The OpenAI CEO Altman envisions a future where countries unite to tackle the ethical, safety, and societal implications of AI technology. By sharing knowledge, best practices, and regulatory frameworks, nations can collectively shape the development and deployment of AI systems, fostering trust and transparency among stakeholders.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nio-cuts-down-prices/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-ceo-sam-altman-optimism-ai/">OpenAI CEO Sam Altman Unveils Optimism about Global Coordination on AI</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-ceo-sam-altman-optimism-ai/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Electric Carmaker Nio Cuts Down Prices, Delays Plans of Business Expansion</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nio-cuts-down-prices/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nio-cuts-down-prices/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 11:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Transportation News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nio]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=258435</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nio-cuts-down-prices/">Electric Carmaker Nio Cuts Down Prices, Delays Plans of Business Expansion</a></p>
<p>Considering the tight market conditions, Nio has also put its expansion plans on hold for the time being. It has stopped any additional incentive programs such as free battery swaps for new users. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nio-cuts-down-prices/">Electric Carmaker Nio Cuts Down Prices, Delays Plans of Business Expansion</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nio-cuts-down-prices/">Electric Carmaker Nio Cuts Down Prices, Delays Plans of Business Expansion</a></p>
<p>In the latest development on Monday, June 12, Chinese electric carmaker <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/nio/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Nio</a> announced cutting the prices of its cars by around $4,200 with immediate effect. Furthermore, the company shall also be ending free battery swaps for new buyers.</p>
<p>This is quite surprising since back in April 2023, Nio CEO William Li’s claimed that the company won&#8217;t be joining a &#8220;price war&#8221;. Rivals such as Tesla and other local Chinese electric carmakers announced a price cut earlier this year in a bid to attract more customers.</p>
<p>Interestingly, last Friday, the Nio CEO also announced that the company has been delaying its capital expenditure plans along with some research and development projects. Li said that this delay will be a part of their efforts to address issues relating to cash flow due to fewer car deliveries.</p>
<p>As of the March-ending quarter, Chinese electric carmaker Nio reported cash and cash equivalents of 14.76 billion yuan ($2.07 billion). This was much below what it disclosed by the end of 2021 and 2022. In a note on Monday, June 12, analysts at China Merchants Bank International said:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Nio’s decision to cut non-core projects is too slow. It now also faces a dilemma between brand positioning and profitability, as it has started to cut service benefits, which could dent its brand image and thus sales more severely than expected.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>As a result, the analysts have cut their rating for the Nio stock to hold from buy.</p>
<h2>Nio Failing on Timely Deliveries</h2>
<p>As per the latest monthly figures for the month of March 2023, the total deliveries from Nio stood at just 6,155. This was down from the first-quarter average deliveries of just over 10,000 vehicles a month. During the fourth quarter, the monthly average deliveries stood at a staggering 13,350 cars.</p>
<p>Interestingly, Nio remains optimistic while setting up the target for at least 20,000 monthly car deliveries during the second half of the year. Nomura believes that the Chinese electric carmaker will improve deliveries with its new models &#8211; the ES6 SUV and ET5 touring sedan.</p>
<p>&#8220;That said, we expect NIO’s implied upside to be capped by intensified competition and limited market share improvement in 2023F,&#8221; Nomura analysts wrote.</p>
<p>By the end of 2019, Nio&#8217;s available cash dropped to less than $1 billion. However, in 2020, the company received a lifeline of around $1 billion from investors, including government-backed entities, which helped them recover. Recently, Li, the company&#8217;s CEO, stated that they have enough cash to support their business operations.</p>
<p>Unfortunately, Nio experienced a significant decline in gross margin during the first quarter. It dropped to 1.5%, down from 14.6% compared to the previous year and 3.9% from the fourth quarter.</p>
<p>With strong government subsidies in place, the Chinese automotive market is the largest in the world. As a result, the electric car industry is growing pretty fast with every one in three cars sold being electric. In a note on Friday, analysts at Mizuho Securities <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/06/12/nio-cuts-prices-for-its-cars-and-delays-business-expansion-plans.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Despite short-term headwinds, we believe NIO remains well-positioned with multiple upcoming ramps including its lowest cost SUV ES6, a multi-year EV adoption tailwind and market leadership in premium EVs in China, the largest EV market, EU/Global expansion, and an expanding product portfolio.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Read other <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/business/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">business news</a> on Coinspeaker.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/a16z-london-crypto-office/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nio-cuts-down-prices/">Electric Carmaker Nio Cuts Down Prices, Delays Plans of Business Expansion</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nio-cuts-down-prices/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>From Silicon Valley to United Kingdom: a16z to Open London Crypto Office </title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/a16z-london-crypto-office/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/a16z-london-crypto-office/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 10:55:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[a16z]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gensyn]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=258441</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/a16z-london-crypto-office/">From Silicon Valley to United Kingdom: a16z to Open London Crypto Office </a></p>
<p>As one of America's leading venture capital firms, a16z has invested in many fintech projects both within and outside the region.  </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/a16z-london-crypto-office/">From Silicon Valley to United Kingdom: a16z to Open London Crypto Office </a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/a16z-london-crypto-office/">From Silicon Valley to United Kingdom: a16z to Open London Crypto Office </a></p>
<p>Andreessen Horowitz (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/a16z/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">a16z</a>), a leading venture capital firm, has joined a wave of US-based companies seeking new opportunities outside the shores of the country following the recent crackdown on crypto in the region. In an official <a href="https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20230611005029/en/Andreessen-Horowitz-%E2%80%9Ca16z%E2%80%9D-Announces-its-First-International-Expansion-to-the-United-Kingdom" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">press release</a> on June 11, the California-based enterprise said its digital asset investment arm, a16z crypto, will open an international office in London, recognizing the UK&#8217;s deep talent pool, leading academic institutions, and entrepreneurial spirit.</p>
<p>The move follows positive engagements with the country&#8217;s prime minister, Rishi Sunak, policymakers, HM Treasury, and the Financial Conduct Authority (FCA), signaling the UK&#8217;s commitment to embracing blockchain technology and creating a conducive business environment through forward-thinking regulations.</p>
<p>&#8220;We&#8217;re thrilled to open our first international office in a jurisdiction that welcomes blockchain technology and is committed to creating a predictable business environment by pursuing regulations that both embrace web3 and protect consumers. We look forward to helping foster the growth of the UK web3 ecosystem while the proper regulations come online,&#8221; said Chris Dixon, a16z crypto founder and managing partner.</p>
<p>a16z said it would seek appropriate regulatory permissions to ensure compliance with local legislation for its operations in the country. By adhering to regulatory requirements, the company aims to uphold the highest standards of integrity and contribute positively to developing the country&#8217;s blockchain ecosystem.</p>
<p>The London office, scheduled to open later this year, will be headed by the <a href="https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20230611005029/en/Andreessen-Horowitz-%E2%80%9Ca16z%E2%80%9D-Announces-its-First-International-Expansion-to-the-United-Kingdom">a16z</a> General Partner, Sriram Krishnan. The new office will work closely with universities to support blockchain clubs and encourage the development of crypto-related curricula.</p>
<h2>Unlocking Opportunities for Web3 in the UK</h2>
<p>UK Prime Minister Rishi Sunak acknowledged the importance of embracing new innovations like Web3 and blockchain technology to solidify the country&#8217;s position as a technology hub. According to him, the government is determined to create the necessary regulatory framework to protect consumers while fostering innovation.</p>
<p>Aside from establishing an international office in the UK, the investment firm plans to host its Crypto Startup School (CSS), a renowned accelerator program tailored to Web3 startups, next year in London during the spring.</p>
<p>The program offers selected companies investment from a16z, mentorship from industry experts, and a Demo Day opportunity to showcase their innovations to potential investors.</p>
<p>With the previous CSS program attracting over 8,000 applicants worldwide, the upcoming event in London holds great promise for driving web3 innovation in the UK.</p>
<h2>a16z Investment Contributions to Crypto</h2>
<p>As one of America&#8217;s leading venture capital firms, a16z has invested in many fintech projects both within and outside the region.</p>
<p>The company recently led a <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gensyn-43m-series-a-funding/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">$43 million</a> funding round conducted by Gensyn, a UK-based firm that allows software developers to build cutting-edge Artificial intelligence (AI) systems on any connected hardware.</p>
<p>In April, a16z and other venture capital firms such as ICONIQ Growth led a $100 million investment round for <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/a16z-100m-ai-pinecone/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Pinecone,</a> an AI infrastructure provider based in New York.</p>
<p>The company has also made a series of contributions to the crypto industry, including <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/a16z-crypto-andreessen-horowitz-launches-300-million-crypto-fund/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">launching </a>a $300 million ecosystem fund in 2018 and introducing an <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/a16z-start-program-accelerator/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">a16z START</a> program for founders across the fintech industry.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gary-gensler-crypto-us-winklevoss/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/a16z-london-crypto-office/">From Silicon Valley to United Kingdom: a16z to Open London Crypto Office </a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/a16z-london-crypto-office/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gary Gensler’s War on Crypto Will Put Off Young Voters, Cameron Winklevoss Says</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/gary-gensler-crypto-us-winklevoss/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/gary-gensler-crypto-us-winklevoss/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 10:45:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cameron winklevoss]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gary gensler]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[us sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=258428</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gary-gensler-crypto-us-winklevoss/">Gary Gensler’s War on Crypto Will Put Off Young Voters, Cameron Winklevoss Says</a></p>
<p>While some Democrats have been criticized for their regulatory stance on cryptocurrencies, it is essential to recognize that not all members of the party hold an anti-crypto position.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gary-gensler-crypto-us-winklevoss/">Gary Gensler’s War on Crypto Will Put Off Young Voters, Cameron Winklevoss Says</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gary-gensler-crypto-us-winklevoss/">Gary Gensler’s War on Crypto Will Put Off Young Voters, Cameron Winklevoss Says</a></p>
<p>In recent years, the world of crypto has grown in popularity, particularly among the younger population and the US Democratic Party&#8217;s stance on crypto regulations in recent times has raised concerns among influential figures in the industry.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/cameron-winklevoss/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Cameron Winklevoss</a>, the co-founder of the crypto exchange Gemini, recently took to <a href="https://twitter.com/cameron/status/1667657675096883201?s=46&amp;t=wxOs6dz_yXlLV9YPYuRzvA" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Twitter</a> to express his worries about the potential alienation of crucial youth voters due to the Democrats&#8217; anti-crypto stance.</p>
<p>Cameron highlighted that crypto has captivated the hearts and minds of Millennials and Gen Z, creating a new wave of financial innovation and investment. Unlike previous generations, these tech-savvy individuals are less concerned with debating the merits of crypto and more focused on determining where and what to build next.</p>
<p>However, Cameron pointed out that recent regulatory actions by figures like Senator Elizabeth Warren and Gary Gensler have raised concerns about potential value destruction.</p>
<p>Notably, Senator Elizabeth Warren has been vocal in expressing <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-warren-regulatory-authority-crypto/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">concerns</a> about the risks associated with cryptocurrencies. Her calls for increased regulation and scrutiny have sparked uncertainty among crypto enthusiasts, who fear stifling innovation and growth.</p>
<p>As the chairman of the US Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>), Gary Gensler has taken a firm stance on regulating cryptocurrencies. Last week, the SEC <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-sec-coinbase-unregistered-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">sued</a> two of the largest crypto exchanges, Binance and Coinbase over their support for unregistered cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>Furthermore, Cameron explained that the Democrats’ stance could be explained by two factors: either they lack a full understanding of the crypto ecosystem, or they underestimate the potential impact of their actions on the millennial vote in the approaching election cycle. In conclusion, Cameron highlighted that while Democrats may not care for crypto, they certainly will care for lost votes from young voters.</p>
<p>Following Cameron Winklevoss&#8217; tweet about the potential alienation of crucial youth voters, Tyler Winklevoss took to Twitter on June 11 to state that Elizabeth Warren and Gary Gensler&#8217;s perceived &#8220;war&#8221; on crypto could lead to the Democrats losing the 2024 election.</p>
<p>Remarkably, the Winklevoss twins have long been Bitcoin bulls, predicting a $500,000 Bitcoin price. Although Cameron has no official party position, he has previously backed Republican politicians.</p>
<h2>Crypto in the Mix of US Politics</h2>
<p>While some Democrats have been criticized for their regulatory stance on cryptocurrencies, it is essential to recognize that not all members of the party hold an anti-crypto position. One notable example is presidential candidate Robert Kennedy Jr., who has emerged as a pro-Bitcoin advocate within the Democratic Party.</p>
<p>Kennedy&#8217;s <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/robert-f-kennedy-jr-sec-crypto/">recent</a> appearance as a keynote speaker at the Bitcoin 2023 conference highlights a possible shift in the party&#8217;s approach to digital currencies in the US.</p>
<p>Republicans, on the other hand, appear to be far more amenable to crypto. Several major Republicans, like Wyoming Senator Cynthia Lummis, House Majority Whip Tom Emmer, and Florida Governor Ron DeSantis, have expressed support for crypto.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/george-soros-25b-empire-son-alex/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gary-gensler-crypto-us-winklevoss/">Gary Gensler’s War on Crypto Will Put Off Young Voters, Cameron Winklevoss Says</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/gary-gensler-crypto-us-winklevoss/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>George Soros Hands Over Control of $25B Empire to Son Alex</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/george-soros-25b-empire-son-alex/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/george-soros-25b-empire-son-alex/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 10:27:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alex soros]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[george soros]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[soros fund management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=258405</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/george-soros-25b-empire-son-alex/">George Soros Hands Over Control of $25B Empire to Son Alex</a></p>
<p>Alex said that he is “more political” than his dad and mentioned his stance against the former president. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/george-soros-25b-empire-son-alex/">George Soros Hands Over Control of $25B Empire to Son Alex</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/george-soros-25b-empire-son-alex/">George Soros Hands Over Control of $25B Empire to Son Alex</a></p>
<p>George Soros, the popular philanthropist, and businessman, revealed that he is handing over his $25 billion empire to his son Alex. According to Forbes, George Soros is one of the top 400 wealthiest people in the world, with a net worth of $6.7 billion.</p>
<p>The billionaire is a celebrated hedge fund tycoon who moved $18 billion from his family office to his Open Society Foundations as of 2018. Notably, the Foundations consist of several charities operating in over 100 countries. And Alex, whom he had just handed over his billion-dollar empire to, was appointed Chair in December. He also oversees George’s “user PAC”. The billionaire’s son is the second-youngest of five children and the only family member that is a member of the investment committee for <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/soros-fund-trading-bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Soros Fund Management</a>, which manages the family’s $25 billion and the charitable foundation.</p>
<h2>Alex Takes Charge of the $25B Empire of George Soros</h2>
<p>Alex <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/george-soros-heir-son-alexander-soros-e3c4ca13?mod=Searchresults_pos1&amp;page=1" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">spoke</a> to the Wall Street Journal over the weekend, noting that he is “more political” than his father. He also referred to a major role for the Soros organization in the upcoming 2024 US elections. Speaking on the potential return of former president Donald Trump, the younger Soros said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“As much as I would love to get money out of politics, as long as the other side is doing it, we will have to do it, too… Our side has to be better about being more patriotic and inclusive. Just because someone votes Trump doesn’t mean they’re lost or racist.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Alex added that he is “more political” than his dad and mentioned his stance against the former president. He said that he would campaign against Trump’s attempt to run for a second term as the president of the United States.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the younger Soros assured that the Open Society Foundations would continue with the same standard it had under his father- George. The Foundations’ aims include minority and refugee rights, free speech, criminal justice reform, and supporting liberal politicians. In addition, Alex wants to have an abortion, voting rights, and gender equity initiatives as he targets a domestic US-focused agenda.</p>
<p>George Soros became known as “The Man who Broke the Bank of England” in 1992 due to his short sale of $10 billion worth of pounds, where he made $1 billion. A Hungary-born who lived through the Nazi occupation from 1944 to 1945, his family was forced to hide their identity for survival. Following the war, he moved to London and then to New York before he started making billions through his hedge fund.</p>
<p>As for the son, Alex is famous for his social life, which includes attending celebrity events in the Hamptons and Cannes.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/onchain-data-outflows-binance-cz/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/george-soros-25b-empire-son-alex/">George Soros Hands Over Control of $25B Empire to Son Alex</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/george-soros-25b-empire-son-alex/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4034 metric#misses=41 metric#hit-ratio=99.0 metric#bytes=1075974 metric#prefetches=203 metric#store-reads=19 metric#store-writes=2 metric#store-hits=209 metric#store-misses=2 metric#sql-queries=34 metric#ms-total=96.23 metric#ms-cache=4.63 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.2317 metric#ms-cache-ratio=4.8 -->