<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 16:30:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>UBS Appoints Credit Suisse CEO Ulrich Koerner to Its Board of Directors</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ubs-credit-suisse-ceo/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ubs-credit-suisse-ceo/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 16:30:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[barclays]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[credit suisse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[deutsche bank]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ubs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=254078</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ubs-credit-suisse-ceo/">UBS Appoints Credit Suisse CEO Ulrich Koerner to Its Board of Directors</a></p>
<p>The acquisition of Credit Suisse by the bigger bank has been viewed using different lenses by industry observers.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ubs-credit-suisse-ceo/">UBS Appoints Credit Suisse CEO Ulrich Koerner to Its Board of Directors</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ubs-credit-suisse-ceo/">UBS Appoints Credit Suisse CEO Ulrich Koerner to Its Board of Directors</a></p>
<p>Swiss multinational investment banking firm <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ubs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">UBS Group AG</a> (SWX: UBSG) has announced that Ulrich Koerner, the CEO of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/credit-suisse/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Credit Suisse</a>, will be joining the executive board of the new joint entity. The update comes a few weeks after an emergency purchase of Credit Suisse by UBS was facilitated by regulators.</p>
<p>UBS confirmed the announcement according to a <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/09/ubs-announces-credit-suisse-ceo-koerner-to-join-board-after-emergency-rescue.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">news release</a>, emphasizing that Koerner will be in charge of maintaining Credit Suisse&#8217;s operational continuity and client focus while assisting the integration process, using his experience in both businesses.</p>
<p>Additionally, UBS stated that the legal completion of its acquisition of Credit Suisse is expected to occur in the coming weeks. Following the completion of the acquisition, the two banks will operate as a consolidated banking group.</p>
<p>This means that the two banks will almost certainly be integrated to some extent. Meanwhile, UBS had given a statement that the Credit Suisse brand will continue to function separately for the “foreseeable future” as UBS integrates the business in a “phased approach”.</p>
<p>Whatever conclusion the bank makes, it will be interesting to see how the merged business operates and how it affects the banking industry and financial markets in general. Notably, Koerner will be working together with Sergio Ermotti as the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ubs-sergio-ermotti-new-ceo/">new CEO</a> to oversee the Credit Suisse takeover, while UBS veteran Todd Tuckner will become Chief Financial Officer (CFO) for the group.</p>
<p>According to the information provided, the combined firm will have five business divisions, seven functions, and four regions in addition to Credit Suisse, each represented by a board member reporting to Ermotti.</p>
<h2>Is the UBS Acquisition the Best Deal for Credit Suisse?</h2>
<p>The acquisition of Credit Suisse by the bigger bank has been viewed using different lenses by industry observers. Markedly, an earlier report revealed that shares of the Swiss banking behemoths UBS and Credit Suisse plummeted following the latter&#8217;s takeover. According to the details, the stock of Credit Suisse dropped by 60%, while shares of UBS dropped by 10%.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the European banking index was down approximately 2% around the same time.  Also, lenders such as <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/deutsche-bank/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Deutsche Bank AG</a> (ETR: DBK), <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/barclays/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Barclays PLC</a> (LSE: BARC), and ING Group (AMS: INGA) traded lower by more than 1.36% at the time of writing.</p>
<p>While commenting on the takeover, Colm Kelleher, Chairman of UBS stated that the deal is part of a cut-price deal to stem a larger banking contagion, as “attractive” for UBS shareholders. However, the UBS Chairman went on to say that such an appeal does not always pose the same proposition for the acquired bank.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, UBS stated in a release that the collaborative endeavor should generate more than $5 trillion in total invested assets. Furthermore, the banking behemoth stated that the merging of banking resources would result in sustainable value opportunities that will end up being profitable for all.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hong-kong-crypto-businesses-regulation/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ubs-credit-suisse-ceo/">UBS Appoints Credit Suisse CEO Ulrich Koerner to Its Board of Directors</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ubs-credit-suisse-ceo/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hong Kong Warns Crypto Businesses Not to Expect Special Treatment as City Readies Regulation</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/hong-kong-crypto-businesses-regulation/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/hong-kong-crypto-businesses-regulation/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 15:29:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hkma]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=254052</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hong-kong-crypto-businesses-regulation/">Hong Kong Warns Crypto Businesses Not to Expect Special Treatment as City Readies Regulation</a></p>
<p>A high-ranking Hong Kong official has warned crypto exchanges to expect strict regulation and advises those in opposition to go elsewhere. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hong-kong-crypto-businesses-regulation/">Hong Kong Warns Crypto Businesses Not to Expect Special Treatment as City Readies Regulation</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hong-kong-crypto-businesses-regulation/">Hong Kong Warns Crypto Businesses Not to Expect Special Treatment as City Readies Regulation</a></p>
<p>Hong Kong has stated that its upcoming crypto regulation would not promote a light-touch approach despite the city’s crypto-friendly disposition. The Chinese special administrative region is putting the finishing touches to digital asset licensing rules as it seeks to become a global crypto hub.</p>
<p>Speaking at Tuesday’s Bloomberg Wealth Asia Summit, Hong Kong Monetary Authority CEO Eddie Yue Wai-man <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-05-09/hong-kong-says-its-crypto-regulations-will-shun-any-light-touch-approach" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">warned</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Our regulations will be tight.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Yue added that crypto players opposed to the new licensing regime could go elsewhere.</p>
<p>The HKMA chief executive’s comments come just weeks ahead of Hong Kong effecting new regulation and licensing rules for crypto exchanges. The city has joined a growing number of governments worldwide that embrace the crypto industry despite last year’s meltdowns. Hong Kong, in particular, has re-emerged as an enticing crypto destination compared to mainland China which remains largely conservative to digital assets. Last October, the Chinese special administrative city announced plans to become a global virtual asset center.</p>
<p>Pursuant to this agenda, Hong Kong will embark on its licensing regime on June 1st. Despite Hong Kong’s intent to “let the [crypto] industry develop and innovate,” government officials set to wield oversight in this industry say rules will be tight. According to Eddie Yue, they “will let them create the ecosystem here, and that actually brings a lot of excitement. But that doesn’t mean light-touch regulation.”</p>
<h2>Hong Kong Previously Proposed Crypto Regulation to Leverage Digital Asset Adoption &amp; Induce Growth</h2>
<p>In February, Hong Kong’s Securities and Futures Commission (SFC) proposed new rules governing retail participation in crypto trading. The securities watchdog suggested allowing retail investors to buy tokens, such as <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> (BTC) and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/">Ether</a> (ETH), on licensed virtual asset platforms. According to the SFC, such permissible conditions would place Hong Kong at the forefront of financial advancement. Furthermore, the SFC opined that supporting digital currencies with large market capitalizations would jumpstart the city’s emerging economy.</p>
<p>The SFC is preparing the crypto regulatory framework, which includes guidelines for banks dealing with crypto customers. These rules call for mandatory regulatory licensing of all centralized digital asset trading platforms in Hong Kong. Furthermore, the rules also require that crypto exchanges that market their services to Hong Kong investors have to secure regulatory licensing. In addition, Eddie Yue said Hong Kong’s government entity would soon reveal the extent to which individual investors could participate.</p>
<p>The HKMA is also readying a mandatory licensing regime that would cover stablecoin-related activities next year. Currently, written rules require the value of backing reserve assets to always equal outstanding token value.</p>
<p>Eddie Yue commented on Hong Kong’s comprehensive airtight regulatory framework for all types of digital assets, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>“What we want to do in Hong Kong is to say that, hey, this trend will continue. Let’s put in the right regulatory framework using the principle of the same activity, same risk, and same regulation.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Furthermore, the HKMA CEO believes that the crypto legislative framework would bring transparency and clarity to the sector.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tether-usdt-prefered-stablecoin-banking-crisis/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hong-kong-crypto-businesses-regulation/">Hong Kong Warns Crypto Businesses Not to Expect Special Treatment as City Readies Regulation</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/hong-kong-crypto-businesses-regulation/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tether (USDT) Emerges as Prefered Stablecoin amid US Banking Crisis with Over $86B in Total Supply</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tether-usdt-prefered-stablecoin-banking-crisis/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tether-usdt-prefered-stablecoin-banking-crisis/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 15:05:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[matic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[polygon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sol]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[solana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[usdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=254057</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tether-usdt-prefered-stablecoin-banking-crisis/">Tether (USDT) Emerges as Prefered Stablecoin amid US Banking Crisis with Over $86B in Total Supply</a></p>
<p>The stablecoins market is expected to significantly grow amid the mainstream adoption of Bitcoin and other digital assets globally.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tether-usdt-prefered-stablecoin-banking-crisis/">Tether (USDT) Emerges as Prefered Stablecoin amid US Banking Crisis with Over $86B in Total Supply</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tether-usdt-prefered-stablecoin-banking-crisis/">Tether (USDT) Emerges as Prefered Stablecoin amid US Banking Crisis with Over $86B in Total Supply</a></p>
<p>The rise of the Tether (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/tether/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">USDT</a>) stablecoin has been undisputed for several years. The Tether (USDT) stablecoin runs on more than 10 blockchains including Ethereum, Binance Smart Chain, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/matic-network/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Polygon</a>, and Tron, among others. On the Ethereum network, Tether (USDT) has more than $36 billion in supply with about 4.3 million holders. The Tron network holds a vast amount of Tether (USDT) with about $46 billion. On the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/solana/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Solana</a> blockchain, Tether (USDT) has a total supply of about $1.8 billion.</p>
<p>In total, the Tether (USDT) has a total supply of more than $82 billion, thus holding the top US dollar-backed stablecoins. Notably, Tether (USDT) has the highest daily traded volume in the digital asset industry with about $25.57 billion, compared to Bitcoin at $16.5 billion.</p>
<h2>Banking Crisis Lifts Tether (USDT)</h2>
<p>Amid the United States banking crisis, which has seen more than three regional banks succumb to fintech and big valued banks, investors are more aware of self-custody through stablecoins. According to the latest aggregate data from <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/categories/stablecoins" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">CoinGecko</a>, the Tether USDT market valuation has reclaimed ATH achieved right before last year’s crypto capitulation.</p>
<p>Notably, Tether USDT bottomed out at a market capitalization of about $65 billion during the FTX and Alameda Research implosion late last year. With the de-pegging of Circle’s USDC during the collapse of Silvergate Capital, Tether USDT’s valuation climbed exponentially to date.</p>
<p>The narrative that Bitcoin is a better hedge against inflation than any other market equities has increased the adoption of Tether stablecoins.</p>
<p>“The banking crisis is fuelling &#8216;hyper-bitcoinisation&#8217; &#8211; the inevitable endgame that the dollar will be worthless,” <a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/cryptoverse-tether-gets-lift-stability-doubts-2023-05-09/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a> Anders Kvamme Jensen, Oslo-based founder of the AKJ global brokerage and digital asset specialist.</p>
<h2>King of the Stablecoin Market</h2>
<p>The stablecoins market cap is about $130,788,346,187, with Tether controlling more than half. According to aggregate data from Binance-backed <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/view/stablecoin/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">CoinMarketCap</a>, only Tether (USDT) has seen its market valuation increase YTD in the top three stablecoins. The second largest stablecoin, USDC by Circle has been on a decline since the Silvergate Capital saga.</p>
<p>Similarly, Binance-backed BUSD has significantly shrunk since the issuer ceased issuing new coins following the SEC charges.</p>
<div style="width: 1034px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img decoding="async" src="https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/tether-usdt-prefered-stablecoin-banking-crisis-1.jpg" alt="Tether (USDT) Emerges as Prefered Stablecoin amid US Banking Crisis with Over $86B in Total Supply" width="1024" height="1004" /><p class="wp-caption-text">Photo: CoinGecko</p></div>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h2>Bigger Picture</h2>
<p>The stablecoins market is expected to significantly grow amid the mainstream adoption of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> and other digital assets globally. Moreover, there are more crypto-friendly markets &#8211; including the EU, Hong Kong, UK, El Salvador, and UAE, among others &#8211; than there were a few years ago.</p>
<p>As a result, Tether (USDT) is expected to grow exponentially in the coming years. Furthermore, the company has launched more stablecoins denominated in other global currencies including the Euro.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-bitcoin-ordinals-nft/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tether-usdt-prefered-stablecoin-banking-crisis/">Tether (USDT) Emerges as Prefered Stablecoin amid US Banking Crisis with Over $86B in Total Supply</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tether-usdt-prefered-stablecoin-banking-crisis/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Unveils Plans to List Bitcoin Ordinals on Its NFT Marketplace</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-bitcoin-ordinals-nft/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-bitcoin-ordinals-nft/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 14:54:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Ordinals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFT Marketplace]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=254025</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-bitcoin-ordinals-nft/">Binance Unveils Plans to List Bitcoin Ordinals on Its NFT Marketplace</a></p>
<p>Binance has been aggressively growing its NFT marketplace in a variety of ways in order to become a top platform for buying, selling, and trading NFTs.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-bitcoin-ordinals-nft/">Binance Unveils Plans to List Bitcoin Ordinals on Its NFT Marketplace</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-bitcoin-ordinals-nft/">Binance Unveils Plans to List Bitcoin Ordinals on Its NFT Marketplace</a></p>
<p>Binance, the world&#8217;s largest crypto exchange has expressed interest in adding Bitcoin Ordinals to its Non-Fungible Token (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NFT</a>) marketplace by the end of May. According to the announcement, Binance will also offer royalty support and additional revenue-generating opportunities for Bitcoin NFT creators.</p>
<p>Bitcoin Ordinals are becoming popular and unique in the NFT ecosystem thus fueling the push by Binance to add it to its marketplace. This listing is essential in order to attract more customers and provide more diversified NFT options.</p>
<p>While commenting on the update, Binance’s Head of Product Mayur Kamat highlighted that the firm is thrilled to be bringing Bitcoin Ordinals to Binance NFT. Additionally, he added that “Bitcoin is the OG of crypto”.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the BNB Chain, Ethereum, and Polygon have already been integrated into the Binance exchange NFT. Thus, permitting users to purchase, deposit, withdraw, and list NFTs from the Polygon network on the Binance NFT Marketplace. Additionally, users can trade digital collectibles on the Binance NFT Marketplace by holding MATIC or any token in their spot wallets.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/introduction-to-bitcoin-ordinals/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin ordinals</a>, also known as Bitcoin NFTs or digital artifacts, provide a novel method of storing digital content on the Bitcoin blockchain. Each NFT in the Bitcoin Ordinals series is hand-painted with a unique representation of the relevant Bitcoin block hash. As with other NFTs, the value of Bitcoin Ordinals is determined by supply and demand.</p>
<p>Notably, the artwork is designed to represent the historical and technological significance of the Bitcoin blockchain, as well as the proof of work mechanism that secures it. The series is highly sought after by collectors and cryptocurrency enthusiasts due to its unique concept and limited availability.</p>
<h2>Binance Actively Expanding Its NFT Marketplace</h2>
<p>Binance has been aggressively growing its NFT marketplace in a variety of ways in order to become a top platform for buying, selling, and trading NFTs.</p>
<p>Notably, Binance has been collaborating with various artists and creators to offer exclusive and unique NFTs on its marketplace. For example, Binance has <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-nft-marketplace-live-june-24/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">partnered</a> with Lewis Capaldi, a 2-time BRIT award winner, and soccer stars Michael Owen and Alphonso Davies to offer limited edition NFTs.</p>
<p>Additionally, the exchange had <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-nft-100-creators-campaign/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">announced</a> that its NFT Marketplace had plans to bring 100 creators to its NFT platform. Binance NFT seeks to capture a wide variety of users by resorting to a broad range of voices from across many fields.</p>
<p>Furthermore, Binance has been working to improve the user experience on its NFT marketplace, making it easier for users to browse, purchase, and manage their NFTs. For instance, the firm has implemented a function that allows users to view an NFT&#8217;s whole history, including past owners and transaction histories. Ultimately, Binance hopes to attract a broader spectrum of users to its platform by offering a diverse choice of NFTs.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/digital-asset-global-blockchain-network/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-bitcoin-ordinals-nft/">Binance Unveils Plans to List Bitcoin Ordinals on Its NFT Marketplace</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-bitcoin-ordinals-nft/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Digital Asset to Start Global Blockchain Network with Goldman Sachs, Deloitte, BNP and Others</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/digital-asset-global-blockchain-network/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/digital-asset-global-blockchain-network/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sanaa Sharma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 14:03:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bnp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital asset]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[goldman sachs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jpmorgan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[microsoft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[s&p global]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[saesforce]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[samsung]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=253933</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/digital-asset-global-blockchain-network/">Digital Asset to Start Global Blockchain Network with Goldman Sachs, Deloitte, BNP and Others</a></p>
<p>The network combines applications designed with Daml, Digital Asset's smart contract language.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/digital-asset-global-blockchain-network/">Digital Asset to Start Global Blockchain Network with Goldman Sachs, Deloitte, BNP and Others</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/digital-asset-global-blockchain-network/">Digital Asset to Start Global Blockchain Network with Goldman Sachs, Deloitte, BNP and Others</a></p>
<p>Digital Asset, which is a financial technology firm, plans to <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/05/09/digital-asset-announces-launch-of-global-blockchain-network-with-deloitte-goldman-and-others/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">introduce</a> a global privacy-enabled interoperable blockchain network curated to offer a decentralized infrastructure for institutional clients, the announcement for which was made on Tuesday. Participants of the network, which is also called the Canton Network, include companies like <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/bnp-paribas/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BNP Paribas</a>, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/deloitte/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Deloitte</a>, Cboe Global Markets, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/goldman-sachs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Goldman Sachs</a>, Broadridge, S&amp;P Global, and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/microsoft-corporation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Microsoft</a> among others.</p>
<p>According to Chris Zuehlke, partner at DRW and global head of Cumberland, the Canton Network is a strong key to the industry&#8217;s quest for a solution that harbors the potential of blockchain while retaining the most primitive privacy specifications for institutional finance. According to Zuehlke, the out-of-the-box approach to looking at the problem, while combining it with the ability to process an atomic transaction via multiple smart contracts, makes it the building block needed to gather these on a chain.</p>
<p>The network combines applications designed with Daml, Digital Asset&#8217;s smart contract language while enabling several systems in financial marketplaces to communicate and synchronize.</p>
<p>According to Jens Hachmeister, head of Issuer services and new digital markets at Deutsche Borse Group, solutions like these have the potential to become building blocks for future virtual and distributed financial market establishments. Even though Digital Asset offers and holds the technology backing the infrastructure, the Daml smart contracts, and the Canton protocol that allows for applications, it does not own the network as it is owned by other participants that also include Digital Asset.</p>
<p>Digital Asset, which was founded in 2014, is a company that develops ledger technology aimed at building distributed, encrypted straight-through processing tools. This is a New-York based company established by Don Wilson, Eric Saraniecki, Sunil Hirani, and Yoval Rooz. Digital Asset is backed by strategic investors like 7RIDGE, Elridge, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/salesforce/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Salesforce</a>, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/samsung/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Samsung</a>, VMware, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/accenture/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Accenture</a>, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/citigroup/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Citi</a>, Goldman Sachs, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ibm/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">IBM</a>, and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/jpmorgan-chase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">JPMorgan</a>.</p>
<p>The firm aims at creating platforms and developer tools that utilize modern infrastructure to revolutionize the way companies communicate. Its service offering is Daml, an application platform that is not restrained by organizational limitations where firms can design new multi-party resolutions that alter contrasting silos into synchronized networks while removing latency and errors.</p>
<p>While the popular belief that the future of institutional finance spins around blockchain and tokenization is still prevalent, these efforts tend to create new siloed blockchains. These silos are then addressed by distributed ledgers wherein interoperability is the solution to unlocking the captivating possibility of composability and collateral mobility.</p>
<p>According to Saraniecki, the founder of Digital Asset, on a public blockchain, one has to use the same set of validators and the data is also completely transparent, hence are non-starters for a regulatory-compliant institution.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/visa-blockchain-small-businesses/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/digital-asset-global-blockchain-network/">Digital Asset to Start Global Blockchain Network with Goldman Sachs, Deloitte, BNP and Others</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/digital-asset-global-blockchain-network/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Here’s How Visa’s Blockchain Innovations Are Empowering Small Businesses</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/visa-blockchain-small-businesses/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/visa-blockchain-small-businesses/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 13:53:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FinTech News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[visa]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=253953</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/visa-blockchain-small-businesses/">Here&#8217;s How Visa&#8217;s Blockchain Innovations Are Empowering Small Businesses</a></p>
<p>Visa is working with its partners to launch programmable CBDCs thereby optimizing capital flows to SMEs. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/visa-blockchain-small-businesses/">Here&#8217;s How Visa&#8217;s Blockchain Innovations Are Empowering Small Businesses</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/visa-blockchain-small-businesses/">Here&#8217;s How Visa&#8217;s Blockchain Innovations Are Empowering Small Businesses</a></p>
<p>Although blockchain technology has shown its prowess in multiple business verticals, its adoption hasn&#8217;t been fast enough. However, payments giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/visa-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Visa Inc</a> (NYSE: V) is now working towards pushing innovative blockchain use-cases towards real-world use cases.</p>
<p>As part of its most recent LIFT Challenge, Visa is exploring blockchain-based use cases for Brazil&#8217;s central bank digital currency aka Digital Real. For this, the payments giant has also partnered with companies such as Microsoft, Agrotoken, and Sinqia.</p>
<p>With its LIFT Challenge participation, Visa is building a programmable finance platform for Small and Medium Enterprises (SMEs), thereby offering them access to global capital markets. This will also improve operational processes, facilitate interoperability between currencies, as well as uncover new growth opportunities.</p>
<h2>Visa and Blockchain Helping Small Businesses</h2>
<p>SMEs play a crucial role in negotiating favorable contracts, however, the financing methods of today are quite outdated leading to losses for farmers. Visa aims to solve this lacuna by providing farmers with more timely and greater access to a global pool of investors for timely investing.</p>
<p>Thus, it allows SMEs to get the best price discovery for their goods. In this way, Visa plans to empower SMEs with additional options to finance their businesses in a secure and frictionless manner. They will optimize existing money movement operations while alleviating the pain points caused by the inaccessibility to traditional services. While working on Brazil&#8217;s <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-central-bank-digital-currency-cbdc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CBDC</a> Digital Real, Visa seeks to address these issues at hand. Speaking on the matter, Catherine Gu, Global Head of CBDC for Visa <a href="https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20230508005774/en/Visa%E2%80%99s-Blockchain-Based-Innovations-Can-Take-Small-Businesses-to-the-Next-Level" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Small businesses are essential contributors to our local economies, such as in Brazil where they employ over half the population and contribute to nearly a third of the country’s GDP. At Visa, we are committed to help them grow, exploring new technologies that will empower them to more easily maintain and expand their business operations.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Enabling Programmable Finance in CBDCs</h2>
<p>As major economies across the world are exploring CBDCs, Visa is working with its partners to demonstrate how CBDCs can enable cross-border payments programmatically, while providing global investment resources to SMEs.</p>
<p>The programmable aspects of CBDCs will allow delivery as well as payment of assets when certain conditions are met. This opens the door for efficient capital usage with reduced counterparty risks, backed by the stability, security, and safety offered by the central bank.</p>
<p>The prototype platform built by Visa brings all the current financial processes and assets on-chain. This will allow farmers and SMEs to tokenize traditional financial contracts. The press release notes: &#8220;Combined with tokenization, Visa implemented a new onchain sealed-bid auction mechanism through smart contracts to enable a global pool of investors on the blockchain to participate in the financing process, achieving competitive price discovery.&#8221;</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ibm-ai-watsonx/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/visa-blockchain-small-businesses/">Here&#8217;s How Visa&#8217;s Blockchain Innovations Are Empowering Small Businesses</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/visa-blockchain-small-businesses/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>IBM Uncovers AI Platform Watsonx for Client Enterprises to Level Up Their Technological Capabilities</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ibm-ai-watsonx/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ibm-ai-watsonx/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 13:44:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ibm]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[watsonx]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=254011</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ibm-ai-watsonx/">IBM Uncovers AI Platform Watsonx for Client Enterprises to Level Up Their Technological Capabilities</a></p>
<p>IBM said Watsonx is an AI solution that enhances machine learning and foundation models using trusted data, speed, and governance.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ibm-ai-watsonx/">IBM Uncovers AI Platform Watsonx for Client Enterprises to Level Up Their Technological Capabilities</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ibm-ai-watsonx/">IBM Uncovers AI Platform Watsonx for Client Enterprises to Level Up Their Technological Capabilities</a></p>
<p>IBM (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ibm/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">International Business Machines Corporation</a>) (NYSE: IBM) has <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/ibm-unveils-the-watsonx-platform-to-power-next-generation-foundation-models-for-business-301818945.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">unveiled</a> an artificial intelligence-facilitating platform Watsonx. At Tuesday&#8217;s annual Think conference, IBM stressed that Watsonx would cater to foundational models and generative AI. The company also added that Watsonx offers a studio, data store, and governance toolkit.</p>
<h2>Watsonx as an AI-Facilitating Solution</h2>
<p>In addition to enhancing next-gen business foundation models, Watsonx seeks to accelerate the impact of the most sophisticated AI with trusted data. According to IBM, the incoming AI and data platform is a one-stop shop that supports enterprises with a complete technology stack. These enterprises would be able to train, tune and deploy machine learning capabilities and foundation models across their organization. Also, enterprises that tap into Watsonx will benefit from the platform&#8217;s trusted data, speed, and governance.</p>
<p>IBM said it would launch the new Watsonx products for code, AIOps, digital labor, security, and sustainability. Furthermore, the AI facilitator&#8217;s products would run across any cloud environment. The information technology powerhouse announced further planned advancements, such as a specialized GPU-as-a-service infrastructure for AI-intensive workloads. IBM also said Watsonx would feature an AI-powered dashboard to manage and report on cloud carbon emissions.</p>
<p>All the offerings in Watson&#8217;s AI development studio are IBM-curated and open-source. Commenting on how Watsonx provides a seamless end-to-end AI workflow that expedites AI adaptation and growth, IBM Chairman and CEO Arvind Krishna explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;With the development of foundation models, AI for business is more powerful than ever. Foundation models make deploying AI significantly more scalable, affordable, and efficient. We built IBM Watsonx for the needs of enterprises so that clients can be more than just users; they can become AI advantaged.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Krishna added:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;With IBM Watson, clients can quickly train and deploy custom AI capabilities across their entire business, all while retaining full control of their data.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Breakdown of IBM Watsonx Product Sets</h2>
<p>The IBX Watsonx platform comprises three unique product sets to meet its clients&#8217; AI needs and requirements. These product sets are its next-gen enterprise studio IBM Watsonx.ai; a specialized data store called IBM Watsonx.data, and the AI governance toolkit IBM Watsonx.governance.</p>
<p>In July, IBM Watsonx.ai, the IT giant&#8217;s primary product set supporting AI builders, would be available. IBM Watsonx.data, optimized for governed data and AI workloads, will also be available in July. Watsonx.ai is built on open lakehouse architecture.</p>
<p>Lastly, IBM Watsonx.governance is the artificial intelligence toolkit that permits trusted AI workflows. The solution&#8217;s functionality includes mitigating risks associated with manual processes and providing required documentation to facilitate favorable outcomes. IBM Watsonx.governance also protects customer privacy and helps organizations measure up to their ethical standards. Watsonx.governace will become available at an undisclosed time later this year.</p>
<p>Another upcoming IBM offering is its Consulting Center of Excellence for Generative AI. This solution sports more than 1,000 generative AI experts to cater to numerous client engagements in the field.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/former-ftx-ceo-fraud-charges/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ibm-ai-watsonx/">IBM Uncovers AI Platform Watsonx for Client Enterprises to Level Up Their Technological Capabilities</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ibm-ai-watsonx/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Former FTX CEO SBF Files Motion to Dismiss Fraud Charges</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/former-ftx-ceo-fraud-charges/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/former-ftx-ceo-fraud-charges/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Babafemi Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 13:27:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sam bankman-fried]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sbf]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=253419</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/former-ftx-ceo-fraud-charges/">Former FTX CEO SBF Files Motion to Dismiss Fraud Charges</a></p>
<p>Meanwhile, the defunct FTX continues to pursue various options to recover customer funds.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/former-ftx-ceo-fraud-charges/">Former FTX CEO SBF Files Motion to Dismiss Fraud Charges</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/former-ftx-ceo-fraud-charges/">Former FTX CEO SBF Files Motion to Dismiss Fraud Charges</a></p>

<p>Former <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a> CEO <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/sam-bankman-fried/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Sam Bankman-Fried</a> has on Monday <a href="https://edition.cnn.com/2023/05/08/tech/sbf-ftx-dismissal-hnk-intl/index.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">filed</a> an ex parte motion before a Federal Court. The motion, as filed through the office, seeks to dismiss 10 out of 13 US charges against the former CEO. The remaining charges include conspiracy to commit commodities fraud, conspiracy to commit securities fraud, and conspiracy to commit money laundering. Interestingly, the former CEO previously pled ‘Not guilty” to all the allegations laid against him.</p>
<p>According to Bankman-Fried’s attorneys, the government has failed to establish the offenses the former CEO is accused of. Consequently, the attorneys urged the judge to dismiss the cases summarily. The government has two weeks to respond to the motions from Bankman-Fried’s lawyers. The next case is due to be heard in court by June 15.</p>
<h2>Is the Former FTX CEO Guilty or Not?</h2>
<p>Before its collapse, FTX was one of the largest cryptocurrency exchanges globally. That was until Bankman-Fried was accused of mismanaging FTX customer deposits by using it to finance risky bets in Alameda Research. The firm was also accused of using company funds to funnel contributions to American politicians.</p>
<p>In his defense, SBF acknowledged that he mishandled customer deposits but rejected the fraud charges. Interestingly, SBF’s former business partners, Gary Wang, Caroline Ellison, and Nishad Singh, have all pleaded guilty to numerous charges.</p>
<p>While he awaits trial, SBF is under house arrest in Palo Alto, California on a $250 million bond. Should the charges prove true, SBF faces between 115 and 155 years in prison. The criminal trial has been scheduled for October.</p>
<h2>Defunct FTX May Restart Operations Next Year</h2>
<p>Meanwhile, the defunct FTX continues to pursue various options to recover customer funds. As of April 12, the firm had recovered $7.3bn (£5.8bn) in customer funds, according to <a href="https://www.theguardian.com/business/2023/apr/13/ftx-customers-funds-recovered-cryptocurrency-exchange" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">The Guardian</a>. While maintaining that the actual fund shortfall is unknown, Andy Dietderich said:</p>
<blockquote>
<p>“The situation has stabilized, and the dumpster fire is out.”</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Moving on, the company will assess the possibility of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-restart-operations-investments-vc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">restarting the exchange</a> by the end of June. Plans to kickstart the company operations from early next year may also materialize, according to the company lawyers.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-earnings-q1-2023/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/former-ftx-ceo-fraud-charges/">Former FTX CEO SBF Files Motion to Dismiss Fraud Charges</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/former-ftx-ceo-fraud-charges/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>PayPal Q1 2023 Earnings Beats Analysts’ Expectations by 1%</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-earnings-q1-2023/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-earnings-q1-2023/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 13:12:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wall Street]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dan schulman]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[paypal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[paypal stock]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=253937</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-earnings-q1-2023/">PayPal Q1 2023 Earnings Beats Analysts&#8217; Expectations by 1%</a></p>
<p>PayPal has been forced to update its 2023 earnings outlook due to its latest financial reports.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-earnings-q1-2023/">PayPal Q1 2023 Earnings Beats Analysts&#8217; Expectations by 1%</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-earnings-q1-2023/">PayPal Q1 2023 Earnings Beats Analysts&#8217; Expectations by 1%</a></p>
<p>Multinational digital payment company <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">PayPal</a> (NASDAQ: PYPL) has <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/paypal-reports-first-quarter-2023-results-301818662.html" target="_blank">released</a> the financial report of its earnings in the first quarter of 2023. PayPal benefited from the outbreak of the novel coronavirus in 2020 as more people switched to online transactions. The company&#8217;s revenue ascended from $17.8 billion in 2019 to over $25 billion in 2021. Its shares also increased significantly during the global spread of the deadly virus. PayPal accounted for more than 16.4% of total retail sales in the US during the period but has slipped under 15% in the past two years.</p>
<p>At the end of the first quarter of 2023, PayPal earnings increased by 33% from the previous year to $1.17 per share. Last year, PayPal generated a revenue of $6.48 billion, earning 88 cents per share. The online payment company noted that its revenue spiked by 9% to $7.04 billion, beating estimates by 1%. Meanwhile, analysts expected PayPal to announce a share price of $1.10, earning $6.98 billion in revenue.</p>
<h2>Analysts Speak on PayPal Q1 2023 Earnings</h2>
<p>After easing pandemic restrictions, PayPal&#8217;s stock growth began to decline. A senior equity and research analyst at Sumitomo Mitsui Banking Corp., Andrew Bauch, said PayPal&#8217;s traditional retail volume has exceeded a volume perspective over a year and a half. Another senior analyst and executive director, Dominick Gabriele, explained that many investors and PayPal expected the financial bumper run to continue.</p>
<p>PayPal has been forced to update its 2023 earnings outlook due to its latest financial reports. In a previous report, the company aims to hit a 19% predicted adjusted earnings growth to about $4.87 per share. However, PayPal now expects an adjusted earnings growth of about 20% to $4.95 per share.</p>
<p>The financial technology company has shifted from an online checkout site to a mobile shopping and in-person payment hub. The recent PayPal switch has increased competition with local companies like Square-parent Block and others. Last August, PayPal announced a $15 billion share buyback program. The digital payment company has <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-2000-employees-pypl/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">announced</a> plans to slough off its operating cost by cutting about 2000 jobs, approximately 7% of its workforce.</p>
<p>The CEO of PayPal Dan Schulman did not comment on the earnings report for the first quarter of 2023. During the 2022 third-quarter earnings report, the executive said there are several unknown factors regarding the macro environment. He noted that the company would control its expenditure and reduce implications on earnings growth.</p>
<p>After amassing exponential gains due to the global health crisis, PayPal stock has plummeted from an all-time high of $310.16 achieved on July 26, 2021, and currently trades at $72.09 per share. The company&#8217;s shares currently hold a Relative Strength Rating of 43 out of the best-possible 99.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/wakweli-blockchain-lawyers-group/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-earnings-q1-2023/">PayPal Q1 2023 Earnings Beats Analysts&#8217; Expectations by 1%</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-earnings-q1-2023/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Wakweli Inked New Partnership with Blockchain Lawyers Group for Web3 Certification</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wakweli-blockchain-lawyers-group/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wakweli-blockchain-lawyers-group/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 13:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain Lawyers Group]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[polygon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wakweli]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=253852</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/wakweli-blockchain-lawyers-group/">Wakweli Inked New Partnership with Blockchain Lawyers Group for Web3 Certification</a></p>
<p>The partnership between Wakweli and the Blockchain Lawyers Group will offer a number of notable advantages that include but are not limited to boosting the liquidity of the entire Wakweli ecosystem.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/wakweli-blockchain-lawyers-group/">Wakweli Inked New Partnership with Blockchain Lawyers Group for Web3 Certification</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/wakweli-blockchain-lawyers-group/">Wakweli Inked New Partnership with Blockchain Lawyers Group for Web3 Certification</a></p>
<p>Wakweli, a <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/">Non-Fungible Token</a> (NFT) certification protocol, has announced its latest partnership with the Blockchain Lawyers Group (BLG) as it seeks to establish its outfit as one of the most legitimate for certifying tokenized assets. As contained in the Press Release shared with Coinspeaker, Wakweli said the collaboration aims to enhance the evolving Web3 legal expertise and enable deeper protocol refinements for the Proof of Democracy (PoD) consensus algorithm it is introducing.</p>
<p>Wakweli is occupying a very unique offshoot of the blockchain ecosystem as it concerns digital collectibles. Designed to issue NFT Certificates that can be verified through its Proof of Democracy model. Wakweli hopes to solve the inherent challenge of authentication in the blockchain ecosystem that can also be transferred to the broader blockchain ecosystem.</p>
<p>With the partnership with the BLG, members of the group will help in participating in the first validation of the very first certificates and assist in strengthening the whole process. The lawyers in the BLG have varying and deep experiences in blockchain-related litigation. Their pedigree and experience will go a long way in certifying the legitimacy of NFT certificates which are churned out by Wakweli.</p>
<p>&#8220;We are excited to partner with such an innovative company as Wakweli, which is trying to solve a preeminent issue in the NFT space. We are confident that our collaboration will bring new levels of innovation and user-friendliness to the market,&#8221; said Blockchain Lawyers Group Founder and Member Miguel Dinis Lucas in a statement.</p>
<p>The partnership between Wakweli and the Blockchain Lawyers Group will also offer a number of notable advantages. These advantages include but are not limited to boosting the liquidity of the entire Wakweli ecosystem.</p>
<h2>Wakweli and Its Steady Growth Pace</h2>
<p>The development of Wakweli has spanned many months followed by very well-diversified product testing.  As Coinspeaker <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/web3-0-wakweli-polygon/">reported</a>, in a bid to advance its technology to more users, earlier Wakweli landed <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/matic-network/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Polygon</a> as its strategic partner.</p>
<p>The Polygon partnership was inked so that Wakweli can extend its NFT certification to decentralized applications hosted on the layer-2 blockchain network.</p>
<p>Commenting on the Polygon partnership, Antoine Sarraute, Wakweli founder said the protocol was primarily “built Wakweli to create a safer web3 space across all chains, and today we are thrilled to collaborate with Polygon. This will enable Wakweli’s certification power to all Polygon users and unlock a definitive way to fight scam attempts, creating more trust in this thriving ecosystem”.</p>
<p>The project has secured funding from some of the biggest names in the industry and with the $1.1 million funding it has secured to date, it aims to stay steadfast in its goal of building one of the most reliable and functionally Web 3.0 infrastructures in the industry today.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bank-digital-canadian-dollar/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/wakweli-blockchain-lawyers-group/">Wakweli Inked New Partnership with Blockchain Lawyers Group for Web3 Certification</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wakweli-blockchain-lawyers-group/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4563 metric#misses=43 metric#hit-ratio=99.1 metric#bytes=1319394 metric#prefetches=203 metric#store-reads=21 metric#store-writes=13 metric#store-hits=209 metric#store-misses=4 metric#sql-queries=34 metric#ms-total=109.82 metric#ms-cache=6.10 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.1850 metric#ms-cache-ratio=5.6 -->