<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 18:10:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The TON Foundation launches file-storage solution</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/the-ton-foundation-launches-file-storage-solution/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/the-ton-foundation-launches-file-storage-solution/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 18:10:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/the-ton-foundation-launches-file-storage-solution/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TON Storage is a new file sharing and data storage platform on the TON blockchain. An incentivised node ecosystem means users can file and store data for perpetuity. Users will utilise smart contracts to pay nodes using Toncoin, the native token on the TON blockchain. The TON Foundation, the group behind the development of The [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-ton-foundation-launches-file-storage-solution/">The TON Foundation launches file-storage solution</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr"><strong>TON Storage is a new file sharing and data storage platform on the TON blockchain.</strong></li>
<li dir="ltr"><strong>An incentivised node ecosystem means users can file and store data for perpetuity.</strong></li>
<li dir="ltr"><strong>Users will utilise smart contracts to pay nodes using Toncoin, the native token on the TON blockchain.</strong></li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">The TON Foundation, the group behind the development of The Open Network (TON) blockchain, has l<a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/in/news-releases/the-ton-foundation-launches-ton-storage--a-next-generation-file-storage-solution-301713232.html" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">aunched</a> a new decentralised file sharing and data solution dubbed TON Storage.</p>
<p dir="ltr">TON Storage works similar to available peer-to-peer file sharing platforms where &ldquo;torrents&rdquo; are used. However, it employs the TON blockchain to allow for the decentralised transfer of data and files of any size, doing away with the need for users to utilise centralised servers.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The storage system also means users can enjoy automatically backed up and encrypted file sharing, with an added layer of security provided by the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/glossary/blockchain/">blockchain</a>.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Step towards open internet</h2>
<p dir="ltr">According to Anatoly Makosov, a TON Foundation founding member, the official launch of TON Storage has been long overdue.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>This technology can be used by both individual users and services with a multimillion-dollar audience</em>,&rdquo; he said in a statement. TON Storage is a step towards actualizing the vision of having a decentralised, open internet, he added.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As traditional torrents do not offer guarantee of storage, but with TON Storage, that changes. This is because of an incentivized ecosystem that allows for files to exist virtually forever. To achieve this, the new file sharing and data storage technology will deploy a smart contracts-based node system.</p>
<p dir="ltr">An agreement between a user and a node will see the user pay for file storage using <a href="https://coinjournal.net/toncoin/">Toncoin</a> &ndash; in essence making it possible to store files for as long as possible. Toncoin is the native cryptocurrency of the TON blockchain.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>Anyone can become a node operator on the TON network and receive payments from other users for hosting files &ndash; even if operating just one node. The accessibility of this new product will incentivise new, independent users to join the TON network, helping to grow the TON ecosystem even further</em>,&rdquo; TON Foundation team noted.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-ton-foundation-launches-file-storage-solution/">The TON Foundation launches file-storage solution</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/the-ton-foundation-launches-file-storage-solution/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Monero (XMR) Price Prediction 2025 &#8211; Here&#8217;s why investors prefer Metacade (MCADE)</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/monero-xmr-price-prediction-2025-heres-why-investors-prefer-metacade-mcade/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/monero-xmr-price-prediction-2025-heres-why-investors-prefer-metacade-mcade/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice Davies]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 17:37:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Monero News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/monero-xmr-price-prediction-2025-heres-why-investors-prefer-metacade-mcade/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>According to leading industry experts, GameFi and play-to-earn (P2E) are set to explode in 2023-2025. New market entrants in this sector are already gaining significant traction with investors, often at the expense of more established players in the wider market. The Monero price prediction 2025 illustrates this trend. It&#8217;s clear that many investors are now [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/monero-xmr-price-prediction-2025-heres-why-investors-prefer-metacade-mcade/">Monero (XMR) Price Prediction 2025 &#8211; Here&#8217;s why investors prefer Metacade (MCADE)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">According to leading industry experts, GameFi and play-to-earn (P2E) are <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/play-to-earn-gaming-revolution-capexmove/?trk=organization-update-content_share-article" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>set to explode in 2023-2025</u></a>. New market entrants in this sector are already gaining significant traction with investors, often at the expense of more established players in the wider market. The Monero price prediction 2025 illustrates this trend. It&rsquo;s clear that many investors are now choosing crypto gaming stars such as Metacade over Monero. Read on to understand why.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Metacade is set to star</h2>
<p dir="ltr">In just a short time, <a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>rising star Metacade</u></a> has become one of the most talked about players in the GameFi sector. Metacade stands to lead well, at the convergence of 3 key areas: metaverse, arcade games, and cryptos. The platform&rsquo;s goal is to become the #1 Web3 community hub for gamers, developers, investors and crypto fanatics.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>Metacade is proving hugely popular with investors, because it offers something of real value to crypto gaming.&nbsp;</strong>Blockchain gamers will enjoy an unrivalled choice of games with genuine P2E potential. Developers benefit from a platform where they can test and market their games, run competitions, and find new staff. And investors and crypto fans can generate income through profitable investment and staking opportunities.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How Metacade Works</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Mark Twain once famously said &ldquo;Find a job you enjoy doing, and you will never have to work a day in your life.&rdquo; That sentiment definitely applies to Metacade gamers, who can earn income through its Play2Earn games, Compete2Earn contests and tournaments, Create2Earn content creation, and Work2Earn testing and employment. Metacade directly connects players and developers, opening up opportunities for market research, new games and recruitment.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Underlining its commitment to its members, Metacade is creating exciting potential with its Metagrants initiative. Metagrants provide funding for designers to develop exciting new games on the platform. Factor in Metacade&rsquo;s community-based model &ndash; ultimately leading to the creation of a full DAO &ndash; and it&rsquo;s clear that all parts of the Metacade hub will benefit from the synergies across the group.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Monero&rsquo;s secret</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The premise behind <a href="https://www.getmonero.org/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Monero (XMR)</u></a> is simple: it offers peer-to-peer currency transactions that are secret, anonymous and untraceable. That smart functionality is Monero (XMR)&rsquo;s greatest strength &ndash; and its greatest weakness. There are plenty of people who have legitimate reasons for wanting to keep their businesses private. But there are also others who want to make secret transactions in order to cover up illegal activities like drug dealing, corruption or fraud.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In the aftermath of the FTX crash, people who lost large sums of money are calling for <a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/after-ftx-collapse-pressure-builds-tougher-crypto-rules-2022-12-02/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>the introduction of tighter and tougher regulations</u></a>.<strong>&nbsp;</strong>It&rsquo;s clear that<strong>&nbsp;if organizations like the SEC follow through on regulation, it could make Monero (XMR)&rsquo;s position challenging at best, and untenable at worst.</strong></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Metacade (MCADE) tops Monero (XMR)</h2>
<p dir="ltr">While Monero must worry about the impact of new regulations, Metacade has no such fears. It can look forward to being part of a market sector that is only going one way. <a href="https://metacade.co/whitepaper.pdf" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade&rsquo;s powerful business model</u></a>, connecting all sides of the crypto gaming community, has won favor with expert analysts, developers, gamers and investors alike.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">What&rsquo;s more, some seasoned observers are predicting great things for the company&rsquo;s share price when it launches &ndash; especially when taking advantage of their <a href="https://metacadeofficial.com/dex" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>presale offer</u></a>. All things considered,<strong>&nbsp;it&rsquo;s easy to see why Metacade is clearly the best investment opportunity&nbsp;</strong>when compared to Monero.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Metacade (MCADE) Price Prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr">You can still <a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>buy into Metacade</u></a> at the stage 1 prelaunch price of $0.01. The predicted launch price already looks like it will ensure a favorable return for early investors. But it&rsquo;s when the P2E market really starts to take off that things could get interesting.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Investors in The Sandbox (SAND) at launch saw a 100x ROI at the height of the market, and there&rsquo;s a chance Metacade could replicate that performance between 2023 and 2025, making it a better bet than the Monero price prediction.</p>
<p dir="ltr">But you need to be quick to make the most of <a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>the Metacade presale</u></a>, as the first phase is selling out fast.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Monero (XMR) Price Prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr">When making the Monero price prediction up to 2025, it&rsquo;s important to factor in a number of considerations. First, if volumes stay low, people will not need to use Monero. Second, if regulators push hard for greater transparency, it could spell trouble for Monero&rsquo;s secret services. And third, there is always the chance that Monero could be hacked, thereby damaging its reputation.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">For those reasons, the Monero price prediction 2025 is for no increase on the end 2022 price of $145.38.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Investors Prefer Metacade to Monero</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Choosing between Metacade and Monero is not a difficult decision. One is an exciting, innovative newcomer in a booming sector. The other offers a service which could very realistically be outlawed by regulators looking to clean up the crypto industry. It&rsquo;s no wonder that investors are choosing Metacade (MCADE) over Monero (XMR). You can join them by taking the opportunity to <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-could-triple-its-price-in-presale-experts-predict/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>buy at the presale price</u></a>.</p>
<p><strong>You can buy XMR at eToro&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://coinjournal.net/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=OTkxNzI" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong><u>here</u></strong></a><strong>.</strong></p>
<p><strong>You can participate in the Metacade presale&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong><u>here</u></strong></a><strong>.</strong></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/monero-xmr-price-prediction-2025-heres-why-investors-prefer-metacade-mcade/">Monero (XMR) Price Prediction 2025 &#8211; Here&#8217;s why investors prefer Metacade (MCADE)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/monero-xmr-price-prediction-2025-heres-why-investors-prefer-metacade-mcade/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The big lesson with FTX&#8217;s collapse is onshore vs. offshore, says former Barclays CEO</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/the-big-lesson-with-ftxs-collapse-is-onshore-vs-offshore-says-former-barclays-ceo/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/the-big-lesson-with-ftxs-collapse-is-onshore-vs-offshore-says-former-barclays-ceo/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 13:27:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Interview]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/the-big-lesson-with-ftxs-collapse-is-onshore-vs-offshore-says-former-barclays-ceo/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bob Diamond believes that cryptocurrency is a very broad term. The former Barclays CEO said the big lesson with FTX&#8217;s collapse is onshore vs. offshore. His firm Atlas Merchant Capital is an active investor in the stablecoin issuer Circle. Crypto is a broad term and has a lot of use cases Bob Diamond, Atlas Merchant [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-big-lesson-with-ftxs-collapse-is-onshore-vs-offshore-says-former-barclays-ceo/">The big lesson with FTX&#8217;s collapse is onshore vs. offshore, says former Barclays CEO</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Bob Diamond believes that cryptocurrency is a very broad term.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The former Barclays CEO said the big lesson with FTX&rsquo;s collapse is onshore vs. offshore.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">His firm Atlas Merchant Capital is an active investor in the stablecoin issuer Circle.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Crypto is a broad term and has a lot of use cases</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Bob Diamond, Atlas Merchant Capital CEO and former Barclays CEO told CNBC in a recent interview that cryptocurrency is a broad term and has a lot of use cases.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">"The big lesson with <a href="https://twitter.com/FTX_Official?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@FTX_Official</a> is onshore vs. offshore," says Atlas Merchant Capital CEO &amp; fmr. <a href="https://twitter.com/Barclays?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@Barclays</a> CEO Bob Diamond. "Strong banks want strong regulation. Will strong firms in the crypto space want strong regulation?" <a href="https://t.co/FJXchVBtU9">pic.twitter.com/FJXchVBtU9</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Squawk Box (@SquawkCNBC) <a href="https://twitter.com/SquawkCNBC/status/1610635817050857472?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 4, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">He revealed that Atlas Merchant Capital has been working with and investing in Circle for quite some time. Diamond said Atlas Merchant Capital is bullish about cryptocurrency and blockchain technology. He stated that;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;Do we believe there is going to be a digital version of the US Dollar over time? Absolutely. Do we believe that the best way to develop that is to have the central bank do it or have the private sector do it? We believe strongly in what Circle is doing.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p dir="ltr">Diamond added that Atlas Merchant Capital is confident that Circle will become real winner in the cryptocurrency space. He added that;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;Crypto is a very broad term. Our focus is on the technology of blockchain and the excitement of having a digital version of the major fiat currencies.&rdquo;</em></p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>FTX&rsquo;s collapse is a lesson for the crypto space</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">When asked about his outlook on the crypto space in the next 2-3 years, the former Barclays CEO believes the crypto industry is going to be different. Diamond added that what happened with FTX (<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/this-week-in-crypto-ftx-files-for-chapter-11-bankruptcy/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>the exchange&rsquo;s collapse</u></a>) reminded him a lot about what happened with Enron (the now-defunct American energy company). He said;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;FTX was like the go-to brand in the crypto space. It had incredibly smart people. It took very illiquid and bad positions during the crypto winter, and it had criminal accounting. As we come out of this, I think there is going to be a lot of focus on payments, technology and blockchain.&rdquo;</em><br>The Atlas Merchant CEO added that the other big lesson from all these is onshore vs. offshore. He added that;</p>
<p><em>&ldquo;Circle operates within the regulatory perimeter of the US while FTX was operating in the Bahamas. Strong banks want strong regulation. Will strong firms in the crypto space want strong regulation? Part of that is operating within the US perimeter.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p>This&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>latest cryptocurrency news</u></a> comes as Sam Bankman-Fried&rsquo;s case with the United States government continues over the collapse of the FTX exchange.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-big-lesson-with-ftxs-collapse-is-onshore-vs-offshore-says-former-barclays-ceo/">The big lesson with FTX&#8217;s collapse is onshore vs. offshore, says former Barclays CEO</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/the-big-lesson-with-ftxs-collapse-is-onshore-vs-offshore-says-former-barclays-ceo/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The rise and fall of Internet Computer: How ICP imploded</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/the-rise-and-fall-of-internet-computer-how-icp-imploded/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/the-rise-and-fall-of-internet-computer-how-icp-imploded/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 12:06:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Opinion]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/the-rise-and-fall-of-internet-computer-how-icp-imploded/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Internet Computer is a major blockchain project valued at over $1 billion. ICP&#8217;s token has slumped by over 95% from its all-time high. Its ecosystem is a bit weak to justify a billion-dollar valuation. Internet Computer has had a spectacular fall from grace in less than two years. ICP, its token, has crashed by more [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-rise-and-fall-of-internet-computer-how-icp-imploded/">The rise and fall of Internet Computer: How ICP imploded</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Internet Computer is a major blockchain project valued at over $1 billion.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">ICP&rsquo;s token has slumped by over 95% from its all-time high.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Its ecosystem is a bit weak to justify a billion-dollar valuation.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/internet-computer/"><u>Internet Computer</u></a> has had a spectacular fall from grace in less than two years. ICP, its token, has crashed by more than 98% from its all-time high. Its total market cap has plunged from over $100 billion in May 2021 to about $1 billion. So, what went wrong?</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Internet Computer?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Internet Computer is a blockchain project that was launched by Dfinity, a Swiss non-profit organization in 2021. Its launch came at a time when most cryptocurrencies, including&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/shiba-inu/"><u>Shiba Inu</u></a><strong>,&nbsp;</strong>were being launched. As a result, because of the hype surrounding the token, the price surged, pushing it into the top ten of the biggest coins in the world.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Internet Computer is one of the best-funded projects in the blockchain industry. According to Crunchbase, Dfinity raised over $166 million from a group of investors like Andreessen Horowitz and Polychain Capital. At the time of listing, their investments had ballooned into billions of dollars.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Internet Computer&rsquo;s goal was to create a blockchain-based supercomputer that runs in a decentralized way. At the time of launch, the&nbsp;<a href="https://www.ft.com/content/a1f7a90d-68cc-4854-9896-c538e2be58ca"><u>Financial Times</u></a> claimed that the technology would disrupt cloud computing giants like AWS and Google Cloud.</p>
<p dir="ltr">For example, developers would use its technology to build blockchain-based apps that are equivalent to popular ones like Whatsapp and Venmo.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Why Internet Computer failed</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Most people who follow the crypto space believe that Internet Computer has not lived to the hype it expected when it was launched. This explains why the ICP price has struggled since its inception. Unlike other popular blockchains like Ethereum, Polkadot, and Binance Chain, it is not possible to see what is built in Internet Computer.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Internet Computer has several apps in its ecosystem. But a deep dive shows that some of them are no longer in development while others have little or no activity. For example, OpenChat is a platform that seeks to be a blockchain-based alternative to Whatsapp. I tried to create an account but the process was long and I received a notification that they were no longer accepting new members.</p>
<p dir="ltr">I also attempted to use DSCVR, a community-owned professional network that looks like Reddit. I tried using it but found no meaningful content. The same was true for other dApps in its ecosystem like DFinance, Portal, and NFT Studio.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Internet Computer is not dead. A look at its explorer shows that there is still some activity in the ecosystem. The question is whether that activity is worth over $1 billion as ICP&rsquo;s market cap suggests.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy Internet Computer</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    Binance</h3>

    <p>Binance is one of the largest cryptocurrency exchanges in the world. It is better suited to more experienced investors and it offers a large number of cryptocurrencies to choose from, at over 600.

Binance is also known for having low trading fees and a multiple of trading options that its users can benefit from, such as; peer-to-peer trading, margin trading and spot trading.
</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/binance-crypto?guid=OTkxNjU&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=AZ&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy ICP with Binance today            </a>
    </p><h3>
    Binance.US</h3>

    <p>Binance.US provides secure and reliable access to the world&rsquo;s most popular cryptocurrencies, with some of the lowest fees in the industry.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/binance-us-crypto?guid=OTkxNjU&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=AZ&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy ICP with Binance.US today            </a>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-rise-and-fall-of-internet-computer-how-icp-imploded/">The rise and fall of Internet Computer: How ICP imploded</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/the-rise-and-fall-of-internet-computer-how-icp-imploded/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin remains close to $17k after FOMC minutes release: Will BTC rally soon?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-remains-close-to-17k-after-fomc-minutes-release-will-btc-rally-soon/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-remains-close-to-17k-after-fomc-minutes-release-will-btc-rally-soon/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 11:35:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-remains-close-to-17k-after-fomc-minutes-release-will-btc-rally-soon/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin price steadied above $16,800 as US Federal Reserve officials agreed to slow its pace of interest rate hikes. The latest FOMC minutes indicate that US policymakers are focused on controlling the pace of price hikes. Bitcoin could surge past the $17k resistance level soon. BTC eyes the $17k resistance level The United States Federal [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-remains-close-to-17k-after-fomc-minutes-release-will-btc-rally-soon/">Bitcoin remains close to $17k after FOMC minutes release: Will BTC rally soon?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin price steadied above $16,800 as US Federal Reserve officials agreed to slow its pace of interest rate hikes.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The latest FOMC minutes indicate that US policymakers are focused on controlling the pace of price hikes.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin could surge past the $17k resistance level soon.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>BTC eyes the $17k resistance level</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">The United States Federal Reserve recently released minutes from the Federal Open Market Committee for December. Fed members agreed that a restrictive policy stance would need to be maintained for now until the incoming data provided confidence that core inflation was on a sustained downward path back down to 2%.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>latest cryptocurrency news</u></a> saw Bitcoin, the world&rsquo;s leading cryptocurrency by market cap, maintain its price above the $16,800 level over the last 24 hours. It has lost less than 1% of its value, and the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/"><u>price of Bitcoin</u></a> now stands at $16,834.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The broader crypto market is also recovering from its recent slump. At press time, the total cryptocurrency market cap stands at $819 billion, up by less than 1% in the last 24 hours.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Key levels to watch</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The BTC/USD 4-hour chart is bullish as Bitcoin has held its ground above the 50-day Exponential Moving Average (EMA) at $16,714 over the last few days.&nbsp;</p>
<div class="fr-img-space-wrap"><span class="fr-img-caption fr-fic fr-dib fr-draggable fr-fil" style="width: 600px"><span class="fr-img-wrap">
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/00/05/1672918312743-4bc47cda-34f3-4279-bfdb-ac3aadc1412f.png" style="width: 600px" class="fr-fic fr-dib fr-fil" width="600" height="284"><span class="fr-inner"><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/?exchange=COINBASE"><u>BTC/USD Chart By TradingView</u></a></span></p>
<p></p></span></span>
<p class="fr-img-space-wrap2">&nbsp;</p>
</div>
<p dir="ltr">The MACD line is above the neutral zone, indicating that the leading cryptocurrency has preserved its downward trend from the standpoint of realised price. The 14-day RSI of 61 also shows that more bulls controlling the market could see BTC enter the overbought region.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">If the bullish momentum increases, BTC could surge past the first major resistance level at $17,145 over the next few hours. However, Bitcoin could struggle to surpass the second major resistance level at $17,485 in the short term, unless it gains support from the broader crypto market.&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Where to buy Bitcoin now</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>

    <p>eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=OTkxNTc&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=AZ&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy BTC with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    Binance</h3>

    <p>Binance is one of the largest cryptocurrency exchanges in the world. It is better suited to more experienced investors and it offers a large number of cryptocurrencies to choose from, at over 600.

Binance is also known for having low trading fees and a multiple of trading options that its users can benefit from, such as; peer-to-peer trading, margin trading and spot trading.
</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/binance-crypto?guid=OTkxNTc&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=AZ&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy BTC with Binance today            </a>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-remains-close-to-17k-after-fomc-minutes-release-will-btc-rally-soon/">Bitcoin remains close to $17k after FOMC minutes release: Will BTC rally soon?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-remains-close-to-17k-after-fomc-minutes-release-will-btc-rally-soon/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Classic eyes the $20 resistance level after its latest rally</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-classic-eyes-the-20-resistance-level-after-its-latest-rally/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-classic-eyes-the-20-resistance-level-after-its-latest-rally/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 11:33:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum Classic News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-classic-eyes-the-20-resistance-level-after-its-latest-rally/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum Classic is the best performer amongst the top 50 cryptocurrencies by market cap today. ETC is up by more than 4% today and has added 21% to its value in the last seven days. The broader crypto market is underperforming after a positive start to the week. ETC is outperforming the other major cryptocurrencies [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-classic-eyes-the-20-resistance-level-after-its-latest-rally/">Ethereum Classic eyes the $20 resistance level after its latest rally</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Ethereum Classic is the best performer amongst the top 50 cryptocurrencies by market cap today.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">ETC is up by more than 4% today and has added 21% to its value in the last seven days.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The broader crypto market is underperforming after a positive start to the week.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>ETC is outperforming the other major cryptocurrencies today</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">ETC, the native coin of the Ethereum Classic blockchain, is the best performer amongst the top 50 cryptocurrencies by market cap today. It is up by more than 4% in the last 24 hours, and the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum-classic/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>price of Ethereum Classic</u></a> now stands at $18.73.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to the crypto analytics platform <a href="https://insights.santiment.net/read/new-years-parties-may-have-ended-but-altcoins-haven-t-7169" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Santiment</u></a>, Ethereum Classic is enjoying a pretty nice rally of its own. Not only is volume high, but ETC is also being shorted big time by traders on exchanges.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>latest cryptocurrency news</u></a> could be the major catalyst driving ETC higher. The broader crypto market had a positive start to the week but is now retreating. The total crypto market cap stands at $817 billion, down by less than 1% in the last 24 hours.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin and Ether continue to maintain their prices above the $16,800 and $1,250 levels, respectively.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Key levels to watch</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The ETC/USD 4-hour chart is bullish as Ethereum Classic has been performing well over the last few days. The technical indicators show that ETC is outperforming the broader crypto market.</p>
<div class="fr-img-space-wrap"><span class="fr-img-caption fr-fic fr-dib fr-draggable fr-fil" style="width: 600px"><span class="fr-img-wrap">
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/00/05/1672918312771-242b08a3-e09e-4008-8d33-a4be09305bcf.png" style="width: 600px" class="fr-fic fr-dib fr-fil" width="600" height="261"><span class="fr-inner"><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ETCUSD/?exchange=COINBASE"><u>ETC/USD Chart By TradingView</u></a></span></p>
<p></p></span></span>
<p class="fr-img-space-wrap2">&nbsp;</p>
</div>
<p dir="ltr">The MACD line is deep within the positive territory, indicating that the bulls are in charge of the market. The 14-day relative strength index of 78 shows that ETC could enter the overbought region if the rally continues.</p>
<p dir="ltr">With the bulls in charge, ETC could surge past the first major resistance level at $20.12 before the end of the day. In the event of an extended rally, ETC could trade above the $23 psychological level for the first time since November 2022.</p>
<p></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Where to buy Ethereum Classic now</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>

    <p>eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=OTkxNTY&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=AZ&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy ETC with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    Binance</h3>

    <p>Binance is one of the largest cryptocurrency exchanges in the world. It is better suited to more experienced investors and it offers a large number of cryptocurrencies to choose from, at over 600.

Binance is also known for having low trading fees and a multiple of trading options that its users can benefit from, such as; peer-to-peer trading, margin trading and spot trading.
</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/binance-crypto?guid=OTkxNTY&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=AZ&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy ETC with Binance today            </a>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-classic-eyes-the-20-resistance-level-after-its-latest-rally/">Ethereum Classic eyes the $20 resistance level after its latest rally</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-classic-eyes-the-20-resistance-level-after-its-latest-rally/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bonk price has soared: prepare for a major dive</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bonk-price-has-soared-prepare-for-a-major-dive/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/bonk-price-has-soared-prepare-for-a-major-dive/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 11:10:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bonk-price-has-soared-prepare-for-a-major-dive/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bonk has captured the attention of most traders and investors. History suggests that Bonk price will implode soon. Tokens like Tamadoge, Saudi Shiba Inu, and Dogelon have been forgotten. Bonk price has made headlines in 2023 as it became one of the best-performing tokens in the world. The token&#8217;s price surged to a high of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bonk-price-has-soared-prepare-for-a-major-dive/">Bonk price has soared: prepare for a major dive</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Bonk has captured the attention of most traders and investors.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">History suggests that Bonk price will implode soon.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Tokens like Tamadoge, Saudi Shiba Inu, and Dogelon have been forgotten.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Bonk price has made headlines in 2023 as it became one of the best-performing tokens in the world. The token&rsquo;s price surged to a high of $0.0000036, which was dramatically higher than its all-time low. According to CoinMarketCap, the meme coin&rsquo;s market cap surged to more than $200 million.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Beware of an upcoming crash</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Meme coins have become popular in the financial industry in the past few months. Besides, creating these tokens has become easy because of smart contract platforms like Ethereum and Solana. Also, some developers have made a fortune launching meme coins like Dogecoin, Shiba Inu, Tamadoge, Dogelon Mars, and Floki Inu.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bonk is a&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/why-is-bonk-going-up-be-careful-of-doggy-tokens-we-have-seen-this-movie-before/"><u>new meme coin</u></a> that was launched on Christmas day. It is a meme coin whose developers aim will become the Shiba Inu equivalent of Solana. They hope that it will be used to power the Solana ecosystem, which is going through turmoil because of its exposure to FTX and Alameda. We have covered the link between the entities&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/near-price-stages-a-slow-recovery-will-these-gains-hold/"><u>here</u></a><strong>.</strong></p>
<p dir="ltr">Bonk has become highly popular in the past few days. Indeed, the total volume of the token traded in the past 24 hours in centralised exchanges rose to $152 million. It has also become popular in Solana Dex platforms like Orca and Saber.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bonk price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr">However, there are reasons to be cautious about Bonk price. First, its price action resembles what we saw with other meme coins like Tamadoge and even Saudi Shiba Inu. In this, the token tends to rise sharply and then decline as it moves into the distribution phase.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Second, it appears like Bonk is a way for Solana insiders to make a killing. A quick look at its whitepaper<strong>&nbsp;</strong>shows that most of the Bonk tokens are allocated to insiders, including the makers of OpenBook. OpenBook is a new iteration of Serum, which collapsed in November.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Third, Bonk price will likely resume the bearish trend as the momentum surrounding it wanes. We saw this with other popular meme tokens before. While Dogelon Mars and its peers were highly popular at their prime, they have since then been forgotten.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Finally, it is hard to imagine a meme coin with no utility do well in a period of high-interest rates. Fed minutes published on Wednesday showed that the committee expects that rates will remain high for a while. Therefore, I expect that BONK will crash to $0.00000011 in the next few days.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy Bonk</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bonk-price-has-soared-prepare-for-a-major-dive/">Bonk price has soared: prepare for a major dive</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/bonk-price-has-soared-prepare-for-a-major-dive/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Creating the ideal trading desk setup: 5 steps</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/creating-the-ideal-trading-desk-setup-5-steps/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 10:08:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/creating-the-ideal-trading-desk-setup-5-steps/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Comfortability is essential in managing and growing your portfolio. A good trading desk setup helps to counter the stress of training and increase the chances of success. Here are some essential requirements for creating the perfect trading desk setup.&#160; Day traders typically work from home, but the task of day trading can be stressful even [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/creating-the-ideal-trading-desk-setup-5-steps/">Creating the ideal trading desk setup: 5 steps</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Comfortability is essential in managing and growing your portfolio.</li>
<li dir="ltr">A good trading desk setup helps to counter the stress of training and increase the chances of success.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Here are some essential requirements for creating the perfect trading desk setup.&nbsp;</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Day traders typically work from home, but the task of day trading can be stressful even from the comfort of your own home. It is difficult to predict an unpredictable market and making the right moves is essential for managing and growing your portfolio especially when <a href="http://%20https://coinjournal.net/cryptocurrencies/trade/">trading cryptocurrencies</a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This is why traders invest in creating the perfect desk setup to counter the stress of training, improve focus, and increase the chances of success. In this article, we&rsquo;ll cover the essential requirements for creating the perfect trading desk setup.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What you need for a trading desk setup</h2>
<p dir="ltr">These are the main 5 things you need to consider for your new setup.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">1. Get an adjustable trading desk.</h3>
<p dir="ltr">So, what&rsquo;s the distinction between a regular desk and a stock trading desk setup? The main differences are defined by the following elements: ERGONOMICS, QUALITY, AND PRICE. Trading desks, as opposed to standard office furniture, are designed, customized and adjustable to meet the specific needs of individual traders. These include the number and total weight of screen displays, the size and layout of the office, colour and aesthetics, as well as post-sale maintenance services and warranties.</p>
<h4 dir="ltr">Requirements for a Trading Desk</h4>
<p dir="ltr">Before buying a trading desk, it should meet the following requirements:</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr"><strong>Price:&nbsp;</strong>Manufacturers do a good job of producing high-quality trading desks that can cost anywhere from $5,000 to $10,000, depending on the level of customization.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr"><strong>Make it a standing desk:&nbsp;</strong>You can easily find a variety of adjustable desk options that are ideal for home trading and it is advisable to go with a standing desk. Trading requires you to sit all day which can be harmful to your health in the long run. So, it is advisable to get a desk that allows you to change your positions when you need to so that you can keep <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-spot-trading-the-best-coins-to-consider-in-it/"><u>trading the best assets in the crypto market.</u></a></p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr"><strong>Size: &nbsp;</strong>Ideally, go for a desk with a work surface of 70.5&Prime; x 30&Prime;. This gives you more than enough space to house whatever your trading desk setup may require, and the ideal blank canvas for you to configure your desk setup to work best for you.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">One side of the desk can easily be dedicated to multiple screen displays and trading tools, while the other side of the desk can be configured to suit whatever your other full-time job requires.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">You will be able to easily switch between different tasks if you organize your workspace in this manner.&nbsp;</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">2. Screen space</h3>
<p dir="ltr">Forex traders require more detailed on-screen information as they take on more risk. Traders must make room for future opportunities by concentrating on markets that are not currently traded.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Monitors have become more affordable in recent years. Multiple monitors can be connected to the same graphics card, increasing your efficiency. Also, in order to understand both the long-term and short-term trends, you may need to monitor multiple timeframes when <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/what-are-the-best-cryptocurrencies-for-swing-trading/"><u>trading the best cryptocurrencies in the market</u></a>.</p>
<h4 dir="ltr">Ideal Number of Monitors</h4>
<p dir="ltr">So, how many monitors/screens do home traders need to monitor the markets effectively? The number of monitors is determined by your budget and you can find some of the <a href="https://howtotrade.com/blog/best-trading-computers-and-laptops/"><u>best trading monitors in the market</u></a> within your desired price range. A 42-inch screen with a high resolution of 1024 x 768 is ideal when buying a monitor. Anything less may make it difficult for you to study charts and note other key details.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">For thorough visual analysis, you should ideally have three trading screens; your laptop and two monitors. You can choose to invest more if you have the budget but it will make it difficult to analyze key information.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/00/05/1672911464802-4d3f7314-b14f-4cbf-992f-49670f992ce0.jpg" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="615" height="409"></p>
<h3 dir="ltr">3. A comfortable chair</h3>
<p dir="ltr">Chair designers have done an excellent job of making computer users feel at ease. It makes life easier for those who must work on a computer all day. Because they support your body while working, it is important to take your time when picking out a chair for your trading setup. &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Investing in a nice comfortable chair is not a waste of money because better posture and relaxed seating can help you be more effective and make better decisions. The goal is to make your work comfortable and stress-free for your body, as well as to support the body parts involved in your work the most.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The chair should be fully adjustable, with height, backrest tilt, headrest, armrests, and a flexible lumbar system with height and tension adjustability. By allowing the lumbar support design to be flexible, the chair can actively optimize itself to help support your back in real-time.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">4. Quick internet access</h3>
<p dir="ltr">To keep up with every movement in the market, you&rsquo;ll need to invest in the most powerful high-speed internet connection you can afford. Although it may appear obvious, a consistent and dependable internet connection is required for the serious day trader when you cannot make quick buy and sell decisions <a href="https://coinjournal.net/compare/best-cryptocurrency-apps/"><u>using crypto trading apps</u></a>, trading halts.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Failure to carry out your responsibilities correctly and on time can be extremely costly to your investment.&nbsp;</p>
<h4 dir="ltr">Improving your internet speed</h4>
<p dir="ltr">There are easy ways to speed up your internet access without having to spend hours on the problem. You can use the following:</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr"><strong>Get a router:&nbsp;</strong>Utilize a high-speed internet connection with a router in conjunction with a backup mobile connection.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr"><strong>Get a high-performance laptop:&nbsp;</strong>Invest in the fastest computer your budget allows. If you are serious about day trading, you will need a fast computer. Computers are a recurring expense that appears every few years or so. Rather than investing in a low-quality laptop with low battery life and slow performance, spend the money on a dependable, well-functioning machine.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">For mobile traders who need portability on a daily basis, high-performance laptops are also an option. Make sure that whatever computer you choose is never the limiting factor in your trading.</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr"><strong>Get an ad blocker:&nbsp;</strong>As long as you are working online, you are going to be faced with endless ads and auto-played videos. Even if you don&rsquo;t mind the ads, they slow down your internet connection and by extension, affect your trading.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">It is preferable to install an ad-blocking plugin that will shut down data-consuming ads and free your internet connection.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/00/05/1672911632041-5cabba8f-4bae-4d5c-a438-de4a138642be.jpg" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="615" height="345"></p>
<h3 dir="ltr">5. Distraction-free and peaceful surroundings</h3>
<p dir="ltr">To conduct online trading, you must select the quietest area of your home. Noise is avoided by most traders because it disrupts and reduces productivity. It is not a good idea to set up your home office in a busy room. here are a few things you can do to get the perfect trading environment:</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr"><strong>Stay far away from distracting objects:&nbsp;</strong>You should also keep a safe distance between yourself and the television and lounge area. Select a location with a door to keep outside noise to a minimum.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr"><strong>Inform your family members:&nbsp;</strong>Not everyone, however, has the luxury of private space at home. If possible ask for cooperation from family members as well so that you can easily carve out a space for yourself. &nbsp;</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr"><strong>Maintain a clutter-free desk:&nbsp;</strong>A clean desk should be part of your home trading setup, as clutter on your desk can hinder productivity. Additionally, make an effort to keep the room clean and free of dirt and disorganized items.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">In addition, avoiding on-screen distractions such as social media and other notifications and alerts that divert your attention and cause you to miss out on opportunities is critical. Only enable the most important desktop notifications and alerts and disable the rest.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Conclusion&nbsp;</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Whether you are a new trader or an experienced one, having the perfect trading desk setup creates the perfect environment for success. It allows you to focus on the tasks that are truly important free from chaos and distractions.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Before buying desks, chairs, and monitors, take some time to consider the different options and check the reviews of other buyers before making a purchase. This way, you are assured of getting value for your investment.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/creating-the-ideal-trading-desk-setup-5-steps/">Creating the ideal trading desk setup: 5 steps</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Markets where crypto usage is highly likely to explode in 2023</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/markets-where-crypto-usage-is-highly-likely-to-explode-in-2023/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 10:05:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto adoption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/markets-where-crypto-usage-is-highly-likely-to-explode-in-2023/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Despite the current crypto winter more and more people would want to link their businesses to cryptocurrencies. Online casinos are now accepting crypto deposits and withdrawals. There are also various companies that have ventured into creating infrastructure for the crypto industry. In 2021, the cryptocurrency market experienced significant growth, which led to many global companies [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/markets-where-crypto-usage-is-highly-likely-to-explode-in-2023/">Markets where crypto usage is highly likely to explode in 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Despite the current crypto winter more and more people would want to link their businesses to cryptocurrencies.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Online casinos are now accepting crypto deposits and withdrawals.</li>
<li dir="ltr">There are also various companies that have ventured into creating infrastructure for the crypto industry.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">In 2021, the cryptocurrency market experienced significant growth, which led to many global companies showing interest in digital assets. If earlier <a href="https://coinjournal.net/cryptocurrencies/invest/hub/">investments in cryptocurrency</a> were made only by companies that firmly believed in this industry&rsquo;s development, now more and more people would want to transfer their business to tokens.</p>
<p dir="ltr">You should not think that the transition to cryptocurrency is connected only with trends and that now everyone uses such coins. Today we will discuss why traditional companies use digital currency. We will also tell you about the markets that will switch to cryptocurrency in 2023.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Crypto in Gambling</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The most popular area of application of cryptocurrency is the sphere of gambling on the Internet. Both <a href="https://coinjournal.net/casinos/">online casinos</a> and bookmakers can make payments in bitcoins and other tokens. The transition of many sites to cryptocurrencies is due to the advantages that these coins provide:</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Fast speed of payments. Casino customers can replenish their accounts and withdraw winnings almost instantly.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">No need for verification.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Minimal commissions or their complete absence.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">With cryptocurrency, you will have access to the whole range of gambling entertainment &ndash; games with live dealers (here&rsquo;s a trusted site to try it out; <a href="https://www.ignitioncasino.eu/live-dealer"><u>https://www.ignitioncasino.eu/live-dealer</u></a>), classic video slots, sports betting, lotteries, and much more.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Technology Sector&nbsp;</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Already, cryptocurrencies are actively used by companies from the technology sector. Schematically, such companies can be divided into three groups. Below, we describe each group in more detail.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr"><em>Investor Companies</em></h3>
<p dir="ltr">This category includes firms that convert their regular fiat money into cryptocurrencies. The brightest representatives are Tesla and Microstrategy. They are interested in Bitcoin, despite its recent instability.</p>
<p dir="ltr">It is now known that about 7.5% of <a href="https://www.tesla.com/"><u>Tesla&rsquo;s</u></a> free money is in cryptocurrency. Not all the company&rsquo;s investors appreciate this approach. Many people are sure that buying cryptocurrency is a dangerous and thoughtless act that can lead to losing a significant amount of funds.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/00/05/1672912461754-09b9a432-1d15-428c-85cb-d5842b742a61.jpg" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="615" height="409"></p>
<p dir="ltr">Microstrategy is even more interested in Bitcoin. Currently, the company has more digital coins on its balance sheet than regular money. At the same time, the management is not even afraid of the situation with bitcoin &ndash; after the fall in the rate, the most famous cryptocurrency was not only not sold but also bought more.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Now, cryptocurrency is one of the safest ways to store money if you do not consider fluctuations in the exchange rate. Modern <a href="https://coinjournal.net/compare/best-cryptocurrency-wallets/"><u>cryptocurrency wallets</u></a> provide secure storage of coins. No outsider will be able to access your account.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr"><em>Companies That Create Infrastructure for Crypto</em></h3>
<p dir="ltr">We are talking about companies that develop and produce equipment for the extraction of cryptocurrency &ndash; for mining. The following manufacturers fall into this category:</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Nvidia;</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://www.amd.com/en"><u>AMD</u></a>;</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">TSM;</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Bitfury;</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Bitmain;</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Canaan;</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Ebang.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">The development of the crypto industry has led to the fact that over the past few years, the cost of video cards suitable for coin mining has increased several times. The market is constantly replenished with new manufacturers who strive to offer customers productive and energy-efficient mining equipment.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr"><em>Companies Building an Ecosystem for Cryptocurrencies</em></h3>
<p dir="ltr">This category includes firms that accept cryptocurrency as a payment method. This includes PayPal, Visa, Mastercard, JP Morgan, and many of the world&rsquo;s central banks. Moreover, these firms use tokens in internal processes.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Every year, the list of such companies continues to expand. This is mainly because cryptocurrency is legalized and beginning to be accepted at the state level.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Benefits of Cryptocurrency</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The ubiquity of digital tokens is due to several advantages they have:</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Inflation protection. Inflation causes the value of any currency to decrease over time. Cryptocurrency is issued with a fixed amount.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Security and privacy. The blockchain is based on complex mathematical operations, so it takes time to decode it.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Decentralization. Many cryptocurrencies are controlled not only by the developers but also by the people who use them.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Convenient transactions. Cryptocurrencies allow you to make payments instantly with a minimum commission. It is also one of the most convenient ways to send money to other countries.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/00/05/1672912571729-17786a8c-5cf6-4aba-af33-b5342b228a35.jpg" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="615" height="409"></p>
<p dir="ltr">Remember some disadvantages of cryptocurrency. The biggest drawback is the exchange rate instability. Tokens change their value several times a day.</p>
<p dir="ltr">At the same time, exchange rate fluctuations can be severe. If you decide to invest in crypto tokens, it is worth remembering all the possible risks you may face. It is possible that the coins can completely depreciate.</p>
<p dir="ltr">It is worth remembering the situation with bitcoin. At the end of 2021, the coin&rsquo;s price reached an all-time high, exceeding $60,000 per token. And 2022 was not the most successful year for bitcoin &ndash; this year, the price dropped to $16,000 and below.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Conclusion</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Every year, more and more companies are starting to use cryptocurrency as their primary payment method. It is too early to say that tokens will completely replace fiat money. But in the future, people will have even more opportunities to use digital coins.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/markets-where-crypto-usage-is-highly-likely-to-explode-in-2023/">Markets where crypto usage is highly likely to explode in 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
