<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 17:45:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Analyst Suggests Replacing FAANG with MATANA in Hierarchy of Stocks</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/analyst-faang-matana-stocks/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/analyst-faang-matana-stocks/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 17:24:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wall Street]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alphabet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[faang]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[facebook]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[google]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MAANG]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MATANA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Meta]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[microsoft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[netflix]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nvidia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tesla]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=259433</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/analyst-faang-matana-stocks/">Analyst Suggests Replacing FAANG with MATANA in Hierarchy of Stocks</a></p>
<p>Ray Wang, Constellation Research Principal Analyst, believes that due to market changes FAANG should be replaced with MATANA in stock ranking.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/analyst-faang-matana-stocks/">Analyst Suggests Replacing FAANG with MATANA in Hierarchy of Stocks</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/analyst-faang-matana-stocks/">Analyst Suggests Replacing FAANG with MATANA in Hierarchy of Stocks</a></p>
<p>In the ever-evolving tech world, the dominance of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-are-faang-stocks/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FAANG</a> &#8211; <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/facebook/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Facebook Inc</a>, now <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/meta/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Meta Platforms Inc</a> (NASDAQ: META), <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/apple-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Apple Inc</a> (NASDAQ: AAPL),<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/amazon/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"> Amazon.com Inc</a> (NASDAQ: AMZN), <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/netflix/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Netflix Inc</a> (NASDAQ: NFLX), and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/google/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Google</a> alongside its parent company <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/alphabet-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Alphabet Inc</a> (NASDAQ: GOOGL) &#8211; has been unquestionable. However, as the sector evolves, some experts suggest that it is necessary to rethink the hierarchy and put a new lineup at the top even before earlier proposed <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-are-manta-stocks-and-how-are-they-taking-over-faang/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">MANTA</a> stocks. In a <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tech-stocks-matana-is-the-new-faang-analyst-says-145511543.html?guccounter=1&amp;guce_referrer=aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuZ29vZ2xlLmNvbS8&amp;guce_referrer_sig=AQAAAL1DXACbr0q6JRkF315Jk_Tkw1_642GIrrk6AmGDhJl-c6yFjTQc44i2tDnPy3h7Us4KY7RGVVZfDW5p9aLgGjp0mmCVsMs2URZBXnvbcKRdb0zeq6MZdvxDXHkya4W5-7XTvoe9TLdOSgvUy90gwRlf1QYeT657wapaRWnDgDLH" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a>, Constellation Research Principal Analyst and Founder, Ray Wang, recently proposed a revamped lineup known as MATANA &#8211; an acronym that presupposes excluding Meta and Netflix stocks from FAANG while adding <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/microsoft-corporation/">Microsoft Corporation</a> (NASDAQ: MSFT), <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/tesla/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tesla Inc</a> (NASDAQ: TSLA), and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/nvidia/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Nvidia Corp</a> (NASDAQ: NVDA).</p>
<h2>MATANA Stocks</h2>
<p>CNBC&#8217;s “Mad Money” anchor Jim Cramer coined the phrase “FAANG” also known as “<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-are-maang-stocks/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">MAANG</a>” to designate the tech giants Meta Platforms, Apple, Amazon, Netflix, and Google in 2013. At the time, these companies were seen as disruptive startups that had transformed their respective markets.</p>
<p>However, Wang now believes that it is time to re-evaluate the position of Meta and Netflix within the Big Tech ecosystem. Wang argues that both companies require a fresh perspective and, in particular, Meta needs a new plan to regain its competitive edge.</p>
<p>Wang argues that the growth potential of Netflix raises questions about the scalability of its subscription-based model. Notably, Netflix&#8217;s success in the media and entertainment industry is founded on its subscription-based strategy, in which customers pay a monthly fee for access to a massive library of content.</p>
<p>However, Wang is concerned that as the streaming scene becomes more saturated, Netflix has difficulties in maintaining subscriber growth. He, therefore, suggests that exploring alternative revenue streams, such as product placement and Intellectual Property (IP) licensing, could be crucial for Netflix&#8217;s long-term success.</p>
<p>In the instance of Meta, Wang claims that the company&#8217;s reliance on advertising revenue has created fundamental growth constraints. He highlighted that Meta needs to diversify its revenue streams to ensure sustainable growth and address the negative sentiment associated with its advertising-focused approach.</p>
<h2>Wang’s Argument in Favor of Microsoft, Tesla, and Nvidia</h2>
<p>Furthermore, Wang argues in favor of Microsoft. He established that Microsoft&#8217;s diversified portfolio and strategic positioning in critical areas such as the metaverse, cloud computing, and gaming places it among the industry&#8217;s most significant corporations.</p>
<p>While rounding up the grouping, Wang revealed that Tesla and Nvidia have emerged as major contenders deserving of inclusion in the elite group of technology powerhouses.</p>
<p>Notably, Tesla&#8217;s revolutionary advances in battery technology, autonomous driving capabilities, and network of Supercharger stations have set new industry norms. The company&#8217;s relentless pursuit of innovation has made electric vehicles increasingly accessible and desirable to a wider consumer base.</p>
<p>Similarly, Wang emphasizes that Nvidia&#8217;s impact extends far beyond its physical products. He reiterated that the company&#8217;s positioning as a leader at the edge of AI, the metaverse, and the future of computing places it at the forefront of transformative technologies.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/do-kwon-guilty-4-months-jail/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/analyst-faang-matana-stocks/">Analyst Suggests Replacing FAANG with MATANA in Hierarchy of Stocks</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/analyst-faang-matana-stocks/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Terraform Labs Founder Do Kwon Found Guilty of Document Forgery and Sentenced to 4 Months in Jail</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/do-kwon-guilty-4-months-jail/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/do-kwon-guilty-4-months-jail/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 17:01:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[do kwon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[terra]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[terra luna]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[terraform]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[terraform labs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=259430</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/do-kwon-guilty-4-months-jail/">Terraform Labs Founder Do Kwon Found Guilty of Document Forgery and Sentenced to 4 Months in Jail</a></p>
<p>A court in Montenegro has found Do Kwon guilty of document forgery and has sentenced him to jail. Kwon will remain in custody longer pending the country's response to an extradition request.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/do-kwon-guilty-4-months-jail/">Terraform Labs Founder Do Kwon Found Guilty of Document Forgery and Sentenced to 4 Months in Jail</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/do-kwon-guilty-4-months-jail/">Terraform Labs Founder Do Kwon Found Guilty of Document Forgery and Sentenced to 4 Months in Jail</a></p>
<p>CEO and co-founder of Terraform Labs Do Kwon has been found guilty of document forgery and sentenced to a four-month jail term. Kwon was convicted and sentenced by a Basic Court in Podgorica, the capital of Montenegro.</p>
<p>Authorities in Montenegro arrested Do Kwon back in March for carrying fake documents. Law enforcement arrested Kwon and Han Chang-Joon, another executive at Terraform Labs. They have both been in custody since their arrest.</p>
<p>Although the Podgorica High Court had approved bail for the executives, a local news outlet RFE <a href="https://www.slobodnaevropa.org/a/kralj-kriptovaluta-pritvor-crna-gora/32460870.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reported</a> that Kwon would remain in custody for six months. The period will see local courts deliberate on whether or not to allow an extradition request from South Korea to take effect. The Podgorica High Court <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/06/15/do-kwon-to-remain-in-custody-while-montenegro-courts-consider-extradition-request-report/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">confirmed</a> the news report to CoinDesk.</p>
<p>Like South Korea, the US has also requested an extradition. Both countries want Kwon to answer for the collapse of Terraform Labs, including the LUNA and UST cryptocurrencies.</p>
<h2>Bail Conditions Denied for Do Kwon Before Guilty Verdict</h2>
<p>Last month, a Basic Court in Podgorica agreed to a bail proposal initiated by Kwon’s attorneys to release the CEO and Chang-Joon. The lawyers proposed a supervised bail, with each person paying 400,000 euros (or $435,000) as the trial progresses. Following the approval, the plaintiff quickly appealed the decision to a High Court in Podgorica, which eventually ruled against the approval.</p>
<p>Notably, the court’s ruling specified that the four-month sentence will include the time the executives already spent in custody. The ruling also instructed authorities to confiscate two Belgian passports, two Costa Rican passports, and two ID cards owned by the two execs.</p>
<p>In September last year, South Korea began searching for Do Kwon and even asked Interpol to issue a “Red Notice” for Kwon. A Red Notice is a call to Interpol to immediately detain a person pending surrender, extradition, or other action. However, Do Kwon declared on Twitter in a <a href="https://twitter.com/stablekwon/status/1571197150863695872?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener">thread</a> that he was not guilty of anything and was not on the run. He also said there was no need for anyone to know his precise GPS coordinates, adding that he will defend himself against any accusations.</p>
<blockquote><p>“I am not ‘on the run’ or anything similar &#8211; for any government agency that has shown interest to communicate, we are in full cooperation and we don’t have anything to hide. We are in the process of defending ourselves in multiple jurisdictions &#8211; we have held ourselves to an extremely high bar of integrity, and look forward to clarifying the truth over the next few months.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Last May, the National Tax Agency of South Korea found Do Kwon and Terraform Labs guilty of tax evasion and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/do-kwon-terraform-tax-evasion/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">fined them $78 million</a>. According to the agency, Terraform and Do Kwon violated the South Korean Corporate Tax Act, which requires foreign companies to pay tax if managed domestically, regardless of the country of registration. The agency also alleges that before the Terraform crash, Kwon tried to liquidate the company and exit South Korea.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ethereum-developers-max-effective-balance/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/do-kwon-guilty-4-months-jail/">Terraform Labs Founder Do Kwon Found Guilty of Document Forgery and Sentenced to 4 Months in Jail</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/do-kwon-guilty-4-months-jail/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Developers Propose to Increase Max Effective Balance from 32 ETH to 2048 ETH per Validator</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ethereum-developers-max-effective-balance/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ethereum-developers-max-effective-balance/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 14:30:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=259416</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ethereum-developers-max-effective-balance/">Ethereum Developers Propose to Increase Max Effective Balance from 32 ETH to 2048 ETH per Validator</a></p>
<p>The developers led by Mike Neuder opine that a validator set contraction has positive implications for the beacon chain decentralization roadmap, the current p2p layer, and the validators. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ethereum-developers-max-effective-balance/">Ethereum Developers Propose to Increase Max Effective Balance from 32 ETH to 2048 ETH per Validator</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ethereum-developers-max-effective-balance/">Ethereum Developers Propose to Increase Max Effective Balance from 32 ETH to 2048 ETH per Validator</a></p>
<p>The Ethereum (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ETH</a>) network is best described as art in development amid mainstream crypto and blockchain adoption. With the proof-of-stake (PoS) still young under the beacon chain, the Ethereum core developers continually engage each other on ways to help in the decentralization aspect. Moreover, the Ethereum network accommodates global investors and also different countries with different sets of crypto regulatory policies. As a result, constant development to onboard new <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-decentralized-finance-defi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">DeFi</a> and users with different requirements has helped the network remain at the top of the smart contract industry.</p>
<h2>Closer Look at Ethereum Proposal to Increase MaxEB</h2>
<p>According to Ethereum proposals by top researchers and developers &#8211; including Mike Neuder, Francesco d’Amato, Aditya Asgaonkar, and Justin Drake &#8211; the current Max Effective Balance (MaxEB) is a limit to the Ethereum’s decentralization progress. Moreover, low MaxEB increases the set of validators without necessarily increasing the single nodes at hand. Essentially, solo Ethereum stakers became a validator by investing 32 ETH through the beacon chain, however, an investor can decide to delegate several thousands of ETH in a staking program, which adds the validators.</p>
<p>According to Ethereum&#8217;s on-chain data, there are about 600k validators with more than 90k in the activation queue. As a result, the Ethereum developers propose to increase the MaxEB without increasing the minimum amount required to become a validator.</p>
<p>“We argue that increasing the MaxEB (i) unblocks future consensus layer upgrades on the roadmap 4, (ii) improves the performance of the current consensus mechanism and p2p layer, and (iii) enhances operational efficiency for both small and large-scale validators,” the proposal <a href="https://ethresear.ch/t/increase-the-max-effective-balance-a-modest-proposal/15801" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">noted</a>.</p>
<p>According to an Ethereum validator on Twitter Vizsla (@AnotherVizsla), the immediate benefit of increasing MaxEB to solo stakers is the compounding of ETH rewards. As a result, Ethereum solo stakers can now compete with large entities like Lido (LDO), <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase Global Inc</a> (NASDAQ: COIN), and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/kraken/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Kraken</a> among others that operate liquids staking programs.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">For solo validators, the most immediate benefit of an increase in MAX_EFFECTIVE_BALANCE would be to allow instant compounding of ETH rewards by simply leaving them in the existing validator. Suddenly, solo stakers can compete with large operations. <a href="https://t.co/8K7nN43dDh">https://t.co/8K7nN43dDh</a></p>
<p>— Vizsla (@AnotherVizsla) <a href="https://twitter.com/AnotherVizsla/status/1666054695176257536?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 6, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Reportedly, the Ethereum researchers want the MaxEB to be capped at 2,048 ETH, which would drastically reduce the current number of validators. The details of the proposal are open for discussion before the validators are scheduled to vote on the way forward.</p>
<h2>Market Outlook</h2>
<p>The Ethereum network remains the undisputed leader in the decentralized financial ecosystem and smart contracts adoption. According to market aggregate data provided by Defillama, the Ethereum network has a total value locked (TVL) of about $24.7 billion with about 100 million non-zero addresses. Trading around $1,727 on Monday, Ethereum (ETH) had a total market capitalization of about $208 billion and a 24-hour trading volume of approximately $4 billion.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/buffett-berkshire-hathaway-japan/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ethereum-developers-max-effective-balance/">Ethereum Developers Propose to Increase Max Effective Balance from 32 ETH to 2048 ETH per Validator</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ethereum-developers-max-effective-balance/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway Increases Stake in Five Major Trading Firms in Japan</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/buffett-berkshire-hathaway-japan/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/buffett-berkshire-hathaway-japan/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 14:26:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investors News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[berkshire hathaway]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[byd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tesla]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[warren buffett]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=259360</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/buffett-berkshire-hathaway-japan/">Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway Increases Stake in Five Major Trading Firms in Japan</a></p>
<p>Warren Buffett has again increased its stakes in the 5 large trading firms in Japan where Berkshire Hathaway had a 7.4% stake.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/buffett-berkshire-hathaway-japan/">Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway Increases Stake in Five Major Trading Firms in Japan</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/buffett-berkshire-hathaway-japan/">Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway Increases Stake in Five Major Trading Firms in Japan</a></p>
<p>American multinational conglomerate holding company <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/berkshire-hathaway/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Berkshire Hathaway</a> (NYSE: BRK) has increased its stake in a few trading firms in Japan through a wholly-owned subsidiary, National Indemnity Company. The average stake in these firms is over 8.5%.</p>
<p>Berkshire Hathaway announced that National Indemnity Company now has more stakes in Mitsubishi, Marubeni, Sumitomo, Itochu, and Mitsui. According to the firm, the total value of its stake in these companies is higher than the total value of its stake in any other country but the US. The company also said it will hold these stocks for the long term.</p>
<p>Berkshire Hathaway invested in 5 of Japan’s largest trading companies. Also called “sogo-shosha”, these general trading companies are large Japanese companies dealing in a diverse range of products. Other major sogo-shosha companies include Toyota Tsusho, a member of the Toyota Group, and Sojitz Corporation.</p>
<p>In April, Berkshire Hathaway CEO Warren Buffett <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/04/12/warren-buffett-why-he-bought-5-japanese-trading-houses.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">told CNBC</a> he was “confounded” that buying into these companies was possible. Speaking to CNBC’s Becky Quick, Buffett said the earnings yield on these companies was “maybe 14%”. The earnings yield is a metric calculated by dividing profit per share by share price. A high earnings yield simply means that investors were making more per share.</p>
<h2>Why Berkshire Hathaway Bought Stakes in Japan&#8217;s Sogo Shosha</h2>
<p>Berkshire Hathaway first bought stakes in Japan&#8217;s Sogo Shosha in August 2020, spending around $6 billion on the purchase. In April, Buffett raised the stake to 7.4%. Explaining to Becky Quick, he said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“I just thought these were big companies. They were companies that I generally understood what they did. Somewhat similar to Berkshire in that they owned lots of different interests. And they were selling at what I thought was a ridiculous price, particularly the price compared to the interest rates prevailing at that time.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Investors generally criticize the sogo shosha for the unusual complexity of their operations, including exposure to overseas risks. However, Buffett seems unbothered by this and may be investing in these companies for this particular reason.</p>
<p>In its <a href="https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20230506005003/en/Berkshire-Hathaway-Inc.-First-Quarter-2023-Earnings-Release" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">earnings release</a> for Q1 2023, Berkshire Hathaway climbed nearly 13% year-on-year, mostly from its insurance business. The company’s net earnings per average equivalent Class A and Class B Shares both jumped by 544% between Q1 2022 and 2023.</p>
<p>Automobile insurance company Geico, a wholly-owned Berkshire Hathaway subsidiary, recorded $703 million in profit. However, Berkshire’s energy and railroad endeavors plunged. The first quarter of the year also saw Berkshire repurchasing $4.4 billion worth of stock, beating its previous $2.8 billion record.</p>
<p>Last year, Berkshire offloaded its shares in Chinese electric automaker <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/byd/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BYD</a> (HKG: 1211). The company dumped 1.33 million BYD shares worth $34.43 million at the time. For a long time, Berkshire was one of BODY’s largest shareholders, holding more than 220 million shares for over 14 years.</p>
<p>As of 2021, Berkshire Hathaway held 21% of BYD. However, the company began selling off its BYD stake and now owns <a href="https://markets.businessinsider.com/news/stocks/warren-buffett-elon-musk-berkshire-hathaway-sells-byd-stock-electric-2023-5#:~:text=Berkshire%20originally%20purchased%20its%20BYD,at%20its%20peak%20last%20year." target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">under 10%</a> of the automaker. Speaking at Bekrshire’s annual shareholder meeting, Buffet said he was unwilling to “compete with Elon”, referring to Elon Musk-led automaker <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/tesla/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tesla</a> (NASDAQ: TSLA).</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/wyre-closure-platform/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/buffett-berkshire-hathaway-japan/">Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway Increases Stake in Five Major Trading Firms in Japan</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/buffett-berkshire-hathaway-japan/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Wyre Announces Closure of Platform and Winding Down Next Month</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wyre-closure-platform/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wyre-closure-platform/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 14:15:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FinTech News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bolt Financial]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[wyre]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=259393</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/wyre-closure-platform/">Wyre Announces Closure of Platform and Winding Down Next Month</a></p>
<p>According to reports, problems began at Wyre when it set withdrawal limits for user accounts, claiming the community's best interests.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/wyre-closure-platform/">Wyre Announces Closure of Platform and Winding Down Next Month</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/wyre-closure-platform/">Wyre Announces Closure of Platform and Winding Down Next Month</a></p>
<p>Wyre, a prominent payments firm in the crypto industry, has recently planned toward the closure of its business as it plans to cease operations by the end of next month.</p>
<p>As highlighted in a <a href="https://twitter.com/sendwyre/status/1669688772844220418?s=20" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">tweet</a>, the company attributed this move to protecting the best interests of its key stakeholders and customers, citing market conditions as the primary motivator. Additionally, Wyre clarified that the closure was not influenced by any regulatory agency direction and reassured its users that their assets would continue to be securely managed.</p>
<h2>Wyre Advised Its Users on Closure Formalities</h2>
<p>Following the recent announcement of Wyre&#8217;s decision to wind down its operations, the company has provided instructions for users who have assets on the platform. Users are advised to withdraw their assets through Wyre&#8217;s dashboard by Friday, July 14th. For any remaining assets on the platform after this date, Wyre stated that it will implement a separate process for recovery.</p>
<p>Over the years, Wyre has established itself as a prominent service provider, catering to individuals, businesses, and developers in need of seamless digital asset transfers. With its user-friendly interface and robust infrastructure, Wyre emerged as a preferred choice for many users in the crypto space.</p>
<p>Notably, Wyre made headlines in April 2022 when it stated its intentions to be <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bolt-acquire-wyre-payments-1-5b/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">acquired</a> by Bolt Financial. The acquisition deal valued Wyre at an impressive $1.5 billion, marking it as one of the largest crypto deals to be announced at the time. The potential acquisition by Bolt was expected to provide synergistic benefits to both parties. Bolt, with its extensive network and expertise in digital commerce, sought to tap into the rapidly expanding crypto market.</p>
<p>However, Bolt <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bolt-crypto-firm-wyre/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">opted out</a> of the acquisition deal for unknown reasons. While specifics of the decision were not disclosed, Bolt stated that it intends to continue working with Wyre. The company indicated that remaining independent would allow it to focus on its core competencies, implying that the acquisition was no longer in line with its strategic goals.</p>
<h2>Signs of Troubles for Wyre</h2>
<p>According to <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/wyre-imposes-withdrawal-limit/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reports</a>, problems began at Wyre when it set withdrawal limits for user accounts, claiming the community&#8217;s best interests. At the time, the firm stated that withdrawals will be limited to no more than 90% of the funds in each customer&#8217;s account, subject to daily limits.</p>
<p>In addition, the company also disclosed alterations to its management structure. Stephen Cheng, a former Chief Risk and Compliance Officer, was chosen as the organization&#8217;s interim CEO.</p>
<p>The move signaled that Wyre was planning to close its doors. While Wyre declined these allegations, stating that it is not winding down, insights from two former employees of the firm suggest that the company may indeed be scaling back to strategize and plan its next steps.</p>
<p>Another indicator of more difficulties for the company is the removal of Wyre from MetaMask&#8217;s mobile aggregator, which lets users buy digital assets directly through its extension.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/britcoin-launch-project-rosalind-cbdc/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/wyre-closure-platform/">Wyre Announces Closure of Platform and Winding Down Next Month</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wyre-closure-platform/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Britcoin’s Launch Nears after Project Rosalind CBDC Study</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/britcoin-launch-project-rosalind-cbdc/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/britcoin-launch-project-rosalind-cbdc/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Temitope Olatunji]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 13:28:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bank of england]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[boe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[britcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=259368</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/britcoin-launch-project-rosalind-cbdc/">Britcoin&#8217;s Launch Nears after Project Rosalind CBDC Study</a></p>
<p>The Bank of England is progressing with its Britcoin digital currency project as it released results from the Rosalind project, which started in July 2022.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/britcoin-launch-project-rosalind-cbdc/">Britcoin&#8217;s Launch Nears after Project Rosalind CBDC Study</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/britcoin-launch-project-rosalind-cbdc/">Britcoin&#8217;s Launch Nears after Project Rosalind CBDC Study</a></p>
<p>As the idea of making cash more decentralized continues to grow in popularity, the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-central-bank-digital-currency-cbdc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CBDC</a> has also been an up-and-coming project in different countries. Britcoin, the name for the Bank of England (BoE) digital currency, is also closer to being launched.</p>
<p>The digital currency, which is to be backed by the British Pound, is aimed at sustaining the trust people have in money while protecting the country’s financial system from high-profile crashes and exposure to scams, which many volatile digital currencies have had to deal with.</p>
<p>CBDC has been the subject of the ongoing Project Rosalind, which is part of the move to test the best way an Application Programming Interface (API) could be implemented in CBDC for retail transactions. The study started in 2022 and is being controlled by the Bank for International Settlements (BIS) and the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/bank-of-england/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bank of England.</a></p>
<h2>Results from Project Rosalind CBDC Study</h2>
<p>According to a report published on June 16 by the BIS Innovation Hub, the study shows that using a good API can help achieve a broad range of use cases. The project saw the development of 33 API functionalities to test more than 30 CBDC use cases and how they work for online and offline payments using QR codes, mobile phones, digital cards, and carrying out micropayments.</p>
<p>Project Rosalind tried to explore the general benefits of a CBDC and how it could work, seeing that central banks are increasingly turning their attention to it. The results from the ongoing research show that CBDC could make payment easier, facilitate the creation of more financial products, and reduce the chances of financial fraud.</p>
<p>It was stated in <a href="https://www.bis.org/publ/othp69.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">the report</a> that &#8220;Project Rosalind demonstrated that a well-designed API layer can enable a central bank ledger to interact with private sector service providers to safely provide retail CBDC payments.&#8221;</p>
<p>Quant, a blockchain network, also announced that it is a part of the vendor team for Project Rosalind. The company also mentioned partnering with UST to carry out the project. While UST is working on the frontend Rosalind API layer, the Quant team makes the infrastructure and blockchain platform available to provide smart contracts and easy interoperability.</p>
<p>The company stated on <a href="https://quant.network/news/quant-collaborates-with-bis-and-the-bank-of-england-on-project-rosalind/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">its website</a> that:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We&#8217;re proud to announce our role as part of the vendor team for Project Rosalind. The project, led by the Bank for International Settlements and the Bank of England, explored how application programming interfaces could be used for central bank digital currency systems.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>CBDC &#8211; a Central Bank Response to Cryptocurrency Adoption</h2>
<p>As cryptocurrencies become more widespread, central banks could eventually lose control over how money is supplied, the general payment system, and even countries&#8217; economies at large. However, the creation of CBDC serves as the central banks&#8217; reaction to these moves, putting them in a better position to compete with or displace other cryptocurrencies for transactions within the country.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-hinman-documents-ethereum/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/britcoin-launch-project-rosalind-cbdc/">Britcoin&#8217;s Launch Nears after Project Rosalind CBDC Study</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/britcoin-launch-project-rosalind-cbdc/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>JPMorgan: Hinman Documents Could Boost Ethereum and Improve Decentralization </title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-hinman-documents-ethereum/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-hinman-documents-ethereum/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 13:13:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jpmorgan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[william hinman]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=259386</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-hinman-documents-ethereum/">JPMorgan: Hinman Documents Could Boost Ethereum and Improve Decentralization </a></p>
<p>In a report published June 15, JPMorgan's analyst Nikolaos Panigirtzoglou said that SEC officials were unsure of Ethereum's legal status in 2018.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-hinman-documents-ethereum/">JPMorgan: Hinman Documents Could Boost Ethereum and Improve Decentralization </a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-hinman-documents-ethereum/">JPMorgan: Hinman Documents Could Boost Ethereum and Improve Decentralization </a></p>
<p>Leading American financial services company <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/jpmorgan-chase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">JPMorgan</a> has highlighted the significant impact of the release of the Hinman documents on Ethereum in an ongoing court case between the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) and blockchain firm <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ripple-labs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ripple Labs</a>.</p>
<p>According to <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/06/19/hinman-documents-release-in-sec-ripple-case-is-a-boost-to-ether-jpmorgan/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reports</a>, Hinman&#8217;s documents, which include emails tied to former SEC Director William Hinman&#8217;s 2018 speech regarding Ethereum (ETH) regulatory status, can potentially boost the second-largest crypto asset and ignite a movement towards greater decentralization in the space.</p>
<p>In the speech, the former SEC director of the Division of Corporation Finance unit said ether is not considered a <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-director-hinman-ripple/">security</a> in the eyes of the financial regulator. This contrasts the SEC&#8217;s position on XRP, which it has classified as a security.</p>
<p>The SEC&#8217;s lawsuit against Ripple alleges that the company sold <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/xrp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">XRP</a> as an unregistered security. Last week, the blockchain-based company made Hinman&#8217;s emails public as part of its defense against the SEC&#8217;s civil suit shedding light on a crucial aspect of its argument with the Commission.</p>
<h2>SEC Unsure of Ether Legal Status</h2>
<p>In a report published June 15, JPMorgan&#8217;s analyst Nikolaos Panigirtzoglou said that SEC officials were unsure of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a>&#8216;s legal status in 2018. The report notes that the Hinman documents acknowledged the existence of an &#8220;other category&#8221; where certain assets, like ether, do not fit the traditional definition of securities.</p>
<p>While there may be a need for regulation to protect consumer&#8217;s interest, the crypto asset is not deemed a security due to its lack of a controlling group as defined by the Howey Test &#8211; a legal criterion used to determine if an investment qualifies as a security, according to the report.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the documents are expected to influence the ongoing US congressional efforts to provide a clear regulatory framework to govern the crypto industry.</p>
<p>&#8220;The Hinman documents are likely to influence the direction of the current US congressional effort to regulate the crypto industry in a way that ether would avoid being designated as a security,&#8221; said Panigirtzoglou.</p>
<h2>JPMorgan Proposed to Regulate Ethereum as Commodities</h2>
<p>JPMorgan proposed in its research to place ether in the same category as Bitcoin (BTC) and regulate it as a commodity under the oversight of the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/cftc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CFTC</a>).  Last year, two US senators, Sens. Cynthia M. Lummis, and Kirsten Gillibrand, signed a bill that gave the CFTC authority to regulate cryptocurrencies that fall under the commodities category.</p>
<p>According to the report, this approach would establish a new &#8220;other category&#8221; tailored explicitly to decentralized cryptocurrencies like ether that manage to fall outside the SEC&#8217;s jurisdiction.</p>
<p>Additionally, the report stated that the level of decentralization of a crypto could determine whether it is designated as security.</p>
<p>&#8220;A new &#8220;other category&#8221; could be introduced specifically to ether and other cryptocurrencies that are decentralized enough to avoid being classed as securities. The more decentralized a cryptocurrency is, the higher its chance that it would avoid being designated as a security,&#8221; the bank said.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-withdraws-request-fca-uk/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-hinman-documents-ethereum/">JPMorgan: Hinman Documents Could Boost Ethereum and Improve Decentralization </a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-hinman-documents-ethereum/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Withdraws Request for FCA Registration in UK</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-withdraws-request-fca-uk/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-withdraws-request-fca-uk/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 11:45:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Binance News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fca]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=259351</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-withdraws-request-fca-uk/">Binance Withdraws Request for FCA Registration in UK</a></p>
<p>Binance has been considering expanding its business to the UK and other regions due to the crackdown on crypto exchanges in the US. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-withdraws-request-fca-uk/">Binance Withdraws Request for FCA Registration in UK</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-withdraws-request-fca-uk/">Binance Withdraws Request for FCA Registration in UK</a></p>
<p>Following its lawsuit with the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>), the global leading digital asset service provider Binance has <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/cryptocurrency/binance-markets-limited-deregisters-with-the-uks-fca/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">withdrawn</a> its registration of Binance Markets Limited (BML) with the Financial Conduct Authority (FCA). Markedly, BML is the United Kingdom subsidiary of the global crypto exchange. With these latest developments, Binance and its associates hold no operational license or approval in the UK.</p>
<p>BML submitted a cancellation request for the FCA approval which was completed almost three weeks ago. The FCA confirmed that &#8220;Following the completion of the cancellation of permissions, the firm is no longer authorized by the FCA. No other entity in the Binance Group holds any form of UK authorization or registration to conduct regulated business in the UK.&#8221;</p>
<p>Noteworthy, BML was <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-financial-regulator-binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">banned</a> by FCA in June 2021 from transacting any business in the UK region. The ban came with several instructions including removing any promotions and financial adverts related to cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>Binance was also required to reveal to its clients on its website and its social media platform that it had no ties with businesses in the UK. Consequently, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/barcays/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Barclays PLC</a> (LSE: BARC) announced plans to <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/barclays-blocks-payments-binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">block</a> the use of debit and credit cards when making any form of payment to the renowned exchange.</p>
<p>Also, the ban coincided with numerous crackdowns on Binance from Canada, Japan and Thailand. British investment banking giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/hsbc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">HSBC Holdings plc</a> (LON: HSBA) also <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-uk-crackdown-hsbc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">stopped</a> its UK clients from making payments to Binance on the premise that it is passionate about investor protection.</p>
<h2>FCA Registration Cancelation: Binance UK Was Never in Business</h2>
<p>Now that it has withdrawn its registration with the UK regulator, Binance&#8217;s Sub-Regional Manager for Growth in the UK and Europe, Ilir Laro, claimed that the cancelation did not have any operational impact on the company as they were never in business.</p>
<p>He explained further that since BML was acquired in 2020 by Binance Group, it has remained dormant. According to Laro, there was an attempt made earlier to launch a regulated business in the UK but this proved abortive.</p>
<p>To put it in perspective, the manager emphasized:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;To clarify, BML has never conducted any type of regulated business in the UK. In keeping with the FCA&#8217;s firm&#8217;s guidance on canceling unused FCA permissions, BML is now no longer authorized by the FCA.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Push for Alternative Location by US Crypto Firms</h2>
<p>Unfortunately, Binance has been considering expanding its business to the UK and other regions due to the crackdown on crypto exchanges in the US.</p>
<p>The SEC <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-binance-matic-sol-lawsuit/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">sued</a> Binance on Monday, 5th June for several charges including operating unregistered companies, flouting Know-Your-Customers (KYC) rules, misleading investors and mishandling customers&#8217; funds.</p>
<p>American cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase also <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-sec-coinbase-unregistered-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">faced</a> enforcement action for operating as an unregistered national securities exchange and broker, a move that has forced the firm to be reconsidering other regions.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fidelity-investments-big-crypto-move/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-withdraws-request-fca-uk/">Binance Withdraws Request for FCA Registration in UK</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-withdraws-request-fca-uk/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rumor: Fidelity Investments Preps to Make Big Crypto Move, Here’s What to Expect</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fidelity-investments-big-crypto-move/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fidelity-investments-big-crypto-move/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 11:43:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funds & ETFs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fidelity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fidelity investments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gary gensler]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=259344</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fidelity-investments-big-crypto-move/">Rumor: Fidelity Investments Preps to Make Big Crypto Move, Here&#8217;s What to Expect</a></p>
<p>The traditional firm could dominate the US digital asset space for a long time to come.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fidelity-investments-big-crypto-move/">Rumor: Fidelity Investments Preps to Make Big Crypto Move, Here&#8217;s What to Expect</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fidelity-investments-big-crypto-move/">Rumor: Fidelity Investments Preps to Make Big Crypto Move, Here&#8217;s What to Expect</a></p>
<p>Asset management firm Fidelity Investments is reportedly planning a major move that can potentially shake the cores of the crypto markets. According to WhaleChart, the firm has two major moves lined up and would be hoping to achieve one or both of them soon. The Monday morning <a href="https://twitter.com/WhaleChart/status/1670676003931168770?t=9ET7sIPn5zqRRKPKqoZ8IA&amp;s=19" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announcement</a> reads:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Fidelity Investments is preparing to apply for a Bitcoin ETF and submit an offer to acquire Grayscale.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Fidelity Investments Keen About US Digital Assets Market Dominance</h2>
<p>Fidelity, the world’s third-largest asset manager, has always shown itself to be enthusiastic about crypto. While it has been mining Bitcoin since 2014, it launched a crypto-focused arm – Fidelity Digital Assets (FDA) – in 2018, before expanding to Europe in 2020.</p>
<p>Since launching the FDA, Fidelity has introduced various offerings and initiatives to promote investing in digital assets. However, it appears that the ultimate goal might be market dominance. Especially in light of recent events, reports that Fidelity may be considering acquiring Grayscale or applying for a Bitcoin spot ETF could not have emerged at a better time.</p>
<p>Recall, that the world&#8217;s largest asset manager <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/blackrock/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BlackRock</a> also recently applied for a <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> spot ETF. That was on June 15. If both firms are successful in their quest, they could both dominate the US digital asset space for a long time to come.</p>
<h2>Better Times Ahead</h2>
<p>For what it&#8217;s worth, the United State Securities and Exchange Commission has declined several applications for a Bitcoin ETF in the past. Even Fidelity had its initial proposal declined in January 2022. But the disapprovals have mostly bordered on the SEC&#8217;s fear of potential market manipulation.</p>
<p>Fidelity, however, being a reputable traditional firm, whose proposal reportedly relies on pricing the Bitcoin from a variety of spot markets, might cause the SEC to have a change of heart. More so, there&#8217;s a possibility that Fidelity Investments is applying, albeit strategically now that lawmakers are <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-lawmakers-bill-sec-gary-gensler/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">calling for the removal of SEC Chair</a> Gary Gensler.</p>
<p>Without a doubt, getting a Bitcoin ETF approval would be a huge win not just for Fidelity but for every single Bitcoin holder. First and foremost, the approval would add more legitimacy to the flagship cryptocurrency. But more importantly, it would also lead to a massive influx of new investment from retail and institutional clients alike. In the long run, the price of Bitcoin is expected to surge massively.</p>
<p>Nonetheless, the question on everyone&#8217;s mind at the moment is whether traditional companies are gradually taking over crypto.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/goldman-sachs-growth-outlook-china/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fidelity-investments-big-crypto-move/">Rumor: Fidelity Investments Preps to Make Big Crypto Move, Here&#8217;s What to Expect</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fidelity-investments-big-crypto-move/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Goldman Sachs Cuts Growth Outlook on China Following Similar Reductions from Major Wall Street Banks</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/goldman-sachs-growth-outlook-china/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/goldman-sachs-growth-outlook-china/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 11:21:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Currencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wall Street]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[goldman sachs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=259334</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/goldman-sachs-growth-outlook-china/">Goldman Sachs Cuts Growth Outlook on China Following Similar Reductions from Major Wall Street Banks</a></p>
<p>Several Wall Street Banks, including Goldman Sachs, have cut their outlook on growth in China as the economy struggles.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/goldman-sachs-growth-outlook-china/">Goldman Sachs Cuts Growth Outlook on China Following Similar Reductions from Major Wall Street Banks</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/goldman-sachs-growth-outlook-china/">Goldman Sachs Cuts Growth Outlook on China Following Similar Reductions from Major Wall Street Banks</a></p>
<p>Leading global investment banking and management firm <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/goldman-sachs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Goldman Sachs</a> has joined several Wall Street banks to reduce its growth outlook for China. This downgrade comes as the East Asian powerhouse is experiencing a dwindling economy as it battles the effects of the coronavirus pandemic.</p>
<p>Goldman Sachs reduced the growth outlook for China’s full-year 2023 GDP (gross domestic product) to 5.4% from 6%, and that of 2024 to 4.5% from 4.6%. Led by Chief China Economist Hui Shan, the Goldman economists said in a Sunday research note:</p>
<blockquote><p>“With continued challenges from the property market, pervasive pessimism among consumers and private entrepreneurs, and only moderate policy easing to partially offset the strong growth headwinds, we mark down our 2023 real GDP forecast.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Goldman Sachs joins several other institutions that cut their growth outlook for China. Bank of America cut its outlook from 6.3% to 5.7%, with JPMorgan also dropping its forecast to 5.5% from 5.9%. Others include Standard Chartered’s 5.4% from 5.8%, and UBS from 5.7% to 5.2%. Nomura was the lowest at 5.1%, cutting down from 5.5%.</p>
<p>According to the economists from Goldman Sachs, multiple issues continue to plague China’s growth outlook. China reopened its economy following lockdowns introduced to control the spread of coronavirus. The Chinese foreign ministry also recently announced that all types of foreign visas will now be available again. China had reopened borders in January but restricted visits to business and family purposes. However, analysts have now noted that the “reopening boost [is] quickly fading”.</p>
<h2>More Challenges Facing China&#8217;s Growth Outlook</h2>
<p>Goldman Sachs also highlighted several “medium-term challenges”, including debt problems plaguing local governments, demographics, and a property downturn. In addition, the economists highlighted geopolitical tensions as one of the factors negatively affecting China’s growth outlook.</p>
<p>The Chinese government put its GDP growth for the year at 5%. Officials likely limited their outlook after missing the forecast set last year. Judging by this, the current growth outlooks set by these Wall Street institutions seem relatively at par with Beijing’s figure. Nonetheless, Wall Street is not optimistic.</p>
<p>For instance, China’s recent <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/06/14/china-is-seen-to-be-kicking-off-a-new-cycle-of-rate-cuts.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reduction in its repurchase rate points</a> to more easing. The economists say this will cause rate differentials that eventually weaken the Yuan against the Dollar.</p>
<p>UBS also has a weak outlook. According to the bank’s Chief China Economist Wang Tao:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Q2 sequential growth may slow to only 1-2% quarter-on-quarter saar [seasonally adjusted annual rate], weaker than our earlier expectation of 4.5%.”</p></blockquote>
<p>The economist also pointed to problems with China’s property sector, specifying that the problems are strong enough to dampen the growth outlook.</p>
<p>In February, Goldman Sachs analysts had more faith in the Chinese economy. These analysts had <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/goldman-sachs-china-stocks-growth/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">projected</a> that stocks in China could rise up to 24% before 2023 runs out. According to Chief China equity strategist Kinger Lau, the stock market will begin to recover after the country’s reopening phase.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/1-million-crypto-investigator-zachxbt/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/goldman-sachs-growth-outlook-china/">Goldman Sachs Cuts Growth Outlook on China Following Similar Reductions from Major Wall Street Banks</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/goldman-sachs-growth-outlook-china/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4178 metric#misses=41 metric#hit-ratio=99.0 metric#bytes=1042014 metric#prefetches=204 metric#store-reads=19 metric#store-writes=2 metric#store-hits=210 metric#store-misses=2 metric#sql-queries=34 metric#ms-total=90.28 metric#ms-cache=5.64 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.2822 metric#ms-cache-ratio=6.3 -->