<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 13:37:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Justin Sun addresses Huobi&#8217;s insolvency concerns, calls it a FUD</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/justin-sun-addresses-huobis-insolvency-concerns-calls-it-a-fud/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 13:34:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Huobi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Huobi-token News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/justin-sun-addresses-huobis-insolvency-concerns-calls-it-a-fud/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Huobi saw a record $64 million in outflows over the weekend. The Outflows followed reports that the exchange&#8217;s executives had been arrested in China. An Angel investor has also pointed to inconsistencies in Huobi&#8217;s reserves. Huobi customers withdrew $64 million over the weekend due to worries about the cryptocurrency exchange company going bankrupt and rumours [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/justin-sun-addresses-huobis-insolvency-concerns-calls-it-a-fud/">Justin Sun addresses Huobi&#8217;s insolvency concerns, calls it a FUD</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Huobi saw a record $64 million in outflows over the weekend.</li>
<li>The Outflows followed reports that the exchange&rsquo;s executives had been arrested in China.</li>
<li>An Angel investor has also pointed to inconsistencies in Huobi&rsquo;s reserves.</li>
</ul>
<p>Huobi customers withdrew $64 million over the weekend due to worries about the cryptocurrency exchange company going bankrupt and rumours that Chinese authorities were looking into their management.</p>
<p>All these started on August 4 after Chinese authorities allegedly detained Huobi&rsquo;s top executives. It was reported that the arrests were the result of an investigation into the exchange&rsquo;s ties to betting websites.</p>
<h2>Huobi woes</h2>
<p>The rules governing cryptocurrency trading platforms appear to be getting stricter in China. Also, uncertainty exists regarding whether the recent resignation of one of the exchange&rsquo;s senior executives was related to the ongoing investigations in China.</p>
<p>However, Huobi&rsquo;s social media manager refuted the allegations and stated that the exchange is &ldquo;currently doing well.&rdquo;</p>
<p>But according to angel investor and fintech executive Adam Cochran, Huobi is allegedly having financial issues. Adam Cochran has specifically pointed to some inconsistencies in the exchange&rsquo;s <a href="https://coinjournal.net/tether/what-is-tether/">Tether (USDT)</a> balances.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">11/16</p>
<p>So users *think* they have balances of $631M in Huobi, but there is only $90M there.</p>
<p>The rest Justin Sun is using to prop up his other defi apps, and paying a yield on it to get users to deposit more into Huobi.</p>
<p>&mdash; Adam Cochran (adamscochran.eth) (@adamscochran) <a href="https://twitter.com/adamscochran/status/1687959127048298496?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 5, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>According to Cochran, Huobi&rsquo;s most recent &ldquo;Merkle Tree Audit&rdquo; claims that they hold $630 million in USDT, but on-chain data revealed that as of August 5, they had less than $90 million in assets, which according to the investor suggests that Huobi might not be able to pay its debts.</p>
<h2>Justin Sun&rsquo;s response</h2>
<p>Justin Sun, the CEO of the Huobi Exchange, responded to the circulating allegations of the crypto exchange being about to fail and called it a FUD.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">The past two days have seen people getting concerned due to the spreading FUD. </p>
<p>We want to take a second to respond in the open, with absolute sincerity and clarity:<a href="https://t.co/t4tf1uiE9q">https://t.co/t4tf1uiE9q</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Huobi (@HuobiGlobal) <a href="https://twitter.com/HuobiGlobal/status/1688459973141966848?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 7, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script> </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/justin-sun-addresses-huobis-insolvency-concerns-calls-it-a-fud/">Justin Sun addresses Huobi&#8217;s insolvency concerns, calls it a FUD</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase to buy back up to $150M of its $1B bonds</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-to-buy-back-up-to-150m-of-its-1b-bonds/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-to-buy-back-up-to-150m-of-its-1b-bonds/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 12:49:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-to-buy-back-up-to-150m-of-its-1b-bonds/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Coinbase&#8217;s partial bonds buyback targets up to $150 million of the $1 billion bonds. City Global Managers will be the offer&#8217;s dealer manager. Coinbase said on Monday that it is commencing a partial repurchase of its $1 billion bonds. Per the company, whose Q2, 2023 financial report came in stronger than forecast, the plan is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-to-buy-back-up-to-150m-of-its-1b-bonds/">Coinbase to buy back up to $150M of its $1B bonds</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Coinbase&rsquo;s partial bonds buyback targets up to $150 million of the $1 billion bonds.</li>
<li dir="ltr">City Global Managers will be the offer&rsquo;s dealer manager.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/coinbase/">Coinbase</a> said on Monday that it is commencing a partial repurchase of its $1 billion bonds.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Per the company, whose Q2, 2023 financial report came in stronger than forecast, the plan is to buy back up to $150 million of the 3.265% bonds. The bonds are set to mature in 2031.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Offer expires on September 1</h2>
<p dir="ltr">A <a href="https://investor.coinbase.com/news/news-details/2023/Coinbase-Commences-Cash-Tender-Offer-for-Up-to-150.0-Million-Aggregate-Purchase-Price-of-its-Outstanding-3.625-Senior-Notes-Due-2031/default.aspx" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">press release</a> from Coinbase indicated that investors who tender their Notes for the purchase program before August 18 will be eligible for an early buy offer that includes a $30 premium. This group of holders will receive $645 per $1,000 of the bond&rsquo;s principal amount, translating to 64.5 cents on each dollar.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Meanwhile, participants who validly offer to sell their bonds after August 18 but before the offer&rsquo;s expiry date of September 1 will get $615 per $1000 of the bond&rsquo;s principal value. In any case, both sets of participants will see a premium return on unaffected, preannouncement bond price of 60 cents per dollars&rsquo; worth.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Coinbase reported $708 million in revenue for the second quarter, beating analyst estimates of $628 million by more than 13%. Adjusted earnings per share loss came in at $0.42, compared to forecasts of $0.76.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Citigroup Global Markets will be the buyback program&rsquo;s Dealer Manager.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-to-buy-back-up-to-150m-of-its-1b-bonds/">Coinbase to buy back up to $150M of its $1B bonds</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-to-buy-back-up-to-150m-of-its-1b-bonds/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why is Hedera (HBAR) trending?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/why-is-hedera-hbar-trending/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/why-is-hedera-hbar-trending/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 12:43:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/why-is-hedera-hbar-trending/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Hedera (HBAR) token price has increased by 16% over the past week. Hedera (HBAR) recently announced a strategic partnership with FreshSupplyCoAu to integrate with the Continuity API. The integration allows Hedera users to access Mastercard Payment Gateway Services (MPGS). The Hedera (HBAR) has been trending within the crypto circles for its consistent price rally [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/why-is-hedera-hbar-trending/">Why is Hedera (HBAR) trending?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>The Hedera (HBAR) token price has increased by 16% over the past week.</li>
<li>Hedera (HBAR) recently announced a strategic partnership with FreshSupplyCoAu to integrate with the Continuity API.</li>
<li>The integration allows Hedera users to access Mastercard Payment Gateway Services (MPGS).</li>
</ul>
<p>The Hedera (HBAR) has been trending within the crypto circles for its consistent price rally since mid-July.</p>
<p>The <a href="https://coinjournal.net/hedera/">HBAR token price</a> has reclaimed its July Highs after a short pullback between July 20 and July 25.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/07/08/1691498039633-1638acc9-b59d-4645-b410-5ad71f0cb3aa.jpg" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="615" height="398"></p>
<h2>Here&rsquo;s why the HBAR price is rising</h2>
<p>The current Hedera (HBAR) price surge is largely pegged on the recent strategic partnership between Hedera and FreshSupplyCoAu to integrate with the Continuity API and enable seamless connections to banks and the Mastercard Network.</p>
<p>According to a tweet from the HBAR Foundation, FreshSupplyCoAu, a pioneer in the field of digital innovation, will see significant improvements by seamlessly integrating Hedera into its Continuity API. By integrating with the Mastercard Network, this dynamic fusion extends the reach of the Hedera network by connecting it to the traditional banking system.</p>
<p>Users can now access Mastercard Payment Gateway Services (MPGS) and other upcoming Hedera Foundation projects, including their cutting-edge Web3 and digital asset solutions, thanks to the integration. The move represents a strategic step towards enhancing the usability and interoperability of Hedera rather than merely a development in technology.</p>
<p>The initiative from FreshSupplyCoAu is ready to create new opportunities for efficiency, accessibility, and value for both individual users and businesses.</p>
<p>The FreshSupplyCoAu integration is just the tip of the iceberg. The vision of the Hedera Hashgraph blockchain includes more collaborations and innovations to continually bridge the gap between decentralized finance and traditional finance. The blockchain was recently <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/hyundai-and-kia-tap-hedera-network-for-co2-emission-monitoring-system/">tapped by Kia and Hyundai automakers</a> for an AI-powered CO2 emission monitoring system</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/why-is-hedera-hbar-trending/">Why is Hedera (HBAR) trending?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/why-is-hedera-hbar-trending/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Litecoin price forecast: Brace for more weakness</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/litecoin-price-forecast-brace-for-more-weakness/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/litecoin-price-forecast-brace-for-more-weakness/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 12:17:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/litecoin-price-forecast-brace-for-more-weakness/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Litecoin price has slumped in the past few weeks as it ignored key events. It went through its third halving that reduced its block rewards last week. Litecoin price has underperformed the market as the hype surrounding the halving event waned. LTC price dropped to a low of $80, the lowest level since June 21st. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/litecoin-price-forecast-brace-for-more-weakness/">Litecoin price forecast: Brace for more weakness</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Litecoin price has slumped in the past few weeks as it ignored key events.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">It went through its third halving that reduced its block rewards last week.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/litecoin"><u>Litecoin</u></a> price has underperformed the market as the hype surrounding the halving event waned. LTC price dropped to a low of $80, the lowest level since June 21st. It has dropped by more than 28% from the highest point this year.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Litecoin&rsquo;s price action is a reflection of the overall performance of the crypto industry. Bitcoin, its biggest peer, has remained at the $29,000 level in the past few weeks. Similarly, the total market cap of all cryptocurrencies has remained at $1.12 trillion.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Litecoin price has ignored several important events in the ecosystem. Last week, it went&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/litecoin-completes-third-halving-block-reward-cut-to-6-25-ltc/"><u>through halving</u></a>, a process that reduces the block rewards to miners in its ecosystem. Historically, Litecoin and other cryptocurrencies tend to show some volatility before and after a halving event.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Further, it reacted mildly to last week&rsquo;s credit rating downgrade of America&rsquo;s debt by Fitch, one of the big three credit rating agencies. In an ideal situation, the credit rating downgrade should have been a good for Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies because they are designed to be anti-US dollar.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Meanwhile, on-chain metrics shows that the number of Litecoin transactions has been a bit muted in the past few months. On a positive side, the hash rate has remained at an all-time high of 800 TH/s.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Hash rate is an important metric that looks at the computational power of a network. In most cases, a strong hash rate means that the network is healthier.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Litecoin price prediction</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/07/08/1691497014108-ea4e44db-50d2-4b7a-a236-036019a7ec54.png" style="width: 668px;height: 325.093px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="668" height="325.093"></p>
<p dir="ltr">The future price action of Litecoin price will depend on the performance of Bitcoin since the two have a close correlation. On the daily chart, the LTC price has dropped below the important resistance level at $105.75, the highest point in February.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Most importantly, Litecoin has formed what looks like a head and shoulders pattern, which is usually a bearish sign. It has also dropped below the 50-day and 200-day moving averages. The two averages are about to make a bearish crossover, which is known as a death cross.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The coin has also formed a bearish flag pattern. Therefore, the outlook for Litecoin price is bearish, with the next level to watch being at $71.20.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy Litecoin</h2>
<p dir="ltr">
        </p><div class="relative">

            <div class="mb-3  pb-6  px-6  bg-slate-50  rounded-xl  ps-shadow-inner">

    <h3 class="inline-block">
        eToro    </h3>

            <p class="text-sm">eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>
    
    <div class="w-full  flex  flex-wrap  items-start  flex-col  gap-2">

        
<a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=MTQ4OTU0&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="nofollow sponsored noopener" target="_self" class="inline-block  text-indigo-600  underline  hover:text-indigo-200  ease-in-out  duration-300  transition-all" title="Buy LTC with eToro today">Buy LTC with eToro today</a>

    </div>

</div><div class="  pb-6  px-6  bg-slate-50  rounded-xl  ps-shadow-inner">

    <h3 class="inline-block">
        Public    </h3>

            <p class="text-sm">Public is an investing platform that allows you to invest stocks, ETFs, crypto, and alternative assets like fine art and collectibles&mdash;all in one place.</p>
    
    <div class="w-full  flex  flex-wrap  items-start  flex-col  gap-2">

        
<a href="/visit/public-crypto?guid=MTQ4OTU0&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="nofollow sponsored noopener" target="_self" class="inline-block  text-indigo-600  underline  hover:text-indigo-200  ease-in-out  duration-300  transition-all" title="Buy LTC with Public today">Buy LTC with Public today</a>

    </div>

</div>
        </div>



<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/litecoin-price-forecast-brace-for-more-weakness/">Litecoin price forecast: Brace for more weakness</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/litecoin-price-forecast-brace-for-more-weakness/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Concerning revelation: PayPal&#8217;s stablecoin can wipe out account balances</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/concerning-revelation-paypals-stablecoin-can-wipe-out-account-balances/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/concerning-revelation-paypals-stablecoin-can-wipe-out-account-balances/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 11:54:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto payments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/concerning-revelation-paypals-stablecoin-can-wipe-out-account-balances/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>PayPal launched its stablecoin on the Ethereum blockchain. Huobi has already announced it will launch the new stablecoin. The PYUSD has an &#8220;assetProtection&#8221; role that can wipe your balance in two transactions (first `freeze`, then `wipeFrozenAddress`). The recently launched Paypal stablecoin, the Paypal USD (PYUSD), has been reviewed by Pashov, an expert in smart contracts [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/concerning-revelation-paypals-stablecoin-can-wipe-out-account-balances/">Concerning revelation: PayPal&#8217;s stablecoin can wipe out account balances</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>PayPal launched its stablecoin on the Ethereum blockchain.</li>
<li>Huobi has already announced it will launch the new stablecoin.</li>
<li>The PYUSD has an &ldquo;assetProtection&rdquo; role that can wipe your balance in two transactions (first `freeze`, then `wipeFrozenAddress`).</li>
</ul>
<p>The recently <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/paypal-launches-a-us-dollar-stablecoin-on-the-ethereum-blockchain/">launched Paypal stablecoin</a>, the Paypal USD (PYUSD), has been reviewed by Pashov, an expert in smart contracts security reviews. The PYUSD was announced on August 7 and a brief review has shown some unsettling revelations as posted by Pashov on X platform on the same day that the stablecoin was launched.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">The new Paypal USD stablecoin has an "assetProtection" role which can wipe your balance in two transactions (first `freeze`, then `wipeFrozenAddress`)</p>
<p>In smart contract security we call this a "centralisation attack vector" <a href="https://t.co/RsmqvsnKvi">pic.twitter.com/RsmqvsnKvi</a></p>
<p>&mdash; pashov (@pashovkrum) <a href="https://twitter.com/pashovkrum/status/1688591468498239496?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 7, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>According to Pashov, selected development team members at PayPal will be able to execute delicate code functionalities like freezing accounts and cleaning frozen account balances using the &ldquo;assetProtection&rdquo; role.</p>
<h2>USDT and USDC have similar attack vectors</h2>
<p>While a majority of crypto enthusiasts expected PayPal&rsquo;s stablecoin to stand out, Pashov&rsquo;s revelation revealed that the new Paypal USD stablecoin is no different to USDT and USDC in terms of security.</p>
<p>The PayPal USD (PYUSD), the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/tether/what-is-tether/">Tether (USDT)</a>, and the USD Coin ( USDC), all have &ldquo;assetProtection&rdquo; role, which in smart contract security is referred to as a &lsquo;centralization attack vector.&rsquo;&rdquo;</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Newsflash: USDT &amp; USDC both have similar attack vectors as well. I thought this one might be different, but it's really isn't.</p>
<p>&mdash; pashov (@pashovkrum) <a href="https://twitter.com/pashovkrum/status/1688615907323428865?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 7, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The feature makes PayPal stablecoin a centralized stablecoin just like a majority of other popular stablecoins.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/concerning-revelation-paypals-stablecoin-can-wipe-out-account-balances/">Concerning revelation: PayPal&#8217;s stablecoin can wipe out account balances</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/concerning-revelation-paypals-stablecoin-can-wipe-out-account-balances/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Huobi to list PayPal’s PYUSD stablecoin</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/huobi-to-list-paypals-pyusd-stablecoin/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/huobi-to-list-paypals-pyusd-stablecoin/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 11:51:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Huobi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/huobi-to-list-paypals-pyusd-stablecoin/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Huobi plans to list PayPal USD (PYUSD), the stablecoin launched by PayPal.&#160; Trading for PYUSD/USDT will open when liquidity conditions are met. Crypto exchange Huobi has announced it will list PayPal USD (PYUSD), a newly launched stablecoin from PayPal. Accordingly, Huobi will open trading for the PYUSD/USDT pair, offering permanent zero fees. Huobi to open [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/huobi-to-list-paypals-pyusd-stablecoin/">Huobi to list PayPal’s PYUSD stablecoin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Huobi plans to list PayPal USD (PYUSD), the stablecoin launched by PayPal.&nbsp;</li>
<li>Trading for PYUSD/USDT will open when liquidity conditions are met.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Crypto exchange <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/huobi/">Huobi</a> has <a href="https://www.huobi.com/support/en-us/detail/44945804382445" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">announced</a> it will list PayPal USD (PYUSD), a newly launched stablecoin from PayPal. Accordingly, Huobi will open trading for the PYUSD/USDT pair, offering permanent zero fees.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Huobi to open trading for PYUSD/USDT</h2>
<p dir="ltr">PayPal&rsquo;s stablecoin is pegged on the US dollar and is targeted for transfers and payments. Paxos Trust Company will issue the token, which is 100% backed by USD deposits, short-term US Treasury bonds, and cash equivalents. &nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>When the market circulation and liquidity conditions are ripe, Huobi will open trading at the first time</em>,&rdquo; the exchange said in a notice to customers.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The announcement comes just a day after PayPal <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/paypal-launches-a-us-dollar-stablecoin-on-the-ethereum-blockchain/">unveiled</a> its stablecoin on Ethereum. Tron founder Justin Sun posted on X (formerly Twitter) that PayPal would be welcome to issue PYUSD on the TRON network.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>I cordially invite PayPal to consider issuing PYUSD on #TRON, which is Fast, secure, and cost-effective with 12 billion USD daily transactions. Mutual benefits await in the digital payment landscape. Let&rsquo;s collaborate for a thriving ecosystem</em>,&rdquo; Sun wrote.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">I cordially invite PayPal to consider issuing PYUSD on <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/TRON?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#TRON</a>, which is Fast, secure, and cost-effective with 12 billion USD daily transactions. Mutual benefits await in the digital payment landscape. Let's collaborate for a thriving ecosystem! &#128591;</p>
<p>&mdash; H.E. Justin Sun &#23385;&#23431;&#26216; (@justinsuntron) <a href="https://twitter.com/justinsuntron/status/1688573051179552768?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 7, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">On Monday, both Sun and Huobi <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/justin-sun-addresses-huobis-insolvency-concerns-calls-it-a-fud/">downplayed</a> the latest rumours about potential insolvency for the exchange, terming claims that Chinese authorities were investigating the company as false and mere FUD.</p>
<p>CoinMarketCap ranks Huobi 13th among largest cryptocurrency exchanges by 24-hour spot trading volume.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/huobi-to-list-paypals-pyusd-stablecoin/">Huobi to list PayPal’s PYUSD stablecoin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/huobi-to-list-paypals-pyusd-stablecoin/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>TaskChain: A World First Quest2Earn Web3 Platform Launches Presale</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/taskchain-a-world-first-quest2earn-web3-platform-launches-presale/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/taskchain-a-world-first-quest2earn-web3-platform-launches-presale/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire &#160;]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 10:34:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=148937</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Vienna, Austria, August 8th, 2023, Chainwire TaskChain, a groundbreaking Web3 project, has just announced the launch of its presale today. This new development comes prior to the introduction of TaskChain&#8217;s innovative platform which is set to transform the way users earn income online. For early investors, the news about TaskChain&#8217;s presale launch is another exciting [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/taskchain-a-world-first-quest2earn-web3-platform-launches-presale/">TaskChain: A World First Quest2Earn Web3 Platform Launches Presale</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Vienna, Austria, August 8th, 2023, Chainwire</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://www.taskchain.co/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">TaskChain</a>, a groundbreaking Web3 project, has just announced the launch of its presale today. This new development comes prior to the introduction of TaskChain&rsquo;s innovative platform which is set to transform the way users earn income online.</p>
<p>For early investors, the news about TaskChain&rsquo;s presale launch is another exciting opportunity to be part of a new Web3 platform&rsquo;s journey.</p>
<p>With a vision to empower individuals worldwide, TaskChain combines Web3 technology with GameFi features with the ultimate goal of creating a virtual space where everyone can easily find diverse opportunities for extra income as they collaborate with others.</p>
<p><iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/zFy5hOhYZAw?showinfo=0"></iframe></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h2><strong>What is TaskChain&rsquo;s Mission</strong></h2>
<p>At its core, TaskChain champions the financial inclusion of the masses through fun and user-friendly Web3 features. The platform has the potential to level the playing field, especially for low-income regions, thanks to the Quests, digital jobs, or one-time gigs that users can take on to earn cryptocurrency rewards on the platform.</p>
<p>Each &ldquo;Quest&rdquo; fulfillment is supported by video game mechanics with plans to introduce VR/AR features into the platform for a more immersive experience for users in the future.</p>
<p>Simply put, each &ldquo;Quest&rdquo; on TaskChain&rsquo;s &ldquo;Quest2Earn&rdquo; feature breaks down everyday tasks into a game-like experience where users who fulfill these tasks get to earn XP points as they level up and collect rewards.</p>
<p>The rewards are paid in TaskChain&rsquo;s native token called $TASKC.</p>
<p>In contrast to other similar platforms, TaskChain stands out as a true pioneer in the Web3 space.</p>
<p>Unlike traditional microtask platforms, TaskChain&rsquo;s Quest2Earn feature brings the thrill of gaming to real-life tasks, making the earning process enjoyable.&nbsp;By providing a wide range of Quests and Quest2Earn functions tailored to individual preferences, TaskChain ensures that everyone, regardless of their background or location, can participate and earn rewards.</p>
<p>This inclusive approach empowers users from all walks of life to access valuable income opportunities and take charge of their financial futures.</p>
<h2><strong>How TaskChain works</strong></h2>
<p>As mentioned earlier, Quest2Earn is at the heart of TaskChain&rsquo;s platform. Inspired by popular video game quests, Quest2Earn offers a dynamic and engaging earning experience, allowing users to boost their income, regardless of their location or skills.</p>
<p>Quest2Earn presents a wide array of exciting quests, each tailored to individual interests and categorized into various themes such as shopping, traveling, learning, trading, events, etc. By completing these and many other tasks within these quests, users not only earn cryptocurrency rewards but also gain experience (XP) points to level up and unlock milestone rewards, making the earning process enjoyable and rewarding.</p>
<p>Tom Klein, CEO of TaskChain, said;</p>
<p>&ldquo;TaskChain&rsquo;s Quest2Earn is a game-changer, transforming mundane tasks into exciting opportunities to earn income while having fun. We believe in providing diverse earning opportunities for our users and creating a vibrant community where collaboration and support thrive.&rdquo;</p>
<p><img decoding="async" src="https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/FIX_TaskChain_diagram_1200x720_02_1691411272T6jtZNWUsY.jpg"></p>
<h2><strong>TaskChain Presale</strong></h2>
<p>TaskChain is set for kick-off with a listing price of $0.011 per TASKC token. With a current beta-stage price set at $0.004 per token, the 175% price difference marks the first phase of the presale. Early investors can participate in funding the project in an earlier price tranche.</p>
<p>TaskChain has confirmed it has successfully passed a full security audit and KYC, providing extra security for investors.</p>
<p>There is also a massive <a href="https://www.taskchain.co/giveaway" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">giveaway</a> of $120,000 in rewards for presale participants to spice up involvement in the presale.</p>
<h2><strong>$TASKC Token</strong></h2>
<p>$TASKC ERC20 token, the lifeblood of TaskChain, is built on the most popular Ethereum Blockchain, which will provide transparency, security, and fast payouts with valuable rewards.</p>
<p>With a total supply of 4 billion $TASKC tokens, scarcity, and value are baked into $TASKC&rsquo;s design, the presale will give investors a chance to grab a share of 2.8 billion tokens spread across all the 11 exclusive stages.</p>
<h2><strong>About TaskChain:</strong></h2>
<p>TaskChain is set to build the world&rsquo;s first unique Web3 earning platform. By combining a fun experience with crypto earnings and financial inclusion, TaskChain&rsquo;s Quest2Earn feature will revolutionize the way individuals earn income and interact with blockchain technology. To get involved with TaskChain, visit the official website at taskchain.co and join the growing community.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.taskchain.co/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Website</a> | <a href="https://drive.google.com/file/d/10UQeM8HMT4N7T_Tsm5nYs3cVFufSlHXp/view" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Whitepaper</a> | <a href="https://linktr.ee/taskchain" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Socials</a></p>
<h3>Contact</h3>
<p>Tom Klein, TaskChain, contact@taskchain.co</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/taskchain-a-world-first-quest2earn-web3-platform-launches-presale/">TaskChain: A World First Quest2Earn Web3 Platform Launches Presale</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/taskchain-a-world-first-quest2earn-web3-platform-launches-presale/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitstamp is raising funds to expand services in Asia and Europe: Bloomberg report</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitstamp-is-raising-funds-to-expand-services-in-asia-and-europe-bloomberg-report/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitstamp-is-raising-funds-to-expand-services-in-asia-and-europe-bloomberg-report/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 10:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitstamp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Europe]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitstamp-is-raising-funds-to-expand-services-in-asia-and-europe-bloomberg-report/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TL;DR Bitstamp wants to raise funds to expand its services in Asia and Europe.&#160; Galaxy Digital Holdings is acting as an adviser for the platform in its funding venture. Bitstamp seeks to expand the number of markets it serves Bitstamp, one of the oldest crypto exchanges, has revealed that it is currently in talks with [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitstamp-is-raising-funds-to-expand-services-in-asia-and-europe-bloomberg-report/">Bitstamp is raising funds to expand services in Asia and Europe: Bloomberg report</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">TL;DR</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Bitstamp wants to raise funds to expand its services in Asia and Europe.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Galaxy Digital Holdings is acting as an adviser for the platform in its funding venture.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitstamp seeks to expand the number of markets it serves</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Bitstamp, one of the oldest crypto exchanges, has revealed that it is currently in talks with investors to raise fresh funding.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This is according to Bitstamp&rsquo;s CEO, Jean-Baptiste Graftieaux. The CEO&nbsp;<a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-08-07/crypto-exchange-bitstamp-in-fundraising-talks-seeks-expansion?sref=3REHEaVI#xj4y7vzkg" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>told Bloomberg</u></a> that the cryptocurrency exchange began the fundraising process a few weeks ago, and Galaxy Digital Holdings serves as its adviser.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The cryptocurrency exchange will use the funds to expand its operations. Bitstamp wants to launch its derivatives trading service in Europe by next year and will also expand the number of markets it serves in Asia. The company will also expand its operations in the U.K.,</p>
<p dir="ltr">While commenting on this&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>latest cryptocurrency news</u></a>, Jean-Baptiste Graftieaux stated that;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;Bitstamp is not for sale, and we are not actively looking to sell the company. Our current and exclusive priority is to raise money through strategic investors to accelerate Bitstamp&rsquo;s growth by providing new products and services to retail and institutional crypto customers.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitstamp has been expanding its business in the crypto space in recent months. In June,&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitstamp-registered-as-a-cryptoasset-business-by-uks-fca/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Bitstamp was registered</u></a> as a cryptoasset business by the UK&rsquo;s Financial Conduct Authority (FCA).&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">By doing so, Bitstamp joined other platforms like eToro, Revolut and Moonpay on the FCA list of firms complying with Money Laundering, Terrorist Financing and Transfer of Regulations (MLRs).</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitstamp is a UK-based cryptocurrency exchange and has been around since 2011.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitstamp-is-raising-funds-to-expand-services-in-asia-and-europe-bloomberg-report/">Bitstamp is raising funds to expand services in Asia and Europe: Bloomberg report</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitstamp-is-raising-funds-to-expand-services-in-asia-and-europe-bloomberg-report/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Xsolla and Crypto.com Partner to Integrate Payment Solutions</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/xsolla-and-crypto-com-partner-to-integrate-payment-solutions/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/xsolla-and-crypto-com-partner-to-integrate-payment-solutions/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire &#160;]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 08:26:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=148916</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>LOS ANGELES, United States, August 8th, 2023, Chainwire Xsolla, a global video game commerce company, and global cryptocurrency platform Crypto.com have announced a partnership for the integration of Crypto.com&#8217;s checkout solution into Xsolla&#8217;s Pay Station platform. This transformative integration of Crypto.com Pay represents a significant advancement in the gaming industry and creates new possibilities for [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/xsolla-and-crypto-com-partner-to-integrate-payment-solutions/">Xsolla and Crypto.com Partner to Integrate Payment Solutions</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>LOS ANGELES, United States, August 8th, 2023, Chainwire</strong></p>
<p>Xsolla, a global video game commerce company, and global cryptocurrency platform Crypto.com have announced a partnership for the integration of Crypto.com&rsquo;s checkout solution into Xsolla&rsquo;s Pay Station platform.</p>
<p>This transformative integration of Crypto.com Pay represents a significant advancement in the gaming industry and creates new possibilities for game developers and players, enabling them to accept cryptocurrency payments and streamline transactions in a user-friendly and secure manner for a universally enhanced experience. This pivotal update broadens the horizon for digital payment methods, offering players more diverse and preferred transaction options in digital and metaverse environments. This collaboration also marks a significant step for Crypto.com in building its presence and network across the gaming industry.</p>
<p>&ldquo;There is significant potential in the convergence of gaming and Web3,&rdquo; said Eric Anziani, President and Chief Operating Officer of Crypto.com. &ldquo;By partnering with a global gaming leader like Xsolla and leveraging our respective assets and expertise, we are helping make that potential a reality &ndash; giving developers, publishers, and players a seamless way to engage and create value in the crypto economy.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Xsolla&rsquo;s Pay Station, which facilitates in-game purchases across 200+ regions and countries using a variety of compliant payment providers, is enhancing its service with the integration of Crypto.com Pay. This forthcoming development promises to expand the reach of developers and publishers, enabling them to engage a more diverse player base and tap into new, dynamic markets and revenue streams.</p>
<p>&ldquo;We are thrilled about this partnership with Crypto.com and the significant integration of Crypto.com Pay into our Pay Station platform. The gaming industry is rapidly evolving, and we must adapt to meet those changes. The integration of cryptocurrencies as a form of payment offers game developers and players an innovative payment solution that aligns with the global shift towards digital currencies,&rdquo; said Chris Hewish, CEO of Xsolla. &ldquo;Our collaboration with Crypto.com marks a pivotal moment for the gaming industry, paving the way for a more inclusive and secure gaming ecosystem.&rdquo;</p>
<p>&ldquo;We are tremendously excited to take this first step with Xsolla as part of a broader collaboration initiative in Korea and on a global level,&rdquo; said Patrick Yoon, General Manager of Crypto.com Korea. &ldquo;We look forward to continuing to work with Xsolla in developing and advancing payment ecosystems and digital asset adoption.&rdquo;</p>
<p><strong>For more information about Crypto.com Pay and Pay Station, please visit: </strong><a href="https://xsolla.pro/cryptocom" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><strong>xsolla.pro/cryptocom</strong></a><strong>&nbsp;</strong></p>
<h3>About Xsolla</h3>
<p>Xsolla is a global video game commerce company with a robust and powerful set of tools and services designed specifically for the industry. Since its founding in 2005, Xsolla has helped thousands of game developers and publishers of all sizes fund, market, launch, and monetize their games globally and across multiple platforms. As an innovative leader in game commerce, Xsolla&rsquo;s mission is to solve the inherent complexities of global distribution, marketing, and monetization to help our partners reach more geographies, generate more revenue and create relationships with gamers worldwide. Headquartered and incorporated in Los Angeles, California, with offices in Berlin, Seoul, Beijing, Kuala Lumpur, Tokyo, and cities around the world, Xsolla supports major gaming titles like Valve, Twitch, Roblox, Ubisoft, Epic Games, Take-Two, KRAFTON, Nexters, NetEase, Playstudios, Playrix, miHoYo, and more.</p>
<p>For additional information and to learn more, please visit: <a href="https://xsolla.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">xsolla.com</a></p>
<h3>About Crypto.com</h3>
<p>Founded in 2016,<a href="http://crypto.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"> Crypto.com</a> is trusted by more than 80 million customers worldwide and is the industry leader in regulatory compliance, security, and privacy. Our vision is simple: Cryptocurrency in Every Wallet&trade;.<a href="http://crypto.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"> Crypto.com</a> is committed to accelerating the adoption of cryptocurrency through innovation and empowering the next generation of builders, creators, and entrepreneurs to develop a fairer and more equitable digital ecosystem.</p>
<p>Learn more at<a href="https://crypto.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"> crypto.com</a></p>
<h3>Contact</h3>
<p>Global Director of Public Relations, Derrick Stembridge, Xsolla, d.stembridge@xsolla.com, 919-971-7855</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/xsolla-and-crypto-com-partner-to-integrate-payment-solutions/">Xsolla and Crypto.com Partner to Integrate Payment Solutions</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/xsolla-and-crypto-com-partner-to-integrate-payment-solutions/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
