<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 14:08:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Twitter May Face Legal Complications Following Rebranding to X</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-legal-complications-x/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-legal-complications-x/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 14:08:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[facebook]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Meta]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[microsoft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[twitter]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[x]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=264432</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-legal-complications-x/">Twitter May Face Legal Complications Following Rebranding to X</a></p>
<p>Trademark attorney Douglas Masters emphasized that protecting a single letter like “X” can be particularly challenging, especially when it is widely used commercially and lacks distinctive characteristics.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-legal-complications-x/">Twitter May Face Legal Complications Following Rebranding to X</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-legal-complications-x/">Twitter May Face Legal Complications Following Rebranding to X</a></p>
<p>In a bold and unexpected move, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/twitter/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Twitter</a>’s owner and former CEO <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/elon-musk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Elon Musk</a> recently <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/musk-twitter-logo-x/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">announced</a> a rebranding initiative, changing the company’s name to “X”.</p>
<p>The switch to X is likely to be the first of many moves in the gradual transition of Twitter into X Corp, Musk&#8217;s promised and long-awaited &#8220;everything app&#8221;. However, this seemingly harmless rebranding has sparked a storm of legal issues for the corporation, with trademark conflicts and intellectual property challenges threatening to overshadow the intended transformation.</p>
<h2>Concerns over Trademark Infringement</h2>
<p>In a <a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/problem-with-x-meta-microsoft-hundreds-more-own-trademarks-new-twitter-name-2023-07-25/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a> from Reuters, trademark attorney Josh Gerben asserts that there is a “100% chance” that Twitter will face lawsuits over its rebranding to “X”, adding that nearly 900 active US trademark registrations are already covering the letter “X” across various industries.</p>
<p>Trademarks play a crucial role in protecting brand names, logos, and slogans that distinguish the source of goods or services. When a new branding could potentially cause confusion among consumers with existing trademarks, the owners of those trademarks have the right to claim infringement.</p>
<p>In the case of Twitter’s rebranding to “X”, companies that already hold trademarks for the letter “X” or similar stylized versions may argue that the new logo and name could create confusion among consumers.</p>
<p>Specifically, the report highlighted that <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/meta/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Meta Platforms Inc</a> (NASDAQ: META) formerly known as Facebook and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/microsoft-corporation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Microsoft Corp</a> (NASDAQ: MSFT) already holds intellectual property rights related to the same letter. Both companies have intellectual property rights over the letter “X” in different contexts.</p>
<p>Microsoft’s ownership of the “X” trademark is related to communications about its Xbox video game system. On the other hand, Meta Platforms own a federal trademark registered in 2019 covering a blue-and-white letter &#8220;X&#8221; for software and social media fields.</p>
<p>Trademark disputes are complex legal matters, and it is challenging to predict the exact course of action each company would take. Whether Microsoft and Meta would sue Twitter over the trademark infringement or not largely depends on their perception of the threat posed by Twitter’s rebranding.</p>
<p>Trademark attorney Douglas Masters emphasized that protecting a single letter like “X” can be particularly challenging, especially when it is widely used commercially and lacks distinctive characteristics. As a result, the protection granted to Twitter&#8217;s “X” logo would likely be limited and applicable only to graphics closely resembling their specific logo.</p>
<h2>Meta’s Trademark Lawsuits</h2>
<p>Meanwhile, Meta’s rebranding from Facebook to Meta has not been without its fair share of intellectual property challenges.</p>
<p>Upon its name change, Meta found itself embroiled in trademark disputes with investment firm Metacapital and virtual-reality company MetaX. Both entities claimed that the new name “Meta” could create confusion among consumers and dilute their brand identities, given the similarities in their names.</p>
<p>Additionally, Meta had to <a href="https://www.reuters.com/legal/meta-settles-us-lawsuit-over-infinity-logo-trademark-2023-02-07/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">settle</a> another dispute concerning its new infinity-symbol logo, indicating that the rebranding process has not been without legal hurdles.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/spotify-revenue-q2-2023/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-legal-complications-x/">Twitter May Face Legal Complications Following Rebranding to X</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-legal-complications-x/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Spotify Grows Revenue to €3.2B in Q2 2023, with 551M Active Users </title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/spotify-revenue-q2-2023/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/spotify-revenue-q2-2023/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 14:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[spotify]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=264423</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/spotify-revenue-q2-2023/">Spotify Grows Revenue to €3.2B in Q2 2023, with 551M Active Users </a></p>
<p>Spotify's Q2 2023 figures shows a strong quarter as its revenue and monthly active users both beat the company's guidance.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/spotify-revenue-q2-2023/">Spotify Grows Revenue to €3.2B in Q2 2023, with 551M Active Users </a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/spotify-revenue-q2-2023/">Spotify Grows Revenue to €3.2B in Q2 2023, with 551M Active Users </a></p>
<p>Swedish audio streaming giant Spotify has released its <a href="https://newsroom.spotify.com/2023-07-25/spotify-reports-second-quarter-2023-earnings/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">earnings report for Q2 2023</a>, pointing to a strong quarter for the company.</p>
<p>According to the report, Spotify’s monthly active users (MAUs) jumped 27% to 551 million, recording a net addition of 36 million, which beat the company’s guidance by 21 million, pulling in an all-time high. All Spotify regions outperformed expectations and recorded higher MAU net additions compared to the same period last year.</p>
<p>The report also states that Spotify subscribers hit 220 million after growing 17% year-over-year (YoY). The net addition of 10 million surpassed the company’s guidance by 3 million, making the quarter Spotify’s highest-ever Q2 for subscriber growth. Furthermore, Spotify reported an 11% YoY growth to €3.2 billion, exactly on par with guidance.</p>
<p>Spotify also recorded an adjusted operating loss of €112 million, lower than the €129 period the company’s guidance expected. Gross profit increased 9% from Q2 2022 to 766 million but remained unchanged from Q1 2023. According to the company, “Spotify had a very strong quarter. We beat guidance and welcomed more users and subscribers than expected, with growth continuing to come from markets all over the world.”</p>
<p>Spotify is forecasting another 4 million Premium subscribers for Q3 this year. It also expects to add 21 million MAUs in total. Currently, Spotify’s anticipated revenue for Q3 is €3.3 billion, slightly higher than the reported figure for Q2.</p>
<h2>Spotify Cut Staff Count and Increased Prices in Q2 2023</h2>
<p>On Monday, Spotify <a href="https://variety.com/2023/music/news/spotify-raises-us-premium-subscription-price-1235678308/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">increased</a> its Premium subscription price in the US from $9.99 to $10.99. The increase comes following intense pressure on music streaming services from players in the music industry. Unlike Apple Music, Deezer, and other competitors that have increased prices at different points in the past, this is Spotify’s first increase since it launched in the US in 2011.</p>
<p>In an official <a href="https://newsroom.spotify.com/2023-07-24/adjusting-our-spotify-premium-prices/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">blog post</a> announcing the change, Spotify explained that the increase is necessary so the company can continue to innovate as the market landscape changes. According to Spotify, the change will “help us to continue to deliver value to fans and artists on our platform.”</p>
<p>Last month, Spotify <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/spotify-cut-headcount-200-employees/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">revealed</a> plans to reduce its staff headcount by 2%, affecting about 200 employees. The company said affected staff will get severance packages with access to outplacement support and healthcare coverage.</p>
<p>In January, the company <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/spotify-layoff-scheme-tech-downturn/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">announced</a> a layoff plan, noting that it was necessary because of the general economic downturn. Spotify had also laid off 38 staff from the Parcast and Gimlet Media podcast studios, absorbing both into its Spotify Studios. The company did this despite highlighting in an official <a href="https://newsroom.spotify.com/2023-06-05/an-update-on-changes-to-spotifys-podcast-business-june-2023/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">publication</a> that it has more than 100 million Podcast listeners and is the most-used audio podcast platform in most of the world. Spotify also announced it has grown its podcast content from 200,000 to over 5 million shows. The publication states that Spotify is the number 1 podcast publisher in the US.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/japan-pm-web3-stance-binance/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/spotify-revenue-q2-2023/">Spotify Grows Revenue to €3.2B in Q2 2023, with 551M Active Users </a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/spotify-revenue-q2-2023/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Japan PM Reaffirms Web3 Stance, Binance Poised for Return</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/japan-pm-web3-stance-binance/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/japan-pm-web3-stance-binance/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mercy Tukiya Mutanya]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 12:50:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sakura exchnage bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sebc]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=264410</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/japan-pm-web3-stance-binance/">Japan PM Reaffirms Web3 Stance, Binance Poised for Return</a></p>
<p>Meanwhile, Binance is preparing to launch its service on a new Japanese platform next month.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/japan-pm-web3-stance-binance/">Japan PM Reaffirms Web3 Stance, Binance Poised for Return</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/japan-pm-web3-stance-binance/">Japan PM Reaffirms Web3 Stance, Binance Poised for Return</a></p>
<p>Japan’s Prime Minister Fumio Kishida has described Web3 as a “new form of capitalism”. He made these remarks during his keynote address on day one of the two-day WebX conference in Tokyo, asserting the country’s commitment to ensuring the growth of the local Web3 industry, an industry that he believes has the potential to transform the internet and foster social reform.</p>
<p>WebX, self-described as “Asia’s largest web3 conference”, attracts attendance from startups, investors, government officials, the media, and industry heavyweights, among others. Opening the conference, the chairman of the Liberal Democratic Party&#8217;s Policy Research Council, Koichi Hagiuda highlighted the country’s progress in Web3 adoption. He noted the country&#8217;s efforts in establishing a regulatory framework tailored to the industry and designed to protect investors. Hagiuda also commended individual projects, hailing the &#8220;Start Next Innovator&#8221; project as key to the proliferation of locally-owned Web3 businesses. The Economy, Trade, and Industry Ministry project will, over a five-year period, work at fostering the growth of Web3 startups by sending 1,000 entrepreneurs and students to Silicon Valley.</p>
<p>Prime Minister Kishida also expressed confidence in the technology&#8217;s ability to promote cross-industry innovation, <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/headlines/news/web3-part-of-a-new-capitalism-says-japan-pm-kishida/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">adding</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“I hope that the Web3 industry will regain its attention and vitality, and that various new projects will be born.”</p></blockquote>
<p>EOS Foundation CEO Yves La Rose was present at the event and tweeted that the prime minister&#8217;s words were a sign of Asia&#8217;s welcoming attitude toward Web3.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="474" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Here live at <a href="https://twitter.com/WebX_Asia?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@WebX_Asia</a> and <a href="https://twitter.com/JPN_PMO?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@JPN_PMO</a> Fumio Kishida just stated that Web3 is &quot;the new form of capitalism&quot;.</p>
<p>While the West continues to antagonize blockchain companies, Asia is welcoming us in with their arms wide open.</p>
<p>In Asia, the future is bright for crypto! <a href="https://t.co/eZ9puYdzoR">pic.twitter.com/eZ9puYdzoR</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Yves La Rose (@BigBeardSamurai) <a href="https://twitter.com/BigBeardSamurai/status/1683665502336438272?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 25, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The sentiments come as global crypto exchange <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a> is preparing to launch its service on a new Japanese platform next month. This was made possible when the crypto exchange made a 100% purchase of the Japan Financial Services Agency (JFSA) -registered Sakura Exchange BitCoin (SEBC), a crypto exchange service provider in November 2022.</p>
<p>“The Japanese market will play a key role in the future of cryptocurrency adoption. As one of the world’s leading economies with a highly-developed tech ecosystem, it’s already poised for strong blockchain uptake. We will actively work with regulators to develop our combined exchange in a compliant way for local users. We are eager to help Japan take a leading role in crypto,” said the general manager of Binance Japan Takeshi Chino, said in the official announcement of the acquisition.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/adidas-ads-stock-yeezy-sales/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/japan-pm-web3-stance-binance/">Japan PM Reaffirms Web3 Stance, Binance Poised for Return</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/japan-pm-web3-stance-binance/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Adidas (ADS) Stock Jumps 6% after Strong Yeezy Sales and Trimming Losses</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/adidas-ads-stock-yeezy-sales/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/adidas-ads-stock-yeezy-sales/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 12:45:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[adidas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[adidas stock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ads stock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[yeezy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=264404</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/adidas-ads-stock-yeezy-sales/">Adidas (ADS) Stock Jumps 6% after Strong Yeezy Sales and Trimming Losses</a></p>
<p>Adidas is able to alleviate the impact of operational losses as the clearance of the massive Yeezy inventory takes turn for the good. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/adidas-ads-stock-yeezy-sales/">Adidas (ADS) Stock Jumps 6% after Strong Yeezy Sales and Trimming Losses</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/adidas-ads-stock-yeezy-sales/">Adidas (ADS) Stock Jumps 6% after Strong Yeezy Sales and Trimming Losses</a></p>
<p>On Monday, July 24, German sportswear giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/adidas/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Adidas AG</a> (ETR: ADS) said that it expects a significant drop in operating losses for the year 2023. This commentary from the management comes after Adidas managed better-than-expected sales of its Yeezy inventory after breaking ties with the rapper and designer Kanye West.</p>
<p>The German sports company has revised its 2023 operating loss forecast to €450 million ($499 million), down from the previous estimate of €700 million. This positive change is due to the initial sales of its Yeezy sneakers inventory. The company expects future releases of Yeezy sneakers to potentially further improve its financial results.</p>
<p>During the trading hours on Tuesday, July 25, the Adidas (ADS) stock price is trading at 5.76% up at a price of <span class="IsqQVc NprOob wT3VGc">184.86</span><span class="knFDje"> EUR. For the second quarter of 2023, Adidas reported sales of €5.34 billion, beating the average estimate of €5.05 billion. </span></p>
<p>The company&#8217;s main Adidas business performed slightly better than expected. It anticipates that the operating profit, excluding any extraordinary Yeezy-related expenses and the ongoing strategic review, will be approximately break-even for the year. Referring to the further release of its existing inventory, Adidas said: “If successful, potential future Yeezy drops would further improve the company’s results.”</p>
<h2>Adidas Breaking Up with Kanye West</h2>
<p>Adidas terminated its collaboration with musician Ye (formerly known as Kanye West) in October 2022 due to his offensive and antisemitic remarks. After facing widespread criticism online, Adidas deemed Ye&#8217;s comments &#8220;unacceptable, hateful, and dangerous&#8221;. As a result, they discontinued the production of Yeezy-branded products, including footwear and clothing, and ceased all payments to Ye and his companies.</p>
<p>However, the decision left the company thinking about what would it do with the existing Yeezy stock. In May, Adidas declared its plan to sell the inventory and donate a substantial portion of the proceeds to organizations such as the Anti-Defamation League and the Philonise and Keeta Floyd Institute for Social Change.</p>
<p>In a note, James Grzinic of Jefferies <a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/adidas-gets-565-mln-orders-first-batch-unsold-yeezy-shoes-ft-2023-07-24/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The key takeaway here is the remarkable markup that Yeezy still commands.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The analyst&#8217;s estimate indicates that Yeezy contributed approximately €450 million in revenue during the second quarter. They also mentioned that Adidas&#8217;s new forecast is cautious and includes measures to protect against potential risks in the broader economic conditions.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-shuts-down-ai-detection/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/adidas-ads-stock-yeezy-sales/">Adidas (ADS) Stock Jumps 6% after Strong Yeezy Sales and Trimming Losses</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/adidas-ads-stock-yeezy-sales/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>OpenAI Shuts Down Its AI Detection Tool Due to Low Accuracy</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-shuts-down-ai-detection/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-shuts-down-ai-detection/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Darya Rudz]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 12:26:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ai]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ai classifier]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AI classifier shutdown]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[artificial intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[open ai classifier]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[openai]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[openai artificial intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[openai chatgpt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=264377</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-shuts-down-ai-detection/">OpenAI Shuts Down Its AI Detection Tool Due to Low Accuracy</a></p>
<p>The link leading to the tool is no longer functioning. However, OpenAI has promised to come up with other detection tools that users can trust. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-shuts-down-ai-detection/">OpenAI Shuts Down Its AI Detection Tool Due to Low Accuracy</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-shuts-down-ai-detection/">OpenAI Shuts Down Its AI Detection Tool Due to Low Accuracy</a></p>
<p>OpenAI, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/technology/artificial-intelligence-news/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">artificial intelligence</a> (AI) research laboratory and creator of a renowned AI chatbot <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/everything-you-need-to-know-about-chatgpt-ai-chatbot/#:~:text=What%20Is%20ChatGPT%3F,the%20field%20of%20artificial%20intelligence." target="_blank" rel="noopener">ChatGPT</a>, has quietly shut down its AI detection tool – AI Classifier. The suspension of the tool has been a result of a low rate of accuracy. As OpenAI has said, its team has been working towards incorporating feedback and is currently looking for more effective solutions.</p>
<p>A <a href="https://openai.com/blog/new-ai-classifier-for-indicating-ai-written-text" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">blog post</a> that has been initially released to introduce AI Classifier has now been updated with the following:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;As of July 20, 2023, the AI classifier is no longer available due to its low rate of accuracy. We are working to incorporate feedback and are currently researching more effective provenance techniques for text, and have made a commitment to develop and deploy mechanisms that enable users to understand if audio or visual content is AI-generated.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>It turns out that the accuracy of the tool has been below what was expected. As OpenAI has revealed, its team evaluated a &#8220;challenge set&#8221; of English texts where the classifier correctly identified 26% of AI-written text as &#8220;likely AI-written&#8221;, while incorrectly labeling human-written text as AI-written 9% of the time. Notably, the tool was unreliable when working with texts with fewer than 1,000 characters. The longer the text was, the higher the accuracy could be. Thus, OpenAI referred to AI Classifier as a &#8220;not fully reliable&#8221; detection tool.</p>
<p>The link leading to the tool is no longer functioning. However, OpenAI has promised to come up with other detection tools that users can trust.</p>
<h2>Can AI Transform the Education Sector?</h2>
<p>Initially, AI Classifier was intended for educators who could use the tool to check on the integrity of students using the chatbot to write essays.</p>
<p>OpenAI said:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We recognize that identifying AI-written text has been an important point of discussion among educators, and equally important is recognizing the limits and impacts of AI-generated text classifiers in the classroom.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>AI Classifier was seen as a resource to help educators, journalists, and researchers study misinformation. Thus, shutting down the detector has come as a downer for educators worldwide who have been struggling to identify AI-generated content.</p>
<p>In general, the development of AI has had an impact on every industry, solutions it provides have also started transforming education. AI solutions for education analyze enormous data sets using sophisticated algorithms, providing personalized and adaptable learning experiences. Students get personalized learning, prompt feedback, and access to immersive technologies like augmented and virtual reality in education. All this promotes independent learning and revolutionizes the way of studying. However, AI in education poses a few risks.</p>
<p>Firstly, there is a lack of human interaction and emotional support that students receive when using AI-powered educational tools. AI can personalized learning and instant feedback, but it can not replace the human and emotional support that students need to succeed.</p>
<p>Secondly, there are privacy concerns as AI systems might need to collect specific data about the identity of students or staff, which threatens their online identity and private information.</p>
<p>Further, AI might take out the thinking power of students and make them more dependent on technology instead of learning how to do things themselves.</p>
<p>As of 2023, AI in the education market is set to have an annual growth rate of about 36% from nowadays to 2030 with projected revenue of $32.27 billion.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/worldcoin-whitepaper-token-supply/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-shuts-down-ai-detection/">OpenAI Shuts Down Its AI Detection Tool Due to Low Accuracy</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-shuts-down-ai-detection/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Worldcoin Unveils Its Whitepaper Stirring Concerns Over Token Supply</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/worldcoin-whitepaper-token-supply/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/worldcoin-whitepaper-token-supply/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 12:13:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[openai]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sam altman]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[wld]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[worldcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=264385</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/worldcoin-whitepaper-token-supply/">Worldcoin Unveils Its Whitepaper Stirring Concerns Over Token Supply</a></p>
<p>During the token's launch, the circulating supply was limited to 143 million tokens, with 43 million of the asset reserved for early adopters and 100 million provided as loans to non-US market makers.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/worldcoin-whitepaper-token-supply/">Worldcoin Unveils Its Whitepaper Stirring Concerns Over Token Supply</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/worldcoin-whitepaper-token-supply/">Worldcoin Unveils Its Whitepaper Stirring Concerns Over Token Supply</a></p>
<p>The highly anticipated crypto token, Worldcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/worldcoin/">WLD</a>), co-founded by OpenAI&#8217;s CEO Sam Altman, made a splash on its first day of trading as investors rushed to be part of the artificial intelligence (AI) hype. WLD&#8217;s value skyrocketed from its initial price of $1.70 to a high of $3.58 before settling at $2.52, according to CoinMarketCap data. Trading volume reached nearly $350 million on various exchanges, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-bybit-okx-worldcoin-wld/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">including</a> Binance, Bybit, and OKX.</p>
<p>Worldcoin&#8217;s impressive surge coincided with the release of its whitepaper, shedding light on the token&#8217;s tokenomics and underlying principles. According to the document, the total supply of WLD tokens is capped at 10 billion for the first 15 years of the network&#8217;s existence. After this period, voters may decide to introduce a 1.5% inflation rate.</p>
<h2>Worldcoin Not Available to Users Globally</h2>
<p>According to a Decrypt <a href="https://decrypt.co/149865/worldcoin-tokenomics-at-launch-supply-market-maker-loans" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a>, concerns have been raised over the discrepancy between the total supply of 10 billion tokens and the initial circulating supply of 106 million WLD tokens, valued at around $219 million. Industry experts, such as Tom Dunleavy, the founder of Alethia, have expressed concerns, pointing out that projects with similar tokenomics have been susceptible to quick sell-offs.</p>
<p>&#8220;Most tokens that have a small amount of distribution or a large fully diluted valuation have shown themselves to be easy targets for quick sell-offs. The history of airdrops, in general, has not been favorable,&#8221; said Dunleavy.</p>
<p>Worldcoin aims to establish itself as a financial and identity network, offering an app for payments and utilizing biometric data from &#8220;shiny, metal orbs&#8221; to create unique World IDs. This approach has sparked controversy, raising concerns over privacy and the availability of the whitepaper.</p>
<p>The report also disclosed that the whitepaper was not accessible in the US and UK but was available in Colombia, despite the ability for users to verify their identity in multiple regions. The lack of accessibility has led to further scrutiny.</p>
<h2>Worldcoin Launch Relies on Market Maker Loans</h2>
<p>During the token&#8217;s launch, the circulating supply was limited to 143 million tokens, with 43 million of the asset reserved for early adopters and 100 million provided as loans to non-US market makers. These loans have a three-month duration and allow market makers to buy WLD tokens instead of returning them.</p>
<p>The agreement with market makers has received mixed reactions. Sadettin Kerim, a digital assets product manager at Yapı Kredi, believes it offers them an advantage, allowing them to manipulate prices.</p>
<p>&#8220;The agreement is an absolute win for market makers. If they do not face a huge market demand, they will easily dip the price and then buy it back. It&#8217;s easy money for them,&#8221; Kerim told Decrypt.</p>
<p>Conversely, Dunleavy considers it speculative in the medium to long term, with no incentives for market makers after the three months.</p>
<h2>75% Worldcoin Token to be Distributed among the Community</h2>
<p>The whitepaper also outlined the allocation of WLD tokens, with 75% going to the Worldcoin community over time. The rest is divided among the initial development team, investors, and a reserve of 170 million WLD. The allocation to insiders increased to 25% due to the complexities and costs of developing and launching the network, as stated in the revised whitepaper.</p>
<p>Additionally, Bruno Faviero, co-founder and CEO of Magna, a token distribution platform, finds the low circulating supply, mainly in loans, difficult to gauge in terms of community response.</p>
<p>Despite the challenges and controversies surrounding Worldcoin, the project managed to verify the identities of more than 2 million people in 35 countries using biometric data. However, it&#8217;s worth noting that while World ID verification is available worldwide, WLD trading is restricted in the US and other territories.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/xrp-crypto-regulation-woes/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/worldcoin-whitepaper-token-supply/">Worldcoin Unveils Its Whitepaper Stirring Concerns Over Token Supply</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/worldcoin-whitepaper-token-supply/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Becomes White Knight of Crypto, Thwarts Regulation Woes</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/xrp-crypto-regulation-woes/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/xrp-crypto-regulation-woes/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 10:43:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ripple labs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=264388</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/xrp-crypto-regulation-woes/">XRP Becomes White Knight of Crypto, Thwarts Regulation Woes</a></p>
<p>Despite the surge in the crypto market, Ripple's legal victory does not guarantee smooth sailing for XRP or the broader altcoin sector.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/xrp-crypto-regulation-woes/">XRP Becomes White Knight of Crypto, Thwarts Regulation Woes</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/xrp-crypto-regulation-woes/">XRP Becomes White Knight of Crypto, Thwarts Regulation Woes</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/xrp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">XRP</a>, the digital currency associated with Ripple Labs Inc, has emerged as an unlikely white knight, turning the tides against its regulation concerns and reinvigorating the entire market.</p>
<h2>Long Drawn XRP Regulation Woes</h2>
<p>For years, XRP and Ripple Labs were subjected to intense regulatory scrutiny, with the Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) claiming that the digital asset should be categorized as a security.</p>
<p>This classification would have subjected Ripple Labs to strenuous rules and potentially resulted in the delisting of XRP from key exchanges. However, earlier this month, the tide reversed in favor of the embattled cryptocurrency. The presiding US judge, Analisa Torres decided in favor of Ripple, ruling that XRP sales on public exchanges did not violate securities regulations.</p>
<p>Following the favorable ruling, XRP has <a href="https://www.aol.com/news/cryptoverse-ripple-effect-explosive-xrp-051511819.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reportedly</a> experienced an astounding 78% price increase. Such a rapid surge not only caught the attention of investors and traders but also positioned XRP as one of the best-performing digital assets in recent times.</p>
<p>The <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/xrp-4th-largest-crypto-victory/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">surge</a> also led to a remarkable increase in XRP’s market capitalization, which soared to $36 billion from $25 billion, indicating a newfound sense of trust and belief in the asset’s potential. Moreover, XRP’s market share within the broader crypto market also witnessed a notable boost, climbing from 2% to 3.5%.</p>
<p>While this might seem modest at first glance, one must consider the vastness of the crypto market, where even a slight shift in market share represents billions of dollars in value.</p>
<p>The significance of Ripple’s victory cannot be overstated, as it has set a strong legal precedent for other altcoins and raised hopes that they too may be exempt from being classified as tightly-regulated securities. The verdict has inspired confidence among market participants, as indicated by the significant increase in the value of altcoins.</p>
<p>According to CoinGecko, the market cap of altcoins has risen to $665.2 billion from $636.38 billion prior to the ruling. This substantial increase reflects the renewed investor interest and confidence in these alternative digital assets.</p>
<p>Furthermore, Bitcoin, often considered a commodity rather than a security, also experienced a surge in value, reaching a 13-month high following the ruling. However, it is essential to note that Bitcoin’s price has retraced below the $30,000 mark at the time of writing.</p>
<h2>Looking Ahead amidst Challenges</h2>
<p>Despite the surge in the crypto market, Ripple&#8217;s legal victory does not guarantee smooth sailing for XRP or the broader altcoin sector. The regulatory landscape remains <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bank-of-america-ripple-sec-ruling/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">uncertain</a>, and challenges persist, potentially impacting the future trajectory of these digital assets.</p>
<p>One significant hurdle is the possibility of the SEC appealing the recent ruling. Legal experts suggest that the SEC may not accept the court’s decision and could seek further legal recourse. An appeal would extend the period of uncertainty surrounding the XRP regulation status and could lead to fluctuations in its price and market sentiment.</p>
<p>Adding to the challenges, the rise of competitors such as stablecoins has provided alternative options for users seeking stability and utility in the crypto space. This increased competition may have affected XRP’s position in the market and its adoption for various use cases.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-volatility-index-deribit/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/xrp-crypto-regulation-woes/">XRP Becomes White Knight of Crypto, Thwarts Regulation Woes</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/xrp-crypto-regulation-woes/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Volatility Index Hits All-Time Low on Deribit</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-volatility-index-deribit/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-volatility-index-deribit/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 10:41:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin volatility]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc price forecast]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=264353</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-volatility-index-deribit/">Bitcoin Volatility Index Hits All-Time Low on Deribit</a></p>
<p>The implied volatility levels mean that derivatives traders do not see any major price shake-ups happening in the interim.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-volatility-index-deribit/">Bitcoin Volatility Index Hits All-Time Low on Deribit</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-volatility-index-deribit/">Bitcoin Volatility Index Hits All-Time Low on Deribit</a></p>
<p>Crypto options exchange Deribit may have reasons to believe that the near future holds some positives for Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/standard-chartered-bitcoin-btc-2024/">BTC</a>). This follows after the exchange&#8217;s Bitcoin volatility index recently reached its lowest level since 2021.</p>
<p>The index is a measure of the degree of fear that crypto users have in Bitcoin. And by a larger effect, may also indicate an absence of price volatility for <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a> in the near future.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Volatility Index Suggests a Near-Steady Next 30 Days for BTC Price</h2>
<p>DVOL is the Deribit Implied Volatility Index. It tracks the degree of volatility that is expected of a crypto asset over the next 30 days. In other words, the index shows how confident or negative investors are about a crypto&#8217;s price turbulence.</p>
<p>As earlier mentioned, the current implied volatility level is Deribit&#8217;s lowest since launching in 2021. However, it is also the lowest level in crypto&#8217;s entire history, according to the DVOL algorithm.</p>
<p>Interestingly, the crypto derivatives analytics platform Greeks Live has also shared a similar index. On Monday, July 24, Greeks Live <a href="https://twitter.com/GreeksLive/status/1683488907097264128?t=4oxZ6uSfL78HFKqlNfEcSw&amp;s=19" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">noted</a> that the volatility index for both Bitcoin and Ether (ETH) combined has fallen to 37%. This represents a multi-year low, according to the platform. The analytics firm also explained further that continued low liquidity has severely affected implied volatility (IV) levels for Bitcoin. It wrote:</p>
<blockquote><p>“It is an indisputable fact that the overall volatility of cryptocurrencies is declining, which will inevitably force the implied volatility of cryptocurrencies to keep going to new lows.”</p></blockquote>
<p>By implication, the implied volatility levels mean that derivatives traders do not see any major price shake-ups happening in the interim. And there is also the belief that crypto markets may not see any major activity, at least, for the next few months.</p>
<p>For what it&#8217;s worth, crypto markets appear to have been in a restful state since mid-March. Its total capitalization goes back and forth around the $1.2 trillion mark and there has been little to no significant change from this level.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tsmc-ai-2-9b-investment-chip/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-volatility-index-deribit/">Bitcoin Volatility Index Hits All-Time Low on Deribit</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-volatility-index-deribit/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>TSMC to Capitalize on AI Boom with $2.9B Investment in Advanced Chip Packaging Plant</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tsmc-ai-2-9b-investment-chip/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tsmc-ai-2-9b-investment-chip/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 10:38:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tsmc]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=264382</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tsmc-ai-2-9b-investment-chip/">TSMC to Capitalize on AI Boom with $2.9B Investment in Advanced Chip Packaging Plant</a></p>
<p>According to Taiwan’s official Central News Agency, “the rapid growth of the artificial intelligence (AI) market has driven a surge in demand for TSMC’s advanced packaging.”</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tsmc-ai-2-9b-investment-chip/">TSMC to Capitalize on AI Boom with $2.9B Investment in Advanced Chip Packaging Plant</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tsmc-ai-2-9b-investment-chip/">TSMC to Capitalize on AI Boom with $2.9B Investment in Advanced Chip Packaging Plant</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/tsmc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">TSMC</a> is intensifying its efforts towards AI with its latest plan to invest $2.9 billion in an advanced chip packaging plant in Taiwan. The semiconductor manufacturing company wants to capitalize on the trending AI buzz after recently noting the high demand for AI chips. Earlier in the month, TSMC <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tsmc-sales-ai-tools-chips/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a> higher sales than expected amid increased demand for AI tools and applications. Bloomberg calculations revealed that the company’s Q2 sales for June were NT$156.4 billion. Meanwhile, analysts’ expectation was NT$476.2 billion. Like TSMC, global chipmakers are looking to take advantage of the AI boom.</p>
<h2>TSMC to Invest in Advanced Chip Packaging Plant amid AI Boom</h2>
<p>According to <a href="https://www.cna.com.tw/news/afe/202307250038.aspx" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Taiwan’s official Central News Agency</a>, “the rapid growth of the artificial intelligence (AI) market has driven a surge in demand for TSMC’s advanced packaging”. The company is responding to the market demand by investing billions of dollars in the plant in Tongluo Science Park, Taiwan. By the side, the investment also creates up to 1,500 local job opportunities. The report added:</p>
<blockquote><p>“ At present, the management authority has officially issued a letter to approve the land lease application of TSMC Tongluo Science Park, and arranged a land lease briefing.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Before now, Goldman Sachs analysts raised their target on TSMC to NT$700, signaling their confidence in the company&#8217;s future performance. Evelyn Yu and Bruce Lu said they see the semiconductor manufacturer as the “key enabler” among other semi-coverage. The analysts referred to TSMC’s “leadership stance in leading-edge nodes and advanced packaging technology&#8221;.</p>
<p>While presenting the <a href="https://investor.tsmc.com/english/encrypt/files/encrypt_file/qr/phase4_reports/2023-07/2e2a9800157e3792623694196d1d71504313c375/2Q23ManagementReport.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Q2 earnings report</a>, C.C. Wei, the CEO of TSMC, spoke about the company’s performance with AI. He revealed that TSMC is recording solid demand for AI and noted that it has no problem in supporting the front-end part. However, the manufacturer is experiencing “some very tight capacity” on the advanced packaging side. Notably, the packaging stage is one of the final steps in semiconductor production. This is when the chips are placed in protective cases, creating connections needed for electronic devices.</p>
<p>Furthermore, fingers are crossed on if chip-related equipment manufacturers will benefit from the TSMC investment in an advanced chip packaging plant in Taiwan. The Central News Agency said the market is optimistic that the likes of Xinyun, Wanrun, and Hongsu will benefit from the operation of equipment factories.</p>
<p>TSMC recorded its first profit decline since 2019 during the second quarter. This is because companies that stockpiled during the pandemic are now struggling with excess processors as customers cut down on electronics expenses.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/dogecoin-price-twitter-x/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tsmc-ai-2-9b-investment-chip/">TSMC to Capitalize on AI Boom with $2.9B Investment in Advanced Chip Packaging Plant</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tsmc-ai-2-9b-investment-chip/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dogecoin Price Surges after Elon Musk Rebrands Twitter to X</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/dogecoin-price-twitter-x/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/dogecoin-price-twitter-x/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Babafemi Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 09:36:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[doge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogecoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[linda yaccarino]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[twitter]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[x]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=264180</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/dogecoin-price-twitter-x/">Dogecoin Price Surges after Elon Musk Rebrands Twitter to X</a></p>
<p>The rebranding of Twitter as X is part of Musk’s vision to create an “everything app” like WeChat.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/dogecoin-price-twitter-x/">Dogecoin Price Surges after Elon Musk Rebrands Twitter to X</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/dogecoin-price-twitter-x/">Dogecoin Price Surges after Elon Musk Rebrands Twitter to X</a></p>

<p>The price of meme token Dogecoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/dogecoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">DOGE</a>) soared to its highest in recent times following a surprise announcement by Twitter owner Elon Musk. Musk triggered the surge when he announced plans to change the Twitter name to X. DOGE surged by 10% in the past 24 hours, <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/dogecoin" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">according to CoinGecko data</a>.</p>
<h2>Dogecoin’s Rise in Popularity</h2>
<p>Dogecoin was created in 2013 as an internet meme token. Dogecoin’s popularity has grown over the years, thanks to its loyal fan base and celebrity endorsements, including from <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/elon-musk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Elon Musk</a>.</p>
<p>Musk has always been a vocal supporter of Dogecoin, calling it the future of currency. In April, Musk replaced the Twitter logo with the Dogecoin logo briefly and sparked a 30% spike in the price of the asset. He also teased the possibility of DOGE payments for Twitter’s premium service subscription.</p>
<p>Because it has no real utility, experts warn that dogecoin is highly volatile and risky and that investors should be cautious before buying it. Should X allow DOGE as a means of payment, everything about the token could change.</p>
<h2>Dogecoin Price Speculations Fanned by Musk</h2>
<p>Given Musk’s history with the meme token, it didn’t take long for the Twitter rebrand announcement to fuel speculations about DOGE. Since the token is already accepted as a form of payment at Tesla, analysts believe X could also do the same.</p>
<p>Real Vision CEO Raoul Pal said:</p>
<blockquote>
<p>“He will use crypto to be able to make global payments for creators, etc. My guess is he uses Doge.”</p>
</blockquote>
<p>“The speculation is that advertisers could be able to pay DOGE for ads and for other uses on Twitter,” Kryptomon Chief Marketing Officer Tomer Nuni explained.</p>
<p>To broaden the speculation, some users pointed out the X and D in Elon Musk’s profile location. They conclude that while the X refers to the Twitter rebrand, the D could be a reference to Dogecoin. Notably, much of the speculative moves are happening on UpBit, which is known for attracting speculative plays.</p>
<h2>Twitter to Morph into an Everything App</h2>
<p>Meanwhile, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-risks-logo-letter-x/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">the rebranding of Twitter as X</a> is part of Musk’s vision to create an “everything app” like WeChat. The app is expected to offer various services such as audio, video, messaging, payments, and banking.</p>
<p>According to Twitter CEO Linda Yaccarino, users should expect more features and innovations with the rebrand to X. She noted that the company was “just getting started”.</p>
<p>Already, Musk has purchased the X.com domain, which now redirects to Twitter. He has also asked Twitter users to submit their logo suggestions.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/blackrock-asia-bitcoin-etf/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/dogecoin-price-twitter-x/">Dogecoin Price Surges after Elon Musk Rebrands Twitter to X</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/dogecoin-price-twitter-x/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4132 metric#misses=43 metric#hit-ratio=99.0 metric#bytes=1120553 metric#prefetches=203 metric#store-reads=22 metric#store-writes=3 metric#store-hits=210 metric#store-misses=4 metric#sql-queries=35 metric#ms-total=93.31 metric#ms-cache=5.20 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.2167 metric#ms-cache-ratio=5.6 -->