<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 14:19:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Crypto spot trading volume rose 16% to $575 billion in June: CCData</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-spot-trading-volume-rose-16-to-575-billion-in-june-ccdata/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-spot-trading-volume-rose-16-to-575-billion-in-june-ccdata/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 14:19:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Derivatives]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-spot-trading-volume-rose-16-to-575-billion-in-june-ccdata/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Spot trading volume across centralised exchanges rose 16.4% to $575 billion in June, the first time volumes rose in three months. Derivatives trading volume on CEXs also rose, with the month seeing a 13.7% spike to $2.13 trillion. Binance saw a decline in both spot and derivatives volumes as OKX registered an increase. According to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-spot-trading-volume-rose-16-to-575-billion-in-june-ccdata/">Crypto spot trading volume rose 16% to $575 billion in June: CCData</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Spot trading volume across centralised exchanges rose 16.4% to $575 billion in June, the first time volumes rose in three months.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Derivatives trading volume on CEXs also rose, with the month seeing a 13.7% spike to $2.13 trillion.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Binance saw a decline in both spot and derivatives volumes as OKX registered an increase.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">According to the latest &ldquo;Exchange Review&rdquo;&nbsp;<a href="https://ccdata.io/reports/exchange-review-june-2023" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>report</u></a> by research and data platform CCData shows that the spot volumes jumped 16.4% to $575 billion in June as the crypto market experienced increased volatility over the month.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Meanwhile, the combined CEX volumes across spot and <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/derivatives/">derivatives</a> markets hit $2.7 trillion. The monthly trading volume for the two metrics rose 14.2%, while it was 13.7% for derivatives as volumes hit $2.13 trillion &ndash; the first increase for derivatives trading volume in three months.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Crypto?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Crypto</a> trading volumes in June rose for the first time in 3 months, following BlackRock &amp; other spot <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24BTC&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$BTC</a> ETF proposals.</p>
<p>&#128200;As per our Exchange Review, spot &amp; derivative trading on centralised exchanges rose 14% to $2.71tn.</p>
<p>Full Story by <a href="https://twitter.com/CoinDesk?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@CoinDesk</a> &#128071;<a href="https://t.co/5OVY6fwE8c">https://t.co/5OVY6fwE8c</a></p>
<p>&mdash; CCData (@CCData_io) <a href="https://twitter.com/CCData_io/status/1676575783261708294?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 5, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Positive news fuel crypto trading activity</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The spike in volatility was fueled by the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC)&rsquo;s lawsuit against leading exchanges <a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/binance/">Binance</a> and Coinbase.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Also key to this was the positivity that greeted the filing of spot Bitcoin exchange traded funds (ETFs) by major Wall Street asset managers BlackRock and Fidelity, and the launch of Citadel backed crypto exchange EDX Markets.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>The increase in the market share of spot trading volume hints at the healthy accumulation of crypto following recent positive news in the markets</em>,&rdquo;CCData researchers note in the report.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This outlook was indeed visible in the market. Increased trading activity saw Bitcoin price shoot to a new year-to-date high above $31k, while altcoins like Litecoin and Bitcoin Cash rode the optimistic outlook to break above critical resistance levels. [<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-cash-surges-as-bch-hits-3-month-high-heres-why/">Read more</a>]</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Binance&rsquo;s spot and derivatives volumes decline</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Despite the above increases, the quarterly spot trading volumes on CEXs still hover near &ldquo;historically low levels.&rdquo; For instance, quarterly spot volumes for Q2, 2023 were the lowest since the fourth quarter of 2019.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Also notably, the spot market share of Binance declined 41.6% in June to see the leading exchange record a fourth consecutive month of declines, and its lowest market share since August 2022. And although Binance continues to dominate the crypto derivatives trading market with $1.21 trillion, it fell 56.8% in June.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/okx-review-a-one-stop-platform-for-crypto-defi-dapps-nfts-and-gamefi/">OKX</a>, which is the world&rsquo;s second-largest derivatives exchange, recorded a 44.9% increase in its trading volume to hit $416 billion in June. The crypto exchange&rsquo;s market share has now grown to 19.5%, its highest level since April 2022.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-spot-trading-volume-rose-16-to-575-billion-in-june-ccdata/">Crypto spot trading volume rose 16% to $575 billion in June: CCData</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-spot-trading-volume-rose-16-to-575-billion-in-june-ccdata/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Saxo Bank ordered to dispose of crypto holdings by Denmark&#8217;s DFSA</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/saxo-bank-ordered-to-dispose-of-crypto-holdings-by-denmarks-dfsa/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/saxo-bank-ordered-to-dispose-of-crypto-holdings-by-denmarks-dfsa/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 13:09:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/saxo-bank-ordered-to-dispose-of-crypto-holdings-by-denmarks-dfsa/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The DFSA ordered the Saxo Bank to dispose of its own holdings in crypto. The Financial regulators in Denmark have said that local banks are not allowed to hold crypto to hedge against trading risks. DFSA&#8217;s order concerning Saxo Bank&#8217;s crypto holdings will have little impact on the bank&#8217;s business. Local investment bank Saxo Bank [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/saxo-bank-ordered-to-dispose-of-crypto-holdings-by-denmarks-dfsa/">Saxo Bank ordered to dispose of crypto holdings by Denmark&#8217;s DFSA</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>The DFSA ordered the Saxo Bank to dispose of its own holdings in crypto.</li>
<li>The Financial regulators in Denmark have said that local banks are not allowed to hold crypto to hedge against trading risks.</li>
<li>DFSA&rsquo;s order concerning Saxo Bank&rsquo;s crypto holdings will have little impact on the bank&rsquo;s business.</li>
</ul>
<p>Local investment bank Saxo Bank has received a formal order from the Danish Financial Supervisory Authority (DFSA) directing it to dispose of its own cryptocurrency holdings.</p>
<p>According to the regulator, Saxo Bank&rsquo;s cryptocurrency activity &ldquo;lies outside of the legal business area of financial institutions,&rdquo; citing section 24 of the Danish Financial Business Act.</p>
<h2>Cryptocurrency service providers in Denmark</h2>
<p>Danish financial regulators are going after cryptocurrency service providers, saying that local banks are not allowed to hold cryptocurrencies as a form of risk management.</p>
<p>Pinpointing why it singled out Saxo Bank, the DFSA claims that Saxo Bank gives its customers the option to <a href="https://coinjournal.net/cryptocurrencies/trade/">trade a variety of cryptocurrencies</a> on its platform. The regulator stated that the company also provides a number of exchange-traded funds and exchange-traded notes that are linked to cryptocurrencies, adding that &ldquo;it is possible to speculate on crypto assets.&rdquo;</p>
<p>The DFSA also noted that Saxo Bank has its own portfolio of bitcoin assets, which is kept as a hedge to counteract the market risk connected to the bank&rsquo;s cryptocurrency products. The regulator cited Annex 1 of the Financial Business Act in stating that dealing in crypto-assets does not appear to be under the lawful business scope of Danish financial institutions.</p>
<p>Based on the above reasons, the DFSA stated:</p>
<p><em>&ldquo;Based on the above, Saxo Bank&rsquo;s trading in crypto assets for its own account is found to be outside the legal business area of financial institutions. On this basis, Saxo Bank is ordered to dispose of its own holdings of crypto assets.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p>It will be interesting to see how Saxo Bank will move ahead with its crypto offering seeing that their customers do not own underlying cryptocurrencies but instead buys financial products that follow the price of cryptocurrencies.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/saxo-bank-ordered-to-dispose-of-crypto-holdings-by-denmarks-dfsa/">Saxo Bank ordered to dispose of crypto holdings by Denmark&#8217;s DFSA</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/saxo-bank-ordered-to-dispose-of-crypto-holdings-by-denmarks-dfsa/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto prices rising and sentiment flipping but liquidity &#038; macro picture are ominous</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-prices-rising-and-sentiment-flipping-but-liquidity-macro-picture-are-ominous/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-prices-rising-and-sentiment-flipping-but-liquidity-macro-picture-are-ominous/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dan Ashmore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 12:15:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-prices-rising-and-sentiment-flipping-but-liquidity-macro-picture-are-ominous/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key Takeaways Crypto prices are rising sharply, with Bitcoin up 20% in the last three weeks The filing of a number of high-profile Bitcoin ETFs has pushed optimism in the market Under the hood, liquidity remains low and some worrisome trends emerge, however The regulatory woes are still present, with Coinbase and Binance facing a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-prices-rising-and-sentiment-flipping-but-liquidity-macro-picture-are-ominous/">Crypto prices rising and sentiment flipping but liquidity &amp; macro picture are ominous</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2 dir="ltr">Key Takeaways</h2>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Crypto prices are rising sharply, with Bitcoin up 20% in the last three weeks</li>
<li dir="ltr">The filing of a number of high-profile Bitcoin ETFs has pushed optimism in the market</li>
<li dir="ltr">Under the hood, liquidity remains low and some worrisome trends emerge, however</li>
<li dir="ltr">The regulatory woes are still present, with Coinbase and Binance facing a murky future</li>
<li dir="ltr">The macro picture also remains uncertain, with the prospect of a lagged impact via tightening monetary policy looming large</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p dir="ltr">It wouldn&rsquo;t be like crypto markets to get overly excited. In the past couple of weeks, positivity has returned to the space, led by the seminal filings for a Bitcoin spot ETF by two of the world&rsquo;s biggest asset managers, Blackrock and Fidelity.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Additionally, Fidelity were among a cohort of large trad-fi operators, including Schwab and Citadel, to back the new exchange EDX, which offers trading for Bitcoin, Ether, Litecoin and Bitcoin Cash.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin is up 20% in the last three weeks, breaching past the $30,000 mark, while Ether is up 16% in the same timeframe, approaching the $2,000 mark once more. A glance at the <a href="https://alternative.me/crypto/fear-and-greed-index/"><u>Fear and Greed</u></a> index, an interesting metric which gauges overall sentiment in the space, shows it is markedly in the &ldquo;greed&rdquo; sector with a score of 61 (0 represents extreme fear, 100 represents extreme greed).&nbsp;</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/05/1688557574714-e61e6782-a3ef-4b4a-9f4f-a101fbbe3e8d.png" style="width: 600px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="600" height="535">And yet, a look under the hood betrays some concern. Firstly, if the filing of the ETFs is the reason for the recent ramp, as it appears to be, is a 20% jump justified? The SEC has declared the recent filings as &ldquo;inadequate&rdquo;, according to the WSJ, informing the Nasdaq and CBOE (who filed the paperwork on behalf of the asset managers) that there is not enough detail with respect to &ldquo;surveillance-sharing agreements&rdquo;. The SEC had previously said that sponsors of a Bitcoin trust are required to enter into a surveillance-sharing agreement with a regulated market of significant size.</p>
<p dir="ltr">While the applications can be updated and refiled (and the CBOE did indeed refile theirs since, with Nasdaq likely soon to follow) the development hints at how difficult it has been to get the much-coveted spot ETF over the line. There is no guarantee that these are approved, despite the big names involved &ndash; the SEC even rejected an application from Fidelity in the past, turning it away in January 2022.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">In truth, it feels inevitable that Bitcoin spot ETFs will one day be traded freely, but a 20% jump on a mere filing in the last couple of weeks is a massive ramp when considering what else has happened in the space, and the state of markets, which we will delve into now.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Liquidity</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Liquidity continues to lag, a factor which cannot be overstated &ndash; and indeed one which the eventual approval of spot ETFs should help.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Looking at centralised exchanges per data from Kaiko as we close out the second quarter of 2023, volume over the past three months was lower again, coming in at the lowest number since 2020, before Bitcoin and crypto embarked on their inexorable price rises and took the financial world by storm.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/05/1688557591169-492d05de-add9-47cf-86fa-47539ff38e28.png" style="width: 600px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="600" height="324"></p>
<p dir="ltr">But with lower liquidity, moves to both the upside and downside are exacerbated. This has perhaps contributed to Bitcoin&rsquo;s steep rise in the past few weeks, and also year-to-date, with it currently up 83%.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">But liquidity and volumes being so low should be alarming for market participants. Much of the inroads made during the pandemic, with regard to Bitcoin taking its place next to bona-fide asset classes from a trading perspective, have slowed if not reversed &ndash; at least from a liquidity perspective.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">As further evidence of this, in the below chart, I&rsquo;ve presented the total balance of stablecoins across exchanges, which has fallen a staggering 60% in the past six months &ndash; an outflow of $26 billion.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14290288">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">Having said that, there are pockets of optimism which hint at a brighter future if/when these spot ETFs do get approved. Looking at volume in derivatives markets, it has been rather consistent. In fact, it is markedly up on the second half of 2022. Perhaps this means the spot market has been greater affected by the regulatory crackdown. Either way, it&rsquo;s a less gruesome picture than what we are seeing in spot markets.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/05/1688557591126-4dee794c-aab5-4225-8275-f59e55c418c3.png" style="width: 600px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="600" height="327"></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Regulation</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Right now, with regard to crypto-specific risk, it really all comes back to regulation. We have discussed the ETF filings, but June also brought two seminal moments: formal charges brought against Coinbase and Binance.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The two cases are extremely different, mind you. Binance&rsquo;s lawsuit <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/opinion-binance-sued-by-sec-an-inevitable-but-ominous-day-for-crypto/"><u>could not be less surprising</u></a>, with the exchange constantly skirting guidelines and laws. The charges amount to a laundry list of different offences, including trading against customers, manipulating trade volume, encouraging users to circumvent geographical restrictions and securities violations.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">It is the latter charge which is the centre of the suit against Coinbase, however, and the most pivotal of the lot. It is also why the Coinbase suit is <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-and-cryptos-fate-hangs-by-a-string-a-deep-dive/"><u>far more intriguing</u></a>. Do not forget that the allegations are coming from the SEC, the same body which presided over Coinbase&rsquo;s IPO in April 2021. Why did the SEC let an unregistered securities exchange float on a US stock exchange? You tell me.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">But let&rsquo;s get back to the point: what this all means for crypto markets. While Bitcoin appears to be carving its own place out in the eyes of the law, a slew of other tokens were named as securities by the SEC. Despite this, they have risen sharply since off the Bitcoin ETF news. Does this make sense?&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Conclusion</h2>
<p dir="ltr">At the end of the day, crypto is going to crypto. Prices move, and trying to pinpoint reasons is often a fool&rsquo;s errand. The last month, however, feels like we have seen an extremely aggressive price rise despite some bad news on the regulatory front.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Additionally, the macro picture has not changed much, even with the pause at the last Fed meeting. Fed chair Jerome Powell&rsquo;s comments made it clear that this was a pause rather than an about-turn in policy.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;Looking ahead, nearly all committee participants view it as likely that some further rate increases will be appropriate this year,&rdquo; Powell said when announcing the pause.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The market believes him. I backed out probabilities from Fed futures in the next chart, which show that there is currently an 86% chance of a 25 bps hike at the next Fed meeting in three weeks time, with only a 14% chance of rates being left unchanged again. I have presented this next to the same probabilities conveyed by the market exactly a month ago (Bitcoin is up 20% in the time since), showing softer forecasts do not explain the sharp price (the chance of no hike has actually come down).&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14349271">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">As I said, crypto going to crypto. But with assets as notoriously volatile as what we see in this sector, it would be wise to stop and think about whether the sudden wave of positivity is justified. When considering the liquidity picture and the regulatory trouble, there are plenty of reasons to hesitate.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Then when one layers in the macro picture, the picture becomes murkier again. Let us not forget that we are in the midst of one of the swiftest rate hiking cycles in modern history, with rates rising all the way from zero to above 5%, and the prospect of them rising even further later this month.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Monetary policy operates with a lag, and the scale of that tightening is enormous. Sentiment may feel like it has flipped dramatically, but there is a long road ahead yet.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-prices-rising-and-sentiment-flipping-but-liquidity-macro-picture-are-ominous/">Crypto prices rising and sentiment flipping but liquidity &amp; macro picture are ominous</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-prices-rising-and-sentiment-flipping-but-liquidity-macro-picture-are-ominous/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance suspends transfers for several Multichain-bridged tokens</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-suspends-transfers-for-several-multichain-bridged-tokens/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-suspends-transfers-for-several-multichain-bridged-tokens/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 11:45:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-suspends-transfers-for-several-multichain-bridged-tokens/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Binance will cease deposit and withdrawals support for Multichain-bridged tokens Polkastarter (POLS), Alchemy Pay (ACH), Alpaca Finance (ALPACA) and Travala (AVA. The tokens are minted on BNB Smart Chain, Fantom, Ethereum and Avalanche C-Chain. The exchange says the suspension follows an earlier one taken in May after an incident involving Multichain-bridged tokens. Binance is suspending [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-suspends-transfers-for-several-multichain-bridged-tokens/">Binance suspends transfers for several Multichain-bridged tokens</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Binance will cease deposit and withdrawals support for Multichain-bridged tokens Polkastarter (POLS), Alchemy Pay (ACH), Alpaca Finance (ALPACA) and Travala (AVA.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The tokens are minted on BNB Smart Chain, Fantom, Ethereum and Avalanche C-Chain.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The exchange says the suspension follows an earlier one taken in May after an incident involving Multichain-bridged tokens.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/binance/">Binance</a> is suspending deposits and withdrawals for several tokens linked to cross-chain router protocol Multichain, according to an <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/support/announcement/updates-on-the-suspension-of-deposits-withdrawals-for-multichain-bridged-tokens-3c7d279dd37043bd8290ac718b5c08a4" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">announcement</a> the crypto exchange published on Wednesday.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The crypto behemoth states that the suspension of the Multichain-bridged tokens will take effect on July 7 starting at 00:00 UTC and will last &ldquo;until further notice.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The price of <a href="https://coinjournal.net/multichain/">Multichain</a> was down nearly 6% in the past 24 hours and traded near $3.14 at the time of writing.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Binance?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Binance</a> will suspend deposits and withdrawals for a number of Multichain-bridged tokens from July 7, 00:00 UTC until further notice.</p>
<p>More details here &#128071;<a href="https://t.co/CL7V8UeT9l">https://t.co/CL7V8UeT9l</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Binance (@binance) <a href="https://twitter.com/binance/status/1676493768856305664?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 5, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Polkastarter (POLS), Alchemy Pay (ACH) among affected tokens</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Binance says in the notice to users that the deposits and withdrawals pause will impact different networks, including BNB Smart Chain, Fantom, Ethereum and Avalanche C-Chain. In particular, Multichain-bridged tokens that users can no longer transfer via the above chains are:</p>
<p dir="ltr">Polkastarter (POLS), Alchemy Pay (ACH), and SuperVerse (SUPER) and Harvest Finance (FARM) on the BNB Smart Chain; Alpaca Finance (ALPACA) and Beefy.Finance (BIFI) tokens that are minted on Fantom Network; Spell Token (SPELL) on Avalanche C-Chain and Travala (AVA) on the Ethereum bridge.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Although the Binance did not provide specific details on why its ceasing support for the above bridge tokens, it highlights that the move as related to the earlier suspension of several Multichain bridge tokens.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">On May 24, the crypto giant announced a temporary suspension to multiple tokens after an incident involving Multichain bridge transfers.</p>
<p dir="ltr">While deposits and withdrawals for the above tokens are suspended on Binance via the listed chains, users can still access these transfers via other Binance-supported network, the exchange reiterated.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-suspends-transfers-for-several-multichain-bridged-tokens/">Binance suspends transfers for several Multichain-bridged tokens</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-suspends-transfers-for-several-multichain-bridged-tokens/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>AAVE hikes as holders vote on converting 1,600ETH into rETH and wstETH</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/aave-hikes-as-holders-vote-on-converting-1600eth-into-reth-and-wsteth/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/aave-hikes-as-holders-vote-on-converting-1600eth-into-reth-and-wsteth/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 10:34:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Aave News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/aave-hikes-as-holders-vote-on-converting-1600eth-into-reth-and-wsteth/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Aave holders are voting on a governance proposal to convert 1,600 ether (ETH) to wstETH and rETH. Aave currently earns a yield of 1.69% from the ETH that it has staked on the Aave v2 platform. At press time all the 252,152 votes cast were in favor of the proposal. AAVE&#8217;s Bull Run has gained [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/aave-hikes-as-holders-vote-on-converting-1600eth-into-reth-and-wsteth/">AAVE hikes as holders vote on converting 1,600ETH into rETH and wstETH</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul class="decimal_type">
<li>Aave holders are voting on a governance proposal to convert 1,600 ether (ETH) to wstETH and rETH.</li>
<li>Aave currently earns a yield of 1.69% from the ETH that it has staked on the Aave v2 platform.</li>
<li>At press time all the 252,152 votes cast were in favor of the proposal.</li>
</ul>
<p>AAVE&rsquo;s Bull Run has gained momentum as AAVE holders vote on a governance proposal titled &ldquo;<a href="https://app.aave.com/governance/proposal/?proposalId=261">Treasury Managemet &ndash; Acquire wstETH &amp; rETH</a>.&rdquo; The proposal seeks to convert 1,600 ETH to equal amounts of wstETH and rETH to be held in the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/what-is-ethereum/">Ethereum</a> Collector Contract.</p>
<p><a href="https://coinjournal.net/aave/">AAVE token</a> has gained in excess of 26% in the last seven days and today&rsquo;s surge confirms a long-term bullish trend. The token has hit a daily high of $80.28 today although it had pulled back to $76.92 at the time of writing.</p>
<h2>Why convert the ETH to wstETH and rETH?</h2>
<p>The majority of the Aave DAO seems to be in agreement seeing that all the voters had voted in support of the proposal at press time. 252,152 votes have been cast so far out of the 320,000 votes required for the proposal to be actioned. But what is the catch?</p>
<p><a href="https://coinjournal.net/aave/what-is-aave/">Aave</a> is currently the third-largest DeFi protocol and has a total value locked of $6 billion. The Aave DAO currently holds 1,786.51 awETH and 104.548 ETH in the Collector Contract. The awETH deposit yield in Aave v2 earns 1.69%, compared to the 3.8% and 3.13% that Aave DAO would earn if it held wstETH and rETH respectively.</p>
<p>If passed all the unproductive ETH balance, along with aWETH (v2 and v3) will be converted into the same amounts of wstETH and rETH for higher staking yields.</p>
<p>Besides the higher yields, the wrapped staked ether (wstETH) and rocket pool ether (rETH), which are liquid staking derivatives, will allow Aave to stake the tokens for a yield whilst still retaining liquidity.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/aave-hikes-as-holders-vote-on-converting-1600eth-into-reth-and-wsteth/">AAVE hikes as holders vote on converting 1,600ETH into rETH and wstETH</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/aave-hikes-as-holders-vote-on-converting-1600eth-into-reth-and-wsteth/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Singapore bank DBS allows e-CNY settlements</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/singapore-bank-dbs-allows-e-cny-settlements/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/singapore-bank-dbs-allows-e-cny-settlements/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 09:27:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[China]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Singapore]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/singapore-bank-dbs-allows-e-cny-settlements/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The DBS bank has started an e-CNY collection platform. The platform will enable automated settlement of e-CNY into businesses&#8217; CNY bank deposit accounts. The bank is participating in Project Guardian, a project for testing asset tokenization and DeFi for traditional banks. According to a Wednesday announcement, clients of the Singaporean bank DBS can now receive [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/singapore-bank-dbs-allows-e-cny-settlements/">Singapore bank DBS allows e-CNY settlements</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>The DBS bank has started an e-CNY collection platform.</li>
<li>The platform will enable automated settlement of e-CNY into businesses&rsquo; CNY bank deposit accounts.</li>
<li>The bank is participating in Project Guardian, a project for testing asset tokenization and DeFi for traditional banks.</li>
</ul>
<p>According to a Wednesday announcement, clients of the Singaporean bank DBS can now receive payments in e-CNY, the digital currency issued by the Chinese central bank.</p>
<p>The new platform enables automated e-CNY settlement into business customers&rsquo; bank deposit accounts. According to DBS, at least one client has already completed a transaction using this platform.</p>
<h2>Singapore&rsquo;s Project Guardian</h2>
<p>Besides taking part in experiments aimed at building the infrastructure required to issue a programmable digital Singapore dollar, DBS is also taking part in Project Guardian, a project launched by the Monetary Authority of Singapore to test asset tokenization and <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/defi/">decentralized finance (DeFi)</a> for traditional banks.</p>
<p>Project Guardian involved the DeFi lending platform Aave, the decentralized exchange Uniswap, and the Ethereum scaling system Polygon. The project will also involve several traditional banks including Singapore&rsquo;s DBS Bank, <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/jpmorgan-secures-defi-partnership-in-singapore-as-crypto-giants-leave-for-dubai/">US-based JPMorgan</a>, and Japan&rsquo;s SBI Digital in addition to Marketnode, a digital asset platform built by the Singapore Exchange (SGX) and Temasek.</p>
<p>The first phase of the Project Guardian testing involved trades in tokenized Singapore dollars (SGD), Japanese yen (JPY), Japanese government bonds, and Singapore government securities and was done using Polygon, Aave and Uniswap.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/singapore-bank-dbs-allows-e-cny-settlements/">Singapore bank DBS allows e-CNY settlements</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/singapore-bank-dbs-allows-e-cny-settlements/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alex The Doge (ALEX) Presale Reports 14 Million Tokens Sold</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/alex-the-doge-alex-presale-reports-14-million-tokens-sold/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/alex-the-doge-alex-presale-reports-14-million-tokens-sold/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire &#160;]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 17:20:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=145163</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Frankfurt, Germany, July 4th, 2023, Chainwire Alex The Doge (ALEX), a memecoin designed to transform the GameFi ecosystem, has reported strong demand for its presale. The presale, which is currently ongoing, gives the crypto community their first opportunity to purchase ALEX tokens. Following completion of the token sale, ALEX will launch on decentralized exchanges. ALEX [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/alex-the-doge-alex-presale-reports-14-million-tokens-sold/">Alex The Doge (ALEX) Presale Reports 14 Million Tokens Sold</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Frankfurt, Germany, July 4th, 2023, Chainwire</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://alexthedoge.live/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Alex The Doge (ALEX)</a>, a memecoin designed to transform the GameFi ecosystem, has reported strong demand for its presale. The presale, which is currently ongoing, gives the crypto community their first opportunity to purchase ALEX tokens. Following completion of the token sale, ALEX will launch on decentralized exchanges.</p>
<p>ALEX aims to combine the fun of memecoins with the utility of decentralized finance (DeFi) and play-to-earn gaming. The project has garnered significant attention from crypto enthusiasts, with more than 13.5 million ALEX tokens sold during the presale so far.</p>
<p>ALEX is built on Polygon, a blockchain network known for its scalability, speed, and security. By leveraging the capabilities of Polygon, ALEX is creating a digital gaming world called the Miracle Verse. This innovative ecosystem will empower users with play-to-earn gaming opportunities, social trading, and DeFi activities. With its gamified approach and extensive suite of products under development, ALEX aims to differentiate itself from other memecoins and gain a foothold in the market.</p>
<p>The project operates at the intersection of GameFi and SocialFi, the latter term describing the creation of strong communities that are united by shared interests and common goals. An extensive roadmap gives interested parties an idea of what to expect from the ALEX ecosystem as it takes shape, with the launch of the Miracle Verse sure to be an eagerly anticipated event.</p>
<p>Through combining the fun factor synonymous with memecoins and the utility built into decentralized finance applications, the team behind Alex The Doge believes it has found a winning formula. The completion of the ALEX presale will set the stage for everything that comes next, starting with the token&rsquo;s DEX debut as Alex The Doge goes live.</p>
<p><strong>Join the Alex The Doge (ALEX) presale using the links below:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Website: <a href="https://alexthedoge.live/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://alexthedoge.live/</a></li>
<li>Telegram: <a href="https://t.me/alexthedoge" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://t.me/alexthedoge</a></li>
<li>Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/AlexTheDoge_p2e" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://twitter.com/AlexTheDoge_p2e</a></li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Contact</strong></p>
<p>Community Lead<br>
Zack Anderson<br>
Alex The Doge<br>
support@alexthedoge.live</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/alex-the-doge-alex-presale-reports-14-million-tokens-sold/">Alex The Doge (ALEX) Presale Reports 14 Million Tokens Sold</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/alex-the-doge-alex-presale-reports-14-million-tokens-sold/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cryptocurrencies are back in fashion as the total crypto market cap keeps rising</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/cryptocurrencies-are-back-in-fashion-as-the-total-crypto-market-cap-keeps-rising/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/cryptocurrencies-are-back-in-fashion-as-the-total-crypto-market-cap-keeps-rising/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mircea Vasiu]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 16:46:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/cryptocurrencies-are-back-in-fashion-as-the-total-crypto-market-cap-keeps-rising/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The total cryptocurrency market capitalization grew by more than 50% in the last six months Investors are optimistic as Bitcoin&#8217;s price holds near the yearly high Ethereum, Litecoin, and Ripple have followed Bitcoin higher The first half of the trading year is behind us, and one of the most notable developments is the increase in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/cryptocurrencies-are-back-in-fashion-as-the-total-crypto-market-cap-keeps-rising/">Cryptocurrencies are back in fashion as the total crypto market cap keeps rising</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>The total cryptocurrency market capitalization grew by more than 50% in the last six months</li>
<li>Investors are optimistic as Bitcoin&rsquo;s price holds near the yearly high</li>
<li>Ethereum, Litecoin, and Ripple have followed Bitcoin higher</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p>The first half of the trading year is behind us, and one of the most notable developments is the increase in the total crypto market capitalization. Following 2022, when many crypto investors got fed up with industry scandals and left, the 2023 rally looks like the start of a new bullish market.</p>
<p>The performance is even more impressive, given that the US dollar is trading with a mixed tone against its fiat rivals.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Investors&rsquo; renewed interest in cryptocurrencies led to the total market capitalization growing by more than 50% in the year&rsquo;s first half. Only in the last week, the market grew by more than 3%, and investors are optimistic because Bitcoin, the leading cryptocurrency, holds near the yearly high.&nbsp;</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/04/1688487752291-bb23ca36-fe26-4844-80e1-624cf1e8b9bc.jpg" style="width: 1800px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="1800" height="387"></p>
<h2>Ethereum, Litecoin, and Ripple have followed Bitcoin higher</h2>
<p>Bitcoin is the main reason why investors are optimistic about the cryptocurrency industry despite the ongoing scandals, frauds, and lawsuits. In the end, all that matters for market watchers is that Bitcoin&rsquo;s price holds close to the yearly high, despite rallying in 2023 by over +85%.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Therefore, the path of least resistance in the year&rsquo;s second half seems to be the upside.&nbsp;</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/04/1688489059236-0fc4fc27-7dad-45c0-983a-c87a2b6ea411.jpg" style="width: 1800px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="1800" height="471"></p>
<p><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/?exchange=CRYPTO" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Bitcoin chart by TradingView</a></p>
<p>Not all currencies performed like Bitcoin, though. For instance, Dogecoin is flat on the year, up by about +0.3% in the first six months of 2023. This is a huge divergence from what Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies did (e.g., Ethereum, Litecoin, Ripple), and it reflects the crypto investors&rsquo; concentration in a few cryptocurrencies.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Moving forward in the year&rsquo;s second half, crypto investors might want to watch the developments in the traditional currency market. More precisely, what will the Fed do with the funds rate?&nbsp;</p>
<p>If the US dollar loses ground against its rival fiat currencies in the next six months, Bitcoin and the other leading cryptocurrencies are well positioned to rally some more. As the Fed paused the rate hikes in June, one should embrace the possibility of the current funds rate being the terminal one for this tightening cycle.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/cryptocurrencies-are-back-in-fashion-as-the-total-crypto-market-cap-keeps-rising/">Cryptocurrencies are back in fashion as the total crypto market cap keeps rising</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/cryptocurrencies-are-back-in-fashion-as-the-total-crypto-market-cap-keeps-rising/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitget debuts in lending with the launch of ‘Crypto Loans’</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitget-launches-crypto-loans/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wajeeh Khan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 16:20:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitget]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=145146</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitget launched its native &#8220;Crypto Loans&#8221; product on Tuesday. Digital lending is expected to advance at a CAGR of 20.5%. Singapore and Thailand have recently banned crypto lending. Bitget &#8211; a Seychelles-based digital assets trading platform launched &#8220;Crypto Loans&#8221; to debut in the lending space on Tuesday. Here&#8217;s what we know so far Its new [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitget-launches-crypto-loans/">Bitget debuts in lending with the launch of ‘Crypto Loans’</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitget launched its native &ldquo;Crypto Loans&rdquo; product on Tuesday.</li>
<li>Digital lending is expected to advance at a CAGR of 20.5%.</li>
<li>Singapore and Thailand have recently banned crypto lending.</li>
</ul>
<p>Bitget &ndash; a Seychelles-based digital assets trading platform launched &ldquo;Crypto Loans&rdquo; to debut in the lending space on Tuesday.</p>
<h2>Here&rsquo;s what we know so far</h2>
<p>Its new product will cater particularly to users that are not fully satisfied with the traditional credit institutions. According to Gracy Chen &ndash; the Managing Director of Bitget:</p>
<blockquote><p>Users now have the opportunity to stake less-demanded coins, enabling them to obtain loans in more liquid assets for investment purposes.</p></blockquote>
<p>Each loan, as per the <a href="https://www.bitget.com/blog/articles/12560603794357" target="_blank" rel="noopener">press release</a>, will be coupled with a specific interest rate. Bitget did not, however, reveal the cryptocurrencies that&rsquo;ll be eligible for Crypto Loans.</p>
<p>The news arrives only days after Bitget formally entered Turkey with a new website as part of its commitment to expand globally (<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitget-formally-enters-turkey-bitget-tr/">find out more</a>).</p>
<h2>Digital lending is seeing strong demand</h2>
<p>Digital lending is expected to grow at a compound annual rate of 20.5% between 2023 and 2032 after hitting the $8.5 billion mark last year which suggests strong demand. Chen also said today in the press release:</p>
<blockquote><p>Bitget&rsquo;s new product highlights flexibility of collateralized currency usage, enhancing capital utilization. Our flexible borrowing and repayment mechanism caters to needs of all users.</p></blockquote>
<p>The top crypto derivatives platform is entering the crypto lending sector at a time when multiple countries, including <a href="https://decrypt.co/147091/singapore-regulator-bans-crypto-exchanges-from-lending-staking-retail-investors/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Singapore</a> and <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/cryptocurrency/thailands-sec-bans-crypto-lending-demands-risk-warning-disclosure/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Thailand</a>, have banned crypto companies from issuing loans.</p>
<p>Bitget did not state in its press release whether the new service will be available in the United States.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitget-launches-crypto-loans/">Bitget debuts in lending with the launch of ‘Crypto Loans’</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
