<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
>

<channel>
	<title>CoinCu News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://coincu.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coincu.com</link>
	<description>Coin and Crypto Infomation Update</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 16:15:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/cropped-Screen-Shot-2022-05-31-at-14.56.39-32x32.png</url>
	<title>CoinCu News</title>
	<link>https://coincu.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Avalanche Foundation Announces $50 Million Allocation For Tokenized Asset Purchase </title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/205862-avalanche-foundation-50-million-allocation/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chubbi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 15:27:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Avalanche]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Avalanche blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[market]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=205862</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Avalanche Foundation is gearing up to invest up to $50 million in acquiring tokenized assets on its Layer-1 blockchain. <p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/205862-avalanche-foundation-50-million-allocation/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>Avalanche Foundation allocates $50 million for purchasing tokenized assets on its blockchain, promoting tokenization in sectors like stocks, credit, real estate, and commodities.</em></li>



<li><em>The initiative, called Avalanche Vista, aims to improve liquidity and demonstrate the benefits of blockchain-based asset tokenization, attracting interest from traditional players and fostering blockchain adoption in the financial landscape.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The Avalanche Foundation is gearing up to invest up to $50 million in acquiring tokenized assets on its Layer-1 blockchain.&nbsp;</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Avalanche-raises-230-million-from-Private-Sale-of-AVAX-Tokens.jpeg"><img decoding="async" width="600" height="315" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Avalanche-raises-230-million-from-Private-Sale-of-AVAX-Tokens.jpeg" alt="Avalanche Foundation Announces $50 Million Allocation For Tokenized Asset Purchase " class="wp-image-205868" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Avalanche-raises-230-million-from-Private-Sale-of-AVAX-Tokens.jpeg 600w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Avalanche-raises-230-million-from-Private-Sale-of-AVAX-Tokens-300x158.jpeg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" title="Avalanche Foundation Announces $50 Million Allocation For Tokenized Asset Purchase  1"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>Termed &#8220;Avalanche Vista,&#8221; this initiative seeks to showcase the potential of tokenization across diverse sectors, including stocks, credit, real estate, and commodities. Tokenization involves creating digital representations of real-world assets on a blockchain, providing a faster and more efficient way for companies to issue assets, individuals to own them, and everyone to transfer value.&nbsp;</p>



<p>John Wu, president of Ava Labs, the firm behind <a href="https://coincu.com/201985-oracle-redstone-data-dapps-avalanche-spruce/">Avalanche</a>, highlights the benefits of tokenization in revolutionizing traditional asset ownership and transfer processes. Avalanche has already established its presence in the asset tokenization space, having collaborated with KKR, a prominent U.S. investment management firm, to tokenize a portion of its private equity fund through digital asset securities firm Securitize.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/AVAX.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="640" height="367" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/AVAX.png" alt="Avalanche Foundation Announces $50 Million Allocation For Tokenized Asset Purchase " class="wp-image-205869" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/AVAX.png 640w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/AVAX-300x172.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px" title="Avalanche Foundation Announces $50 Million Allocation For Tokenized Asset Purchase  2"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>According to Wu, through various dealings with conventional market players, the liquidity aspect emerged as a critical challenge. In response, Avalanche aims to address this concern by allocating $50 million to bolster liquidity, aligning with the ongoing pipeline of tokenized assets and the amount required to enhance market liquidity.</p>



<p>Avalanche Vista&#8217;s $50 million investment reflects the foundation&#8217;s confidence in the potential growth and viability of tokenized assets. By showcasing the benefits of blockchain-based asset tokenization, the foundation hopes to attract more interest and participation from companies and individuals alike.</p>



<p>The move comes at a time when the cryptocurrency and blockchain industry is witnessing increasing interest from traditional finance sectors. As tokenization gains momentum, more assets from various industries are expected to undergo the process, unlocking new opportunities for investors and creating a more accessible and efficient financial ecosystem.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER: </em></strong><em>The Information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>



<p>Join us to keep track of news: <a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Chubbi</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Coincu News</strong></p>
<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/205862-avalanche-foundation-50-million-allocation/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ban-sao-cua-Final-Thumb-1-1-1024x731.jpg" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/jpeg" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Optimism Update: Building A Superchain Ecosystem With Layer 2 Solutions</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/205854-optimism-update-superchain/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Harold]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 15:11:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Knowledge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[base]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Layer 2]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OP Mainnet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OP Stack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[optimism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Optimistic Virtual Machine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SuperChain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Zora Network]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=205854</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Optimism rebrands to OP Mainnet, introducing the concept of a Superchain ecosystem comprising various Layer 2 solutions on the OP Stack.<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/205854-optimism-update-superchain/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>Optimism rebrands to OP Mainnet, introducing the concept of a Superchain ecosystem comprising various Layer 2 solutions on the OP Stack.</em></li>



<li><em>Key projects in the Superchain ecosystem include Coinbase&#8217;s Base and Zora Network, both utilizing OP Stack technology to enhance transaction speeds and reduce gas expenses for their users.</em></li>



<li><em>The development journey of Optimism toward Superchain has faced challenges but has resulted in a modular architecture and inter-chain communication, fostering blockchain interoperability and potential widespread adoption.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Recently, Optimism made a remarkable move when it announced its name change to OP Mainnet, thereby realizing the goal of turning the project into a &#8220;Superchain&#8221; network with many different Layer 2. Let&#8217;s learn about this topic in detail with <a href="https://twitter.com/Coincuofficial" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Coincu</a>.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1828.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="546" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1828-1024x546.png" alt="Optimism Update: Building A Decentralized Superchain Ecosystem With Layer 2 Solutions" class="wp-image-205856" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1828-1024x546.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1828-300x160.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1828-768x410.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1828-750x400.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1828-1140x608.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1828.png 1500w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Optimism Update: Building A Superchain Ecosystem With Layer 2 Solutions 3"></a></figure></div>


<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">What is Superchain?</h2>



<p>Superchain is a set of project rollups that have been launched on the OP Stack. <a href="https://coincu.com/197566-optimism-rebranded-op-mainnet-superchain/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Superchain</a> is planned to provide a decentralized, safe, and dependable scaling platform to let developers build decentralized apps on the Ethereum blockchain. The OP Mainnet will serve as the Superchain&#8217;s foundation layer.</p>



<p>Presently, a few famous names have surfaced in this Superchain ecosystem:</p>



<ul>
<li>Coinbase is employing OP Stack technology to create a new Layer 2 dubbed <a href="https://coincu.com/204074-coinbases-base-optimisms-drive/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Base</a>. The Base project is now in beta (testnet) and has completed half of its trip before going to the mainnet. While no exact date has been set, the project has indicated that the mainnet for Base will be deployed in 2023.</li>



<li>Apart from Base, the NFT marketplace project Zora recently revealed Zora Network, a blockchain network. This Layer 2 will assist Zora marketplace users in enhancing transaction speed and cut gas expenses by using OP Stack technology.</li>
</ul>



<p>The development journey of <a href="https://coincu.com/204801-optimism-to-launch-zkps/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Optimism</a> leading to the creation of Superchain has been riddled with numerous challenges and pivotal events that shaped its evolution. From inefficient beginnings to embracing simplicity as a core principle, the Optimism team navigated through obstacles to realize their vision of a robust blockchain platform.</p>



<p>The initial stages of development were focused on creating a Layer 2 solution based on Plasma. However, the team encountered significant setbacks, which ultimately forced them to make a bold switch to the Rollup model. Even with this new approach, the Optimism build process remained an arduous task, demanding immense effort and perseverance from the team.</p>



<p>Amidst these trials, a breakthrough occurred when a talented developer named Geohot joined the ranks. Geohot&#8217;s intervention proved to be a game-changer, as he managed to reduce a colossal 6,000-line codebase that had consumed the Optimism team&#8217;s time and energy for months down to a mere 300 lines within a few short days. This transformative experience led the team to adopt simplicity as a guiding principle for their future endeavors.</p>



<p>In 2021, the team faced another pivotal moment when the Optimistic Virtual Machine (OVM) was phased out. This decision presented a formidable challenge, compelling the team to contemplate a modular approach to implementation and proofing. Despite the difficulty, this shift allowed EVM Equivalence to become available on the Optimism network, expanding the platform&#8217;s compatibility and usability.</p>



<p>The path of Optimism has undoubtedly been fraught with obstacles, and the team recognized the need for a comprehensive solution. Hence, the birth of OP Stack marked a significant turning point in their journey, eventually leading to the emergence of Superchain. Built on the lessons learned and the principles of simplicity and efficiency, Superchain aims to propel blockchain technology forward with a renewed sense of purpose.</p>



<p>As Superchain takes its first successful steps towards the future, the challenges faced by the Optimism team have proven to be instrumental in shaping the platform&#8217;s robustness and potential for widespread adoption. With a modular architecture and EVM Equivalence, Superchain is poised to offer a powerful and user-friendly ecosystem for developers and users alike.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1829.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="919" height="761" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1829.png" alt="Optimism Update: Building A Decentralized Superchain Ecosystem With Layer 2 Solutions" class="wp-image-205857" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1829.png 919w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1829-300x248.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1829-768x636.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1829-750x621.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 919px) 100vw, 919px" title="Optimism Update: Building A Superchain Ecosystem With Layer 2 Solutions 4"></a></figure></div>


<p>At present, the disjointed state of the crypto market poses a significant challenge in onboarding the next generation of users. The Optimism Superchain, however, holds the potential to change this landscape drastically. Acting as a catalyst for Layer 2 chains, advancements in data availability on the main Ethereum network, particularly through EIP-4844 (Proto-Danksharding), play a pivotal role in paving the way for the Superchain&#8217;s success.</p>



<p>EIP-4844 is expected to revolutionize rollup solutions by significantly increasing data availability, resulting in cheaper transactions for end-users. Coinbase engineers&#8217; involvement in the development of EIP-4844 led to a fortuitous collaboration with the Optimism team. As a consequence, Coinbase decided to utilize the OP Stack as the architecture for its own Layer 2 chain, Base. With approximately ninety-eight million users, Base aims to provide an accessible on-ramp into DeFi for Coinbase&#8217;s vast user base.</p>



<p>By adopting the OP Stack, Base achieves a more cohesive foundation, abstracting away technical nuances between chains. Consequently, asset transfers between Optimism and Base become smoother and less risky when compared to transfers between Optimism and other chains like the Binance Smart Chain. The OP Stack acts as an enabler for creating interoperable bridges, connecting Ethereum&#8217;s vast archipelago of chains to the mainland.</p>



<p>To visualize this transformation, one can envision Layer 1 blockchains as isolated and siloed islands surrounded by vast oceans. In contrast, Ethereum and Layer 2 scaling solutions form a rich archipelago of interconnected islands, with the OP Stack allowing the creation of infinite new islands, bridging the gaps between them. This interconnected ecosystem facilitates the seamless movement of assets and users between various platforms.</p>



<p>The implications of the Layer 2 narrative go beyond most people&#8217;s imagination, offering a clear path toward the global adoption of cryptocurrencies and blockchain technology. As the Superchain concept takes flight, crypto&#8217;s fragmented landscape is set to be unified, providing a streamlined and user-friendly experience for both existing and new crypto enthusiasts. With the Optimism Superchain leading the charge, the future of crypto looks promising, leaving behind the limitations of the past to embrace a more connected and inclusive era of digital finance.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">OP Stack &amp; Superchain</h2>



<p>Every Layer 2 chain typically comprises three essential modules: the consensus layer, execution layer, and settlement layer. What sets the OP Stack apart is its ability to generate standardized open-source building blocks for each of these elements, empowering developers to construct distinct Layer 2s that cater to specific needs while promoting code reuse and refinement.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1827.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="800" height="638" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1827.png" alt="Optimism Update: Building A Decentralized Superchain Ecosystem With Layer 2 Solutions" class="wp-image-205855" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1827.png 800w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1827-300x239.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1827-768x612.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1827-750x598.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 800px) 100vw, 800px" title="Optimism Update: Building A Superchain Ecosystem With Layer 2 Solutions 5"></a></figure></div>


<p>Drawing inspiration from Ethereum&#8217;s successful scaling through modularity, the OP Stack replicates this concept for Layer 2 solutions. With each component becoming a standardized module, developers can now construct new Layer 2 chains akin to assembling Lego pieces, whether for general-purpose or application-specific purposes. This approach not only accelerates the process of building Layer 2s but also enhances the strength of the code through iterative improvements.</p>



<p>By curating an extensive open-source library of code and standardized modules, the OP Stack democratizes the creation of Layer 2 chains, enabling anyone to spin up their own chain effortlessly. This development lays the groundwork for what experts are calling a &#8220;Cambrian explosion&#8221; in the number of chains, sparking a flurry of innovative Layer 2 solutions across the Ethereum ecosystem.</p>



<p>David Hoffman from Bankless draws an intriguing analogy, likening the OP Stack&#8217;s impact to that of the ERC-20 token standard. Just as ERC-20 tokens simplified the creation of fungible tokens on Ethereum, the OP Stack aims to make the process of spinning up a Layer 2 chain as effortless as creating an ERC-20 token, further fueling the proliferation of Layer 2 adoption.</p>



<p>The power of the OP Stack lies in its ability to distill each component of a Layer 2 into a standardized module, making it a plug-and-play solution for entities seeking to build their Layer 2 chains. This flexibility empowers developers to choose from a wide array of available module layers, including alternative Layer 2 solutions beyond Rollup, or opting for different consensus mechanisms like ZKP (Zero-Knowledge Proof) instead of Fault Proof. Moreover, developers can even integrate Layer 1 solutions such as Celestia or leverage the Bitcoin network for the execution layer.</p>



<p>Ultimately, the OP Stack empowers individuals and organizations alike, offering them an easy-to-use set of SDKs to build and customize their Layer 2 platforms on Ethereum. With its Lego-like approach to Layer 2 construction and a vast repository of standardized modules, the OP Stack sets the stage for a new era of scalable, efficient, and diverse Layer 2 solutions, propelling Ethereum&#8217;s ecosystem towards unprecedented growth and innovation.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Interaction between Op-chains in Superchain</h2>



<p>According to Optimism&#8217;s vision, the ultimate goal is not merely to construct a single blockchain but to foster a comprehensive Digital Society that thrives on seamless and efficient interaction between different Op-chains. This interconnectedness opens up a world of possibilities for projects and developers within the Optimism ecosystem.</p>



<p>A key feature of Op-chains is their capability to communicate and interact with one another. This inter-chain communication forms the bedrock for establishing an omnichain system that facilitates smooth cross-chain transactions. By enabling Op-chains to message and collaborate, Optimism lays the groundwork for the future of blockchain technology.</p>



<p>The foundational element enabling this interoperability is the OP Stack, which offers a high degree of flexibility in passing the Sequencer—a crucial component in the transaction verification process. However, to further expedite and streamline cross-chain interactions, Optimism encourages Op-chains to share the same Sequencer Set. This shared approach significantly reduces transaction times and minimizes potential risks.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1830.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="798" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1830-1024x798.png" alt="Optimism Update: Building A Decentralized Superchain Ecosystem With Layer 2 Solutions" class="wp-image-205858" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1830-1024x798.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1830-300x234.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1830-768x599.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1830-750x584.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1830-1140x888.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1830.png 1432w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Optimism Update: Building A Superchain Ecosystem With Layer 2 Solutions 6"></a></figure></div>


<p>In a bid to promote collaborative innovation, projects within the Optimism Collective can now register to utilize the Set Sequencer, further reinforcing the vision of a united Superchain. This shared resource pool empowers projects to pool their resources and enhance their operational capabilities collectively.</p>



<p>It is worth noting that projects adopting the common Set Sequencer are considered part of the growing Superchain community. The Superchain represents a major milestone in the platform&#8217;s development journey and is expected to become more decentralized as the foundational Bedrock infrastructure reaches its full potential.</p>



<p>With the Op-chains and Superchain technologies taking center stage, Optimism&#8217;s vision of a Digital Society is closer to becoming a reality. By fostering an environment of interconnectedness and collaboration, the platform aims to revolutionize the blockchain landscape and unlock the true potential of decentralized applications and services.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Conclusion</h2>



<p>The Superchain ecosystem aims to decentralize further, with the transition to becoming fully decentralized happening after the success of Bedrock, which is expected to occur on June 7, 2023. As of now, it&#8217;s difficult to predict the exact future of Superchain, but with OP Labs&#8217; proven experience, there is a level of trust in their capabilities. However, it&#8217;s worth noting that the Bedrock release faced a delay of one year compared to the original expectations.</p>



<p>Base is the first blockchain to participate in the Superchain, but it seems like there is a discussion about whether the benefits it brings should be limited to the Base project only or shared with the entire Optimism Collective. Sharing revenue from transaction fees is seen as a positive concept.</p>



<p>It appears that the current situation requires more time to observe OP Labs&#8217; operations, development, and overall performance before making a more thorough assessment of the Superchain ecosystem. This approach allows for a more informed judgment of the project&#8217;s progress and potential future implications.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER:&nbsp;</em></strong><em>The information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>
<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/205854-optimism-update-superchain/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1831-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pendle War Intensify: PenPie And Equilibria Battle for Yield Farming Supremacy</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/205826-pendle-war-intensify/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Harold]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 13:55:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Knowledge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Equilibria]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pendle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pendle War]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PenPie]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vePENDLE]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=205826</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Pendle War revolves around projects competing for vePENDLE and attempting to attract holders from the parent project to their own child projects.<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/205826-pendle-war-intensify/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The advent of LSDFi has stirred a frenzy among blockchain enthusiasts as it introduces exciting new possibilities to the DeFi space. As a result, various parties are now vying for dominance over vePENDLE, a sought-after asset within the Pendle ecosystem. The battle lines are drawn, and PenPie, Equilibria, and Stake DAO have emerged as the main contenders in this epic conflict.</strong></h5>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>As the conflict intensifies, all eyes turn to two main players, PenPie and Equilibria, due to Stake DAO&#8217;s limited traction in the vePENDLE arena. In this article, <a href="https://twitter.com/Coincuofficial" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Coincu</a> delves into the current situation of the Pendle War.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1824.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="536" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1824.png" alt="Pendle War Intensify: PenPie And Equilibria Battle for Yield Farming Supremacy" class="wp-image-205847" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1824.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1824-300x157.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1824-768x402.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1824-750x393.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Pendle War Intensify: PenPie And Equilibria Battle for Yield Farming Supremacy 7"></a></figure></div>


<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Causes of Pendle War</h2>



<p>With its unique features and tools, <a href="https://coincu.com/200584-pendle-opens-up-new-growth-potential/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Pendle</a> empowers users to maximize interest rates, increase yields during bull markets, and offer hedging plans during bear markets.</p>



<p>At its core, Pendle utilizes three main tools to achieve its objectives. First is the concept of yield tokenization, which involves creating encrypted versions of tokens that yield on the Pendle platform. These yield tokens (PT and YT) are crucial for participating in Pendle&#8217;s ecosystem.</p>



<p>The second tool is Pendle&#8217;s Automated Market Maker (AMM), allowing users to trade the PT and YT yield tokens, enabling them to capitalize on fluctuating yields in response to token price movements and other market factors.</p>



<p>The third tool is governance, where Pendle leverages vePendle for project administration. This mechanism incentivizes projects to accumulate and acquire vePENDLE, sparking a governance battle within the DeFi market, known as Pendle War.</p>



<p>Pendle War revolves around projects competing for vePENDLE and attempting to attract holders from the parent project to their own child projects. The allure lies in the possibility of acquiring a substantial amount of veTokens, which confers greater power in directing incentives, rewards, and emission flows into the pools for their benefit.</p>



<p>The ongoing Pendle War currently features a heated competition between two major projects, Equilibria (ePENDLE) and Penpie (mPENDLE), with others such as Stake DAO and Swell Network also joining the fray. As more projects are expected to participate in the near future, users stand to benefit from the optimized yield sources created by these subprojects.</p>



<p>The success of Pendle is evident in the continuous inflow of funds, propelling its Total Value Locked (TVL) to new all-time highs. According to Defilama, Pendle&#8217;s TVL has surged nearly tenfold since the beginning of the year, growing from $15 million to an impressive $150 million.</p>



<p>In addition to the TVL growth, the native token PENDLE has experienced significant price appreciation despite the overall market being in a downtrend. The token&#8217;s value surged from $0.04 to approximately $1, marking an impressive 25-fold increase in the second half of 2023. Furthermore, Pendle&#8217;s listing on Binance on July 3 has attracted additional attention and interest from the market.</p>



<p>Another factor fueling Pendle&#8217;s growth is its association with the booming LSDFi (Leveraged Staking DeFi) array. As LSDFi&#8217;s TVL continues to climb, Pendle&#8217;s prominence within this segment also rises. Reports from reputable organizations like Binance Research have contributed to a surge in community attention towards LSDFi and Pendle.</p>



<p>Pendle has created a new market in the Crypto market that is DeFi Yield &#8211; Trading Protocol. With Pendle, users can build strategies to generate profits from their own future profits. Currently, the assets that Pendle is aiming for are LST (Liquid Staking Token), such as sfxrETH, stETH. It can be said that up to the present time, Pendle is doing one of the platforms leading the recent LSDfi trend.</p>



<p>Pendle&#8217;s veToken model has some of the following characteristics:</p>



<ul>
<li>vePENDLE will be locked for a maximum of 2 years the value of vePENDLE will gradually decrease within 2 years.</li>



<li>Voters use vePENDLE to boost yield from LPs and share revenue with the protocol.</li>



<li>Participating in voter voting will receive additional incentives &amp; transaction fees from voting pools.</li>
</ul>



<p>It can be seen that the model of vePENDLE has many similarities with the model of veCRV. The key point here is that Pendle must have a large revenue stream, which is currently being shown when <a href="https://defillama.com/top-protocols" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">TVL</a> and volume on Pendle are still growing very well.</p>



<p>This has opened up a real war that is Pendle War. In this war, two names are competing fiercely, which are Penpie and Equilibria. Now we&#8217;ll take a closer look at this war to see who is benefiting and which project&#8217;s strategy will help them win the Pendle War.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Overview of Pendle War</h2>



<p>PenPie and Equilibria, are currently engaged in a heated battle for dominance in the <a href="https://dune.com/coumarin/pendle-war" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Pendle War</a>. The focus lies on their vePENDLE holdings, with both projects accounting for a substantial amount of this coveted asset, while Stake DAO trails behind with a mere 2.99 percent share.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Nansen_Brief_44_Header_85abb0439e-scaled.webp"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="576" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Nansen_Brief_44_Header_85abb0439e-1024x576.webp" alt="Pendle War Intensify: PenPie And Equilibria Battle for Yield Farming Supremacy" class="wp-image-205849" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Nansen_Brief_44_Header_85abb0439e-1024x576.webp 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Nansen_Brief_44_Header_85abb0439e-300x169.webp 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Nansen_Brief_44_Header_85abb0439e-768x432.webp 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Nansen_Brief_44_Header_85abb0439e-1536x864.webp 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Nansen_Brief_44_Header_85abb0439e-2048x1152.webp 2048w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Nansen_Brief_44_Header_85abb0439e-750x422.webp 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Nansen_Brief_44_Header_85abb0439e-1140x641.webp 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Pendle War Intensify: PenPie And Equilibria Battle for Yield Farming Supremacy 8"></a></figure></div>


<p>VePENDLE, an essential asset for yield optimization, serves as the battleground for PenPie and Equilibria, and understanding their respective approaches is crucial.</p>



<ul>
<li>PenPie, a robust Yield Farming platform, is deployed on both Ethereum and Arbitrum chains. The vePENDLE amount on PenPie is calculated by combining holdings on both chains, offering users the potential for higher rewards.</li>



<li>On the other hand, Equilibria also operates on two chains but solely calculates its vePENDLE amount on Ethereum. Although it provides a Yield Farming solution for vePENDLE holders, it lacks the cumulative approach offered by PenPie.</li>
</ul>



<p>A Brief Introduction to PenPie and Equilibria:</p>



<ul>
<li>PenPie, designed by the Magpie team, aims to maximize profits for PENDLE holders. It leverages the expertise gained from the successful Wombat Wars project on both BNB Chain and Arbitrum.</li>



<li>Equilibria, on the other hand, provides a platform for PENDLE holders to profit from vePENDLE without the concern of locked assets in the protocol.</li>
</ul>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-25-at-20.30.43-1024x480.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="480" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-25-at-20.30.43-1024x480.png" alt="Pendle War Intensify: PenPie And Equilibria Battle for Yield Farming Supremacy" class="wp-image-205846" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-25-at-20.30.43-1024x480.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-25-at-20.30.43-300x141.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-25-at-20.30.43-768x360.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-25-at-20.30.43-750x352.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-25-at-20.30.43-1140x534.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-25-at-20.30.43.png 1250w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Pendle War Intensify: PenPie And Equilibria Battle for Yield Farming Supremacy 9"></a></figure></div>


<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The Battle Factors</strong></h3>



<p>In this Pendle War clash, several factors will determine the ultimate victor:</p>



<ul>
<li>APR from PENDLE deposits: PenPie holds a clear advantage in terms of profitability metrics for PENDLE depositors into the protocol. Its higher APR attracts users seeking greater returns.</li>



<li>Peg holding during AMM switches: The ability to maintain the peg when users switch back to PENDLE on the AMM is a crucial factor. Both platforms will be evaluated based on their efficiency in this regard.</li>



<li>Native tokens for Liquidity Mining: The availability of remaining Native Tokens to use for Liquidity Mining will play a significant role in attracting users and Total Value Locked (TVL).</li>



<li>Team Experience: The development teams&#8217; experience in similar battles will be a determinant in ensuring a robust and reliable platform.</li>
</ul>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Current Status</strong></h3>



<p>As of now, both platforms hold a comparable amount of vePENDLE. PenPie, apart from its substantial vePENDLE holdings, has also established itself as a successful project on Camelot, the premier Launchpad platform on the Arbitrum ecosystem. Its token price has experienced a fivefold increase compared to the initial IDO price, adding to its allure for users.</p>



<p>Equilibria, while offering a slightly better option for compounding Pendle profits, faces stiff competition from PenPie. Both platforms have recently launched their native tokens, creating incentives to attract users, with TVL levels remaining on par.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-25-at-20.30.30-1024x159.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="159" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-25-at-20.30.30-1024x159.png" alt="Pendle War Intensify: PenPie And Equilibria Battle for Yield Farming Supremacy" class="wp-image-205845" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-25-at-20.30.30-1024x159.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-25-at-20.30.30-300x47.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-25-at-20.30.30-768x119.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-25-at-20.30.30-1536x239.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-25-at-20.30.30-2048x318.png 2048w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-25-at-20.30.30-750x117.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-25-at-20.30.30-1140x177.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Pendle War Intensify: PenPie And Equilibria Battle for Yield Farming Supremacy 10"></a></figure></div>


<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Conclusion</h2>



<p>The Pendle War is in full swing, with PenPie and Equilibria battling it out for supremacy in the yield farming landscape. PenPie&#8217;s cumulative vePENDLE holdings, higher APR, and successful track record provide a competitive edge. However, Equilibria&#8217;s unique proposition for mitigating locked assets may also resonate with some users. As the war unfolds, factors like user adoption, community support, and platform innovation will ultimately determine the winner in this highly contested arena.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER:&nbsp;</em></strong><em>The information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>
<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/205826-pendle-war-intensify/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1826-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Worldcoin Takes Over The World As Its Name, Except The United States</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/205839-worldcoin-takes-over-the-world-as-name-except/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Thana]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 12:15:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[WLD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[WLD US]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Worldcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=205839</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Worldcoin notes that WLD tokens are not available to persons or companies residing in the United States. However, World ID and TFH's World App are still available in the United States.<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/205839-worldcoin-takes-over-the-world-as-name-except/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>Worldcoin is not available for use or purchase by US persons or companies.</em></li>



<li><em>US persons are restricted from accessing Worldcoin and services of certain countries and regions.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Unlike offshore exchanges, none of the U.S.-based cryptocurrency exchanges, such as Coinbase Kraken, has Worldcoin listed. Worldcoin <a href="https://whitepaper.worldcoin.org/tokenomics" target="_blank" data-type="URL" data-id="https://whitepaper.worldcoin.org/tokenomics" rel="noreferrer noopener">notes </a>that WLD tokens are not available to persons or companies residing in the United States. However, World ID and TFH&#8217;s World App are still available in the United States.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1823.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="576" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1823-1024x576.png" alt="Worldcoin Takes Over The World As Its Name, Except The United States" class="wp-image-205841" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1823-1024x576.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1823-300x169.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1823-768x432.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1823-750x422.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1823-1140x641.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1823.png 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Worldcoin Takes Over The World As Its Name, Except The United States 11"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>Worldcoin, the most widely distributed digital currency, is making waves in the cryptocurrency world. The WLD token, alongside World ID, will be used for protocol governance and form the foundation of the largest privacy-preserving identity and financial network. However, US-based cryptocurrency exchanges such as Coinbase and Kraken do not currently list Worldcoin. The WLD tokens are unavailable to US persons or companies, although World ID and TFH’s World App remain available in the United States.</p>



<p>According to the whitepaper, the majority of WLD tokens will be given to individuals simply for being unique humans. The majority of humans who are alive today will receive WLD tokens, making it the most widely distributed digital currency. This makes Worldcoin an attractive option for those who want to be part of a digital currency that is accessible to everyone.</p>



<p>Worldcoin is not intended to be available for use, purchase, or access by US persons, including US citizens, residents, or persons in the United States, or companies incorporated, located, or resident in the United States, or who have a registered agent in the United States. Worldcoin is not alone in restricting access to its services. US persons are restricted from accessing services of countries or regions such as Syria, Crimea, Donetsk, Luhansk, Kherson, and Zaporizhzhia regions of Ukraine, Russia, North Korea, Iran, or Cuba.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote">
<p class="has-small-font-size"><strong><a href="https://vault.pactsafe.io/s/8a18d792-fd76-44db-9b92-b0bb7981c248/legal.html#contract-byutjvtyt" target="_blank" data-type="URL" data-id="https://vault.pactsafe.io/s/8a18d792-fd76-44db-9b92-b0bb7981c248/legal.html#contract-byutjvtyt" rel="noreferrer noopener">1.2 Eligibility</a>.</strong> In order to use the Services, you must comply with these Terms and all applicable laws. You cannot use the Services to conduct, promote, or help others to carry out any illegal activity.</p>
</blockquote>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote">
<p class="has-small-font-size">In addition, you must meet all of the following criteria:</p>
</blockquote>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote">
<ul>
<li class="has-small-font-size">You are 18 years of age or older;</li>



<li class="has-small-font-size">You are&nbsp;<strong>not</strong>&nbsp;located in, under the control of, a national, or resident of: Syria, the Crimea, Donetsk, Luhansk, Kherson and Zaporizhzhia regions of Ukraine, Russia, North Korea, Iran, Cuba, or any other country or region with whom the United States, the European Union, or any other country or jurisdiction has restricted the access of the Services; and</li>



<li class="has-small-font-size">You are not a “Specially Designated National” as declared by the U.S. Department of the Treasury Office of Foreign Assets Control (“OFAC”) or the sanctions lists of any other country, and your name is not on the U.S. Department of Commerce’s Denied Persons List or the banned persons lists of any other country.</li>
</ul>
</blockquote>



<p id="block-643c4ba8-b40b-4525-9a96-f280dbfbeb9d"><strong><em>DISCLAIMER:&nbsp;</em></strong><em>The Information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>
<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/205839-worldcoin-takes-over-the-world-as-name-except/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ban-sao-cua-Ban-sao-cua-Noi-dung-doan-van-ban-cua-ban-2023-07-25T191353.424-1024x731.jpg" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/jpeg" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>TronLink Chrome Wallet Upgrades To V4.1.1, Introducing EVM Network Support</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/205817-tronlink-chrome-wallet-v4-1-1-evm-network/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chubbi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 10:21:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto wallet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[EVM]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[market]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=205817</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[TronLink, the popular Chrome plug-in wallet, is set to receive a significant upgrade with the latest V4.1.1 version, as announced on July 25. <p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/205817-tronlink-chrome-wallet-v4-1-1-evm-network/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>TronLink Chrome wallet releases V4.1.1 update, adding support for EVM-based networks (Ethereum, BSC, BTTC), expanding choices for users.</em></li>



<li><em>Upgrade enables seamless asset management on different networks with a single HD wallet, fostering TRON and BTTC ecosystem development.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>TronLink, the popular Chrome plug-in wallet, is set to receive a significant upgrade with the latest V4.1.1 version, as announced on July 25.&nbsp;</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/4-9.jpeg"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="600" height="389" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/4-9.jpeg" alt="TronLink Chrome Wallet Upgrades To V4.1.1, Introducing EVM Network Support" class="wp-image-205827" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/4-9.jpeg 600w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/4-9-300x195.jpeg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" title="TronLink Chrome Wallet Upgrades To V4.1.1, Introducing EVM Network Support 12"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>Users will have access to a greater variety of options as a result of this update&#8217;s addition of support for <a href="https://coincu.com/203512-neon-evm-now-supports-ethereum-on-solana/">EVM</a>-based networks like as Ethereum, BSC, and BTTC networks. TronLink Chrome wallet will be able to cater to more complicated DApp application situations as a result of this extension. It will also be able to fulfill a wider variety of asset management demands, which will support the growth of the TRON and BTTC ecosystems.</p>



<p>Users will now have the option to switch between different networks&#8217; wallets by accessing the wallet interface&#8217;s icon in the upper left corner. The new version will also feature a single HD wallet structure, streamlining asset management for TRON, Ethereum, BSC, and BTTC networks. Users can now manage all these networks&#8217; assets with a single set of mnemonics, making the process more user-friendly.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/timthumb.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="600" height="315" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/timthumb.png" alt="TronLink Chrome Wallet Upgrades To V4.1.1, Introducing EVM Network Support" class="wp-image-205828" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/timthumb.png 600w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/timthumb-300x158.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" title="TronLink Chrome Wallet Upgrades To V4.1.1, Introducing EVM Network Support 13"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>The BTTC&#8217;s decentralized cross-chain bridge, BT.io, has shown their support for the adaption of TronLink to the EVM chain-related functions by providing their assistance. Additionally, future plans call for additional EVM-based decentralized applications (DApps) to integrate and support TronLink&#8217;s plug-in wallet, which will expand the wallet&#8217;s accessibility and usage.</p>



<p>This version represents a huge step forward for TronLink, as it enables users to more easily manage their assets and gain seamless access to a variety of EVM-based networks. TronLink&#8217;s improved features position it as a versatile and user-centric wallet solution for crypto fans across a variety of ecosystems. This is important because the demand for decentralized applications is expected to continue to rise.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER: </em></strong><em>The Information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>



<p>Join us to keep track of news: <a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Chubbi</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Coincu News</strong></p>
<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/205817-tronlink-chrome-wallet-v4-1-1-evm-network/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ban-sao-cua-Final-Thumb-3-1024x731.jpg" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/jpeg" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Raft Review: Steady Waters Of Stability And Profit DeFi</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/205709-raft-review/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Harold]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 10:10:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Reviews]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Flash Mint]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LSDfi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MCR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Oracle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[R]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Raft Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[wstETH]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=205709</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Raft Finance, a pioneering project in the LSDfi (Liquid Staking Derivatives Finance) sector, has attracted attention for its unique operational mechanisms<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/205709-raft-review/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>In the fast-evolving world of finance (DeFi), <a href="https://raft.fi/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Raft Finance</a>, a pioneering project in the LSDfi (Liquid Staking Derivatives Finance) sector, has attracted attention for its unique operational mechanisms. Focused on the cutting edge of DeFi innovation, Raft Finance presents a remarkable opportunity that aligns perfectly with the current industry trend.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1820.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="576" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1820-1024x576.png" alt="Raft Review: Steady Waters Of Stability And Profit DeFi" class="wp-image-205805" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1820-1024x576.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1820-300x169.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1820-768x432.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1820-1536x864.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1820-750x422.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1820-1140x641.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1820.png 1600w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Raft Review: Steady Waters Of Stability And Profit DeFi 14"></a></figure></div>


<p>As interest in the LSDfi sector grows, investors and enthusiasts are closely monitoring the development potential and community support for this attractive project. This is a remarkable project and follows the current trend. Does the project have enough development potential and receive great investment from the community? Let&#8217;s find out with Coincu through this article.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">What is Raft?</h2>



<p>Raft Finance is a decentralized borrowing and lending protocol on the Ethereum network, providing users with the means to optimize capital efficiency while ensuring asset stability.</p>



<p>The core concept behind Raft Finance lies in its unique approach to lending stablecoin R. Users can achieve this by staking stETH or wstETH, two innovative tokens that play a vital role in the borrowing and lending process. By staking these tokens, users gain access to stablecoin R, receiving a loan amount equivalent to the value of their staked assets. This groundbreaking mechanism empowers users to make the most of their holdings and enhance profits through efficient lending and borrowing.</p>



<p>At its heart, Raft Finance aims to establish a decentralized financial ecosystem on the Ethereum network, enabling users to effectively manage and optimize their capital in a secure and stable environment. By harnessing the power of DeFi, Raft Finance presents a solution to enhance capital efficiency for its growing user base.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Highlights</h2>



<p>What sets R apart from its predecessors, SAI (Single Collateral Dai) and LUSD, is its innovative approach to stability, enhanced capital efficiency, and flexible fee structures, making it the preferred choice for borrowing against LSD collateral.</p>



<p>At the heart of R&#8217;s stability lies a unique combination of two mechanisms: the Hard Peg and the Soft Peg. Together, these mechanisms ensure that the value of R always remains fixed to the US dollar, offering a stable price between $1 and $1.20.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Hard Peg: The Arbitrage Mechanism</strong></h3>



<p>The Hard Peg is the foundation upon which R maintains its stable price within the designated range. This mechanism is governed by two key features: Redemption and Over-Collateralization.</p>



<p>The Redemption feature allows users to exchange R tokens for wstETH (wrapped stETH) at a value equivalent to 1 USD. Notably, when R tokens are redeemed, they are subsequently burned, effectively reducing the circulating supply and contributing to an increase in the price of R. This ensures that even if the price of R falls below the $1 mark, users have the opportunity to redeem their tokens and help stabilize the value.</p>



<p>On the other hand, Over-Collateralization empowers users to mortgage their wstETH in order to mint R tokens. This process enables users to create R tokens at a fixed price of 1 USD, providing an opportunity for profit-making through price differences. By allowing an increase in the supply, the protocol also counterbalances situations where the price of R might surge beyond the $1.20 threshold, thereby aiding in stabilizing the coin&#8217;s value.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Soft Peg: Unleashing Capital Efficiency</strong></h3>



<p>Complementing the Hard Peg, the Soft Peg mechanism optimizes capital utilization for users by leveraging price fluctuations of R tokens. This approach grants users the freedom to employ strategic tactics to predict and capitalize on the future price movements of R.</p>



<p>During instances where the price of R experiences fluctuations, the protocol incentivizes borrowers to hold onto their positions instead of immediately returning them. This encouragement to hold positions is driven by the understanding that other users may seize the opportunity for profit-making during these price swings.</p>



<p>In conclusion, R has emerged as a game-changer in the realm of stablecoins, harnessing the power of Liquid Staking Tokens (LSDs) like stETH and rETH to ensure capital efficiency on the Ethereum network. Its robust combination of the Hard Peg and Soft Peg mechanisms guarantees that the value of R remains steadfastly anchored to the US dollar while also promoting efficient and instant liquidation. As the cryptocurrency market continues to evolve, R stands at the forefront, providing users with a reliable and innovative stablecoin solution that paves the way for a more secure and prosperous future in the decentralized financial landscape.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-25-at-17.07.42-1024x428.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="428" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-25-at-17.07.42-1024x428.png" alt="Raft Review: Steady Waters Of Stability And Profit DeFi" class="wp-image-205823" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-25-at-17.07.42-1024x428.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-25-at-17.07.42-300x125.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-25-at-17.07.42-768x321.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-25-at-17.07.42-1536x642.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-25-at-17.07.42-2048x857.png 2048w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-25-at-17.07.42-750x314.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-25-at-17.07.42-1140x477.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Raft Review: Steady Waters Of Stability And Profit DeFi 15"></a></figure></div>


<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Products</h2>



<p>Raft primarily offers borrowing and lending products on Ethereum.</p>



<p>The core features of Raft&#8217;s revolutionary protocol are designed to cater to the financial needs of its users:</p>



<ul>
<li>Borrowing Stablecoin R: Through the process of staking stETH or wstETH, users gain access to borrowing stablecoin R. This enables them to secure a loan amount equivalent to the value they have staked, providing a seamless and efficient borrowing experience.</li>



<li>Lending and Profit: Raft protocol extends the opportunity for users to lend the borrowed R stablecoin, which they obtained through staking stETH or wstETH. By actively participating in the lending process, users can increase their overall returns on assets.</li>



<li>Efficient Asset Management: A standout advantage of the Raft protocol in its ability to assist users in managing and optimizing their capital effectively. By engaging in borrowing and lending using stETH or wstETH, individuals can unlock the full potential of their assets, leading to enhanced financial growth and stability.</li>



<li>Asset Stability: One of the paramount concerns for users engaged in trading and borrowing is asset stability. Raft addresses this by users allows to stake stETH or wstETH to borrow stablecoin R, thus safeguarding the stability of their assets throughout these processes.</li>
</ul>



<p>In essence, Raft&#8217;s decentralized lending and borrowing protocol on the Ethereum network stands as a pivotal step forward in the realm of blockchain-based finance. By granting users the ability to borrow stablecoin R through staking stETH or wstETH, the platform offers a powerful and secure means of optimizing capital efficiency and enabling asset stability in an ever-evolving digital landscape.</p>



<p>The R token economy has introduced a groundbreaking borrowing and repayment system, revolutionizing the way users interact with the token. This system requires users to create a position by depositing their LSD with a collateral rate of at least 120% for every R token borrowed. The minimum amount of R borrowed has been set at 3,000 tokens (~3,000 USD), ensuring a stable and secure borrowing process.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Borrowing</strong></h3>



<p>To borrow R tokens, users must deposit their LSD as collateral, maintaining a collateral rate of at least 120%. This mechanism acts as a safety net for the lending process and protects both borrowers and lenders.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Returning</strong></h3>



<p>There are three distinct methods for repaying the borrowed R tokens:</p>



<ul>
<li>Loan Repayment: Borrowers can repay the previous loan along with accrued interest to retrieve their collateral LSD token. This method encourages responsible borrowing and timely repayment.</li>



<li>Redemption: Holders of R tokens can participate in the market and acquire another borrower&#8217;s collateral LSD. This allows for greater flexibility in the ecosystem, as tokens can change hands while maintaining stability.</li>



<li>Liquidation: In case of default, a Liquidator pays off the borrower&#8217;s debt with R tokens at the Minimum Mortgage Rate (MCR) and receives the collateral LSD token along with the Liquidation Bonus from the previous borrower. This process helps maintain the liquidity and health of the overall economy.</li>
</ul>



<p>Furthermore, to ensure the stability of the R token economy, the number of R tokens used in these repayment methods will be burned.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Flash Mint</strong></h3>



<p>The introduction of Flash Mint has empowered users with a powerful tool that allows them to mint R tokens up to 10% of the total R supply without making any initial payments. However, there is a 0.5% Fast Mint Rate applicable, which needs to be repaid in the same transaction. Initially, the rate has been capped at 0.5%, but market efficiency can push it up to 5%.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Oracle</strong></h3>



<p>The R token economy boasts a sophisticated Oracle system designed to be adaptable and maintainable in a multi-signature configuration. This setup enables participants with multisig capabilities to make necessary updates, ensuring the system remains robust and reliable even as market dynamics change.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Features</h2>



<p>Raft has seven features: Position, Redeem, Mint, Leverage, Liquidators, Frontend Operators, and Governance Forum.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Position</strong></h3>



<p>Raft enables users to borrow R tokens by opening a new position, with each wallet address representing one position. To borrow R tokens, users must stake stETH or wstETH with a minimum collateral rate of 120%. The borrowing process entails certain requirements, including a minimum loan amount of 3,000 Rs. Additionally, users are subject to a borrowing fee paid in R tokens, calculated based on the borrowed amount and rate, which is influenced by the frequency of redeeming the R token.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Redeem</strong></h3>



<p>The Redeem feature facilitates the exchange of R tokens for wstETH, with a conversion rate of 1:1 to USD. The feature involves two primary roles: Redeemers and Redemption Providers (RPs). Redeemers seek to convert R tokens into wstETH, while RPs offer wstETH to facilitate redemptions. Raft incorporates a spread mechanism, varying from 0.25% to 100%, to mitigate risks for Redeemers. Additionally, Redeemers are subject to a Redeem Fee, calculated based on the Redeem value and rate, with RPs earning a fee based on a percentage of the total fee.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Mint</strong></h3>



<p>Raft allows users to mint up to 10% of the total supply of R tokens. Minting requires users to pay back R tokens in the same transaction, accompanied by a mint fee of 0.5%. Initially fixed at 0.5%, the mint fee is subject to adjustment based on the effective utilization of R tokens.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Leverage</strong></h3>



<p>The Leverage feature empowers users to enhance their capital ratio for each trade, enabling higher profits from smaller investments through custom margin ratios. However, users should exercise caution, as leverage amplifies the risk of losses, especially during periods of intense market fluctuations. To maintain stability, Raft sets the maximum leverage at 6%.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Liquidator</strong></h3>



<p>The Liquidator&#8217;s role is crucial in ensuring that each R token maintains a value backed by 1 wstETH token, equivalent to 1 USD. In the event that a Minter&#8217;s collateral falls below 120%, they face liquidation. Users can participate as Liquidators, settling a Minter&#8217;s debt and receiving wstETH equivalent to the liquidated amount. Raft incentivizes users to become Liquidators through liquidation rewards, offering an additional source of income.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Frontend Operators</strong></h3>



<p>Raft extends its support to developers through the Frontend Operators feature, offering a toolkit that facilitates seamless integration with user dApps. Additionally, Frontend Operators gain marketing support through promotional campaigns, helping them maximize their potential rewards and contributions to the project.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Governance Forum</strong></h3>



<p>To maintain decentralization, Raft provides users with an opportunity to participate in the governance forum, enabling them to actively contribute to the platform&#8217;s governance. Users can voice their opinions on key areas such as the appointment of the Liquidity Committee, defining liquidity pools for the R token, treasury fund allocation, and protocol fees, including mint fees.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Team</h2>



<p>David Garai (Founder) is the project&#8217;s strategic, financial, and operational leader. He has worked as a lawyer in both London and Tokyo.</p>



<p>Raft&#8217;s co-founder, Ore Mijovi, is in charge of technological supervision. He formerly worked at the Ethereum Foundation as a lead developer of the Solidity compiler.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Investors &amp; Partners</h2>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Investors</strong></h3>



<p>While the precise amount collected by the Raft Finance project is unknown, it is obvious that the initiative has attracted funding from renowned investment firms such as <a href="https://coincu.com/167938-jump-crypto-identified-as-third-party/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Jump Crypto</a> and <a href="https://coincu.com/199861-wintermute-trading-transfers-5-08m/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Wintermute</a>.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-25-at-17.07.51-1024x321.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="321" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-25-at-17.07.51-1024x321.png" alt="Raft Review: Steady Waters Of Stability And Profit DeFi" class="wp-image-205824" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-25-at-17.07.51-1024x321.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-25-at-17.07.51-300x94.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-25-at-17.07.51-768x241.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-25-at-17.07.51-1536x482.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-25-at-17.07.51-2048x642.png 2048w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-25-at-17.07.51-750x235.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-25-at-17.07.51-1140x357.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Raft Review: Steady Waters Of Stability And Profit DeFi 16"></a></figure></div>


<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Partners</strong></h3>



<p>Project partners are Maverick, Uniswap.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Conclusion</h2>



<p>In the realm of decentralized finance (DeFi), the LSDfi sector has seen remarkable innovations, with Raft Finance emerging as a notable player alongside its leading counterpart, Lybra Finance. While both projects operate within the LSDfi landscape, they boast distinctive features that set them apart.</p>



<p>One of the striking contrasts lies in their loan mechanisms. <a href="https://coincu.com/189739-lybra-finance-earn-income-from-staking/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Lybra Finance</a> stands out for its interest-free loans, offering users an attractive borrowing proposition. On the other hand, Raft Finance has opted for a conservative yet practical approach, attaching a modest 5% interest rate to its loans. This distinction signifies a choice between flexible borrowing in Lybra and a slightly costlier but stable borrowing model in Raft.</p>



<p>Collateral requirements further underscore their dissimilarities. Raft Finance necessitates a collateralization rate of 120%, while Lybra Finance sets it at 150%. This variance implies that users have more flexibility with their assets in Lybra, albeit with a higher margin to safeguard against potential risks.</p>



<p>Additionally, Lybra Finance&#8217;s user-friendly environment has garnered attention. It extends a warm welcome to users from all walks of life, allowing both large and small capital holders to secure an eUSD loan. Not imposing a minimum loan amount, Lybra Finance seeks to be inclusive and accessible to all.</p>



<p>In contrast, Raft Finance has chosen to establish a minimum borrowing threshold of Rs 3,000, implying that users need to commit to a slightly higher borrowing amount. While this approach may limit some participants, it aims to maintain stability and mitigate risks through responsible borrowing practices.</p>



<p>One intriguing aspect of Raft Finance lies in its embrace of leverage within its protocol. Encouraging users to &#8220;put their faith&#8221; in the stablecoin R, the project seeks to optimize profits for those willing to take on a calculated level of leverage. Although this approach may raise initial skepticism, it also offers potential rewards for the risk-tolerant and informed investors.</p>



<p>The project&#8217;s emphasis on creating trust around its stablecoin could be seen as a daring move, but it also reveals the team&#8217;s confidence in the stability and value proposition of their offering. This &#8220;trust-building&#8221; strategy will likely unfold over time, allowing the community to assess its effectiveness and risk implications.</p>



<p>At present, the Raft Finance project remains relatively enigmatic, with limited information available for analysis. As the community gains first-hand experience with the platform, a clearer picture will emerge, enabling us to make informed judgments about its position and potential within the LSDfi segment.</p>



<p>In conclusion, the landscape of LSDfi has seen the rise of Raft Finance, presenting itself with distinct characteristics that differentiate it from its counterparts like Lybra Finance. With its prudent interest rates, collateral requirements, and intriguing embrace of leverage, Raft Finance is carving its niche within the DeFi realm. As time unfolds, the community&#8217;s exploration and assessment will determine whether this project indeed sails smoothly in the ever-evolving LSDfi domain.</p>



<p id="block-643c4ba8-b40b-4525-9a96-f280dbfbeb9d"><strong><em>DISCLAIMER: </em></strong><em>The information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>
<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/205709-raft-review/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1821-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>BDO Validates FTX&#8217;s $376 Million Acquisition Of DAAG As Fair Value Amidst Controversy</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/205807-bdo-ftxs-376-million-acquisition/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chubbi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 10:01:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Collapse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[market]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=205807</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[BDO stated that FTX's $376 million acquisition of DAAG is free of problems and represents fair value.<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/205807-bdo-ftxs-376-million-acquisition/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>BDO accounting firm approves FTX&#8217;s $376 million acquisition of DAAG (now FTX Europe) as &#8220;fair value&#8221; despite FTX Trading&#8217;s complaint.</em></li>



<li><em>Controversy arises over allegations of overpayment and close ties with DAAG executives, while BDO&#8217;s endorsement provides an objective perspective on the deal.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>BDO stated that FTX&#8217;s $376 million acquisition of DAAG is free of problems and represents fair value.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/38539225-1bee-4683-8aa0-2b38182323d8_51cdbec1-1024x683.jpeg"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="683" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/38539225-1bee-4683-8aa0-2b38182323d8_51cdbec1-1024x683.jpeg" alt="BDO Validates FTX&#039;s $376 Million Acquisition Of DAAG As Fair Value Amidst Controversy" class="wp-image-205811" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/38539225-1bee-4683-8aa0-2b38182323d8_51cdbec1-1024x683.jpeg 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/38539225-1bee-4683-8aa0-2b38182323d8_51cdbec1-300x200.jpeg 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/38539225-1bee-4683-8aa0-2b38182323d8_51cdbec1-768x512.jpeg 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/38539225-1bee-4683-8aa0-2b38182323d8_51cdbec1-1536x1024.jpeg 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/38539225-1bee-4683-8aa0-2b38182323d8_51cdbec1-2048x1366.jpeg 2048w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/38539225-1bee-4683-8aa0-2b38182323d8_51cdbec1-750x500.jpeg 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/38539225-1bee-4683-8aa0-2b38182323d8_51cdbec1-1140x760.jpeg 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="BDO Validates FTX&#039;s $376 Million Acquisition Of DAAG As Fair Value Amidst Controversy 17"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>Accounting firm BDO has given its stamp of approval to FTX&#8217;s $376 million acquisition of Swiss start-up company Digital Assets AG (DAAG), now known as FTX Europe. BDO&#8217;s assessment asserts that the transaction reasonably represents fair value, countering FTX Trading&#8217;s recent complaint.</p>



<p>The firm faced controversy when its bankruptcy lawyers sought to recover $323 million from FTX Europe&#8217;s leadership. Allegations arose that former CEO Bankman-Fried overpaid for DAAG due to his close ties with executives Patrick Gruhn, Robin Matzke, and Brandon Williams, who are all currently facing lawsuits.</p>



<p>In contrast to <a href="https://coincu.com/203770-former-ftx-at-sino-global-capital/">FTX</a> Trading&#8217;s concerns, BDO&#8217;s independent evaluation stands firm in its belief that the acquisition price was justified and fair. It indicates that the acquisition of DAAG, now operating as Europe Branch, was executed without any issues and represents a reasonable value for the deal. Notably, BDO has recently reduced its presence in the cryptocurrency space, making their objective analysis all the more crucial in this contentious matter.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1920x1440a-1024x768.jpeg"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="768" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1920x1440a-1024x768.jpeg" alt="BDO Validates FTX&#039;s $376 Million Acquisition Of DAAG As Fair Value Amidst Controversy" class="wp-image-205812" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1920x1440a-1024x768.jpeg 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1920x1440a-300x225.jpeg 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1920x1440a-768x576.jpeg 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1920x1440a-1536x1152.jpeg 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1920x1440a-750x563.jpeg 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1920x1440a-1140x855.jpeg 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1920x1440a.jpeg 1920w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="BDO Validates FTX&#039;s $376 Million Acquisition Of DAAG As Fair Value Amidst Controversy 18"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>The controversy surrounding the firm&#8217;s acquisition of DAAG has drawn significant attention within the cryptocurrency community and beyond. As the legal proceedings continue, BDO&#8217;s endorsement could potentially have a significant impact on the case&#8217;s outcome and may help quell doubts surrounding the legitimacy of the acquisition.</p>



<p>Despite BDO&#8217;s validation, the situation remains complex, and the outcome of the legal battle initiated by the firm Trading branch continues to be closely monitored by industry observers. The cryptocurrency market&#8217;s growing prominence has put acquisitions and financial dealings under heightened scrutiny, prompting firms like BDO to provide impartial evaluations of such transactions.</p>



<p>As the story unfolds, market participants and investors will be keeping a close eye on the developments, as the resolution of this dispute could have broader implications for the cryptocurrency industry&#8217;s mergers and acquisitions landscape.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER: </em></strong><em>The Information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>



<p>Join us to keep track of news: <a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Chubbi</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Coincu News</strong></p>
<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/205807-bdo-ftxs-376-million-acquisition/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BDO_Validates_FTXs_376_Million_Acquisition_of_DAAG_as_Fair_Value-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>UK Data Watchdog To Investigate Worldcoin Crypto Project Over Privacy Concerns</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/205796-uk-data-watchdog-worldcoin-crypto-privacy/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chubbi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 09:48:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[# Cryptocurrencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Worldcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=205796</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The UK's data regulator has announced its plan to investigate Worldcoin, a cryptocurrency project spearheaded by Sam Altman, the CEO of OpenAI. <p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/205796-uk-data-watchdog-worldcoin-crypto-privacy/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Key Points:</p>



<ul>
<li><em>The UK&#8217;s data regulator, the Information Commissioner&#8217;s Office (ICO), is launching an investigation into Worldcoin, a crypto project led by OpenAI CEO Sam Altman, which offers free cryptocurrency in exchange for users&#8217; iris scans.</em></li>



<li><em>Worldcoin, which recently launched with a user base of two million from its trial phase, plans to expand its eyeball-scanning operations to 20 countries, raising concerns over potential privacy risks associated with the collection and storage of sensitive biometric data.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The UK&#8217;s data regulator has announced its plan to investigate Worldcoin, a cryptocurrency project spearheaded by Sam Altman, the CEO of OpenAI.&nbsp;</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2022-11-14-at-14.39.37-816x452-1.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="816" height="452" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2022-11-14-at-14.39.37-816x452-1.png" alt="UK Data Watchdog To Investigate Worldcoin Crypto Project Over Privacy Concerns" class="wp-image-205799" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2022-11-14-at-14.39.37-816x452-1.png 816w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2022-11-14-at-14.39.37-816x452-1-300x166.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2022-11-14-at-14.39.37-816x452-1-768x425.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2022-11-14-at-14.39.37-816x452-1-750x415.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 816px) 100vw, 816px" title="UK Data Watchdog To Investigate Worldcoin Crypto Project Over Privacy Concerns 19"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>The project, which offers users the opportunity to receive free cryptocurrency in exchange for their iris scans, has caught the attention of the Information Commissioner&#8217;s Office (ICO). The ICO spokesperson informed Reuters that they have taken notice of the recent launch of Worldcoin in the UK and have decided to initiate further inquiries into the matter. This move comes amid growing concerns over the potential implications of widespread iris scanning and the use of sensitive biometric information in a financial context.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/coin.jpeg"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="600" height="315" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/coin.jpeg" alt="UK Data Watchdog To Investigate Worldcoin Crypto Project Over Privacy Concerns" class="wp-image-205800" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/coin.jpeg 600w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/coin-300x158.jpeg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" title="UK Data Watchdog To Investigate Worldcoin Crypto Project Over Privacy Concerns 20"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p><a href="https://coincu.com/205302-worldcoin-token-openai-ceo-sam-altman/">Worldcoin</a>&#8216;s launch on Monday attracted a substantial user base, with two million individuals participating in the trial phase of the project. As the crypto initiative scales up its operations, it plans to conduct eyeball-scanning procedures in 20 countries, aiming for a global reach.</p>



<p>The concept of utilizing iris scans for digital identification and cryptocurrency rewards has raised eyebrows among privacy advocates and regulatory bodies alike. Critics argue that the collection and storage of biometric data on such a vast scale could pose serious privacy risks for individuals, potentially leading to identity theft and misuse of sensitive information.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1200x0.jpeg"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="683" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1200x0-1024x683.jpeg" alt="UK Data Watchdog To Investigate Worldcoin Crypto Project Over Privacy Concerns" class="wp-image-205801" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1200x0-1024x683.jpeg 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1200x0-300x200.jpeg 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1200x0-768x512.jpeg 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1200x0-750x500.jpeg 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1200x0-1140x760.jpeg 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1200x0.jpeg 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="UK Data Watchdog To Investigate Worldcoin Crypto Project Over Privacy Concerns 21"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>While Worldcoin promises free cryptocurrency as an incentive for users to participate, the use of biometric data remains a contentious issue. Proponents of the project claim that it can foster financial inclusion for those without access to traditional banking systems. However, detractors argue that such benefits may not outweigh the potential dangers associated with compromising biometric data.</p>



<p>As the ICO launches its investigation, Worldcoin&#8217;s future remains uncertain. The outcome of this inquiry will likely have significant implications not only for the project itself but also for the broader crypto industry&#8217;s approach to utilizing biometrics and handling user data.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER: </em></strong><em>The Information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>



<p>Join us to keep track of news: <a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Chubbi</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Coincu News</strong></p>
<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/205796-uk-data-watchdog-worldcoin-crypto-privacy/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/UK_Data_Watchdog_to_Investigate_Worldcoin_Crypto_Project_Over_Privacy-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sui Ecological Social Graph Protocol Releap Completes $2.1 Million Financing</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/205777-sui-protocol-releap-2-1-million-financing/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chubbi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 09:34:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sui]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sui Foundation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=205777</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Releap Protocol, a pioneering decentralized social graph protocol operating on the Sui ecosystem, has achieved a significant milestone by securing $2.1 million in financing. <p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/205777-sui-protocol-releap-2-1-million-financing/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>Sui Ecological Social Graph </em>&#8211; <em>Releap Protocol, a decentralized social graph, secures $2.1 million funding.</em></li>



<li><em>More than 30 venture capital companies and angel investors participate.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Releap Protocol, a pioneering decentralized social graph protocol operating on the </strong><a href="https://coincu.com/171302-sui-review/"><strong>Sui</strong></a><strong> ecosystem, has achieved a significant milestone by securing $2.1 million in financing.&nbsp;</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/FyKiLIiagAAI12O-1024x576.jpeg"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="576" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/FyKiLIiagAAI12O-1024x576.jpeg" alt="Sui Ecological Social Graph Protocol Releap Completes $2.1 Million Financing" class="wp-image-205792" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/FyKiLIiagAAI12O-1024x576.jpeg 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/FyKiLIiagAAI12O-300x169.jpeg 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/FyKiLIiagAAI12O-768x432.jpeg 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/FyKiLIiagAAI12O-750x422.jpeg 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/FyKiLIiagAAI12O-1140x641.jpeg 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/FyKiLIiagAAI12O.jpeg 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Sui Ecological Social Graph Protocol Releap Completes $2.1 Million Financing 22"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>The news was officially announced on July 25, marking a major stride in the development of the innovative social networking platform. The funding round witnessed the participation of numerous prominent investors, including Sui Foundation, GBV Capital, Big Brain Holdings, Shima Capital, Arweave Foundation, Assembly Partners, DWeb3 Capital, Impossible Finance, Solar Eco Fund, MoveBit, and more than 30 other venture capital firms and angel investors.</p>



<p>Sui Protocol&#8217;s Releap core vision is to establish a dynamic and decentralized social graph that revolutionizes the traditional social networking experience. Through its integration with the Sui ecosystem, Releap aims to create a vibrant and interconnected social network ecosystem that empowers users and cultivates a strong sense of community.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F13PAyOaYAEpbxi.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="614" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F13PAyOaYAEpbxi-1024x614.png" alt="Sui Ecological Social Graph Protocol Releap Completes $2.1 Million Financing" class="wp-image-205793" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F13PAyOaYAEpbxi-1024x614.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F13PAyOaYAEpbxi-300x180.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F13PAyOaYAEpbxi-768x461.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F13PAyOaYAEpbxi-1536x922.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F13PAyOaYAEpbxi-2048x1229.png 2048w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F13PAyOaYAEpbxi-750x450.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F13PAyOaYAEpbxi-1140x684.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Sui Ecological Social Graph Protocol Releap Completes $2.1 Million Financing 23"></a></figure></div>


<p>Currently, Releap Protocol is in the beta phase of development, where it is actively refining its platform to provide a seamless and user-friendly social networking experience. With the successful completion of the $2.1 million financing round, the project is poised to accelerate its growth and expand its features to cater to a broader audience.</p>



<p>The involvement of prominent venture capital companies and angel investors underscores the industry&#8217;s recognition of Releap Protocol&#8217;s potential and the importance of its contribution to the blockchain and social networking landscape. These partnerships not only signify the growing interest in decentralized social networks but also signal a strong vote of confidence in Releap&#8217;s mission and execution.</p>



<p>As a social network-centric ecosystem, Releap Protocol envisions a future where users have more control over their data and interactions. By leveraging the decentralized nature of blockchain technology, Releap aims to eliminate intermediaries, enhance privacy and security, and provide users with a unique and rewarding social experience.</p>



<p>With the completion of the financing round, Releap Protocol is now well-positioned to push forward with its development plans and bring its ambitious vision to fruition. As the project continues to make strides in the blockchain and social networking space, industry enthusiasts eagerly await the official launch and the opportunity to explore the future of decentralized social networking.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER: </em></strong><em>The Information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>



<p>Join us to keep track of news: <a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Chubbi</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Coincu News</strong></p>
<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/205777-sui-protocol-releap-2-1-million-financing/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Sui_Ecological_Social_Graph_Protocol_Releap_Completes_2_1_Million-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alphapo Hot Wallet Losses Surge to $60M, ZachXBT Reports</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/205773-alphapo-hot-wallet-losses-surge-to-60m-zachxbt/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Annie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 09:27:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Alphapo]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Alphapo Hot Wallet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hacker]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[scam crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ZachXBT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=205773</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Key Points: ZachXBT has recently tweeted about the Alphapo hot wallet heist, disclosing that an additional $37 million worth of TRON and BTC has been found to be stolen due to this cyberattack. The total amount pilfered from Alphapo has now surged to a staggering $60 million, making it a high-profile attack in the cryptocurrency [&#8230;]<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/205773-alphapo-hot-wallet-losses-surge-to-60m-zachxbt/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>Cryptocurrency heist at Alphapo: $60M stolen.</em></li>



<li><em>Intricate web of transactions and sophisticated operation.</em></li>



<li><em>Collaboration needed to combat rising threats in the crypto space.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>ZachXBT has recently tweeted about the Alphapo hot wallet heist, disclosing that an additional $37 million worth of TRON and BTC has been found to be stolen due to this cyberattack. </strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image is-style-default">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1819.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="861" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1819-1024x861.png" alt="image 1819" class="wp-image-205784" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1819-1024x861.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1819-300x252.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1819-768x646.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1819-750x631.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1819-1140x959.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1819.png 1290w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Alphapo Hot Wallet Losses Surge to $60M, ZachXBT Reports 24"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>The total amount pilfered from Alphapo has now surged to a staggering $60 million, making it a high-profile attack in the cryptocurrency world. The heist has raised concerns over security and highlighted potential vulnerabilities within the crypto ecosystem.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Hack update: An additional $37M stolen on TRON &amp; BTC from this hack has been located.<br><br>This now brings the total amount stolen to $60M.<br><br>This hack appears to likely have been done by Lazarus as they create a very distinct fingerprint on-chain. <a href="https://t.co/ACGSXiDwW3" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/ACGSXiDwW3</a></p>&mdash; ZachXBT (@zachxbt) <a href="https://twitter.com/zachxbt/status/1683747073227624448?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener">July 25, 2023</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>As per previous <a href="https://twitter.com/zachxbt/status/1683747073227624448" target="_blank" data-type="URL" data-id="https://twitter.com/zachxbt/status/1683747073227624448" rel="noreferrer noopener">reports </a>from ZachXBT&#8217;s monitoring, it was initially reported that the Alphapo hot wallet had been breached, leading to a theft of $23 million in US dollars. In response to the attack, the Alphapo HyperDrop client took immediate action by disabling withdrawals to prevent further losses.</p>



<p>The investigation into the theft has unveiled an intricate web of transactions, revealing a sophisticated and well-coordinated operation. The stolen funds were first moved to the Ethereum network, presumably in an attempt to obfuscate the source and origin of the funds. Subsequently, they were cross-linked to the Avalanche network and Bitcoin (BTC), creating multiple layers of complexity to mask the hacker&#8217;s tracks.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image is-style-default">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Alphapo-Hot-Wallet.jpeg"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="768" height="432" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Alphapo-Hot-Wallet.jpeg" alt="Alphapo Hot Wallet" class="wp-image-205786" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Alphapo-Hot-Wallet.jpeg 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Alphapo-Hot-Wallet-300x169.jpeg 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Alphapo-Hot-Wallet-750x422.jpeg 750w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" title="Alphapo Hot Wallet Losses Surge to $60M, ZachXBT Reports 25"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>Attributing the hack to a group with potential links to Lazarus, a notorious cybercriminal organization known for conducting large-scale attacks, has further fueled concerns about the rising threats posed by such sophisticated hacking entities in the cryptocurrency space.</p>



<p>The Alphapo heist serves as a stark reminder that the cryptocurrency world is not impervious to cyberattacks, and all stakeholders must remain vigilant to combat and deter such criminal activities. Collaborative efforts between exchanges, law enforcement agencies, and cybersecurity experts will be essential in bringing the perpetrators to justice and restoring trust in the cryptocurrency ecosystem.</p>



<p id="block-643c4ba8-b40b-4525-9a96-f280dbfbeb9d"><strong><em>DISCLAIMER:&nbsp;</em></strong><em>The Information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>
<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/205773-alphapo-hot-wallet-losses-surge-to-60m-zachxbt/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Alphapo-Hot-Wallet-Losses-Surge-to-60M-ZachXBT-Reports-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
