<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 13:26:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Cash jumps to 14-month high amid South Korea volume spike</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-cash-jumps-to-14-month-high-amid-south-korea-volume-spike/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-cash-jumps-to-14-month-high-amid-south-korea-volume-spike/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 13:26:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BCH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[South Korea]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-cash-jumps-to-14-month-high-amid-south-korea-volume-spike/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin Cash has skyrocketed to a 14-month high above $320, hitting highs of $326 on Coinbase. BCH upside momentum has increased since Wall Street-backed EDX listed the coin alongside BTC, ETH and LTC. A spike in volume on South Korea exchange Upbit helped push CBH price higher on Friday. Bitcoin Cash rallied to its highest [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-cash-jumps-to-14-month-high-amid-south-korea-volume-spike/">Bitcoin Cash jumps to 14-month high amid South Korea volume spike</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitcoin Cash has skyrocketed to a 14-month high above $320, hitting highs of $326 on Coinbase.</li>
<li>BCH upside momentum has increased since Wall Street-backed EDX listed the coin alongside BTC, ETH and LTC.</li>
<li>A spike in volume on South Korea exchange Upbit helped push CBH price higher on Friday.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin-cash/">Bitcoin Cash</a> rallied to its highest price in 14 months on Friday morning, trading at highs of $326 on US-based crypto exchange Coinbase.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Why is BCH price rallying today?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin Cash had stagnated below $165 since dipping below the level in June last year. However, with Bitcoin rallying to above $31k amid bullish sentiment buoyed by BlackRock&rsquo;s spot ETF filing, BCH roared to a <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-cash-price-hits-1-year-high-as-bch-soars-72-this-week/">one-year high</a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The bulls have been relentless since, with price crossing the psychological $300 mark today with more than 30% gains in 24 hours. The cryptocurrency has rallied nearly 200% over the past two weeks, and is now in the green by 110% over the past year.</p>
<p dir="ltr">It is notable that the price of <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/bch/">BCH</a> had raced to a new year high last week after EDX Markets, a new crypto exchange backed by major Wall Street companies including Fidelity and Charles Schwab, listed Bitcoin Cash. EDX only lists three other coins &ndash; BTC, ETH and LTC.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Enthusiasm across the BCH community from this listing has added to the upside momentum. On Friday, the positive outlook on the cryptocurrency&rsquo;s potential saw volume spike on a leading South Korea-based crypto platform.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As crypto markets bid to hold onto the positive sentiment, Bitcoin Cash appears to be getting some extra leg from South Korea. Over the past 24 hours, the BCH/KRW pair on crypto exchange Upbit rose to $557 million, more than thrice the volume of BTC/KRW and nearly 6x greater than BCH/USD.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Data from CoinGecko shows daily trading volume across all exchanges has increased 165% in the past 24 hours to over $2.4 billion. As IntoTheBlock <a href="https://twitter.com/intotheblock/status/1674432186660057092">points out</a>, BCH volume rose to above $750 million on Thursday, a one-year high.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">1/2 Bitcoin Cash (BCH) soars 70% in a week, riding high on its recent inclusion on <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/EDX?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#EDX</a>, the Citadel Securities-Backed Crypto Exchange. Yesterday saw the highest volume of BCH transacted in a year, exceeding a staggering $750M.&#128279; <a href="https://t.co/1qZbEChogW">https://t.co/1qZbEChogW</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/BitcoinCash?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#BitcoinCash</a> <a href="https://t.co/OEOYG61sQR">pic.twitter.com/OEOYG61sQR</a></p>
<p>&mdash; IntoTheBlock (@intotheblock) <a href="https://twitter.com/intotheblock/status/1674432186660057092?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 29, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-cash-jumps-to-14-month-high-amid-south-korea-volume-spike/">Bitcoin Cash jumps to 14-month high amid South Korea volume spike</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-cash-jumps-to-14-month-high-amid-south-korea-volume-spike/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Solana technical analysis update – can it jump to $40?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/solana-technical-analysis-update-can-it-jump-to-40/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/solana-technical-analysis-update-can-it-jump-to-40/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mircea Vasiu]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 13:02:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/solana-technical-analysis-update-can-it-jump-to-40/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Solana rallied in 2023 but failed to break above the horizontal resistance A bullish case remains valid unless the price moves below the 2022 lows If it breaks above horizontal resistance, Solana may trade above $40 Cryptocurrency investors must be thrilled with the 2023 price action. After all, Bitcoin bounced from last year&#8217;s lows, triggering [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/solana-technical-analysis-update-can-it-jump-to-40/">Solana technical analysis update – can it jump to $40?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Solana rallied in 2023 but failed to break above the horizontal resistance</li>
<li>A bullish case remains valid unless the price moves below the 2022 lows</li>
<li>If it breaks above horizontal resistance, Solana may trade above $40</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p>Cryptocurrency investors must be thrilled with the 2023 price action. After all, Bitcoin bounced from last year&rsquo;s lows, triggering a similar move in other major cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>Solana followed suit.</p>
<p>The price more than doubled this year, rising from $10 to over $25 in what appeared to be a clear bullish breakout.</p>
<p>However, after trading above $26 in January, the market failed to build on the bullish trend. Instead, a consolidation started, bringing doubts to bullish traders.</p>
<p>The best way to clear such doubts is to look at the bigger picture. As the chart below shows, it is difficult to build a bullish case while the market holds below horizontal resistance.</p>
<p>However, the 2022 lows remain in place, so one can build a bullish scenario as long as the market does not dip below those lows.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/05/30/1688128168792-a49e9d0f-ca7e-491c-b8fb-341615b6e752.jpg" style="width: 1800px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="1800" height="487"></p>
<p><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/SOLUSD/?exchange=CRYPTO" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Solana chart by TradingView</a></p>
<h2>A break above horizontal resistance should trigger more gains</h2>
<p>Solana&rsquo;s price remains bearish while below horizontal resistance. However, a break above it implies more strength ahead.</p>
<p>That is especially true if the US dollar&rsquo;s weakness resumes. So far in 2023, the dollar traded with a mixed tone.</p>
<p>But as the Fed is on pause, renewed weakness will bode well for cryptocurrencies and for Solana.</p>
<p>A daily close above horizontal resistance opens the gates for a move above $40. If the Fed believes that the US inflation data follows the right path, the dollar should weaken in the year&rsquo;s second half.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/solana-technical-analysis-update-can-it-jump-to-40/">Solana technical analysis update – can it jump to $40?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/solana-technical-analysis-update-can-it-jump-to-40/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A bullish case for Ripple – if current lows hold</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/a-bullish-case-for-ripple-if-current-lows-hold/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/a-bullish-case-for-ripple-if-current-lows-hold/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mircea Vasiu]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 12:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/a-bullish-case-for-ripple-if-current-lows-hold/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ripple builds energy to break higher A series of higher lows points to more upside The bullish case is valid as long as the price holds above $0.3 Ripple is one of the major cryptocurrencies that rallied in 2023. It opened the trading year at $0.3 and rallied all the way to $0.55. But traders [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/a-bullish-case-for-ripple-if-current-lows-hold/">A bullish case for Ripple – if current lows hold</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul class="decimal_type">
<li>Ripple builds energy to break higher</li>
<li>A series of higher lows points to more upside</li>
<li>The bullish case is valid as long as the price holds above $0.3</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p>Ripple is one of the major cryptocurrencies that rallied in 2023. It opened the trading year at $0.3 and rallied all the way to $0.55.</p>
<p>But traders now wonder if the inability to move above $0.55 is a sign of weakness.</p>
<p>It may well be.</p>
<p>However, if Ripple holds above $0.33, a technical trader can build a bullish case for it.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/05/30/1688125686653-40c677ee-6985-40bb-8063-ff3546997ede.jpg" style="width: 1800px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="1800" height="490"></p>
<p><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XRPUSD/?exchange=CRYPTO" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Ripple chart by TradingView</a></p>
<h2>Ripple tries to break above the $0.55 resistance level</h2>
<p>Ripple tried to break above the $0.55 resistance level three times in a row. It failed every time.</p>
<p>But each rejection brought nothing but new buyers buying the dip. Moreover, the series of higher lows holds intact, suggesting that the market builds energy to break above horizontal resistance.</p>
<p>Providing the price action holds above $0.3, which proved to be horizontal support part of a possible double bottom pattern, one can build a bullish case for Ripple.</p>
<p>First, the double bottom pattern does suggest that more upside should follow a break above $0.55.</p>
<p>Second, the market built a series of higher lows, a typical structure in bullish markets.</p>
<p>Therefore, bulls may want to wait for Ripple to close above $0.55 until establishing long positions. Ripple should find little or no resistance until the $0.75 level on such a move.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/a-bullish-case-for-ripple-if-current-lows-hold/">A bullish case for Ripple – if current lows hold</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/a-bullish-case-for-ripple-if-current-lows-hold/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chancer to usher a new era of betting as Mastercard eyes a multi-token network</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-to-usher-a-new-era-of-betting-as-mastercard-eyes-a-multi-token-network/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-to-usher-a-new-era-of-betting-as-mastercard-eyes-a-multi-token-network/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Motiur Rahman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 11:41:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technical Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-to-usher-a-new-era-of-betting-as-mastercard-eyes-a-multi-token-network/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Chancer raises $421.4k in two weeks The token&#8217;s P2P model in betting is attracting investors Chancer&#8217;s value to increase in the subsequent presale phases and upon listing Blockchain is revolutionising traditional sectors in good ways, with the latest being betting. Chancer has been the key project in this shift, focusing on new ways investors can [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-to-usher-a-new-era-of-betting-as-mastercard-eyes-a-multi-token-network/">Chancer to usher a new era of betting as Mastercard eyes a multi-token network</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Chancer raises $421.4k in two weeks</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The token&rsquo;s P2P model in betting is attracting investors</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Chancer&rsquo;s value to increase in the subsequent presale phases and upon listing</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Blockchain is revolutionising traditional sectors in good ways, with the latest being betting. Chancer has been the key project in this shift, focusing on new ways investors can participate in betting and earn. The primary innovative feature of Chancer is its peer-to-peer betting that allows investors to predict in markets created by themselves. Investors have shown enthusiasm for the project, buying more than $421.4k worth of Chancer tokens in the first phase of a&nbsp;<a href="https://chancer.com/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=invezz&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=investment_opportunity" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>presale</u></a> that opened two weeks ago. The successful presale underlines the growing uptake of crypto, with Mastercard considering a multi-token network (MTN).</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Mastercard to make digital transactions secure and interoperable with MTN.</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Payments giant Mastercard wants to enhance digital transactions&rsquo; security, interoperability, and scalability with a Multi-Token Network (MTN) product. The company&nbsp;<a href="https://www.mastercard.com/news/perspectives/2023/blockchain-and-digital-assets-putting-trust-at-the-center/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>says</u></a> MTN will enable efficient and cost-effective payments by using digital assets.</p>
<p dir="ltr">MTN is also expected to enhance identity management and permissions through blockchain networks, thus building trusted business interactions. Using digital identities will also help counter fraud common in card-related transactions.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The new product by Mastercard underlines that big players are getting into the sector, building needed trust. For a global payment network like Mastercard, it means the project will increase digital asset visibility and allow new ones to succeed.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Peer-to-peer betting by Chancer. What is it?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">As the name suggests, peer-to-peer (P2P) is a betting model permitting user relations with each other. Chancer is pioneering a P2P betting where users can build their betting markets via a secure decentralised system. Users can determine what instruments, events, or situations they want to bet on and invite others (peers) into that betting market.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer has the edge over the traditional betting markets in that investors are not restricted to the odds and rules common in betting platforms. They play by their rules and odds betting through Chancer.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">With the ability to create a betting market from almost anything, Chancer brings fun to betting and allows flexibility to investors. It also expands the earning opportunities for investors as they can create limitless betting markets via the P2P model.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>What is the value proposition of Chancer?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer carries value in letting investors create betting markets and earn rewards on successful outcomes against peers. Investors can bet on events from football to politics and elections. But of course, Chancer is built with an investment focus rather than betting.</p>
<p dir="ltr">One of the ways to unlock value through Chancer is by creating predictive markets. Investors get rewarded for market-making activities. It means investors are rewarded for their interests and expertise by participating in the Chancer project.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The second way is through staking $CHANCER. Investors can stake the tokens for yields, thus unlocking liquidity and facilitating the platform&rsquo;s growth. Other ways to earn include token rewards for promoting Chancer to others.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Is Chancer an ideal investment?&nbsp;</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer could be an ideal investment if you are looking for a project with huge growth potential. Betting markets are fast-growing, and the entry of Chancer offers a leeway for investors to do it differently.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Alongside the ability to earn through P2P betting, investors who feel locked out of the traditional markets can find Chancer ideal.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The growth of the Chancer platform could fuel an increase in the value of the token and generate enormous returns for investors. For a token of a novel project like betting, price increases for $CHANCER can be up to 1,000%.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Does buying $CHANCER on presale make sense?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Any token that is newly listed is best bought at the presale. The price level is low, and there is a potential to earn big when it is listed on exchanges.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer&rsquo;s presale will occur in 12 stages, each with a higher price than the previous one. As such, the price is the lowest in the first phase and the most attractive.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-to-usher-a-new-era-of-betting-as-mastercard-eyes-a-multi-token-network/">Chancer to usher a new era of betting as Mastercard eyes a multi-token network</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-to-usher-a-new-era-of-betting-as-mastercard-eyes-a-multi-token-network/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Memecoin MOOKY Raises $900,000 Ahead of Its Final Presale Stage</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/memecoin-mooky-raises-900000-ahead-of-its-final-presale-stage/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/memecoin-mooky-raises-900000-ahead-of-its-final-presale-stage/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire &#160;]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 10:36:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=144650</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>New York, New York, June 30th, 2023, Chainwire Memecoin Mooky is gearing up for its final presale phase, having raised $900,000 to date. More than just a novel crypto token, Mooky aims to support the environment through a major tree-planting campaign. Mooky will be a community-driven platform whose governance lies in the hands of its [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/memecoin-mooky-raises-900000-ahead-of-its-final-presale-stage/">Memecoin MOOKY Raises $900,000 Ahead of Its Final Presale Stage</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>New York, New York, June 30th, 2023, Chainwire</strong></p>
<p>Memecoin Mooky is gearing up for its final presale phase, having raised $900,000 to date. More than just a novel crypto token, Mooky aims to support the environment through a major tree-planting campaign.</p>
<p>Mooky will be a community-driven platform whose governance lies in the hands of its token holders. While the MOOKY token draws its cues from other successful memecoins, the project has a more ambitious mandate. Mooky was conceived to increase awareness of global environmental challenges and to provide real-world solutions.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" src="https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/1_1688110387jD2jn6a98F.jpg"></p>
<p>The project aims to raise enough funds to sustain an extensive reforestation initiative in key locations around the world. As part of its commitment to nature, Mooky has earmarked donations to charities working on sustainable environmental causes.</p>
<p>From a crypto-economic perspective, the MOOKY token features zero tax and low slippage, providing ample incentives for traders to get involved. Underpinning the project is a deep lore that aligns with Mooky&rsquo;s core goals.</p>
<p>Mooky is based on the concept of a mythical land called Pygmy. This fantastical realm has stunning landscapes, abundant vegetation, and wildlife. As settlers came to the island, they destroyed the vegetation and polluted the air. The monkeys of Pygmy decide to fight back peacefully, teaching the settlers how to respect nature and live harmoniously. Under the leadership of Mooky, they become united and restore nature.</p>
<p><iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/IiPyd5VoQIg"></iframe></p>
<p>To support the project&rsquo;s development while providing greater opportunities for community participation, Mooky has created a collection of 1,000 NFTs. Each NFT is linked to a tree planted in the real world. Holders can access the Ventures Club, which grants access to exclusive rewards and events.</p>
<p>With five days left in the <a href="blank" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">$MOOKY token presale</a>, there is still ample opportunity for crypto holders to get involved and capture the upside to a project that combines memes and nature to great effect.</p>
<h3>About MOOKY</h3>
<p>MOOKY is a community-driven initiative launched in 2023 that embraces the spirit of digital innovation to make a positive impact on the environment. More than just a meme token, MOOKY represents a global community united by a common goal: to inspire change and contribute to global tree-planting efforts.</p>
<p>MOOKY also stands as a symbol of creativity in the digital space, offering unique 3D NFTs that are each linked to real-world tree-planting initiatives. These NFTs serve not only as digital collectibles but also as an entry ticket to the exclusive Mooky Ventures Club, a vibrant community of environmentally conscious enthusiasts.</p>
<p>MOOKY is more than a digital token; it&rsquo;s a movement aiming to better our environment while fostering a unique and engaging digital ecosystem. Join MOOKY in its journey to make a difference and follow the community on various social channels to stay updated.</p>
<p>Users can purchase MOOKY <a href="https://buy.mooky.io/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">here</a>.</p>
<p><a href="https://mooky.io/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><strong>Website</strong></a><strong> | </strong><a href="https://buy.mooky.io/#buy" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><strong>Presale</strong></a><strong> | </strong><a href="https://t.me/MOOKYTOKEN" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><strong>Telegram</strong></a><strong> | </strong><a href="https://www.instagram.com/mookytroop/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><strong>Instagram</strong></a><strong> | </strong><a href="https://twitter.com/MOOKYcoin" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><strong>Twitter</strong></a><strong> | </strong><a href="https://discord.com/invite/xHZQMNztdG" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><strong>Discord</strong></a></p>
<h3>Contact</h3>
<p>Mookashi N, contact@mooky.io</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/memecoin-mooky-raises-900000-ahead-of-its-final-presale-stage/">Memecoin MOOKY Raises $900,000 Ahead of Its Final Presale Stage</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/memecoin-mooky-raises-900000-ahead-of-its-final-presale-stage/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Five Marketing Strategies for Crypto Casinos That Actually Work and Boost Revenue</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/five-marketing-strategies-for-crypto-casinos-that-actually-work-and-boost-revenue/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 10:31:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/five-marketing-strategies-for-crypto-casinos-that-actually-work-and-boost-revenue/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Marketing strategies play a crucial role in the success of any business, including crypto casinos. With the rising popularity of cryptocurrencies and online gambling, crypto casinos face fierce competition in attracting and retaining customers. To stand out in this highly competitive market, Bitcoin casinos need to adopt effective marketing strategies. That&#8217;s why this article will [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/five-marketing-strategies-for-crypto-casinos-that-actually-work-and-boost-revenue/">Five Marketing Strategies for Crypto Casinos That Actually Work and Boost Revenue</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Marketing strategies play a crucial role in the success of any business, including crypto casinos. With the rising popularity of <a href="https://coinjournal.net/cryptocurrencies/">cryptocurrencies</a> and online gambling, crypto casinos face fierce competition in attracting and retaining customers.</p>
<p dir="ltr">To stand out in this highly competitive market, <a href="https://bet999.io/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Bitcoin casinos</a> need to adopt effective marketing strategies. That&rsquo;s why this article will explore five marketing strategies for crypto casinos that have proven to be successful.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>1. Social media marketing</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/social-media/">Social media platforms</a> have become powerful tools for marketing in recent years. Crypto casinos can leverage the vast reach and engagement potential of platforms such as Facebook, Twitter, and Instagram to promote their services.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Moreover, Bitcoin casinos can attract and retain a loyal following by creating engaging content, such as posts, images, and videos, and sharing relevant updates about games, promotions, and bonuses.</p>
<p dir="ltr">It is important to use concise and catchy captions to grab users&rsquo; attention and encourage them to take action, such as visiting the casino&rsquo;s website or signing up for an account.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Moreover, selecting the appropriate social media platforms is essential to reach the target audience effectively. Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, and LinkedIn are popular choices for promoting crypto casinos.</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, it&rsquo;s important to remember that each platform has its own unique features and user demographics, so it&rsquo;s essential to research and understand where the target audience is most active.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">2. Influencer partnerships</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Influencer marketing has become a dominant force in the digital realm. <a href="https://blog.bet999.io/anonymous-bitcoin-casinos/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Casinos accepting Bitcoin</a> can collaborate with popular influencers and content creators who have a substantial following in the gambling or cryptocurrency niche.</p>
<p dir="ltr">These influencers can endorse the casino&rsquo;s services through sponsored posts, videos, or live streams, reaching a wider audience and generating interest in the platform.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Short, punchy messages from influencers can create a sense of trust and credibility among their followers, leading to increased brand awareness and potential conversions.</p>
<p dir="ltr">It is crucial to find influencers with a significant following in the cryptocurrency, blockchain, or online gambling niches.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Look for influencers whose audience aligns with the target market of the crypto casino. Research their engagement rates, audience demographics, and the overall quality of their content to ensure they are a good fit for the brand.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Influencer marketing works best when the partnership appears authentic and genuine. It&rsquo;s important to choose influencers genuinely interested in cryptocurrencies or online gambling with a history of providing valuable content to their followers.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This helps establish trust and credibility among their audience, making them more receptive to the endorsement of the crypto casino.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">3. Referral programs</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Word-of-mouth marketing remains one of the most powerful and cost-effective strategies for businesses. By implementing referral programs, crypto casinos can encourage existing customers to refer their friends and family to the platform.</p>
<p dir="ltr">By keeping the referral process simple and rewarding, crypto casinos can tap into the power of social networks as satisfied customers spread the word about their positive experiences. Short and clear instructions regarding the <a href="https://blog.hubspot.com/service/customer-referral-program" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">referral process</a> can increase participation and make it easier for users to take action.</p>
<p dir="ltr">To encourage users to refer their friends and family to the crypto casino, it is essential to offer attractive incentives. Consider offering rewards such as bonus funds, free spins, or exclusive promotions to both the referrer and the referred individual.</p>
<p dir="ltr">These incentives provide a tangible benefit that motivates users to participate in the referral program.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">4. Email marketing</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Despite the rise of social media, email marketing continues to be a valuable tool for engaging with customers. Crypto casinos can build an email list by offering incentives, such as exclusive promotions or freebies, to visitors who subscribe to their newsletters.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Once they have a list of subscribers, casinos can send regular emails with updates on new games, upcoming events, and special offers. Using short and impactful subject lines can grab recipients&rsquo; attention and entice them to open the emails.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Additionally, personalization and segmentation techniques can be employed to tailor the content to the interests and preferences of each subscriber.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Start by building an email list of interested subscribers. Offer incentives, such as exclusive promotions, free spins, or bonus funds, to encourage visitors to sign up for the casino&rsquo;s newsletter.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Place subscription forms prominently on the website and landing pages, and communicate the value subscribers will receive by joining the list. Keep the signup process simple and straightforward, asking for only essential information like name and email address.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">5. Content marketing</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Creating and sharing valuable content is an effective way to establish a crypto casino as an authority in the industry and attract organic traffic. By publishing informative blog posts, guides, or videos related to cryptocurrencies, online gambling strategies, and casino reviews, crypto casinos can provide value to their target audience.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Short, concise paragraphs and bullet points can make the content easy to read and digest. By optimizing the content for search engines, using relevant keywords, and promoting it on social media platforms and forums, crypto casinos can increase their visibility and drive traffic to their website.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Before creating content, it&rsquo;s essential to understand your target audience&rsquo;s preferences, interests, and pain points. Research the demographics, behaviors, and motivations of your ideal players. This knowledge will help you create content that resonates with them and addresses their needs.</p>
<p dir="ltr">You can also optimize your content for search engines to improve its visibility and reach. Conduct keyword research to identify relevant terms and phrases your target audience searches for.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Incorporate these <a href="https://ahrefs.com/seo/glossary/keywords" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">keywords</a> into your content, including titles, headings, and meta descriptions. Short and compelling meta descriptions can entice users to click on your content in search engine results.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Use social media in your favor</h2>
<p dir="ltr">In conclusion, the success of a crypto casino heavily relies on effective marketing strategies. By leveraging the power of social media marketing, influencer partnerships, referral programs, email marketing, and content marketing, crypto casinos can attract and retain customers in a highly competitive market.</p>
<p dir="ltr">If you keep your sentences short and impactful, these strategies are more likely to effectively convey the key messages and entice users to take action. This will ultimately lead to the growth and success of the crypto casino.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/five-marketing-strategies-for-crypto-casinos-that-actually-work-and-boost-revenue/">Five Marketing Strategies for Crypto Casinos That Actually Work and Boost Revenue</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chancer presale storms to $420k amid positive crypto sentiment</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-presale-storms-to-420k-amid-positive-crypto-sentiment/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-presale-storms-to-420k-amid-positive-crypto-sentiment/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 10:08:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-presale-storms-to-420k-amid-positive-crypto-sentiment/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>CHANCER presale has hit $421k days after launch to demonstrate the huge demand among investors. The predictive markets platform is expected to go live later this year, with experts noting its potential to change the global betting industry. For investors, buying $CHANCER at the current price of $0.01 offers could be a great opportunity. With [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-presale-storms-to-420k-amid-positive-crypto-sentiment/">Chancer presale storms to $420k amid positive crypto sentiment</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">CHANCER presale has hit $421k days after launch to demonstrate the huge demand among investors.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The predictive markets platform is expected to go live later this year, with experts noting its potential to change the global betting industry.</li>
<li dir="ltr">For investors, buying $CHANCER at the current price of $0.01 offers could be a great opportunity.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">With the broader <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/category/markets/">crypto market</a> looking for a foothold amid predictions of a bullish flip, Chancer&rsquo;s presale has notched past the $420k mark to highlight the overall market sentiment.</p>
<p dir="ltr">More aptly, the blockchain-based predictive markets platform has seen over 42.1 million of its $CHANCER tokens sold out just days into its recently launched presale event. Could Chancer offer that new opportunity that investors are hunting for ahead of the next bull cycle? &nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Early birds can find out more<a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=media&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal">&nbsp;<u>here</u></a>.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bear markets are for building &ndash; and investing</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> price staying above the $30k level and looking likely to target the next resistance at $34k is a great encouragement for bulls. The same can be said of Ethereum, which has moved closer to regaining the $2k level in recent weeks amid the spot ETF-driven bullish momentum.</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, the broader acknowledgement is that the market hasn&rsquo;t completely turned the corner from the 2022 bear cycle. Yet this in itself is an opportunity for projects and to a larger extent investors, with bear markets seen as the time to build, or BUIDL as compared to the common <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-power-of-hodl/">HODL</a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Projects that build during market downturns often have the ample time to focus on product development, taking into account roadmap goals to deliver. And for investors, the bear market often accords the opportunity to buy low and position oneself for potential windfall when the bulls come charging.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Could Chancer be one of the projects? Highly likely as the team leverages the pre-bull market phase to bring to market a potentially industry-disruptive platform.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Chancer?</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=media&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Chancer</u></a> is a blockchain-based predictive markets platform that aims to become the global destination for decentralised betting.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Leveraging the blockchain technology and a crypto token will bring the benefits of a truly decentralised market, with holders of the native $CHANCER participating in future developments via a governance structure.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As for how Chancer works, the key is in its removal of the power of the bookmaker. Instead of the centralised control that sees bookmakers decide which markets and odds to offer to bettors, Chancer takes that power and hands it to $CHANCER holders.</p>
<p dir="ltr">On Chancer you don&rsquo;t suffer the restrictions of traditional betting platforms &ndash; its &ldquo;your game, your rules, your odds.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">In short, participants create their own prediction events, set the odds and rules. As a peer-to-peer (P2P) betting platform, you can invite family and friends. What&rsquo;s more there is a feature that allows users to broadcast their markets to more participants across the world, increasing the predictions and prizes.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Why would investing in Chancer today be worth it?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The global betting industry is a massive market, with<a href="https://www.grandviewresearch.com/industry-analysis/sports-betting-market-report" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">&nbsp;<u>estimates</u></a> for the next five years projecting a 10% compound annual growth rate. The adoption of blockchain technology across the sector is rising, with Chancer offering the most revolutionary platform.</p>
<p dir="ltr">While it would be unreasonable to predict $CHANCER to the moon now, the anticipation building around the project is massive. And with the token price currently only $0.01, buying now might be the best opportunity to maximise on the potential gains if fresh market demand catapults it to $1 or higher in 2024.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As noted, the wider sentiment is that a bull market is slowly gathering pace. If Chancer rolls into the market via the scheduled exchange listings after the presale, and the platform launch happens as expected, then a pop to new highs in 2025 would be highly likely.</p>
<p dir="ltr">If you bought $CHANCER today, 100% gains would be locked in when the token jumps to $0.021 at the end of the presale later in the quarter.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Can you earn passive income with Chancer?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">An opportunity to earn passive income on the investment is one of the key features investors will fancy $CHANCER for. &nbsp;Other than the anticipated gains on the value of the token as future demand pushes prices higher, holders can also earn passively through staking.</p>
<p dir="ltr">One can run validator nodes to support the network transaction processing and security and earn a reward from it. Node operators will earn 50% of the reward while those staking with the particular node will get the other 50%. Other than staking $CHANCER, users can earn from the Share2Earn program.</p>
<p>&nbsp;You can learn more about Chancer on their <a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=media&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">website</a>.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-presale-storms-to-420k-amid-positive-crypto-sentiment/">Chancer presale storms to $420k amid positive crypto sentiment</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-presale-storms-to-420k-amid-positive-crypto-sentiment/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>North Carolina lawmakers approve bill seeking study on state adoption of Bitcoin</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/north-carolina-lawmakers-approve-bill-seeking-study-on-state-adoption-of-bitcoin/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/north-carolina-lawmakers-approve-bill-seeking-study-on-state-adoption-of-bitcoin/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 17:43:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Policy and Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/north-carolina-lawmakers-approve-bill-seeking-study-on-state-adoption-of-bitcoin/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The &#8220;State Precious Metals Depository Study&#8221; bill received bipartisan support and passed 75-38. North Carolina could look into adding Bitcoin to its State Treasury if the bill is passed. In May, the house voted for another bill that seeks to ban CBDCs in the state.&#160; North Carolina&#8217;s lower house has passed a bill that could [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/north-carolina-lawmakers-approve-bill-seeking-study-on-state-adoption-of-bitcoin/">North Carolina lawmakers approve bill seeking study on state adoption of Bitcoin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">The &ldquo;State Precious Metals Depository Study&rdquo; bill received bipartisan support and passed 75-38.</li>
<li dir="ltr">North Carolina could look into adding Bitcoin to its State Treasury if the bill is passed.</li>
<li dir="ltr">In May, the house voted for another bill that seeks to ban CBDCs in the state.&nbsp;</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">North Carolina&rsquo;s lower house has passed a bill that could see the state initiate a study into the potential benefits of the state&rsquo;s Department of State Treasury adopting <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">&#128226; Another <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bipartisan?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Bipartisan</a> Victory in NC w/ passage of HB721 | <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Bitcoin</a>/<a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/DigitalAssets?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#DigitalAssets</a>/Custody Study Bill</p>
<p>-Passed 75-38<br>-GOP + Dems &#129309; Came Together<br>-Directs/Funds <a href="https://twitter.com/NCTreasurer?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@NCTreasurer</a> to Study Benefits of <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/BTC?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#BTC</a> + <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Custody?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Custody</a><br>-Led by <a href="https://twitter.com/NC_Blockchain?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@NC_Blockchain</a> + <a href="https://twitter.com/SoundMoneyDef?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@SoundMoneyDef</a></p>
<p>&#128206;<a href="https://t.co/0veKPZlbVJ">https://t.co/0veKPZlbVJ</a> <a href="https://t.co/nNYUbfmJd1">pic.twitter.com/nNYUbfmJd1</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Dan Spuller (@DanSpuller) <a href="https://twitter.com/DanSpuller/status/1674136730847399943?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 28, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">North Carolina seeks to add BTC to treasury</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The &ldquo;<em>State Precious Metals Depository Study</em>&rdquo; bill outlines the custody, insurance and liquidation of crypto assets held by the state. It passed 75-38 with bipartisan support and will now be debated in the Senate.</p>
<p dir="ltr">If passed, it will open the path for BTC and gold to be considered as assets that can be added to North Carolina&rsquo;s funds. Specifically, the house&rsquo;s approval puts North Carolina one step towards adding Bitcoin to the state&rsquo;s holdings.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>This is a very important step to a more formal acknowledgement of #bitcoin in North Carolina. Lots of behind the scenes work</em>,&rdquo; said Dan Spuller, Head of Industry Affairs at Blockchain Association.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Spuller noted that the passage of <a href="https://www.ncleg.gov/BillLookUp/2023/H721" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">HB721</a> marks the second time a bill pushed by the North Carolina Blockchain Initiative has received bipartisan support in the General Assembly in 2023.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In early May, the house unanimously passed HB690, a bill that banned the use of <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/cbdcs/">central bank digital currencies (CBDCs)</a> in payments in the state. The bill also bans North Carolina from participating in any testing of CBDC.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">The state of CBDCs globally</h2>
<p dir="ltr">A recent survey<a href="https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/study-shows-130-countries-exploring-central-bank-digital-currencies-2023-06-28/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">&nbsp;<u>showed</u></a> that 130 countries around the world were in various stages of development towards a central bank issued digital currency. According to US-based think tank Atlantic Council these countries included all G20 members.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As highlighted <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/top-banks-in-china-give-backing-to-the-digital-yuan/">here</a>, China&rsquo;s CBDC pilot continues and has support from country&rsquo;s major banks. Meanwhile, India and Brazil are set to launch their versions in 2024.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The European Central Bank is also looking to begin a pilot for the digital euro and the UK is exploring its &ldquo;Britcoin&rdquo; project. In the US, work on a CBDC is advancing only on its use at bank-to-bank level, with the retail digital dollar largely stuck.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/north-carolina-lawmakers-approve-bill-seeking-study-on-state-adoption-of-bitcoin/">North Carolina lawmakers approve bill seeking study on state adoption of Bitcoin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/north-carolina-lawmakers-approve-bill-seeking-study-on-state-adoption-of-bitcoin/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Best Cryptocurrency Launches In 2023. Experts Share The 12 Best New Cryptocurrencies To Invest In</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/the-best-cryptocurrency-launches-in-2023-experts-share-the-12-best-new-cryptocurrencies-to-invest-in/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice Davies]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 15:08:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/the-best-cryptocurrency-launches-in-2023-experts-share-the-12-best-new-cryptocurrencies-to-invest-in/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Hunting for the best new cryptos to invest in? Look no further than this list of 12 expert picks for the top new cryptocurrencies that seem ready to explode in 2023. From players making waves in the GameFi space to exciting new applications of AI technology, these 12 tokens have the potential to disrupt their [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-best-cryptocurrency-launches-in-2023-experts-share-the-12-best-new-cryptocurrencies-to-invest-in/">The Best Cryptocurrency Launches In 2023. Experts Share The 12 Best New Cryptocurrencies To Invest In</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Hunting for the best new cryptos to invest in? Look no further than this list of 12 expert picks for the top new cryptocurrencies that seem ready to explode in 2023. From players making waves in the GameFi space to exciting new applications of AI technology, these 12 tokens have the potential to disrupt their industries and offer significant gains this year.</p>
<p dir="ltr">They are:</p>
<ol>
<li>Chancer (CHANCER)</li>
<li>Shiba Memu (SHIBA MEMU)</li>
<li dir="ltr">Metacade (MCADE)</li>
<li dir="ltr">AltSignals (ASI)</li>
<li dir="ltr">Livepeer (LPT)</li>
<li dir="ltr">Balancer (BAL)</li>
<li dir="ltr">ApeCoin (APE)</li>
<li dir="ltr">Frax Finance (FRAX)/Frax Shares (FXS)</li>
<li dir="ltr">AngelBlock (THOL)</li>
<li dir="ltr">CryptoGPT (GPT)</li>
<li dir="ltr">Stepn (GMT)</li>
<li dir="ltr">Aptos (APT)</li>
</ol>
<p></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">1. Chancer (CHANCER) &mdash; Disrupting the betting industry in favor of bettors</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">What is Chancer?</h3>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Chancer</a> is the world&rsquo;s first blockchain-based decentralized predictive markets app. Chancer aims to revolutionize the betting and gambling industry by removing the need for a bookmaker or house entirely. Chancer is a betting facilitator that allows people to make peer-to-peer (P2P) so the odds are equal and never stacked against users. Any type of bet can be made, from a small bet among friends, to viral bets on huge events such as the Superbowl or the Oscars. Unlike traditional bookies, bets aren&rsquo;t limited to just sports.</p>
<p dir="ltr">All bets and pay-outs are made in Chancer&rsquo;s native token, CHANCER. Additionally, users can earn CHANCER simply by using the platform and placing bets, presenting users with a great opportunity to earn a passive income. The rewards don&rsquo;t stop there; users can get discounts on bets, making it cost-efficient for frequent bettors.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Why invest in Chancer (CHANCER)?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">CHANCER has great utility as a token as it fuels Chancer&rsquo;s entire platform. Given that the size of the betting and gambling industry was worth an eye-watering $64 billion last year, there&rsquo;s a real chance that Chancer will disrupt the market and take a sizeable chunk of it through its democratized, decentralized platform that puts bettors first. This makes Chancer a great investment with lots of potential for both betting and crypto enthusiasts.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>&gt;&gt;&gt; You can find more information, including how to buy Chancer&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong>here</strong></a><strong>&nbsp;&lt;&lt;&lt;</strong></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">2. Shiba Memu (SHIBA MEMU) &mdash; Cute meme coin powered by AI</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">What is Shiba Memu?</h3>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Shiba Memu</a> is a brand new meme coin based on the adorable Japanese Shiba Inu dog. However, this deceptively cute coin has a marketing powerhouse behind it and aims to do the work of 100+ marketing agencies in real time. It&rsquo;s leveraging the power of both blockchain and AI technology to transform marketing, taking time-consuming tasks from marketers so they can focus their efforts elsewhere.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu learns from successful marketing strategies, writes its own PR and promotes itself across relevant forums and social networks. It will be able to generate content based on the data that its AI continually analyzes, publishing this on several online platforms. It will then monitor and analyze the success of its marketing efforts and adjust them accordingly, constantly learning and improving content in order to optimize results.&nbsp;</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Why invest in Shiba Memu (SHIBA MEMU)?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu will undoubtedly benefit from being a cute, funny meme. However, unlike other meme coins in the market which rely on initial hype and then drastically lose value because they have no long-term use, SHIBA MEMU has innate utility as it fuels the entire Shiba Memu platform. Meme fans and crypto enthusiasts looking to invest in a meme coin and see long-term returns should consider Shiba Memu.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>&gt;&gt;&gt; You can find more information, including how to buy Shiba Memu&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong>here</strong></a><strong>&nbsp;&lt;&lt;&lt;</strong></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">3. AltSignals (ASI) &ndash; Using Cutting-Edge AI To Deliver Highly Accurate Trading Signals</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">What is AltSignals (ASI)?</h3>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://token.altsignals.io/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>AltSignals</u></a> is one of the market&rsquo;s leading trading signals providers, racking up over 50,000+ subscribers to its free signals and 1,400 members in its VIP group since 2017. Delivering some of the best signals in the game, AltSignals has sent out over 1,500 trading calls with an average accuracy of 64%. It&rsquo;s received overwhelmingly positive feedback on its <a href="https://uk.trustpilot.com/review/altsignals.io" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Trustpilot</u></a> page, earning almost 500 positive reviews with an average rating of 4.9/5.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Its recent results, for example, have been nothing but phenomenal. Its Binance Futures signals returned 2,163% with a 90% win rate in February, while January was even better: a 2,480% gain with a 92% accuracy. These outstanding results are made possible by AltSignals&rsquo; team of veteran traders and the AltAlgo&trade; algorithm. AltAlgo&trade; is AltSignals&rsquo; proprietary indicator, combining over 34 different filters to produce exceptional gains.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Recently, AltSignals launched its ASI token presale to support its next big project: the ActualizeAI algorithm. ActualizeAI will harness the most advanced AI technology to bring AltSignals&rsquo; average win rate above 80%. It plans to incorporate machine learning, predictive modeling, natural language processing, sentiment analysis, and reinforcement learning to deliver unparalleled results for traders.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Owning the ASI token means that holders will be the first to access the ActualizeAI algorithm but it also opens up a world of opportunity and insights in the platform&rsquo;s AI ecosystem. For example, the algorithm&rsquo;s sentiment analysis capabilities will be used to identify crypto presales before they explode, allowing them to secure an advantage over the competition.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Why Invest in AltSignals (ASI)?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">Becoming an ASI investor not only grants exclusive access to ActualizeAI&rsquo;s signals but also offers them a membership to the AI Members Club. This club is where users can provide feedback, contribute to product development, and participate in backtesting &ndash; all while earning ASI for their efforts. Some have speculated this could be a members-only Discord group, but it&rsquo;s likely AltSignals has a custom-built solution in mind.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">There are even planned trading tournaments where community members can show off their trading skills and compete to earn the most profit. This means they can not only profit from AltSignals&rsquo; trading signals but be in the running to win significant prizes! To help keep the AltSignals&rsquo; &nbsp;priorities aligned with the community, ASI will also act as a governance token, allowing users to vote on changes made to the algorithm and the platform.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Overall, AltSignals looks like one of the hottest new cryptocurrencies hitting the market. Its proven track record, coupled with a solid plan to take its trading signals to the next level, is expected to attract thousands of investors to the ASI token presale.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>&gt;&gt;&gt; You can find more information, including how to buy AltSignals&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://token.altsignals.io/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong>here</strong></a><strong>&nbsp;&lt;&lt;&lt;</strong></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">4. Metacade (MCADE) &ndash; Web3&rsquo;s Home of Play-To-Earn Gaming</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">What is Metacade (MCADE)?</h3>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=26" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade</u></a> is a community hub aiming to become Web3&rsquo;s number-one spot for all things play-to-earn (P2E) gaming. Its vision is to create a fun and dynamic virtual hangout where gamers, crypto fanatics, and developers come together to participate in the growing GameFi revolution. Users can read and share the latest alpha, interact with each other in real-time, and even play a direct role in shaping the GameFi industry for the better.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">At the heart of Metacade&rsquo;s core principles is maximizing user value, giving P2E gamers everything they need to grow their gaming income while enabling an organic community to grow and flourish. Not only will it feature exclusive gaming tournaments and fantastic giveaways with incredible prizes, but Metacade will also reward users for their contributions to the platform.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In return for sharing in-game advancement tips, helping others find the best games to play through reviews, and posting other valuable content, Metacade rewards players with the MCADE token for their role in growing the community. Moreover, in 2024, Metacade plans to launch a job and gig board. Here, members will find roles ranging from casual game-testing gigs that use the platform&rsquo;s native testing environment to salaried positions with Web3 and gaming titans.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Many investors are looking forward to the Metagrant scheme, which solves the real-world issue of inefficient game developer funding. The premise is simple: game developers submit their proposals to one of the Metagrant competitions, and MCADE holders vote on which games they believe should be funded. The winner is awarded financing from the Metacade treasury to turn their idea into reality, with the finished game added to Metacade&rsquo;s virtual arcade for the whole world to play.&nbsp;</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Why Invest in Metacade (MCADE)?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">For anyone looking to capitalize on the growing GameFi market, Metacade seems like the ideal crypto project. While P2E games come and go, Metacade is a unifying force that connects the entire industry, providing a one-stop platform for anyone looking to find their GameFi edge while participating in a vibrant community.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Additionally, social platforms are vital to gamers &ndash; just look at the rise of Discord and Twitch. Metacade has the same potential but with the added bonus of player rewards and a chance to direct the future of P2E. Soon after launch, Metacade will start working on its decentralized autonomous organization (DAO), which will further enhance the value of MCADE for investors, allowing them to vote on important decisions related to the platform&rsquo;s development.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>&gt;&gt;&gt; You can find more information, including how to buy Metacade&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=26" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong>here</strong></a><strong>&nbsp;&lt;&lt;&lt;</strong></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">5. Livepeer (LPT) &ndash; Solving a Massive Headache for Video Broadcasters</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">What is Livepeer (LPT)?</h3>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://livepeer.org/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Livepeer</u></a> is a decentralized video infrastructure protocol built on the Ethereum blockchain. It aims to provide a more cost-effective and efficient way for developers and businesses to build and operate video streaming applications.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Currently, the most expensive aspect for streaming providers is covering and reformatting video so that it can be played across different devices, also known as transcoding. Livepeer aims to disrupt this market by allowing broadcasters to use thousands of nodes, known as orchestrators, to create videos securely without eating heavily into their cash flow.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Users with excess computer resources can stake LPT tokens as collateral and earn crypto assets for handling the transcoding process. If a transcoder fails to deliver, it&rsquo;ll forfeit its staked LPT tokens as a penalty.&nbsp;</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Why Invest in Livepeer (LPT)?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">Livepeer addresses a significant pain point in the video streaming industry: high costs and complex technical requirements. By leveraging the power of decentralization, Livepeer can offer a more affordable and accessible alternative for video processing and delivery, making it an attractive option and one of the best new crypto coins for broadcasters looking to streamline their operations.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Additionally, Livepeer has plenty of real-world utility, which provides a solid backdrop for growth compared to more niche crypto projects. Its staking rewards as either a transcoder or delegator also offer retail investors an opportunity to generate annual returns of up to 23% &ndash; an attractive benefit of helping to contribute to the growing decentralized streaming market. &nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">6. Balancer (BAL) &ndash; The World&rsquo;s First Self-Balancing Weighted DeFi Portfolio</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">What is Balancer (BAL)?</h3>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://balancer.fi/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Balancer</u></a> is an innovative decentralized exchange (DEX) platform built on the Ethereum network. It enables the creation of customizable pools of up to eight tokens in different ratios, allowing for efficient trading and rebalancing of crypto assets. In contrast to traditional exchanges, Balancer does not require a central authority or order book. Instead, it relies on automated market makers (AMMs) to facilitate trades and maintain exchange liquidity.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Balancer&rsquo;s pools are analogous to index funds. Instead of holding a set of stocks at specific ratios, users can create pools of eight different digital currencies. For example, they might create a pool of 50% Bitcoin, 25% Ethereum, 15% Aave, and 5% ApeCoin. If the price of Ethereum doubled, Balancer would use smart contracts to rebalance the pool and reduce its Ethereum holdings. This Ethereum is then made available for traders to purchase.&nbsp;</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Why Invest in Balancer (BAL)?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">Balancer offers a more flexible and customizable approach to AMMs than other DeFi protocols, allowing users to create pools with any combination of assets and weights. Investors looking to generate additional income in a consistent and reliable way can provide liquidity to these pools, earning BAL tokens whenever traders use their liquidity.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">As the first self-balancing weighted portfolio DeFi application, Balancer is positioned to capture a large market share as more users flock to DeFi projects. Moreover, Balancer has secured some partnerships that further reinforce its position as a leading DeFi crypto project, like Aave and Polygon.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">7. ApeCoin (APE) &ndash; The Currency of the Metaverse</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">What is ApeCoin (APE)?</h3>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://apecoin.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>ApeCoin</u></a> is a relatively new cryptocurrency created by Yuga Labs following the success of its world-famous Bored Ape Yacht Club (BAYC) NFT collection. It&rsquo;s the utility and governance token of the Ape ecosystem, offering exclusive access to games, merch, events, and services to holders.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">It&rsquo;s designed to be used across various Web3 applications, most notably in Otherside. Otherside is Yuga Labs&rsquo; metaverse project, which it claims will be one of the most advanced metaverses on the market. Taking place on a distant planet, Otherside players will be able to immerse themselves in an open landscape where they can interact with others, build different experiences, and own virtual property, known as Otherdeeds.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Why Invest in ApeCoin (APE)?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">ApeCoin is considered one of the top new crypto coins for several reasons, not least the epic success of Yuga&rsquo;s previous projects. ApeCoin has already found uses as the native token of Benji Bananas and Dookie Dash, two P2E titles that have seen moderate acclaim amongst the crypto community.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Furthermore, Otherside is being developed in partnership with two key players of the Web3 and gaming industries, <a href="https://www.animocabrands.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Animoca Brands</u></a> and <a href="https://www.improbable.io/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Improbable</u></a>, which boosts the chances of Otherside launching without a hitch. Otherside is already hotly anticipated, with Otherdeeds reaching over $500 million in sales within 24 hours. If Otherside lives up to its promise, then APE could be climbing to new heights soon.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">8. Frax Finance (FRAX)/Frax Shares (FXS) &ndash; Hosting the World&rsquo;s First Fractional Stablecoin</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">What is Frax Finance (FRAX)/Frax Shares (FXS)?</h3>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://frax.finance/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Frax Finance</u></a> was originally a stablecoin that operated on a unique algorithmic model, using collateralized and uncollateralized components to maintain a stable value of $1 USD. However, Frax Shares (FXS) token holders recently voted to fully collateralize its stablecoin, removing the algorithmic element entirely.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Frax introduced the world&rsquo;s first fractional stablecoin and crypto market consumer price index, the Frax Price Index (FPI). Its vision is to create highly scalable, decentralized forms of currency in place of fixed-supply digital assets, like Bitcoin.&nbsp;</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Why Invest in Frax Finance (FRAX)?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">Frax has gained significant traction in the DeFi space over the past couple of years, with its protocol reaching a peak of $3.8 billion in total value locked (TVL) in 2022 (<a href="https://defillama.com/protocol/frax-finance" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>DeFiLlama</u></a>). Frax has also forged partnerships with many popular crypto projects, like Wombat Exchange and OlympusDAO, which speaks to its credibility amongst the crypto community.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Lastly, Frax&rsquo;s approach to decentralized decision-making may be an attractive prospect for investors. Owning Frax Shares (FXS) allows holders to propose and vote on changes to the protocol, which led to Frax moving away from algorithmic pegging entirely.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">9. AngelBlock (THOL) &ndash; Transforming Blockchain-Based Fundraising</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">What is AngelBlock (THOL)?</h3>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://angelblock.io/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>AngelBlock</u></a> is a non-custodial, protocol-based fundraising project offering compelling use cases for investors and startups alike. It sees the current crypto fundraising landscape as highly fragmented and inefficient, with issues like rug pulls, scam projects, and empty promises plaguing the crypto market. AngelBlock protects investors&rsquo; funds, returning them if the startup doesn&rsquo;t deliver on its promises.</p>
<p dir="ltr">AngelBlock&rsquo;s mission is to create a synergistic community of investors, innovators, and supporters that are purely focused on advancing blockchain technology. Capital is paid out to startups that meet their milestones during the fundraising process, with investors voting on whether they believe the project has successfully completed a given milestone.&nbsp;</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Why Invest in AngelBlock (THOL)?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">Effectively, AngelBlock is working to improve trust in the crypto fundraising world. Intending to enhance fundraising transparency and connect startups with an elite team of legal, strategic, and technical advisors, AngelBlock offers a way for investors to support Web3 development while contributing to a safe investment process.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The THOL token itself allows holders to access a wide range of opportunities to invest in up-and-coming crypto projects, as it&rsquo;s necessary to pay gas fees in the protocol. THOL tokens can also be staked, allowing users to earn rewards in exchange for nominating startup validators that are responsible for conducting due diligence on new crypto listings.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">10. CryptoGPT (GPT) &ndash; Giving Users Control Over Their Data in the Future of AI</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">What is CryptoGPT (GPT)?</h3>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://www.cryptogpt.org/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>CryptoGPT</u></a> is one of the many new crypto projects aiming to capitalize on the growing AI trend kickstarted by ChatGPT. It&rsquo;s a unique blockchain project that aims to collect data for AI development, allowing users to earn cryptocurrency by sharing their anonymized data.</p>
<p>CryptoGPT intends to create an entire ecosystem of dApps across a wide range of sectors, like fitness, dating, games, and education, while offering GPT as payment for data collected whenever someone uses these dApps. The platform is built on a layer-2 blockchain architecture using zkRollup technology, making it scalable and compatible with the Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM).&nbsp;</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Why Invest in CryptoGPT (GPT)?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">What sets CryptoGPT apart from other blockchain-based AI projects is its goal of mass retail adoption, offering an untapped opportunity by entering the market via consumer apps. This has already attracted over 2 million users into its ecosystem and led to multiple big-name exchange listings.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">GPT itself is a multi-purpose utility token. While its full uses are still undergoing beta testing, CryptoGPT can be staked, used for liquidity events such as buybacks or burns, and serves as fuel for transactions on the CryptoGPT blockchain. Users can even purchase Capsule NFTs, which enhances their ability to generate cash flow faster. While it&rsquo;s early days for CryptoGPT, it&rsquo;s certainly one of the most exciting new cryptocurrencies at the moment.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">11. Stepn (GMT) &ndash; A Leader in Move-To-Earn</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">What is Stepn (GMT)?</h3>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://stepn.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Stepn</u></a> is a unique mobile app powered by the Solana blockchain that combines gaming, fitness, and crypto in a fun and exciting way. It allows users to earn rewards in the form of a utility token, Green Satoshi Tokens (GST), by walking, jogging or running, whether out in the streets or in real-world gyms. Called a leader in move-to-earn, Stepn has been highly acclaimed as one of the most positive new cryptocurrencies.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The amount users earn is proportional to the attributes of their NFT sneakers, with some of the highest-earning sneakers fetching thousands of dollars in SOL and GST tokens. Stepn also features a token called the Green Metaverse Token (GMT), which is the platform&rsquo;s governance token and can only be earnt once players advance past a certain level. GMT allows users to earn staking rewards from the project and influence Stepn directly through voting and proposing changes.&nbsp;</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Why Invest in Stepn (GMT)?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">Stepn offers an innovative way to incentivize people to lead a healthy lifestyle while earning rewards in the form of crypto. It&rsquo;s one of the few projects that aim to bring positive changes to the lives of users by maximizing the full potential of crypto. The platform also features a user-friendly interface and wallet in its mobile app, making it easy for even non-crypto natives to earn rewards.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Moreover, the platform has gained the attention of major sports brands like ASICS, who added their own NFT sneaker collection to Stepn&rsquo;s catalog. Most importantly, some notable names in the venture capital world have placed big bets on Stepn; MorningStar Ventures, Solana Capital, and Sequoia Capital have all thrown their weight behind the project.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">12. Aptos (APT) &ndash; A New Blockchain From Former Meta Engineers</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">What is Aptos (APT)?</h3>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://aptoslabs.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Aptos</u></a> is a layer-1 blockchain that aims to challenge Ethereum&rsquo;s dominance in the smart contract space. Developed by former Meta engineers and based on the company&rsquo;s failed Diem project, Aptos utilizes a native programming language called Move, developed by Meta and regarded as superior to other blockchain-based languages.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Aptos&rsquo;s architecture is designed to offer faster and cheaper transactions than Ethereum, with a potential capacity of up to 150,000 transactions per second (TPS) once the network is fully developed. The project raised over $350 million in funding before APT crypto listings hit exchanges, in part thanks to its exceptional team of PhDs, researchers, and engineers.&nbsp;</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Why Invest in Aptos (APT)?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">Aptos&rsquo; high transaction capacity and ability to handle smart contracts more efficiently could position it as a leading contender in the space. Google Cloud has already announced a partnership with Aptos as a validator, as it&rsquo;s done with several other crypto assets that it believes have the potential for value appreciation.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Additionally, Aptos has a strong team of experts in various fields that have succeeded in previous crypto projects, like Solana&rsquo;s former Head of Marketing, Austin Virts. The project&rsquo;s ability to attract significant venture capital funding also demonstrates a level of confidence in the project&rsquo;s potential, which is why it&rsquo;s considered one of the best new cryptocurrency releases out there right now.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How Do I Find the Newest Cryptocurrencies That Are Set To Explode?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">There are a few ways to find new cryptocurrencies about to explode. One of the most popular sources for finding new coins is <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/new/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Coinmarketcap&rsquo;s new cryptocurrencies page</u></a>. Here, you&rsquo;ll find a list of the latest coins that have hit the market and essential metrics like market cap and trading volume. Similarly, <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/new-cryptocurrencies" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>CoinGecko&rsquo;s new cryptocurrency list</u></a> is also a valuable resource.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Searching for presales can be a great option if you&rsquo;re looking for even newer coins that haven&rsquo;t yet hit the market. These projects can often be found on Initial Coin Offering (ICO) or Initial Exchange Offering (IEO) aggregator sites, which can be found by searching &ldquo;ICO list&rdquo; or &ldquo;IEO list.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Finally, don&rsquo;t underestimate the power of social media. Joining Discord and Telegram groups, following influential traders on Twitter, and keeping an eye on other social media platforms can give you early access to information about the newest crypto coins before they hit the mainstream.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What Are the Advantages and Disadvantages of Investing in New Cryptos?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Investing in new cryptocurrency projects can be an exciting opportunity to make significant gains, but this approach has pros and cons. One major advantage is the potential to generate large returns as the coin becomes more popular. Tokens with innovative use cases that solve a real-world issue may attract a large user base. If the project becomes widely adopted, early investors could earn 10x, 50x, or even 100x returns.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Additionally, new cryptocurrencies often have some of the best communities, full of investors that are passionate about the project. This can help investors meet like-minded enthusiasts, help them learn more about the inner workings of the new crypto coin, and potentially influence its development.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, there is also the risk that the project may not succeed. With many new cryptocurrencies emerging each week, investors may end up putting their money into a project that was doomed to fail from the start. This can be counteracted by performing due diligence and thoroughly researching the project before investing.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">New crypto projects also tend to be more volatile, swinging much more than more established altcoins. This volatility can make it challenging to predict how the project will perform over the long term and may cause psychological distress if the investor faces heavy unrealized losses.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What Is the Best New Crypto To Invest in Now?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">While finding the best new cryptocurrencies to invest in can be challenging, you now have a solid overview of what experts consider the top projects. Some tokens solve a specific industry problem, like Livepeer and AngelBlock, while others, like ApeCoin and CryptoGPT, hope to capitalize on the rapid ascension of the metaverse and AI technology. But two clear winners emerge when looking at the broader picture: Chancer and Shiba Memu.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Related Crypto FAQs</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">Are new crypto coins a good investment?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">New crypto coins can be a good investment if they have a solid team, innovative technology, and a clear use case. It&rsquo;s important to do thorough research to determine if a new cryptocurrency has the potential for future gains.&nbsp;</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">How are new cryptocurrencies made?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">New cryptocurrencies can be created through a process called tokenization, where a new token is created on an existing blockchain network or through launching a new blockchain network altogether.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Which crypto will explode in 2023?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">It&rsquo;s impossible to predict which crypto will explode in 2023, but the new crypto coins on this list all hold strong potential, particularly Chancer and Shiba Memu.&nbsp;</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">What is a crypto listing?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">A crypto listing is the process of adding a cryptocurrency to a digital asset exchange, allowing users to buy, sell, and trade the token on the exchange&rsquo;s platform. Coin listings can increase visibility and liquidity for the token.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">What kind of use cases should I look for when investing in new tokens?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">Look for projects that solve real-world issues. Tokens that address inefficiencies or pain points can have significant potential for adoption, as they have more utility than purely speculative tokens.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Using an example in the real estate sector, you could look for a mortgage platform that uses blockchain technology to make the lending process more efficient. Or one that solves a pain point in the property maintenance or real estate investing markets.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-best-cryptocurrency-launches-in-2023-experts-share-the-12-best-new-cryptocurrencies-to-invest-in/">The Best Cryptocurrency Launches In 2023. Experts Share The 12 Best New Cryptocurrencies To Invest In</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
