<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 14:42:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Iran and Russia Jointly Working on Gold-Backed Stablecoin</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/iran-russia-gold-backed-stablecoin/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/iran-russia-gold-backed-stablecoin/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 14:42:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[usdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=232718</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/iran-russia-gold-backed-stablecoin/">Iran and Russia Jointly Working on Gold-Backed Stablecoin</a></p>
<p>The two countries shall use this stablecoin to facilitate cross-border transactions and foreign trade between the two. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/iran-russia-gold-backed-stablecoin/">Iran and Russia Jointly Working on Gold-Backed Stablecoin</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/iran-russia-gold-backed-stablecoin/">Iran and Russia Jointly Working on Gold-Backed Stablecoin</a></p>
<p>Amid the changing global geopolitical scenario, Iran and Russia have come together to issue a joint gold-backed stablecoin in the market. The executive director of the Russian Association of Crypto Industry and Blockchain, recently said that the Central Bank of Iran is considering the creation of such a stablecoin with its Russian counterpart.</p>
<h2>Gold-backed Stablecoin</h2>
<p>Russian news agency Vedomosti <a href="https://www.vedomosti.ru/economics/articles/2023/01/16/959100-rossiya-i-iran-nachali-prorabotku-obschego-steiblkoina" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">describes</a> this stablecoin as a “token of the Persian Gulf region” and would serve as a payment method in foreign trade. Both countries plan to use this stablecoin to enable cross-border transactions instead of using fiat currencies such as the USD, the Iranian Ruial or the Russian Ruble.</p>
<p>Furthermore, reports suggest that the specific stablecoin will be used to operate in a special economic zone in Astrakhan. This is the same place where Russia started to accept Iranian cargo shipments.</p>
<p>Anton Tkachev, the Russian lawmaker and the member of the Committee on Information Policy noted that a joint stablecoin project would only be possible after the digital assets market is entirely regulated in the country.</p>
<p>There have been multiple delays by Russian lawmakers in regulating the crypto market. However, the Russian lower house of parliament has once again promised to start regulating crypto transactions in 2023. Anatoly Aksakov, Chairman of the State Duma Committee on the Financial Market, <a href="https://www.vedomosti.ru/finance/news/2022/12/05/953772-v-gosdume-poobeschali" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“I can assure everyone that we will definitely have crypto as a legal product next year, there will definitely be legislation &#8230; I can only say unequivocally that it cannot be used in the Russian Federation as a means of payment for internal settlements&#8221;.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Crypto Regulations in Russia and Iran</h2>
<p>Both Iran and Russia have banned their local residents from using cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a>) as well as other USD-backed stablecoins such as Tether (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/tether/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">USDT</a>). However, on the other hand, both the countries are actively looking to make use of crypto to bypass international sanctions and as a tool of foreign trade.</p>
<p>In August 2022, Iran’s Industry, Mines and Trade Ministry, had approved the use of digital assets for imports into the country. The local government noted that the new measures would help Iran mitigate global trade sanctions.</p>
<p>On the other hand, the Bank of Russia had historically opposed the use of digital assets as a payment method. However, they agreed to use crypto in foreign trade to mitigate the impact of global sanctions.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/north-korean-harmony-hack-lazarus-64m/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/iran-russia-gold-backed-stablecoin/">Iran and Russia Jointly Working on Gold-Backed Stablecoin</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/iran-russia-gold-backed-stablecoin/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alleged North Korean Cyber Criminals behind Harmony Hack Lazarus Group Moves $64M in Stolen Crypto over Weekend</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/north-korean-harmony-hack-lazarus-64m/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/north-korean-harmony-hack-lazarus-64m/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 14:05:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cybersecurity News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[harmony]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[harmony one]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[huobi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[lazarus group]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=232719</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/north-korean-harmony-hack-lazarus-64m/">Alleged North Korean Cyber Criminals behind Harmony Hack Lazarus Group Moves $64M in Stolen Crypto over Weekend</a></p>
<p>Harmony hack perpetrators Lazarus Group recently moved $63.5 million in ETH, with Binance and Huobi recovering $2.5 million. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/north-korean-harmony-hack-lazarus-64m/">Alleged North Korean Cyber Criminals behind Harmony Hack Lazarus Group Moves $64M in Stolen Crypto over Weekend</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/north-korean-harmony-hack-lazarus-64m/">Alleged North Korean Cyber Criminals behind Harmony Hack Lazarus Group Moves $64M in Stolen Crypto over Weekend</a></p>
<p>North Korea’s Lazarus Group of cyber criminals linked to the $100 million Harmony hack recently made moves again. According to pseudonymous blockchain detective ZachXBT, Lazarus Group moved a sizable part of the stolen Harmony funds over the weekend.</p>
<p>Speaking on this development, ZachXBT <a href="https://twitter.com/zachxbt/status/1614771861266792449?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1614771861266792449%7Ctwgr%5E7f09bc662df42b4ca6fb9f02b756e9603e78722f%7Ctwcon%5Es1_&amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.coindesk.com%2Ftech%2F2023%2F01%2F16%2Fnorth-korean-hacking-group-tied-to-100m-harmony-hack-moves-41000-ether-over-weekend%2F" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">pointed out</a> on Twitter:</p>
<blockquote><p>“North Korea’s Lazarus Group had a very busy weekend moving $63.5m (~41000 ETH) from the Harmony bridge hack through Railgun before consolidating funds and depositing on three different exchanges.”</p></blockquote>
<p>The blockchain investigator also <a href="https://www.chainabuse.com/report/0a2e8e00-00e2-4749-9b00-ceb1c6202d33" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">listed</a> more than 350 addresses associated with stolen loot. Furthermore, according to ZachXBT, the North Korean hackers consolidated and deposited the digital assets into three separate crypto exchanges. Despite this revelation, the on-chain detective did not provide the names of the exchanges used by the cybercriminals.</p>
<h2>Binance, Huobi Collaborate to Retrieve Small Portion of Harmony Hack Funds from Lazarus</h2>
<p>Recent <a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/binance-huobi-team-up-to-recover-2-5m-from-harmony-one-hackers" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reports</a> also stated that crypto exchanges <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a> and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/huobi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Huobi</a> were teaming up to recover some of the Harmony One funds. Security teams at both exchanges have jointly frozen and recovered 121 Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a>), or $2.5 million, from the hackers.</p>
<p>Binance chief executive <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/changpeng-zhao/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Changpeng Zhao</a> recently <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1614887319177428992?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1614887319177428992%7Ctwgr%5E35a5cb4e723e59ac43238eeebc7033f11665431c%7Ctwcon%5Es1_&amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fcointelegraph.com%2Fnews%2Fbinance-huobi-team-up-to-recover-2-5m-from-harmony-one-hackers" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">tweeted</a> that the cybercriminals attempted to launder their funds through the Huobi exchange. However, Binance detected the unwholesome scheme and reached out to Huobi to help freeze and confiscate digital assets. Zhao’s tweet, which also revealed that the hackers initially unsuccessfully tried to funnel the stolen funds through Binance, read:</p>
<blockquote><p>“We detected Harmony One hacker fund movement. They previously tried to launder through Binance, and we froze his accounts. This time he used Huobi. We assisted Huobi team to freeze his accounts. Together, 124 BTC have been recovered. CeFi helping to keep DeFi.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>Harmony Hack</h2>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/harmony-horizon-bridge-hacked-one-token-slump/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Last June</a>, the Harmony team first detected the $100 million exploit, including a compromise of bridges linking Ethereum (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ETH</a>) and Bitcoin. At the time, Harmony issued a <a href="https://twitter.com/harmonyprotocol/status/1540110924400324608?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1540110924400324608%7Ctwgr%5E49d12ac5479500ab5c62705aab934e7e64b11f23%7Ctwcon%5Es1_&amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fcointelegraph.com%2Fnews%2Fbreaking-harmony-one-s-horizon-bridge-hacked-for-100m" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">statement</a> on Twitter that read:</p>
<blockquote><p>“The Harmony team has identified a theft occurring this morning on the Horizon bridge amounting to approx. $100MM. We have begun working with national authorities and forensic specialists to identify the culprit and retrieve the stolen funds.”</p></blockquote>
<p>A few days later, the Harmony Protocol attempted to recover the stolen funds by <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/harmony-protocol-1-million-bounty-returning-stolen-funds/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">offering</a> a $1 million bounty to the hacker(s). In addition, the proof-of-stake (PoS) blockchain also promised not to initiate any criminal proceedings if the hacker returned the stolen funds. Harmony’s attempt at remedial measures went unanswered by the hackers because 24 hours later, the criminals started <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/harmony-hackers-laundering-stolen-funds/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">laundering the funds</a>. In response, the blockchain protocol’s team announced that it was working with “national authorities and forensic specialists” to identify the miscreants. In addition, at the time, Harmony expressed the belief that it would eventually retrieve the stolen funds.</p>
<h2>Lazarus Group</h2>
<p>The Lazarus Group of North Korea is widely believed to be the perpetrator of the Harmony hack. The cybercriminal syndicate reportedly enjoys the support of the regime of the country’s dictator and Supreme Leader, Kim Jong-un.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/oxfam-richest-became-richer/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/north-korean-harmony-hack-lazarus-64m/">Alleged North Korean Cyber Criminals behind Harmony Hack Lazarus Group Moves $64M in Stolen Crypto over Weekend</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/north-korean-harmony-hack-lazarus-64m/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Oxfam Reveals How Richest 1% of All People Became Richer in Two Years</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/oxfam-richest-became-richer/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/oxfam-richest-became-richer/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 14:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[oxfam]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=232721</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/oxfam-richest-became-richer/">Oxfam Reveals How Richest 1% of All People Became Richer in Two Years</a></p>
<p>While inflation gulps the wages of at least 1.7 billion workers, billionaires see their fortune increase by $2.7 billion on a daily basis.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/oxfam-richest-became-richer/">Oxfam Reveals How Richest 1% of All People Became Richer in Two Years</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/oxfam-richest-became-richer/">Oxfam Reveals How Richest 1% of All People Became Richer in Two Years</a></p>
<p>According to a new report from global poverty charity Oxfam, two-thirds of the entire new wealth created globally has been amassed by the richest 1% of people in the past two years. The <a href="https://www.oxfam.org/en/research/survival-richest" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a> mentions the alarming rate of multiple crises, including hunger, devastating economies, and the negative effect of the coronavirus, which many are still struggling with. While poverty has increased for the first time in 25 years, the richest amassed more wealth, and corporate revenues hit their peaks.</p>
<h2>Oxfam Issues Report on World&#8217;s Richest Amassing Most Wealth</h2>
<p>In addition to showing the alarming inequality in the world, the report also explained the unprecedented “polycrisis.” A total of $42 trillion in new wealth has been created since 2020. However, 63%, which equals about $26 trillion, has been acquired by the 1% ultra-rich in the world. While the ultra-rich take up two-thirds of all the new wealth in the world, the bottom 99% have to settle for the remnants. This means that 99% of the world&#8217;s population was left with $16 trillion of $42 trillion in new wealth. The study reveals:</p>
<blockquote><p>“A billionaire gained roughly $1.7 million for every $1 of new global wealth earned by a person in the bottom 90 percent.”</p></blockquote>
<p>While <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-inflation-drops-prices-soar/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">inflation</a> gulps the wages of at least 1.7 billion workers, billionaires see their fortune increase by $2.7 billion on a daily basis. At the same time, the corporate space, including food and energy companies, recorded an X2 jump in their profits last year. Wealthy shareholders received $257 billion from these companies in the same year. The global poverty charity estimates more than 800 people lived in abject poverty without food or water.</p>
<p>Oxfam gathered data from Forbes Billionaires List, Forbes Real-Time Billionaires List, and Credit Suisse for information on the changes to the wealth of the richest. The report says billionaires’ wealth has surged by trillions of dollars more than before the pandemic. This set of people profited from the pandemic as many developed countries pumped money into the economy to salvage the situation.</p>
<h2>Should Government Tax the Ultra-Rich More?</h2>
<p>As a solution, Oxfam is proposing that the government tax the 1% richest. The report explains that “&#8230;as a starting point, the world should aim to halve the wealth and number of billionaires between now and 2030, both by increasing taxes on the top 1% and adopting other billionaire-busting policies. This would bring billionaire wealth and numbers back to where they were just a decade ago in 2012. This eventual aim should be to further, and to abolish billionaires altogether, as part of a fairer, more rational distribution of the world’s wealth.”</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tencent-shares-multi-month-highs/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/oxfam-richest-became-richer/">Oxfam Reveals How Richest 1% of All People Became Richer in Two Years</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/oxfam-richest-became-richer/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tencent Shares Hit Multi-Month Highs Atop Regulatory Ease</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tencent-shares-multi-month-highs/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tencent-shares-multi-month-highs/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 12:52:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alibaba]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ant group]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tencent]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tencent shares]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tencent stock]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=232708</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tencent-shares-multi-month-highs/">Tencent Shares Hit Multi-Month Highs Atop Regulatory Ease</a></p>
<p>With the easing of pressure from authorities, Tencent shares may still see additional upshoots when compared to the level it is currently at this time.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tencent-shares-multi-month-highs/">Tencent Shares Hit Multi-Month Highs Atop Regulatory Ease</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tencent-shares-multi-month-highs/">Tencent Shares Hit Multi-Month Highs Atop Regulatory Ease</a></p>
<p>The shares of Chinese multinational internet giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/tencent/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tencent Holdings Ltd</a> (HKG: 0700) have seen multi-month highs as the broader tech industry retraced their plunging valuation with improving regulatory measures from Beijing. As <a href="https://www.businesstimes.com.sg/companies-markets/tencent-shares-nearly-double-october-low-crackdown-eases" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reported</a> by Bloomberg, Tencent shares have now climbed by nearly double the price points back in October 2022.</p>
<p>This growth comes despite the 0.32% slump in the price of the company’s shares to HKD 370.20</p>
<p>Specifically, the shares have grown by about 95% since October 28, pushing back to the list of the most valuable companies in the world. At the time, the pangs in the Chinese tech industry combined with the aftermath of the global financial industry squeeze stirred the plunge of the shares to drop to their lowest price point since 2017.</p>
<p>The regulators at the time were so concerned about the prolific growth of these tech startups and the fears that they may be monopolizing the market. In 2020, the government fueled the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-shares-tanked-7-54-after-halt-of-ant-groups-record-ipo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">crush</a> of the Initial Public Offering (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-initial-public-offering-ipo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">IPO</a>) push of Ant Group, the fintech firm that is affiliated with <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/alibaba-group/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Alibaba Group Holdings Ltd</a> (HKG: 9988).</p>
<p>Should the IPO have been permitted to float at the time, it would have come up as one of the biggest in the world at the time. The refusal at the time marked the start of a broad-based crackdown, one that lasted for way more than 2 years.</p>
<p>One of the options that were being considered by the regulators at the time included splitting Alipay, the digital payments section of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ant-financial/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ant Group</a>. By decentralizing the powers of Alipay, the government hoped to taper down on the dominance of the digital payment outfit in the country’s financial ecosystem.</p>
<p>The industry may soon start enjoying new regulatory ease as the Bloomberg report shows that lawmakers are now beginning to raise tough concerns about the harsh regime that is stiffening the growth of these tech companies.</p>
<h2>Tencent Shares, Others to Grow amid Easing Regulations</h2>
<p>The current era is marked by the permission <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/chinese-ant-consumer-finance-unit/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">granted</a> to Ant Group by the China Banking and Insurance Regulatory Commission (CBIRC) to expand the capital base of its consumer finance unit. With permission, the unit can now increase its capital base from 8 billion Yuan to 18.5 billion Yuan.</p>
<p>With the easing of pressure from authorities, Tencent shares may still see additional upshoots when compared to the level it is currently at this time. At the peak of the sanctions, about $2 trillion in capitalization was removed from the Chinese tech sector and this will come off as a new recovery milestone to look forward to.</p>
<p>The jump in the Hang Seng Tech Index (INDEXHANGSENG: HSI) over the past three months has further lent credence to the ecosystem’s revival across the board.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/decentraland-mana-7-day-surge/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tencent-shares-multi-month-highs/">Tencent Shares Hit Multi-Month Highs Atop Regulatory Ease</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tencent-shares-multi-month-highs/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Decentraland (MANA) Rises 70% on Back of 7-Day Surge</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/decentraland-mana-7-day-surge/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/decentraland-mana-7-day-surge/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 12:49:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[decentraland]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gala]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gala games]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sand]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[The Sandbox]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=232690</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/decentraland-mana-7-day-surge/">Decentraland (MANA) Rises 70% on Back of 7-Day Surge</a></p>
<p>Mana, the native token of 3D virtual world platform Decentraland, is on a sustained surge since December 30th 2022. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/decentraland-mana-7-day-surge/">Decentraland (MANA) Rises 70% on Back of 7-Day Surge</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/decentraland-mana-7-day-surge/">Decentraland (MANA) Rises 70% on Back of 7-Day Surge</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-decentraland-mana/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Decentraland</a> native token MANA recently experienced a 70% surge within the past week amid a strong performance by metaverse tokens to begin the year.</p>
<p>MANA price hit a base of $0.284 at the end of last December. However, the metaverse coin has experienced an upswing in 14 of the subsequent 16 days since then. In addition, although the token has eased some of its intraday gains, MANA&#8217;s price is still up 22% in the past 24 hours. Furthermore, the digital currency changed hands at $0.67 as of press time.</p>
<p>As a result of improving macroeconomic metrics, digital currencies with relatively smaller market caps have outperformed. This trend is due to growing positive investor sentiment regarding the broader crypto markets.</p>
<p>Other notable gaming and metaverse tokens also experienced marked rises in the last seven days. These include Gala Games (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gala-nft-rally/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">GALA</a>), with a 30% increase, and The Sandbox&#8217;s SAND 32% surge in the past week.</p>
<h2>Decentraland (MANA) Surge Coincides with 2023 Edition of Australian Open</h2>
<p>It is also noteworthy that the recent Decentraland (MANA) surge coincides with the start of the Australian Open, which begins January 16th. Decentraland <a href="https://twitter.com/decentraland/status/1614671781754990592" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">heralded</a> the return of the Australian Open on Twitter. According to reports, both the Australian Open &#8220;AOmetaverse&#8221; and Decentraland&#8217;s largest commercial zone Vegas City have a designated Twitter space for January 17th. The two parties plan to disseminate essential details regarding the 14-day activation of the grand slam tennis tournament.</p>
<h2>Australian Open Metaverse Replica</h2>
<p>Exactly a year ago, the yearly-opening Australian Open grand slam tennis tournament <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/australian-open-virtual-replica-metaverse/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">launched a virtual replica</a> in the Decentraland metaverse. The primary motivation behind this initiative is to offer fans more access and possibilities.</p>
<p>At the time, Australian Open and Metaverse and NFT project manager Ridley Plummer described the tournament&#8217;s virtual replica as innovative. In addition, Plummer also stated that Tennis Australia was intent on leveraging the emerging metaverse and non-fungible tokens (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NFTs</a>). As he put it back then:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;I think we&#8217;re a sporting organization, and for the most part of the year, we&#8217;re used to seeing people playing tennis on courts… as we tried to expand what we do as a business, the natural progression of that is to get into gaming and to get into more offline stuff in a second screen. So, when we were discussing six to eight months ago what the next step is, naturally, the metaverse was the first thing that came up, and NFTs as well. So, we sort of jumped headfirst into this space three or four months ago.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Plummer also pointed out the dynamic viewing possibilities of Decentraland&#8217;s Australian Open as appealing to fans. He teased numerous special visual effects and spectacles, including the &#8220;Matrix Effect,&#8221; which provides a reverse feed of the on-court action. Furthermore, as an added bonus, Plummer opined that the AO metaverse could help lure some crypto and NFT buffs to tennis.</p>
<p>Plummer suggested that Tennis Australia viewed the virtual grand slam tournament as a sustainable scheme that would become a sports and entertainment mecca.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/didi-relaunch-china/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/decentraland-mana-7-day-surge/">Decentraland (MANA) Rises 70% on Back of 7-Day Surge</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/decentraland-mana-7-day-surge/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Didi Gets Greenlight to Relaunch in China after 18-Month Suspension</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/didi-relaunch-china/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/didi-relaunch-china/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 12:25:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Transportation News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[didi]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=232692</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/didi-relaunch-china/">Didi Gets Greenlight to Relaunch in China after 18-Month Suspension</a></p>
<p>Before the relaunch of user registration, existing users of the Didi app used it as long as they had it on their phones.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/didi-relaunch-china/">Didi Gets Greenlight to Relaunch in China after 18-Month Suspension</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/didi-relaunch-china/">Didi Gets Greenlight to Relaunch in China after 18-Month Suspension</a></p>
<p>After an 18-month suspension in China, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/didi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Didi</a> finally got approval to relaunch its app on Monday, 16th January 2023. The Chinese authorities authorized the country’s app stores to delist Didi in July 2021. The company, which offers multiple app-based services such as food delivery, ride-hailing, and more, was faced with allegations of illegally collecting user data. The suspension came after the company raised about $4 billion following its debut in one of the US&#8217;s largest initial public offerings (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-initial-public-offering-ipo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">IPOs</a>). Before it was pulled down from China’s App Stores, Didi served around 493 million, annual active users. The company was also involved in about 41 million daily transactions. In response to the “national security concerns” raised by the regulators, Didi said it has started making “corrections.”</p>
<p>However, reports showed that Didi did not defend the safety of its cross-border data practices. This resulted in a more than a year security investigation by the watchdog. The Cyberspace Administration of China (CAC) <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cac-fines-didi-1-19b-data-security/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">asked</a> the company to pay a $1.19 billion fine for breaching rules. The CAC noted that Didi violated the nation’s network security law, data security law, and personal information protection law.</p>
<h2>Didi Announces Relaunch in China</h2>
<p>Announcing its relaunch on Monday morning, Didi <a href="https://m.weibo.cn/status/4858551631087354?wm=3333_2001&amp;from=10D1093010&amp;sourcetype=weixin" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">wrote</a> on Weibo:</p>
<blockquote><p>“For more than a year, our company has seriously cooperated with the national network security review, seriously dealt with the security problems found in the review, and carried out comprehensive rectification. With the approval of the Network Security Review Office, the new user registration of “DiDi Chuxing” will resume immediately. In the future, the company will take effective measures to effectively guarantee the security of platform facilities and big data, and maintain national network security.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Before the relaunch of user registration, existing users of the Didi app used it as long as they had it on their phones. With the resurgence, the company must comply with the heightened regulatory oversight over the ride-hailing industry. And Didi already promised in the Weibo post to take “effective measures.”</p>
<p>China finally eased off on Didi as the government sought to restore the private sector&#8217;s confidence. The country also hopes that the tech space will push the economy that has been impacted by the three years coronavirus pandemic. Meanwhile, many feared that Didi may have to deal with more than just a fine before it gets the green light to relaunch in China. While the Didi app was still banned, a Market Specialist at CGS-CIMB securities Singapore, Samuel Siew, commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Prior to the conclusion of this, there were a lot of fears in markets that there would be more than just a fine. Now with its settling as just a fine, it’s lighter than what the possible implications were initially feared.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Other business news can be found <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/business/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bulgarian-police-nexo-investigation/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/didi-relaunch-china/">Didi Gets Greenlight to Relaunch in China after 18-Month Suspension</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/didi-relaunch-china/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bulgarian Police Denies Any Political Motives into Latest Nexo Investigation</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bulgarian-police-nexo-investigation/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bulgarian-police-nexo-investigation/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 12:22:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nexo]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=232648</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bulgarian-police-nexo-investigation/">Bulgarian Police Denies Any Political Motives into Latest Nexo Investigation</a></p>
<p>Prosecutor General spokesperson for Bulgarian police denied any political agenda behind the recent raids on Nexo's office in Bulgaria. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bulgarian-police-nexo-investigation/">Bulgarian Police Denies Any Political Motives into Latest Nexo Investigation</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bulgarian-police-nexo-investigation/">Bulgarian Police Denies Any Political Motives into Latest Nexo Investigation</a></p>
<p>Last week, the Bulgarian police <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nexo-money-laundering-probe/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">raided</a> Nexo&#8217;s office in a probe over alleged tax evasion and money laundering. The news about the Nexo investigation comes within a month of its exiting the US market in December 2022.</p>
<h2>Nexo Investigation</h2>
<p>Siika Mileva, a spokesperson for Bulgaria’s chief prosecutors, however, has denied any political motivation behind the probe against crypto lending firm Nexo. Mileva&#8217;s comments came in response to the accusations that the investigation into Nexo had a connection with the company&#8217;s political donations.</p>
<p>Besides, Mileva stressed that in almost all cases in recent years, wherein a prosecution starts an investigation that affects someone&#8217;s financial interests, leads to accusations and attacks. &#8220;It has become a national sport to attack the institutions,&#8221; Mileva argued.</p>
<p>Last week on January 12, a group of prosecutors, foreign agents, and investigators searched Nexo&#8217;s Bulgaria office in the capital city of Sofia. In addition to a large-scale money-laundering scheme, the operation also targeted violations of Russia’s international sanctions.</p>
<p>Within 48 hours of raiding Nexo&#8217;s offices, four people familiar with the matter were charged with tax crimes, money laundering, computer fraud, and unlicensed banking. Later, two individuals were released on bail for $550,000. The other two aren&#8217;t in Bulgaria and have been announced as internationally wanted persons.</p>
<p>Prosecutor General spokesperson <a href="https://www.bta.bg/en/news/bulgaria/390387-prosecutor-general-spokesperson-mileva-there-is-nothing-political-in-the-nexo-i" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a> that the case related to so-called &#8220;modern crimes in cyberspace&#8221;, extremely serious crimes. She further noted that the investigation was going on for months, along with international partner services.</p>
<p>Mileva further added that the transactions carried out by Nexo over the last five years totaled $94 billion.</p>
<h2>Nexo Preparing for Lawsuit on Damages</h2>
<p>Soon after Nexo&#8217;s office in Bulgaria was raided last week, the crypto lender complained about the law enforcement stating that they were preparing a lawsuit for damages caused by the abrupt police investigation. Besides, Nexo blamed the authorities for undertaking a “kick first, ask questions later” approach.</p>
<p>Furthermore, Nexo stated that the authorities didn&#8217;t provide a search warrant for hours and never identified themselves to other Nexo employees. In their clarification, Nexo <a href="https://twitter.com/Nexo/status/1613477470732173314" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">noted</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Over the years, we have turned down a lot of business because Nexo never makes compromises with regard to our very stringent anti-money laundering and know-your-customer policies. Since day 1, we have gone the extra mile to implement cutting-edge solutions to ensure adherence to the highest regulatory standards and simultaneously provide a smooth customer onboarding journey.</p>
<p>Unfortunately, with the recent regulatory crackdown on crypto, some regulators have recently adopted the kick first, ask questions later approach. In corrupt countries, it is bordering with racketeering, but that too shall pass&#8221;.</p></blockquote>
<p>Read other <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/crypto/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">crypto</a> and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/crypto/blockchain-news/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">blockchain</a> news on Coinspeaker.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ethereum-eth-price-surges-inflation/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bulgarian-police-nexo-investigation/">Bulgarian Police Denies Any Political Motives into Latest Nexo Investigation</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bulgarian-police-nexo-investigation/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum (ETH) Price Surges to Ten-Week High as Inflation Reduces</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ethereum-eth-price-surges-inflation/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ethereum-eth-price-surges-inflation/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 10:56:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[matic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[near]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[polygon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[polygon (matic)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[shib]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[shiba inu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=232643</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ethereum-eth-price-surges-inflation/">Ethereum (ETH) Price Surges to Ten-Week High as Inflation Reduces</a></p>
<p>Many other notable digital currencies are currently seeing massive gains, bringing the crypto market a remarkable 1.7% increase on the day to surpass the $1 trillion mark.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ethereum-eth-price-surges-inflation/">Ethereum (ETH) Price Surges to Ten-Week High as Inflation Reduces</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ethereum-eth-price-surges-inflation/">Ethereum (ETH) Price Surges to Ten-Week High as Inflation Reduces</a></p>
<p>Ethereum (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ETH</a>) price has surged to its highest level since November 8 as demand for the network also continues to build up. This follows after ETH consolidated its weekend gains, climbing over 3% in the last 24 hours. According to CoinMarketCap <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">data</a>, ETH hit the $1,579 mark in the early hours of Monday, but has now slightly re-traced its steps and was seen trading at $1,542 as of press time.</p>
<h2>Ethereum (ETH) Price Expected to Rally On</h2>
<p>It should be noted, however, that the $1,542 mark has proven to be strong support so far. For several days, ETH has refused to allow any price slips below the mark. And in addition to that, bulls presently have momentum as shown by the high volumes of trades involving the ETH/USD pair.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, various claims have also surfaced regarding how macroeconomic conditions appear to be gradually improving themselves. The claims include the stock market&#8217;s recent rise, deflation &#8211; shown by the Consumer Price Index (CPI), and the expectations of a much lower interest rate hike by the Federal Reserve.</p>
<h2>Crypto Market in Greens</h2>
<p>The price movement of ETH reflects what is generally obtainable in the crypto market as of this moment.  Like Ethereum, Bitcoin&#8217;s (BTC) price is also doing well, but maybe not as well. The flagship cryptocurrency is up 27% in the last two weeks and is only 2.1% up on the day. Therefore, Ethereum may have outperformed Bitcoin with its 30% gain within the same period.</p>
<p>Also, many other notable digital currencies are currently seeing massive gains, bringing the crypto market a remarkable 1.7% increase on the day to surpass the $1 trillion mark. Some of such assets doing great at the moment include Shiba Inu (<a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/shiba-inu/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">SHIB</a>), <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/xrp/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">XRP</a>, Near Protocol (NEAR), and Polygon (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/matic-network/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">MATIC</a>).</p>
<p>Interestingly, the gains have somewhat recovered all the losses that the crypto market incurred from <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-exchange-files-for-bankruptcy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX collapse</a> back in November. Recall that the crash of the $32 billion crypto empire stripped the market of billions at the time. The situation also caused the market to fall below a $1 trillion valuation.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nft-influencer-victim-google-ads-malware/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ethereum-eth-price-surges-inflation/">Ethereum (ETH) Price Surges to Ten-Week High as Inflation Reduces</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ethereum-eth-price-surges-inflation/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>NFT Influencer Is New Victim of Google Ads Malware</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nft-influencer-victim-google-ads-malware/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nft-influencer-victim-google-ads-malware/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sanaa Sharma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 10:53:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cybersecurity News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[google ads]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nft]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=232645</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nft-influencer-victim-google-ads-malware/">NFT Influencer Is New Victim of Google Ads Malware</a></p>
<p>Alex, in their series of tweets, claims to have made a crucial mistake that enabled attackers to use their wallet.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nft-influencer-victim-google-ads-malware/">NFT Influencer Is New Victim of Google Ads Malware</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nft-influencer-victim-google-ads-malware/">NFT Influencer Is New Victim of Google Ads Malware</a></p>
<p>A <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">non-fungible token</a> influencer, called NFT God, has apparently <a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/google-ads-delivered-malware-drains-nft-influencer-s-entire-crypto-wallet" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">lost</a> a significant amount of its net worth in NFTs and crypto following a wrongful download of hostile software found through Google Ads search results. According to the Twitter user called &#8220;NFT God&#8221;, their entire virtual livelihood was caught in an ambush that also attacked their crypto wallet and other related accounts.</p>
<p>NFT God, who also goes by the name Alex, said that they used Google&#8217;s search engine to download OBS, an open-source video streaming software. However, instead of selecting the link via the official website, they clicked the sponsored advertisement for what seemingly looked like the same thing.</p>
<p>However, a few hours later, following a series of phishing tweets sent out by the hackers on two Twitter accounts owned by Alex, they acknowledged the malicious software in their hardware from the sponsored advertisement that had caused unwanted activities.</p>
<p>After a message from some known entity, Alex also realized that their crypto wallet was robbed. The following day, hackers attacked their Substack account and forwarded phishing emails to the sixteen thousand subscribers following Alex.</p>
<p>Blockchain data reflects a loss worth nearly $27000 at the time, a Mutant Ape Yacht Club (MAYC) NFT with a present floor price of 16 <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ETH</a> (around twenty-five thousand USD), and several other NFTs that were stolen from Alex&#8217;s wallet. The attacker transferred most of the ETH through several wallets before sending it to the decentralized exchange (DEX) FixedFloat, where it was exchanged for some other unidentified cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>Alex, in their series of tweets, claims to have made a crucial mistake that enabled attackers to use their wallet, which allowed them to install his hardware wallet as a hot wallet by jotting its seed phrase in a manner that would not keep it cold (or offline). This allowed the cyberpunks to take control of their crypto assets and NFTs.</p>
<p>The news is a sad reminder of how vulnerable one&#8217;s asset in the crypto world is, as this is not the first time the community has had to struggle with crypto-stealing malware in Google Ads. A recent January 12 report from Cybersecurity firm Cyble cautioned users of an information-stealing malicious virus called &#8220;Rhadamanthys Stealer&#8221; that has been circulating via Google Ads on a phishing webpage, which doesn&#8217;t look any different.</p>
<p>In October last year, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a> Chief Executive Officer <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/changpeng-zhao/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Changpeng &#8220;CZ&#8221; Zhao</a> forewarned that Google search results were influencing crypto phishing and scamming websites. While Google did not immediately reply to this allegation, it did announce in a help center that the company was persistently working with veteran advertisers and associates to aid in the prevention of malware.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-mining-difficulty-ecosystem-activity/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nft-influencer-victim-google-ads-malware/">NFT Influencer Is New Victim of Google Ads Malware</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nft-influencer-victim-google-ads-malware/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Mining Difficulty Soars 10% amid Growing Ecosystem Activity</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-mining-difficulty-ecosystem-activity/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-mining-difficulty-ecosystem-activity/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 10:43:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[core scientific]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pow]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=232636</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-mining-difficulty-ecosystem-activity/">Bitcoin Mining Difficulty Soars 10% amid Growing Ecosystem Activity</a></p>
<p>With burnout in reserve cash, and the growing prices of Bitcoin and other related assets, most mining firms are indeed left with no options but to intensify their efforts to get their hands on more BTC from their farms. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-mining-difficulty-ecosystem-activity/">Bitcoin Mining Difficulty Soars 10% amid Growing Ecosystem Activity</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-mining-difficulty-ecosystem-activity/">Bitcoin Mining Difficulty Soars 10% amid Growing Ecosystem Activity</a></p>
<p>The <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> (BTC) mining difficulty has grown by as much as 10% to record a new high since October. According to data from BTC.com, the Bitcoin mining hashrate climbed to a high of 37.59 Terahashes atop a hashrate of 271.97 EH/s.</p>
<p>The Bitcoin mining difficulty is a measure of how hard it is to mine a block in the BTC network, and it rises when there is an increasing number of miners plugged into the system. The mining difficulty is adjusted every 2 weeks and the next update is slated for 13 days and 6 hours with the projected difficulty billed to be pegged at 37.63 Terahashes.</p>
<p>It may be more difficult to understand the source of the new miners entering into the network per time but at this time, it seems existing dormant miners are becoming more active following the growth in the price of Bitcoin and most Layer one Proof-of-Work (PoW) networks respectively.</p>
<p>While BTC is up by 0.62% to $20,776.21 <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/bitcoin/markets/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">according</a> to CoinMarketCap’s data, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/litecoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Litecoin</a> (LTC) is up by 4.48% over the past week to be changing hands at $85.53. The price of Bitcoin in particular accounts for its best price range in close to 90 days.</p>
<p>With the revival in the price of L1 PoW coins across the board, a number of miners are returning to profitability as many complained of headwinds surrounding their core businesses. These headwinds focus on the rising costs of energy as an aftermath of the ongoing war between Russia and Ukraine, the slumping price of the mined assets made the entire venture seem like a fruitless effort.</p>
<p>In the wake of the realities they are faced with, many of the miners started selling out their stacked stash, a move that became necessitated when many could not raise cash to finance their operations. The liquidity strain notably pushed a lot of these miners into bankruptcy, with the likes of Core Scientific Inc (OTCMKTS: CORZQ) coming off as one of the most impacted.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Mining Firms Left with No Options</h2>
<p>With burnout in reserve cash, and the growing prices of Bitcoin and other related assets, most mining firms are indeed left with no options but to intensify their efforts to get their hands on more BTC from their farms.</p>
<p>Core Scientific was <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/core-scientific-bankruptcy-mining/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reportedly</a> still mining its own coins even after filing for bankruptcy and the firm has paved the way for a more profitable showing as it <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/core-scientific-celsius-mining-rigs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">unplugged</a> as much as 37,000 mining machines belonging to the bankrupt crypto lender, Celsius Mining for failure to pay up its electric and management costs.</p>
<p>With the freed-up space, Core Scientific could host other miners that are still solvent enough to pay, thus increasing its bottom line across the board. A similar scenario might apply to other embattled miners, as the recent surge back to profitability comes off as a good omen to intensify mining efforts across the board.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/thailand-first-virtual-banks-2025/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-mining-difficulty-ecosystem-activity/">Bitcoin Mining Difficulty Soars 10% amid Growing Ecosystem Activity</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-mining-difficulty-ecosystem-activity/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>