<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 15:12:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>European Central Bank Tackles Inflation with 25 BPS Rate Hike</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ecb-25-bps-rate-hike/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ecb-25-bps-rate-hike/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 15:12:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ecb]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[inflation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rate Hike]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=264821</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ecb-25-bps-rate-hike/">European Central Bank Tackles Inflation with 25 BPS Rate Hike</a></p>
<p>As the global economy continues to recover from the COVID-19 pandemic, the Eurozone is facing increasing chances of inflationary pressures.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ecb-25-bps-rate-hike/">European Central Bank Tackles Inflation with 25 BPS Rate Hike</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ecb-25-bps-rate-hike/">European Central Bank Tackles Inflation with 25 BPS Rate Hike</a></p>
<p>In a bid to address the persistent challenge of inflation, the European Central Bank (ECB) recently took a significant step by announcing a 25 basis points rate hike, raising its main rate to 3.75%.</p>
<h2>The ECB Remains Vigilant as Inflation Declines</h2>
<p>This decision comes amid a <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ecb-interest-rate-hiking-cycle/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">backdrop</a> of economic recovery in the Eurozone and rising concerns over surging inflation rates. According to recent data, headline inflation in the Eurozone declined to 5.5% in June from 6.1% in May. While this marks a reduction, the rate is still significantly above the ECB&#8217;s target of 2% for price stability.</p>
<p>The ECB noted in a statement <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/07/27/ecb-rate-decision-july-2023-raises-rates-by-25-basis-points.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">released</a> earlier today that inflation is showing indications of lowering; nonetheless, it is projected to stay persistently high for a lengthy period of time. This comes amid worries over the economy’s recovery and its possible impact on individuals and businesses.</p>
<p>The ECB’s recent 25 basis point rate hike was broadly in line with market forecasts, but it has investors and companies anxiously awaiting the central bank’s attitude in the post-summer period.</p>
<p>As the Eurozone grapples with the recovery from the COVID-19 pandemic, there are lingering concerns about whether the ECB’s monetary policy measures might inadvertently push the region into an economic recession.</p>
<p>With the potential dampening effect of higher interest rates on consumer spending and business investments, some market players worry that the rate hike could hinder the fragile economic recovery. The central bank faces a delicate balancing act, as it aims to combat inflationary pressures while also supporting economic growth.</p>
<p>A notable aspect of the recent ECB announcement was the absence of forward guidance regarding future policy moves. The central bank did not provide clear indications of its intentions beyond the rate hike.</p>
<h2>Rising Chances of Inflation in the Eurozone</h2>
<p>As the global economy continues to recover from the COVID-19 pandemic, the Eurozone is facing <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ecb-president-euro-zone-inflation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">increasing</a> chances of inflationary pressures. Several factors are contributing to the rising concerns about inflation in the region.</p>
<p>Firstly, the European Central Bank (ECB) has recently published a survey revealing a significant and concerning trend in the euro zone&#8217;s corporate loans. The data showed that between mid-June and early July, corporate loans dropped to their lowest level ever. This decline in lending to businesses raises concerns about the state of the region&#8217;s economic recovery and the challenges faced by businesses.</p>
<p>Adding to concerns about the eurozone’s economic future, statistics on business activity released earlier this week showed dips in two of the region’s main economies, Germany and France.</p>
<p>Further contributing to the economic apprehensions, the International Monetary Fund (IMF) released its projections for the eurozone&#8217;s economic growth this year. The IMF predicts that the region’s economy would increase by 0.9% in 2023. However, this prediction takes into account the possibility of a recession in Germany, where GDP is predicted to drop by 0.3%.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/barclays-uk-interest-rates/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ecb-25-bps-rate-hike/">European Central Bank Tackles Inflation with 25 BPS Rate Hike</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ecb-25-bps-rate-hike/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Barclays Faces Challenges in UK Division as Inflation and High-Interest Rates Affect Margins</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/barclays-uk-interest-rates/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/barclays-uk-interest-rates/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 14:26:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[barclays]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[deutsche bank]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=264788</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/barclays-uk-interest-rates/">Barclays Faces Challenges in UK Division as Inflation and High-Interest Rates Affect Margins</a></p>
<p>To counter the margin pressure, Barclays announced plans for a share buyback of up to £750 million.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/barclays-uk-interest-rates/">Barclays Faces Challenges in UK Division as Inflation and High-Interest Rates Affect Margins</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/barclays-uk-interest-rates/">Barclays Faces Challenges in UK Division as Inflation and High-Interest Rates Affect Margins</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/barclays/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Barclays</a>, the British multinational bank, has recently announced its Q2 2023 financial results, revealing expectations of earning less interest in its domestic division amid concerns over inflation and high-interest rates. The bank reported a net income of £1.3 billion ($1.68 billion) for the quarter, almost meeting market expectations but leaving some analysts disappointed. The results were influenced by slower momentum in the company&#8217;s investment banking division, which experienced a 3% revenue drop. Consequently, Barclays&#8217; shares saw a 5.4% decline in early trade, highlighting investors&#8217; apprehension.</p>
<p>Despite the challenges faced, there were some positive highlights for the quarter. Revenues for the domestic division and consumer and cards arm increased by 14% and 18%, respectively. The bank&#8217;s CET1 ratio, a measure of its solvency, improved to 13.8% from the previous quarter&#8217;s report of 13.6%, indicating a strong financial position. Additionally, operating costs dropped 6% compared to the previous year.</p>
<h2>Customers Repay Mortgage Loans Using Their Savings</h2>
<p>The company&#8217;s chief executive C. S. Venkatakrishnan <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/07/27/barclays-earnings-result-q2-2023-.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">told</a> CNBC that the expected decrease in net interest margins is primarily driven by customers using their savings to repay their mortgage loans. While this may reduce the risk of payment defaults, it puts pressure on the bank&#8217;s margins. Despite this, Venkatakrishnan reassured that the UK consumer is cautious but not under financial strain.</p>
<p>The bank&#8217;s finance director, Anna Cross, also highlighted the growing pressure on Barclays&#8217; UK business. Stubborn inflation, which is currently the highest among the G7 group of nations, coupled with higher interest rates, has prompted customers to prioritize debt repayment and increase their savings. As a consequence, the bank&#8217;s net interest margin in the domestic bank is expected to reach as high as 4.25% in the UK.</p>
<p>&#8220;Since we put out that full year guidance the facts have changed. Base rates were expected to peak at 4.25% in the UK and we are now sitting here at 5%, inflation is persistently higher and mortgage rates are higher,&#8221; she <a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/barclays-reports-first-half-profit-hits-expectations-bad-loans-rise-2023-07-27/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">told</a> Reuters.</p>
<h2>Barclays to Buyback £750 Million Shares</h2>
<p>To counter the margin pressure, Barclays announced plans for a share buyback of up to £750 million, a move welcomed by analysts at Jefferies. The financial experts referred to it as the &#8220;silver lining&#8221; in an otherwise modestly disappointing quarter for revenue.</p>
<p>Looking ahead, industry analysts expressed concerns about the bank&#8217;s future performance, especially given the squeezed margins in the UK as competition intensifies and households face rising cost of living challenges.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, other European banks are grappling with similar struggles in their investment banking units. <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/deutsche-bank/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Deutsche Bank</a> recently reported that its investment bank revenues were expected to fall this year, adding to the broader concerns in the industry.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fed-rate-hikes-bank-failure/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/barclays-uk-interest-rates/">Barclays Faces Challenges in UK Division as Inflation and High-Interest Rates Affect Margins</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/barclays-uk-interest-rates/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fed Rate Hikes Could Cause More US Bank Failures, Says Shark Tank’s Kevin O’Leary</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fed-rate-hikes-bank-failure/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fed-rate-hikes-bank-failure/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 14:10:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kevin O'Leary]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=264790</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fed-rate-hikes-bank-failure/">Fed Rate Hikes Could Cause More US Bank Failures, Says Shark Tank&#8217;s Kevin O&#8217;Leary</a></p>
<p>O'Leary says the Fed could still increase rates to 6.25% or 6.5%, resulting in bank failures in regional institutions.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fed-rate-hikes-bank-failure/">Fed Rate Hikes Could Cause More US Bank Failures, Says Shark Tank&#8217;s Kevin O&#8217;Leary</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fed-rate-hikes-bank-failure/">Fed Rate Hikes Could Cause More US Bank Failures, Says Shark Tank&#8217;s Kevin O&#8217;Leary</a></p>
<p>Popular Shark Tank investor Kevin O’Leary has sounded a note of warning about the Federal Reserve’s tightening cycle applied to fight inflation. According to O’Leary, the Fed’s continuous rate hikes could result in more US bank failures.</p>
<p>Speaking to CNBC’s Street Signs Asia, O’Leary said that the hikes could cause a breakdown in regional banks, suggesting the situation would become precarious because the banks support 60% of the US economy. Following the recent rate hike, O’Leary said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“You keep squeezing the toothpaste tube, you keep rolling it up, you keep raising rates, and you know things are going to break, you just don’t know when and where.”</p></blockquote>
<p>On Wednesday, the Federal Reserve <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fed-25-basis-point-hike-rates/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">increased interest rates</a> by 25 basis points to keep up with the fight against inflation. The recent increase puts the current rate at a range of 5.25% &#8211; 5.50%. The range’s midpoint is the highest US interest rate since 2001.</p>
<p>In 2023 alone, the Federal Reserve has increased interest rates four times. Last year, the Federal Open Market Committee (FOMC) began increasing rates on March 17, the first increase in more than three years. By the end of 2022, the Fed had increased rates seven times.</p>
<h2>Predictions for Future Hikes Give Credence to Warning on Bank Failures</h2>
<p>Following Wednesday’s increase, Fed Chairman Jerome Powell hinted at another hike after the next FOMC meeting scheduled in September. Powell said a further hike might be necessary because the rate is too far from the intended 2%. However, he assured that the agency would be “making careful assessments” and may choose to leave rates unchanged at the next meeting depending on economic data.</p>
<p>O’Leary says he has told investors to wait 90 days as events unfold in the United States banking arena, as he predicts a possible crash. O’Leary also added that the Fed could continue hikes before stopping at 6.25% or 6.50%.</p>
<p>This prediction rhymes with previous forecasts about the rise of interest rates for the rest of the year. According to an exec at the world’s largest asset manager BlackRock, there’s a chance the Fed could take rates up to 6%. In a February note, the company’s chief investment officer of global fixed income Rick Rieder <a href="https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/blackrock-sees-reasonable-chance-fed-raising-rates-6-2023-03-07/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">said</a> the Fed would likely keep the rate there for “an extended period” until inflation falls near 2%.</p>
<p>Also in February, Coinspeaker <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/wall-street-traders-interest-rate/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a> that Wall Street traders were betting that the Fed would hike rates to 6% in September. One trader placed a bet worth about $18 million and could walk away with up to $135 if the prediction comes to pass. In the same month, BofA Global Research also made <a href="https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/fed-might-raise-policy-rates-6-bofa-2023-02-28/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">the same prediction</a>. According to a note, the researchers said the Fed might struggle with inflation for much longer because of a tight labor market and consumer demand. The note suggests that aggregate demand must fall significantly before inflation drops to the Fed’s target.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-logo-android-app/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fed-rate-hikes-bank-failure/">Fed Rate Hikes Could Cause More US Bank Failures, Says Shark Tank&#8217;s Kevin O&#8217;Leary</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fed-rate-hikes-bank-failure/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Twitter Changes Logo on Android App</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-logo-android-app/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-logo-android-app/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 13:56:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[twitter]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[x]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=264795</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-logo-android-app/">Twitter Changes Logo on Android App</a></p>
<p>Notably, the update currently applies to Android users while the Twitter bird logo remains on the App Store.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-logo-android-app/">Twitter Changes Logo on Android App</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-logo-android-app/">Twitter Changes Logo on Android App</a></p>
<p>After confirming intentions to replace the prominent Twitter logo with the letter X earlier this week, Twitter has finally changed the blue bird symbol to the new design on Android. When CEO <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/elon-musk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Elon Musk</a> announced the rebranding, many <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-risks-logo-letter-x/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">opined</a> that it would bring more damage to the company, which had already recorded significant losses in ads revenue. In addition to its financial losses, Twitter faces major rivalry from Meta’s Threads, amongst others.</p>
<h2>Twitter Logo on Android App Changes to X</h2>
<p>The latest step Twitter took in its rebranding is rolling out the new X logo on its Android app and also updating its listing on the Google Play Store. The social networking service included screenshots of the rebranded X app on Android, showing black backgrounds and the new lettered design. Searches for “Twitter” on the Google Play Store now direct users to download the X app, which “is the trusted digital town square for everyone.” Additionally, X said users can now upload and watch up to 3-hour videos. However, Twitter Blue said on its support page that subscribers can upload up to 2 hours long and 8GB file size videos (1080p).</p>
<p>Notably, the update currently applies to Android users while the Twitter bird logo remains on the App Store. Also, the Twitter Lite app has remained the same since its last update in May 2023.</p>
<h2>X &#8211; Everything App</h2>
<p>Before Musk announced the rebranding, the company had retired the “Twitter Inc” name, according to an <a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.cand.395023/gov.uscourts.cand.395023.123.0.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener">official document</a>. A filing with a California federal court showed that the microblogging social media platform had become a part of the X parent company, X Holdings Corp. The primary vision for X is to make it an everything app like China’s WeChat, owned by Tencent Holdings. The super app provides social media services, and financial services, offering instant messages on the same platform. WeChat started as an instant messaging app in 2011, after which it added purchases and doctors&#8217; appointment scheduling. Now, the service has accumulated over 1.3 billion monthly active users (MAUs) globally.</p>
<p>Musk’s dream for X is similar to WeChat’s achievements, but there are speculations that the billionaire may face some challenges. While Threads is a major opposition to the social networking service, the likes of YouTube, TikTok, and Whatsapp are all working towards evolving into super apps.</p>
<p>About a week before Twitter changed its logo to X on its Android app, the company had made changes to its official handle on the social media platform. It switched from @twitter to @X.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ag-first-crypto-fund-spain/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-logo-android-app/">Twitter Changes Logo on Android App</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-logo-android-app/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A&amp;G Announces Launch of First Crypto Fund in Spain</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ag-first-crypto-fund-spain/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ag-first-crypto-fund-spain/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 13:22:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[A&G]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bit2me]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitstamp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bvnk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto fund]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pwc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ripio]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[santander]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=264791</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ag-first-crypto-fund-spain/">A&#038;G Announces Launch of First Crypto Fund in Spain</a></p>
<p>The fund will be audited independently by PwC, one of the world's leading professional services organizations.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ag-first-crypto-fund-spain/">A&#038;G Announces Launch of First Crypto Fund in Spain</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ag-first-crypto-fund-spain/">A&#038;G Announces Launch of First Crypto Fund in Spain</a></p>
<p>A&amp;G, a prominent Spain-based financial entity focused on private banking, has announced its entry into the crypto market with the launch of the country’s first-ever crypto fund.</p>
<p>With €12.4 billion ($14 billion) in assets under management as of the end of 2022, A&amp;G’s foray into the crypto market demonstrates the firm’s commitment to innovation and its recognition of the growing importance of digital assets in the global financial landscape.</p>
<p>The announcement, <a href="https://www.ayg.es/sala-de-prensa/detalle-noticia/6560/a-and-g-lanza-el-primer-fondo-de-derecho-espanol-de-criptomonedas" target="_blank" rel="noopener">released</a> through an official statement earlier this week, has sent ripples through the financial community in Spain and beyond. The new crypto fund, exclusively accessible to professional investors, aims to capitalize on the growing interest in crypto while providing a safe and regulated investment avenue for A&amp;G’s esteemed clients.</p>
<p>Notably, A&amp;G emphasizes that its crypto fund adheres to Spanish jurisprudence, providing a robust regulatory framework to protect investor interests and maintain transparency. This aspect is expected to instill a sense of trust among potential investors who may have been cautious about investing in crypto due to concerns about regulation and security.</p>
<p>Diego Fernandez Elices, Chief Investment Officer at A&amp;G, commented on the launch, stating, “We consider it an optimal solution for any European professional investor who wants to approach the world of cryptocurrencies, without forgetting that it is a very high-risk fund.”</p>
<p>In an effort to boost investor confidence, A&amp;G has appointed CACEIS, the asset servicing banking company of Crédit Agricole and Santander, as the crypto fund’s depositary. Furthermore, the fund will be audited independently by PwC, one of the world&#8217;s leading professional services organizations.</p>
<h2>Beyond A&amp;G: Crypto Development in Spain</h2>
<p>Cryptocurrencies, particularly Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a>) and Ethereum (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ETH</a>), have garnered immense popularity over the past decade, attracting both retail and institutional investors seeking diversification and potential high returns. Despite this growing interest, the Spanish financial industry has been relatively cautious about embracing digital assets.</p>
<p>However, in recent years Spain has shown a growing interest in the development and regulation of crypto and blockchain technology. In 2022, the Bank of Spain started issuing licenses to providers of services for the exchange of virtual currency for fiat currency and the custody of digital wallets.</p>
<p>This approach aims to increase transparency and legitimacy in the cryptocurrency business while also improving consumer safety. Several well-known companies, including Bit2Me, Bitstamp, BVNK, Crypto.com, and Ripio, were among the first to obtain these licenses.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the Spanish Central Bank (Banco de España) made an announcement about its plans to investigate the establishment of a wholesale Central Bank Digital Currency (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-central-bank-digital-currency-cbdc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CBDC</a>) project. This CBDC push is in line with the other Central Banks from the European Economic Area (EEA).</p>
<p>This project aimed to investigate the potential applications and benefits of a digital currency issued and backed by the central bank, specifically designed for use between financial institutions.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/waymo-scale-back-autonomous-truck/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ag-first-crypto-fund-spain/">A&#038;G Announces Launch of First Crypto Fund in Spain</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ag-first-crypto-fund-spain/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alphabet-owned Waymo Decides to Scale Back on Its Autonomous Truck Technology</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/waymo-scale-back-autonomous-truck/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/waymo-scale-back-autonomous-truck/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 13:08:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Transportation News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[waymo]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=264773</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/waymo-scale-back-autonomous-truck/">Alphabet-owned Waymo Decides to Scale Back on Its Autonomous Truck Technology</a></p>
<p>Although Waymo scales down its autonomous truck technology, it would continue partnership with Daimler Truck North America (DTNA) to develop an autonomous truck platform further.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/waymo-scale-back-autonomous-truck/">Alphabet-owned Waymo Decides to Scale Back on Its Autonomous Truck Technology</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/waymo-scale-back-autonomous-truck/">Alphabet-owned Waymo Decides to Scale Back on Its Autonomous Truck Technology</a></p>
<p>In its latest decision, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/alphabet-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Alphabet</a>-backed Waymo announced that it would scale back on its autonomous truck technology and will focus entirely on its ride-hailing services. In its official announcement, Waymo noted that it would &#8220;push back&#8221; the timeline for its operational efforts for trucking. Thus, it also plans to scale back development in the unit. As a result of this decision, Waymo has also laid off a small number of employees.</p>
<p>Waymo&#8217;s trucking unit, Waymo Via, and its Waymo One Robotaxi division were side by side, reflecting the company&#8217;s push to make its self-driving technology a commercial reality. However, uncertainties now surround the timeline and future of its autonomous trucks.</p>
<p>Waymo noted that they would maintain their partnership with Daimler Truck North America (DTNA) to develop an autonomous truck platform further. The company added that its joint focus is on enhancing road safety and efficiency for fleet customers.</p>
<p>To achieve this, Waymo will continue investing in the development of a redundant chassis that will enable autonomous trucking. Back in 2020, Waymo originally connected with Daimler with a common goal of building  “SAE Level 4 trucks&#8221;. Speaking on the development, Waymo spokesperson Katherine Barna <a href="https://waymo.com/blog/2023/07/doubling-down-on-waymo-one.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>:</p>
<div>
<blockquote><p>“We continue to develop a generalizable Driver that can be applied across a number of vehicle platforms and applications over time &#8211; including trucking. We’re developing a generalizable Driver, continuing our work on freeway, continuing our partnership with Daimler Truck &#8211; all of which will help us to be ready to stand up our trucking efforts when the time is right.”</p></blockquote>
</div>
<h2>Path Ahead for Waymo</h2>
<p>Waymo&#8217;s primary objective is to create substantial value by concentrating on achieving commercial success for our ride-hailing business in the short term. They are diligently enhancing the driver technology, addressing regulatory challenges, and conducting tests to gain valuable insights for future partnerships.</p>
<p>Besides, Waymo firmly believes in the promising commercial potential of its trucking solution and other applications of the Waymo Driver. By prioritizing ride-hailing at present, Waymo positions itself and its partners, and customers for success across all our business lines in the future, highlighting the versatility of the Waymo Driver.</p>
<p>In California, lawmakers are considering a bill that might need human drivers to be present at all times in self-driving trucks. This could be a big problem for driverless trucks in the state, as experts believed that self-driving semi trucks would be a reality before robotaxis due to their simpler technology and challenges.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ethstorage-7m-seed-funding/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/waymo-scale-back-autonomous-truck/">Alphabet-owned Waymo Decides to Scale Back on Its Autonomous Truck Technology</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/waymo-scale-back-autonomous-truck/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>EthStorage Raises $7M in Seed Funding Round</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ethstorage-7m-seed-funding/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ethstorage-7m-seed-funding/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Babafemi Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 12:47:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethstorage]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=264656</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ethstorage-7m-seed-funding/">EthStorage Raises $7M in Seed Funding Round</a></p>
<p>The funding comes at a time when investment in the crypto ecosystem is becoming scarce.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ethstorage-7m-seed-funding/">EthStorage Raises $7M in Seed Funding Round</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ethstorage-7m-seed-funding/">EthStorage Raises $7M in Seed Funding Round</a></p>

<p>Layer 2 data storage project EthStorage has <a href="https://twitter.com/EthStorage/status/1684385120755544065" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">raised</a> $7 million in its seed funding led by crypto investment fund dao5. The round saw the participation of Foresight Ventures, Galxe, Gate Ventures, SevenX Ventures, and Sky9 Capital. Avant Blockchain Capital, Cloud Nine Capital, DragonRoark, Future Money Group, GeekCartel, Rebase D. Ventures, Vitalbridge, W3.Hitchhiker. Some other angel investors also made a contribution. </p>
<p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="474" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">EthStorage has successfully raised $7M in a seed round with a $100M valuation. It was led by <a href="https://twitter.com/daofive?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@daofive</a>, with participation from prominent investors like <a href="https://twitter.com/SevenXVentures?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@SevenXVentures</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/ForesightVen?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@ForesightVen</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/dragonroark?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@dragonroark</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/Sky9Capital?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@Sky9Capital</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/avantfund?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@avantfund</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/fmgroupxyz?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@fmgroupxyz</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/gate_ventures?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@gate_ventures</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/Galxe?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@Galxe</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/geek_cartel?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@geek_cartel</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/HitchhikerW3?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@HitchhikerW3</a>… <a href="https://t.co/jplz6an5iQ">pic.twitter.com/jplz6an5iQ</a></p>&mdash; EthStorage 🔜 EthCC Paris 🇫🇷 (@EthStorage) <a href="https://twitter.com/EthStorage/status/1684385120755544065?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 27, 2023</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Following the seed funding round, the company is now valued at $100 million. Using the funds, EthStorage plans to expand its team, research and develop more products, and attract more ecosystem partners.</p>
<h2>Decline in Crypto Funding</h2>
<p>The funding comes at a time when investment in the crypto ecosystem is becoming scarce. From $12.14 billion raised in Q1 2022 to just $2.34 billion in Q2 2023, venture capital investment in the industry has severely <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2023/07/05/crypto-funding-drops-fifth-straight-quarter/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">declined</a>.</p>
<p>Lydia Chiu, VP of business development at Ava Labs, noted the decline in venture capital funding may be due to the severe regulatory stance of the US. This, she said, has caused a lot of crypto-related deal flows to be patterned after “traditional venture structures, like raising equity, instead of token investments or simple agreement for future tokens (SAFT)”.</p>
<p>Interestingly, EthStorage’s funding round was structured as a SAFT, according to Kevin Yang, managing partner at Gate Ventures. This is suggestive of investor confidence in the project.</p>
<h2>About EthStorage</h2>
<p>EthStorage is a Layer 2 storage solution built on the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a> network. The company was established in 2022 by Qi Zhou, founder of blockchain infrastructure startup QuarkChain. EthStorage is programmed to reduce the cost of storing large chunks of data on the Ethereum network while expanding its storage capacity. This low cost of large data storage by EthStorage is expected to enable a fully decentralized network in the future. Already, the rollup is integrated with EVM. It is also compatible with Solidity, Remix, Hardhat, and MetaMask.</p>
<p>According to Gate Ventures, EthStorage is paving the way for an innovative, cost-effective, and dynamic storage solution that has the potential to address the limitations faced by existing storage options.</p>
<p>More recently, the team <a href="https://twitter.com/EthStorage/status/1683491183362703360" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">introduced</a> the Web3:// Access Protocol that will allow users to browse a fully decentralized dynamic website on EVM. The company also called on interested developers to come and build with them on the project. So far, the EthStorage team received two research grants from the Ethereum Foundation. It also emerged as the winner in the evaluation of the EDCON 2023 Super Demo.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/derivatives-gemini-trading-competition/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ethstorage-7m-seed-funding/">EthStorage Raises $7M in Seed Funding Round</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ethstorage-7m-seed-funding/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Derivatives Exchange Gemini Preps to Host Trading Competition Next Month</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/derivatives-gemini-trading-competition/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/derivatives-gemini-trading-competition/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 12:42:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gemini]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gemini dollar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gemini foundation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[winklevoss brothers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=264706</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/derivatives-gemini-trading-competition/">Derivatives Exchange Gemini Preps to Host Trading Competition Next Month</a></p>
<p>Gemini launched its derivative platform Gemini Foundation in May in the heat of the regulatory tension in the United States.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/derivatives-gemini-trading-competition/">Derivatives Exchange Gemini Preps to Host Trading Competition Next Month</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/derivatives-gemini-trading-competition/">Derivatives Exchange Gemini Preps to Host Trading Competition Next Month</a></p>
<p>As part of efforts to attract new users to its platform, crypto derivatives exchange Gemini Foundation is set to host its first-ever trading competition next month. The move comes amid Gemini recording a massive decline in its trading volume. As of publication, CoinMarketCap <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/exchanges/gemini/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">data</a> suggests that Gemini&#8217;s trading volume has declined nearly 90% over the past year. That is from about $147 million to $17.9 million.</p>
<p>So, by all means, Gemini would be hoping to leverage the trading competition to shine new light on the platform and reel in new users.</p>
<h2>Gemini Shares Competition Details</h2>
<p>According to a Bloomberg <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-07-26/winklevoss-gamify-overseas-derivatives-exchange-to-boost-demand?srnd=cryptocurrencies-v2#xj4y7vzkg" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a>, the Gemini Leaderboard competition is slated to begin on August 1, 2023. Once live, the competition will track the performance of crypto traders on the international derivatives trading platform and reward the top performers accordingly.</p>
<p>But, for traders to be eligible to participate in the competition, they must fund their derivatives account with at least $250 worth of Gemini dollar (GUSD) stablecoin before the month ends.</p>
<p>After funding, the trader must then maintain the said amount in the account throughout the competition. That is, till August 31, 2023.</p>
<p>Gemini <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/non-us-derivatives-gemini-foundation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">launched</a> its derivative platform Gemini Foundation in May. That was in the heat of the regulatory tension in the United States. Like many other firms in the crypto industry, the Winklevoss twins also sought to increase their global presence.</p>
<p>However, activity on the platform has not exactly been going as expected. Hence, the decision to float the trading competition in a bid to bring publicity to the platform.   And, for what it&#8217;s worth, a promotion like this is a common tactic that has been severally employed in the crypto industry. While users compete for rewards and the fame that comes with being tagged the best trader, Gemini also expects to see improved usage on its derivatives exchange.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/eos-foundation-suing-block-one/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/derivatives-gemini-trading-competition/">Derivatives Exchange Gemini Preps to Host Trading Competition Next Month</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/derivatives-gemini-trading-competition/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>EOS Foundation Would Be Suing Block.One for Failing to Honour $1B Commitment</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/eos-foundation-suing-block-one/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/eos-foundation-suing-block-one/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 12:15:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[block.one]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[enf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eos foundation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eosio]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=264702</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/eos-foundation-suing-block-one/">EOS Foundation Would Be Suing Block.One for Failing to Honour $1B Commitment</a></p>
<p>The EOS community has encountered significant problems since Block.one failed to honour its commitments of supporting the EOS Network and community. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/eos-foundation-suing-block-one/">EOS Foundation Would Be Suing Block.One for Failing to Honour $1B Commitment</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/eos-foundation-suing-block-one/">EOS Foundation Would Be Suing Block.One for Failing to Honour $1B Commitment</a></p>
<p>As per the latest development, the EOS Network Foundation (ENF) shall be initiating legal action against major investor Block.one (B1) over its failure to honor investment commitments of over $1 billion.</p>
<p>On July 25, ENF founder and CEO Yves La Rose posted on Twitter that the foundation is getting ready to file a lawsuit against B1 due to its &#8220;failure to fulfill its $1B commitment&#8221;.</p>
<p>La Rose also mentioned that Block.one is currently dealing with another class-action lawsuit for $22 million, as their previous proposed settlement of $27.5 million with lead plaintiff Crypto Assets Opportunity was rejected by a US judge. “You may need to opt-out to be eligible to participate in the ENF’s lawsuit,” La Rose added.</p>
<p>As per La Rose, the class-action lawsuit, which began in 2017, is still in the process of settling. He also stated that individuals who wish to exclude themselves from the lawsuit can reach out to counsel James Koutoulas. The deadline to file a claim or opt out of the class action is August 23rd. La Rose <a href="https://twitter.com/BigBeardSamurai/status/1684007512721219584?s=20" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">added</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“If you opt out of the US class action, there is no guarantee that you will be able to make any other claim against Block.one, or that such a claim will be successful.”</p></blockquote>
<p>La Rose stated that the EOS community has encountered significant problems because he believes Block.one, the creator and initial seller of the EOS token, has not fulfilled its commitment to support the EOS Network and community. ENF has been actively working with stakeholders to hold Block.one accountable for its promises.</p>
<h2>EOS vs Block.one</h2>
<p>Two months ago back in May 2023, La Rose called for slapping a class-action lawsuit against Block.one. furthermore, La Rose also accused Block.one of breaking its promises of investing $1 billion from EOS’ initial coin offering (ICO) to EOSIO developers. Back then, the ENF CEO <a href="https://twitter.com/BigBeardSamurai/status/1659959817719488512" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">wrote</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“It was broadly understood at the time that B1 was making these commitments that these investments would be made in the EOS Network, [&#8230;] and yet B1 has provided minimal real support to EOS Network efforts to develop the network. B1’s promises during the ICO and after have not been fulfilled.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>As mentioned earlier, Block.one <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/block-one-sets-new-ico-record-eos-token-enters-top-10-cryptocurrencies/" rel="">conducted</a> an Initial Coin Offering in 2017, raising $4.1 billion over the course of 12 months. This ICO was one of the biggest crowdfunding campaigns at that time.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shell-q2-2023-profit/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/eos-foundation-suing-block-one/">EOS Foundation Would Be Suing Block.One for Failing to Honour $1B Commitment</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/eos-foundation-suing-block-one/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shell Reports 55% Plunge in Q2 2023 Profit as Commodity Prices Decline</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/shell-q2-2023-profit/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/shell-q2-2023-profit/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 10:48:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wall Street]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[shell]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[shell stock]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=264757</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shell-q2-2023-profit/">Shell Reports 55% Plunge in Q2 2023 Profit as Commodity Prices Decline</a></p>
<p>Shell is struggling with a continuous fall in profits as Q2 2023 figures show significant reductions compared with last quarter and Q2 2022.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shell-q2-2023-profit/">Shell Reports 55% Plunge in Q2 2023 Profit as Commodity Prices Decline</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shell-q2-2023-profit/">Shell Reports 55% Plunge in Q2 2023 Profit as Commodity Prices Decline</a></p>
<p>Oil giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/royal-dutch-shell/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Shell</a> (LON: SHEL) has posted disappointing profits for Q2 2023, largely caused by a reduction in the prices of fossil fuels.</p>
<p>Shell’s report shows that the British giant saw its adjusted earnings crest at $5.1 billion for the quarter ended June, lower than the expected $6 billion from analysts polled by Refinitiv. This is a steep 55.6% fall from the $11.5 billion for Q2 2023, and 46.8% from <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shell-q1-2023/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Q1 this year</a>.</p>
<p>Despite efforts to ramp up profit, Shell is still focused on reducing emissions. Speaking to CNBC’s Squawk Box Europe, Shell CEO Wael Sawan said the company is looking to make moves that are beneficial for its shareholders but also for the planet. Sawan added:</p>
<blockquote><p>“We are focused on creating more value with less emissions. And what that means is we will continue to pull all the levers to drive further value growth in the organization, while at the same time we will continue to meet our aggressive emissions reduction targets &#8211; both for our own emissions, as well as for our customers.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Shell has announced share buybacks worth $3 billion to conclude over the next quarter. In addition to reporting a 15% increase to $0.33 per share in the quarterly dividend, Shell is true to its word on doing right by shareholders. However, RBC Brew Dolphin investment manager Stuart Lamont believes this would “inevitably come with questions attached in the current environment”.</p>
<h2>Shell Plans Past Q2 2023</h2>
<p>The British oil giant received some criticism after it announced a decision to maintain current oil production levels until the decade ends. Activist shareholder group Follow This believes that avoiding new output cuts pushes Shell “on a collision course” with the 2015 Paris Agreement. The agreement includes several points, including a long-term global warming goal and a target to reduce greenhouse gas emissions every five years.</p>
<p>At Shell’s shareholder meeting in May, Follow This garnered 20% support. The group’s founder Mark van Baal insists that Shell is still accountable to the 20%. Nonetheless, Shell has confirmed its commitment to following climate targets. The company assures it is on course to achieving net-zero status by 2050.</p>
<p>Shell intends to spend $15 billion on low-carbon projects over the next three years. Asked whether this will appease climate activists, Shell CEO Sawan said the company’s focus is doing right for its own health and for its shareholders. Although Shell focuses on a balanced energy transition, Sawan said the company looks to deploy capital so shareholders can see returns.</p>
<p>Sawan also added that Shell is very willing to grow its capital if it sees new opportunities that will help do so. According to the CEO, the company cannot grow its capital “on the basis of activist noise”.</p>
<p>A few other oil companies also recorded reduced earnings. TotalEnergies reported a 49% plunge in adjusted income to $5 billion from the same period last year. Norway’s Equinor also <a href="https://cdn.equinor.com/files/h61q9gi9/global/b55339c119a5084d4993d995bd4ea0411ce73130.pdf?q2-2023-press-release-equinor.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">recorded</a> a 57% crash in Q2 profit compared to Q2 2022.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/canada-capital-liquidity-rules-crypto/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shell-q2-2023-profit/">Shell Reports 55% Plunge in Q2 2023 Profit as Commodity Prices Decline</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/shell-q2-2023-profit/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4064 metric#misses=42 metric#hit-ratio=99.0 metric#bytes=1051175 metric#prefetches=199 metric#store-reads=20 metric#store-writes=2 metric#store-hits=205 metric#store-misses=3 metric#sql-queries=34 metric#ms-total=99.45 metric#ms-cache=4.93 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.2349 metric#ms-cache-ratio=5.0 -->