<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 15:51:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Hashed Emergent to host the first multi-chain web3 conference in India</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/hashed-emergent-to-host-the-first-multi-chain-web3-conference-in-india/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 15:47:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Events]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/hashed-emergent-to-launch-the-first-multi-chain-web3-conference-in-india/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The conference will run from December 4 to December 10. The conference will include hackathons, side events, parties, a headline conference, and an ETHIndia hackathon. The conference is organized by Hashed Emergent, a subsidiary of Hashed, a prominent web3 venture fund from South Korea. Hashed Emergent has announced that it will host the first blockchain [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/hashed-emergent-to-host-the-first-multi-chain-web3-conference-in-india/">Hashed Emergent to host the first multi-chain web3 conference in India</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>The conference will run from December 4 to December 10.</li>
<li>The conference will include hackathons, side events, parties, a headline conference, and an ETHIndia hackathon.</li>
<li>The conference is organized by Hashed Emergent, a subsidiary of Hashed, a prominent web3 venture fund from South Korea.</li>
</ul>
<p>Hashed Emergent has announced that it will host the first <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/blockchain/">blockchain</a> conference week in India in December. The week-long series of web3-focused events will be held in Bangalore, the heart of India&rsquo;s tech and startup scene, rightfully known as the &ldquo;Silicon Valley of the East.&rdquo;</p>
<p>The new conference dubbed India Blockchain Week (IBW) aims at becoming India&rsquo;s first world-class, multi-chain web3 conference with a pan-industry agenda. It will reflect India&rsquo;s increasing role in web3, expressed both in terms of crypto adoption and the exciting startups originating from the sub-continent.</p>
<p>Expressing his excitement about the upcoming event, Managing Partner of Hashed Emergent, Tak Lee, said:</p>
<p><em>&ldquo;We&rsquo;re excited to bring the first world-class, pan-industry and multi-chain web3 conference to India, finally giving it the attention it has always deserved. Bangalore ranks among the most prolific startup hubs worldwide, and Indian startups in web3 have made a considerable impact on the industry, spearheaded by multiple hugely successful protocols and products. We believe that IBW will quickly become one of the most interesting and diverse gathering places for the crypto industry.&rdquo;</em></p>
<h2>The India Blockchain Week timetable</h2>
<p>The conference will have a week-long series of web3-focused events lasting from December 4-10.</p>
<p>It will start with a &ldquo;warm-up&rdquo; session on Monday and Tuesday, December 4-5. This will include hackathons, side events and parties.</p>
<p>The IBW headline conference will be held on December 6-7, or Wednesday and Thursday succeeded by the ETHIndia hackathon which set a record last year as one of the largest <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/what-is-ethereum/">Ethereum</a> hackathons with over 2,000 attendees and 450+ project submissions.</p>
<p>The main venue of the IBW conference will be the Sheraton Grand Hotel in Whitefield, a major IT and commercial hub of Bangalore.</p>
<h2>MarketAcross will be IBW&rsquo;s lead media</h2>
<p>MarketAcross, the world&rsquo;s leading web3 PR and marketing agency known for its work in the region with companies like Polygon and Hashed Emergent, will be joining the event as the global lead media.</p>
<p>MarketAcross has served as the official media partner in multiple web3 events including the Korea Blockchain Week, WebX, Paris Blockchain Week, and the IVS Kyoto.</p>
<p>India has rapidly emerged as one of the leading adopters of web3 despite the numerous regulatory hurdles seeing that the Indian government has been historically sceptical to crypto and is now positioning itself for globally harmonized regulation at the G20 Summit.</p>
<p>While the list of speakers at the IBW headline conference is yet to be revealed, Harsh Emergent has confirmed that it will include prominent local and global leaders within the blockchain industry.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/hashed-emergent-to-host-the-first-multi-chain-web3-conference-in-india/">Hashed Emergent to host the first multi-chain web3 conference in India</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stay away from Grayscale Bitcoin Trust despite discount narrowing to 10-month low</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/stay-away-from-grayscale-bitcoin-trust-despite-discount-narrowing-to-10-month-low/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dan Ashmore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 13:36:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Grayscale]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/stay-away-from-grayscale-bitcoin-trust-despite-discount-narrowing-to-10-month-low/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key Takeaways The Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC) has persistently traded at a discount to its net asset value The discount has narrowed to its lowest mark since September off hope the fund is more likely to be converted to an ETF The entire GBTC debacle represents the mess that is the institutional regulatory climate in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/stay-away-from-grayscale-bitcoin-trust-despite-discount-narrowing-to-10-month-low/">Stay away from Grayscale Bitcoin Trust despite discount narrowing to 10-month low</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2 dir="ltr">Key Takeaways</h2>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">The Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC) has persistently traded at a discount to its net asset value</li>
<li dir="ltr">The discount has narrowed to its lowest mark since September off hope the fund is more likely to be converted to an ETF</li>
<li dir="ltr">The entire GBTC debacle represents the mess that is the institutional regulatory climate in the US</li>
<li dir="ltr">Spot ETFs are a question of when rather than if, and such investment vehicles will then be a thing of the past</li>
<li dir="ltr">That won&rsquo;t assuage frustration of GBTC investors, who have been caught badly as alternative Bitcoin investment vehicles have come online and demand for the trust has dried up</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p dir="ltr">Among the interesting aspects of the fallout from the slew of recent spot Bitcoin ETF filings is how it affects the controversial Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC).&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The trust has been flying, up 56% in the three weeks since Blackrock&rsquo;s ETF filing was announced.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14353132">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">Notably, this means it has significantly outpaced its underlying asset, Bitcoin. That sounds like a good thing, but it really summises the problem with this investment vehicle that has done nothing but frustrate investors in recent years, but we will get to that in a moment.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">I have plotted the movement of the GBTC against Bitcoin itself in the next chart, highlighting the outperformance the Trust has had since the ETF filing, with Bitcoin itself up &ldquo;only&rdquo; 21%.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14353266">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<h2 dir="ltr">Grayscale discount to net asset value narrowing but still enormous</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The trust&rsquo;s discount to net asset value has also narrowed to its smallest mark since September, now below 30%. This comes as investors bet the trust is now more likely to finally be allowed to convert to an ETF.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/06/1688650389110-2e2da1ba-ffda-469d-89b2-467982f18dd6.png" style="width: 600px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="600" height="189"></p>
<p dir="ltr">&nbsp;Should this conversion occur, the discount would narrow to near zero, as funds would then be allowed to flow in and out of the vehicle without affecting the underlying assets. For the time being, while it remains a trust, there is no way to get Bitcoin out of GBTC. This, coupled with steep fees (2% annually) means that a heavy discount has persisted.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">In truth, the very existence of the Grayscale trust is a black mark on the sector. The discount it trades at is farcical &ndash; even following the recent narrowing, a 30% delta is an enormous chasm, one that is hurting investors.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The outsized assets under management &ndash; essentially trapped due to the closed-fund nature &ndash; feels like a throwback to the days when anyone and everyone wanted to get exposure to Bitcoin through whatever means necessary. Grayscale was the only shop in town, and such was the demand for Bitcoin, coupled with that monopolistic power, that it even traded at a premium for much of its early history.</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, as more mediums through which Bitcoin exposure can be had have come online, the premium has flipped to a discount, and that discount has become <em>large.&nbsp;</em>It is probably fair to say that investors displayed a lack of due diligence for how the fund works, another throwback to the up-only bull market of days gone by.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Without donning a captain hindsight outfit, there was always going to be competitor firms coming online and the premium was bound to come under pressure. An investment in GBTC essentially amounted to two things: a bet on Bitcoin, and a bet that the trust would be converted into an ETF <em>quickly.&nbsp;</em></p>
<p dir="ltr">But at that, perhaps sympathy can be shown to investors. Investment management firm Osprey Funds has a similar product, and earlier this year sued Grayscale, alleging that its competitor misled investors about how likely it was that GBTC would be converted into an ETF. This, they allege, is how they captured such a share of the market.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;Only because of its false and misleading advertising and promotion has Grayscale been able to maintain to date approximately 99.5% market share in a two-participant market despite charging more than four times the asset management fee that Osprey charges for its services&rdquo;, the suit alleges.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Whether Grayscale knew of the regulatory difficulty it would face or not, it has tried and failed for years to convert the vehicle into an ETF. Last year, it sued the SEC itself, declaring the latest rejection &ldquo;arbitrary&rdquo;.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Institutional climate turning</h2>
<p dir="ltr">My thoughts on the trust overall remain the same. I believe it represents a terrible investment (obviously), and its mere existence is only a byproduct of the regulatory travails that the sector has struggled with. There is no reason to even consider buying this unless there is quite literally no other vehicle through which to gain Bitcoin exposure.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">There will come a day when all this squabbling over trusts and ETFs will likely be nothing but a throwback of a more uncertain time. But time is a luxury that many investors don&rsquo;t have, and Grayscale has been a horrendous investment, typical in a lot of ways of the travails the space has had in bridging the gap to become a respected mainstream financial asset.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Not only is the discount jarring as it is, but it widened beyond 50% in the aftermath of the FTX collapse as it emerged that crypto broker Genesis was in deep trouble. Genesis&rsquo; parent company is Digital Currency Group (DCG), the same parent company of Grayscale. Genesis eventually filed for bankruptcy in January.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">This sparked concern around the safety of Grayscale&rsquo;s reserves, something which they company did not exactly comfort investors about when it refused to provide on-chain proof of reserves, citing &ldquo;security concerns&rdquo;. &nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">6) Coinbase frequently performs on-chain validation. Due to security concerns, we do not make such on-chain wallet information and confirmation information publicly available through a cryptographic Proof-of-Reserve, or other advanced cryptographic accounting procedure.</p>
<p>&mdash; Grayscale (@Grayscale) <a href="https://twitter.com/Grayscale/status/1593737746413244417?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">November 18, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">While the furore over reserves has quietened down, the episode is yet another stark reminder of the oft-repeated (but perhaps not often enough) phrase: &ldquo;not your keys, not your coins&rdquo;.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The problem for institutions to date is that they have had trouble accessing Bitcoin directly for a variety of reasons, primarily regulatory-related. While spot ETFs will also technically violate the &ldquo;not your keys&rdquo; mantra, with prudent regulatory oversight and a strong custodian, this should be a safe way for institutions to gain exposure to Bitcoin.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">That would end all this nonsense (and that really is the right word) such as trusts trading at 30% discounts, and give investors a secure avenue through which to put their views on Bitcoin into conviction. That may still be a long way off, but if demand for these products remains, it&rsquo;s only a matter of time.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/stay-away-from-grayscale-bitcoin-trust-despite-discount-narrowing-to-10-month-low/">Stay away from Grayscale Bitcoin Trust despite discount narrowing to 10-month low</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cronos partners with Filecoin&#8217;s Protocol Labs to boost Web 3 adoption</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/cronos-partners-with-filecoins-protocol-labs-to-boost-web-3-adoption/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/cronos-partners-with-filecoins-protocol-labs-to-boost-web-3-adoption/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 11:47:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto.com]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Filecoin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/cronos-partners-with-filecoins-protocol-labs-to-boost-web-3-adoption/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Cronos Labs has announced a partnership with Protocol Labs. Protocol Labs is the creator of Filecoin and IPFS. Cronos Labs announced a major partnership with Protocol Labs, the creator of&#160;Filecoin, the popular decentralized storage platform. The deal will see the two companies provide finances and other tools to companies building in their ecosystem. Creators in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/cronos-partners-with-filecoins-protocol-labs-to-boost-web-3-adoption/">Cronos partners with Filecoin&#8217;s Protocol Labs to boost Web 3 adoption</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Cronos Labs has announced a partnership with Protocol Labs.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Protocol Labs is the creator of Filecoin and IPFS.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Cronos Labs announced a major partnership with Protocol Labs, the creator of&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/filecoin/"><u>Filecoin</u></a>, the popular decentralized storage platform. The deal will see the two companies provide finances and other tools to companies building in their ecosystem.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Creators in the Cronos Accelerator Program will receive mentorship and technical support from the two companies.&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/cronos/"><u>Cronos</u></a> is now implementing the third cohort of the accelerator program. In the first one, winners received $30,000 upfront and access to another $300k in funding. In a statement, Ruben Amenyogbo of Protocol Labs said:</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;This partnership has tremendous potential to provide robust support and empowerment to the current and future cohorts of blockchain startups, fostering the growth of decentralized finance, GameFi, SocialFi, and web3 infrastructure projects. By pushing boundaries and spearheading computing breakthroughs, we aim to shape the future of the web and create a transformative impact.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Cronos and Protocol Labs are both major players in the industry. Filecoin has built a leading decentralized storage platform that is used by many developers. It recently launched the Filecoin Virtual Machine (FVM), which is slowly gaining traction.</p>
<p dir="ltr">At the same time, the developers recently launched Filecoin Web Services, which provides tools like Kubernetes and containers to developers.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Cronos Labs, on the other hand, is the 11th biggest DeFi chains in the world with over $416 million in total value locked (TVL). Some of the top dApps in the ecosystem are Tectonic, VVS Finance.and MM Finance among others. Cronos Labs is backed by Crypto.com, one of the biggest&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/compare/best-cryptocurrency-exchanges/"><u>crypto exchanges</u></a> in the world.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy Filecoin</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>

    <p>eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=MTQ1Mjg2&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy FIL with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    OKX</h3>

    <p>OKX is a world-leading cryptocurrency exchange, providing advanced financial services to traders globally by using blockchain technology.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/okx-crypto?guid=MTQ1Mjg2&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy FIL with OKX today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Trading in digital assets is considered high risk. Digital assets are NOT backed by any government or central bank. The risk of loss in trading or holding digital assets can be substantial. You should carefully consider whether interacting, holding, or trading digital assets is suitable for you in light of your financial condition." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/cronos-partners-with-filecoins-protocol-labs-to-boost-web-3-adoption/">Cronos partners with Filecoin&#8217;s Protocol Labs to boost Web 3 adoption</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/cronos-partners-with-filecoins-protocol-labs-to-boost-web-3-adoption/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto services provider Matrixport predicts Bitcoin to $125k by the end of 2024</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-services-provider-matrixport-predicts-bitcoin-to-125k-by-the-end-of-2024/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-services-provider-matrixport-predicts-bitcoin-to-125k-by-the-end-of-2024/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 11:42:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-services-provider-matrixport-predicts-bitcoin-to-125k-by-the-end-of-2024/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways Matrixport believes that Bitcoin could rally to $125k by the end of next year. The crypto services provider points out that Bitcoin has already touched its bottom after rallying to the $31k level last month.&#160; Bitcoin could hit $125k by the end of next year Bitcoin, the world&#8217;s leading cryptocurrency by market cap, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-services-provider-matrixport-predicts-bitcoin-to-125k-by-the-end-of-2024/">Crypto services provider Matrixport predicts Bitcoin to $125k by the end of 2024</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Matrixport believes that Bitcoin could rally to $125k by the end of next year.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The crypto services provider points out that Bitcoin has already touched its bottom after rallying to the $31k level last month.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitcoin could hit $125k by the end of next year</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin, the world&rsquo;s leading cryptocurrency by market cap, is up by more than 50% since the start of the year. However, some market experts believe that Bitcoin could rally higher over the next 12-18 months.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Crypto services provider Matrixport believes that Bitcoin could rally as high as $125,000 by the end of 2024.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Matrixport&rsquo;s forecast is based on its data that indicates a multi-month bull market, resulting in a massive rise in the market value of Bitcoin and other leading cryptocurrencies.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to Matrixport, Bitcoin reaching the $31k level indicated the end of the bear market.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">While speaking with CoinDesk, Markus Thielen, head of research and strategy at Matrixport, stated that</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;On June 22, 2023, bitcoin made a new one-year high, marking the first time in a year. This signal has historically indicated the end of bear markets and the start of new crypto bull markets. If history is any guide, bitcoin prices could climb by +123% over twelve months and by +310% over eighteen months &ndash; based on the average return of the signals triggered in 2015, 2019 and 2020. That would lift prices to $65,539 in twelve months and $125,731 over eighteen months.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p dir="ltr">Thielen described the 2012 signal and the subsequent 5,285% price rise in 2013 as an unusual bull market.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitcoin Surged By 50% YTD</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin has surged by more than 50% since the start of the year. It started the year trading just around the $15k level, with the&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>price of Bitcoin</u></a> now at $31,192 per coin.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Matriport&rsquo;s forecast will coincide with the fourth halving. The next halving will see the reduction in the new coins paid per block to 3.25 BTC from 6.5 BTC and will take place in March/April 2024.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-services-provider-matrixport-predicts-bitcoin-to-125k-by-the-end-of-2024/">Crypto services provider Matrixport predicts Bitcoin to $125k by the end of 2024</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-services-provider-matrixport-predicts-bitcoin-to-125k-by-the-end-of-2024/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>CEL falls after Celisus Network and its former CEO found guilty</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/cel-falls-after-celisus-network-and-its-former-ceo-found-guilty/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/cel-falls-after-celisus-network-and-its-former-ceo-found-guilty/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 10:39:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CEL]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Celsius]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/cel-falls-after-celisus-network-and-its-former-ceo-found-guilty/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The United States Commodity and Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) has concluded investigations into Celsius Network. The CFTC has found the former CEO and Celsius Network guilty of breaking several rules before the company collapsed. The price of CLE, the native cryptocurrency of Celsius has lost 10% in value after the revelation. After investigations, the United [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/cel-falls-after-celisus-network-and-its-former-ceo-found-guilty/">CEL falls after Celisus Network and its former CEO found guilty</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>The United States Commodity and Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) has concluded investigations into Celsius Network.</li>
<li>The CFTC has found the former CEO and Celsius Network guilty of breaking several rules before the company collapsed.</li>
<li>The price of CLE, the native cryptocurrency of Celsius has lost 10% in value after the revelation.</li>
</ul>
<p>After investigations, the United States Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) has concluded that cryptocurrency lender Celsius Network and its <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/celsius-ceo-alex-mashinsky-resigns/">former CEO Alex Mashinsky</a> broke US laws before it collapsed.&nbsp;</p>
<p>According to the CFTC report, the findings indicate that Celsius deceived investors and neglected to register with the CFTC. The CFTC may file a lawsuit in federal court within the month if the majority of its commissioners concur with these findings.</p>
<h2>New York Attorney General already sued Celsius</h2>
<p>Letitia James, the attorney general of New York, has already filed a lawsuit following the demise of Celsius Network. James alleged that Mashinsky misrepresented the company&rsquo;s financial situation and made false claims about the platform&rsquo;s security.</p>
<p>James&rsquo; lawsuit charges Mashinsky with defrauding millions of investors, including more than 26,000 residents of New York, in a lawsuit that was filed in January. It states that Mashinsky made &ldquo;false and misleading representations&rdquo; in order to persuade clients to deposit enormous sums of money with the crypto lender.</p>
<h2>What really happened to Celsius?</h2>
<p>Celsius was founded in 2017 and it shot into the limelight during the Covid-19 pandemic when it introduced loan offerings and tempting interest rates for cryptocurrency deposits.</p>
<p>Mashinsky frequently presented these products as less risky options compared to those provided by conventional banks. However, the Celsius market boom did not last long since the demise of Terra&rsquo;s algorithmic stablecoin UST and a slump in the cryptocurrency market had disastrous effects on its business.</p>
<p>Although Celsius initially denied making losses after the Terra Luna collapse, it faced a wave of customer withdrawals. Withdrawals were eventually frozen in June 2022, and a month later, <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/celsius-files-for-chapter-11-bankruptcy-cel-price-on-the-decline/">bankruptcy protection was sought</a>.</p>
<p>The Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and federal prosecutors in Manhattan are, however, also looking into Celsius in accordance with its bankruptcy filings.</p>
<p>In March this year, the court allowed <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/celsius-customers-begin-withdrawing-funds-eight-months-after-bankruptcy-filing/">Celsius withdrawals</a> to resume and in June the crypto lender was <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/court-allows-celsius-to-sell-altcoins-for-btc-eth-starting-july-1/">allowed</a> to convert its altcoin holdings into <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/celsius-files-for-chapter-11-bankruptcy-cel-price-on-the-decline/">Bitcoin (BTC)</a> and <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/what-is-ethereum/">Ethereum (ETH)</a>.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/cel-falls-after-celisus-network-and-its-former-ceo-found-guilty/">CEL falls after Celisus Network and its former CEO found guilty</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/cel-falls-after-celisus-network-and-its-former-ceo-found-guilty/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Veloce Media Group announces major investment commitment of $50 million from GEM Digital Limited</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/veloce-media-group-announces-major-investment-commitment-of-50-million-from-gem-digital-limited/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/veloce-media-group-announces-major-investment-commitment-of-50-million-from-gem-digital-limited/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire &#160;]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 09:12:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=145245</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>London, United Kingdom, July 6th, 2023, Chainwire Veloce Media Group announces major investment commitment of $50 million from GEM Digital Limited&#160;Significant investment to fuel Veloce Media Group&#8217;s growth Gem Digital Ltd a global leading digital asset investment firm Following the announcement of Veloce Media Group&#8217;s evolution to Web3, with the launch of its new blockchain [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/veloce-media-group-announces-major-investment-commitment-of-50-million-from-gem-digital-limited/">Veloce Media Group announces major investment commitment of $50 million from GEM Digital Limited</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>London, United Kingdom, July 6th, 2023, Chainwire</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Veloce Media Group announces major investment commitment of $50 million from GEM Digital Limited&nbsp;Significant investment to fuel Veloce Media Group&rsquo;s growth</li>
<li>Gem Digital Ltd a global leading digital asset investment firm</li>
</ul>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Following the announcement of Veloce Media Group&rsquo;s evolution to Web3, with the launch of its new blockchain utility and governance token, <a href="https://www.velocemediagroup.com/about" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">VEXT</a>, it was today announced that GEM Digital Ltd will invest up to $50 million, through a structured token subscription agreement, into the organisation.</p>
<p><iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/f89kZB5qIBw?showinfo=0"></iframe></p>
<p>Veloce, comprising of industry-leading gaming and racing platform Veloce Esports, and race-winning Extreme E outfit Veloce Racing, has attracted over 35 million subscribers, nearly one billion monthly views, across multiple digital platforms including YouTube and Twitch, and millions of social media followers to become the <a href="https://www.velocemediagroup.com/network" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">world&rsquo;s largest racing gaming media network.</a></p>
<p>The London-based organisation also operates esports and gaming teams and brands for some of the industry&rsquo;s most influential names, including Mercedes AMG, Ferrari, McLaren, Yas Heat, whilst also establishing a successful joint venture sub-brand with Lando Norris &ndash; <a href="https://www.velocemediagroup.com/brands" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Quadrant</a> &ndash; and continually competing and winning with Veloce Elites.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">The introduction of <a href="https://www.velocemediagroup.com/vext" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">VEXT</a> in the coming weeks will position Veloce as a leading decentralised gaming and sports media organisations; providing token holders with real utility through a variety of games integrating VEXT and tangible influence, benefits and rewards across all of the Veloce Media Group assets.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify"><img decoding="async" src="https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1019520927-LAT-20230310-XP2301_084916XE_SAUDI23_CL_16885512239MXS4FBYG3.jpg"></p>
<p>The partnership with GEM Digital has all the signs of being a perfect &lsquo;meeting of minds&rsquo;, as the investment firm moves to increase its stake in this fast-moving world of sourcing, structuring, and investing in utility tokens in relevant and growing industries.</p>
<blockquote><p>&ldquo;This is a very exciting transaction ,&rdquo;&nbsp;said Daniel Bailey, Chief Commercial Officer Veloce and CEO Veloce Racing, &ldquo;It comes very soon after the announcement of VEXT and our plans to evolve our media and sports group into this truly innovative space; validating Veloce&rsquo;s position as a pioneer in the industry.</p></blockquote>
<blockquote><p>&ldquo;The GEM commitment will allow us to focus on growth and expansion, through acquisition of more gaming and real-life racing properties, ultimately giving our vast community further VEXT utility and influence.&rdquo;</p></blockquote>
<p>For GEM Digital, the investment has found a natural home that reflects its ambitions to work with a diverse set of organisations whilst promoting businesses in the emerging markets, supporting sustainable and inclusive ambitions through business. The investment promises to herald mutual long-term opportunities.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" src="https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Garage_Render_F1-min_1688551590uBDaQ64pvp.jpg"></p>
<p class="ql-align-center"><a href="https://www.velocemediagroup.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Website</a>&nbsp;|&nbsp;<a href="https://t.me/vextoken" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Telegram&nbsp;</a>|&nbsp;<a href="https://twitter.com/vextoken" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Twitter</a>&nbsp;|&nbsp;<a href="https://discord.com/invite/yVn3aRXUvv" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Discord</a>&nbsp;|&nbsp;<a href="https://www.instagram.com/vextoken/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Instagram</a>&nbsp;|&nbsp;<a href="https://www.youtube.com/veloce" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">YouTube</a>&nbsp;|&nbsp;<a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/vivaveloce/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Linkedin</a>&nbsp;|&nbsp;<a href="https://www.tiktok.com/@veloceesports" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">TikTok</a></p>
<h3>About Veloce Media Group</h3>
<p>Founded in 2018, Veloce is a multi-pillared gaming and sports media group&#8239;operating across some of the most innovative, fast-growing, and future-focused sectors in the UK.</p>
<p>Headquartered in London, the Veloce brand comprises of the industry-leading gaming and racing platform, Veloce Esports, and race-winning outfit, Veloce Racing, currently competing in the renowned Extreme E championship.</p>
<p>As the world&rsquo;s largest digital racing media network, Veloce has so far attracted over 35 million subscribers and nearly one billion monthly views with a focus on esports, gaming, purpose-driven motorsport, and Web3.</p>
<p>Veloce is partnered with a number of high-profile teams from across the globe, running multiple gaming and esports team operations, including Mercedes AMG, Ferrari, and Yas Heat. Well established JV sub-brands, including Lando Norris&rsquo; gaming and lifestyle brand Quadrant, make up another key aspect of&#8239;Veloce&rsquo;s vast global network.</p>
<p>To learn more, please visit:&nbsp;<a href="https://www.velocemediagroup.com/%C2%A0" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.velocemediagroup.com/&nbsp;</a></p>
<h3>About GEM Digital Limited</h3>
<p>GEM Digital Limited is a digital asset investment firm. Based in The Bahamas, the firm actively sources, structures and invests in utility tokens listed on over 30 CEXs and DEXs globally.</p>
<p>Global Emerging Markets (&ldquo;GEM&rdquo;) is a $3.4 billion, alternative investment group with offices in Paris, New York, and Bahamas. GEM manages a diverse set of investment vehicles focused on emerging markets and has completed over 530 transactions in 72 countries. Each investment vehicle has a different degree of operational control, risk-adjusted return, and liquidity profile. The family of funds and investment vehicles provide GEM and its partners with exposure to: Small-Mid Cap Management Buyouts, Private Investments in Public Equities and select venture investments.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.velocemediagroup.com/sign-up" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><img decoding="async" src="https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/VEXT_SignUP_4x_1688552352gpwr9Zbzh8.jpg"></a></p>
<h3>Contacts</h3>
<p>CEO, Rupert Svendsen-Cook, Veloce Media Group, rupert@veloce.gg<br>
Head Of Digital Marketing, Louis Broomfield, Veloce Media Group, louis@veloce.gg</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/veloce-media-group-announces-major-investment-commitment-of-50-million-from-gem-digital-limited/">Veloce Media Group announces major investment commitment of $50 million from GEM Digital Limited</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/veloce-media-group-announces-major-investment-commitment-of-50-million-from-gem-digital-limited/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>OKX to Launch Signal Trading Platform, Empowering Traders with High-Quality Signals and Seamless Execution</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/okx-to-launch-signal-trading-platform-empowering-traders-with-high-quality-signals-and-seamless-execution/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/okx-to-launch-signal-trading-platform-empowering-traders-with-high-quality-signals-and-seamless-execution/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire &#160;]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 08:21:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=145238</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Dubai, UAE, July 6th, 2023, Chainwire OKX&#8217;s Signal Trading is a trading bot and marketplace that bridges the gap between signal providers and traders Signal Trading will be integrated with TradingView, enabling signal providers and traders to create signals directly on the leading charting platform A pre-launch waitlist is available now for signal providers and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/okx-to-launch-signal-trading-platform-empowering-traders-with-high-quality-signals-and-seamless-execution/">OKX to Launch Signal Trading Platform, Empowering Traders with High-Quality Signals and Seamless Execution</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Dubai, UAE, July 6th, 2023, Chainwire</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>OKX&rsquo;s Signal Trading is a trading bot and marketplace that bridges the gap between signal providers and traders</li>
<li>Signal Trading will be integrated with TradingView, enabling signal providers and traders to create signals directly on the leading charting platform</li>
<li>A pre-launch <a href="https://www.okx.com/landingpage/signal-trading" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">waitlist</a> is available now for signal providers and institutions</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://www.okx.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><u>OKX</u></a>, the world&rsquo;s second-largest crypto exchange by trading volume and a leading Web3 technology company, has announced the upcoming launch of Signal Trading, a marketplace where users can access automated trading strategies based on technical analysis, or &lsquo;signals,&rsquo; which indicate whether to buy or sell crypto.</p>
<p>The marketplace, set to launch in August-September 2023, will allow users to choose from a range of signal providers, including institutions and pro traders. Interested users and signal providers can sign up to the <a href="https://www.okx.com/landingpage/signal-trading" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">waitlist</a> to be the first to receive updates and access.</p>
<p>Signal Trading will be integrated with <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">TradingView</a>, enabling signal providers and traders to create signals directly on the charting platform, as well as specify the desired action, instrument and other parameters associated with that particular trading signal. With Signal Trading, users can access, follow and copy signals without manual execution, saving time and effort.</p>
<p>Advantages for signal providers include:</p>
<ul>
<li>Expansion opportunities by listing signals on OKX&rsquo;s Signal Trading, giving them access to a marketplace of over 50 million traders</li>
<li>Integrated with TradingView, a leading platform for generating signals</li>
<li>In many cases, a significant reduction in latency and costs typically associated with listing signals on third-party platforms</li>
</ul>
<p>Advantages for signal traders include:</p>
<ul>
<li>Avoidance of subscription fees associated with third-party platforms</li>
<li>In many cases, a significant reduction in latency issues that are prevalent on third-party platforms</li>
<li>Trust and reliability of using one of the world&rsquo;s leading crypto exchanges</li>
<li>A wide variety of signal providers to choose from and compare</li>
</ul>
<p>OKX Global Chief Commercial Officer Lennix Lai said: &ldquo;OKX Signal Trading will further improve users&rsquo; trading experience on OKX by providing access to a diverse range of high-quality signals from top providers, reducing manual entry errors and unlocking a world of trading opportunities for traders. With advanced algorithms, real-time market data and a diverse range of signal providers available, Signal Trading will be the ultimate solution for those seeking to elevate their trading game and connect with a global community of traders.&rdquo;</p>
<h3><strong>About OKX</strong></h3>
<p>OKX is the second-largest global crypto exchange by trading volume and a leading Web3 ecosystem. Trusted by more than 50 million global users, OKX is known for being the fastest and most reliable crypto trading app for traders everywhere.</p>
<p>As a top partner of English Premier League champions Manchester City FC, McLaren Formula 1, Olympian Scotty James and F1 driver Daniel Ricciardo, OKX aims to supercharge the fan experience with new engagement opportunities. OKX is also the top partner of the Tribeca Festival as part of an initiative to bring more creators into web3.</p>
<p>Beyond OKX&rsquo;s exchange, the OKX Wallet is the platform&rsquo;s latest offering for people looking to explore the world of NFTs and the metaverse while trading GameFi and DeFi tokens.</p>
<p>OKX is committed to transparency and security and publishes its Proof of Reserves on a monthly basis.</p>
<p>To learn more about OKX, download our app or visit: <a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/Tracker?data=vkUWbL0o0JBxwWO1mi9Q5RYeTcfwfKctC8EsU6CmARry_6kT3HDi2KFTrNH2xhp7HOp5Y3x79UifjEn3MEa1dw==" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><u>okx.com</u></a></p>
<h3><strong>Disclaimer</strong></h3>
<p>This announcement is provided for informational purposes only. It is not intended to provide any investment, tax, or legal advice, nor should it be considered an offer to purchase, sell, hold or offer any services relating to digital assets. Digital assets, including stablecoins, involve a high degree of risk, can fluctuate greatly, and can even become worthless. You should carefully consider whether trading or holding digital assets is suitable for you in light of your financial condition and risk tolerance. OKX does not provide investment or asset recommendations. You are solely responsible for your investment decisions, and OKX is not responsible for any potential losses. Past performance is not indicative of future results. Please consult your legal/tax/investment professional for questions about your specific circumstances.</p>
<h3>Contact</h3>
<p>Press, Media@okx.com</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/okx-to-launch-signal-trading-platform-empowering-traders-with-high-quality-signals-and-seamless-execution/">OKX to Launch Signal Trading Platform, Empowering Traders with High-Quality Signals and Seamless Execution</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/okx-to-launch-signal-trading-platform-empowering-traders-with-high-quality-signals-and-seamless-execution/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase stock could sink all the way back to $60  analyst says</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-stock-could-sink-to-60-analyst-says/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wajeeh Khan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 17:51:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=145221</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Piper Sandler downgraded Coinbase Global Inc on Wednesday. Analyst Patrick Moley cited regulatory uncertainty for dovish view. Coinbase stock has gained close to 60% over the past thirty days. Coinbase Global Inc has been an absolute delight for shareholders over the past thirty days but a sharp downturn is likely moving forward, as per a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-stock-could-sink-to-60-analyst-says/">Coinbase stock could sink all the way back to $60  analyst says</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Piper Sandler downgraded Coinbase Global Inc on Wednesday.</li>
<li>Analyst Patrick Moley cited regulatory uncertainty for dovish view.</li>
<li>Coinbase stock has gained close to 60% over the past thirty days.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/coinbase/">Coinbase Global Inc</a> has been an absolute delight for shareholders over the past thirty days but a sharp downturn is likely moving forward, as per a Piper Sandler analyst.</p>
<h2>Avoid Coinbase stock due to regulatory uncertainty</h2>
<p>On Wednesday, Patrick Moley downgraded the crypto exchange to &ldquo;neutral&rdquo; and lowered his price target as well to $60 that signals a 25% downside from here.</p>
<p>The analyst turned dovish primarily because the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission sued the Nasdaq-listed firm last month for operating as an unregistered exchange (<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-sec-strikes-again-first-binance-now-coinbase/">read more</a>).</p>
<p>In a research note today, he attributed the recent surge in Coinbase stock to prominent asset managers filing for a Spot Bitcoin ETF and the consequent benefit to crypto prices but said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Rising crypto prices have not translated to increased trading volumes for COIN in recent quarters and the timing of a Spot Bitcoin ETF approval is anyone&rsquo;s guess.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Coinbase Global will report a weak second quarter</h2>
<p>Moley expects the crypto company to report monthly transacting users and trading volumes at a two-year low in its second financial quarter.</p>
<p>The Piper Sandler analyst agreed that Coinbase Global will eventually emerge as a major player within the crypto space but said:</p>
<blockquote><p>We&rsquo;d like to see more progress on regulatory front and a convincing turnaround in underlying fundamentals of the business before becoming more positive on Coinbase stock.</p></blockquote>
<p>Despite the regulatory crackdown, though, Coinbase increased its <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/coinbases-market-share-is-on-the-rise-in-spite-of-sec-actions/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">market share</a> last month to a new high since January 2023, as per data from Kaiko &ndash; a digital assets data provider.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-stock-could-sink-to-60-analyst-says/">Coinbase stock could sink all the way back to $60  analyst says</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Initial Coin Offerings (ICO) in 2023. What Are the Best Crypto ICOs To Buy Now?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/initial-coin-offerings-ico-in-2023-what-are-the-best-crypto-icos-to-buy-now/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice Davies]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 17:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/initial-coin-offerings-ico-in-2023-what-are-the-best-crypto-icos-to-buy-now/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As the cryptocurrency market evolves and matures, many investors seek the next big Initial Coin Offering (ICO) that could offer significant returns. But with so many popping up all the time, which are the best crypto ICOs worth investing in? In this article, you&#8217;ll find 14 hand-picked ICOs with promise. From AI-based projects to layer-1 [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/initial-coin-offerings-ico-in-2023-what-are-the-best-crypto-icos-to-buy-now/">Initial Coin Offerings (ICO) in 2023. What Are the Best Crypto ICOs To Buy Now?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">As the cryptocurrency market evolves and matures, many investors seek the next big Initial Coin Offering (ICO) that could offer significant returns. But with so many popping up all the time, which are the best crypto ICOs worth investing in? In this article, you&rsquo;ll find 14 hand-picked ICOs with promise. From AI-based projects to layer-1 solutions, you will find something that catches your eye.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Coin List</h2>
<ol>
<li dir="ltr">Chancer (CHANCER)</li>
<li dir="ltr">Shiba Memu (SHIBA MEMU)</li>
<li dir="ltr">AltSignals (ASI)</li>
<li dir="ltr">Metacade (MCADE)</li>
<li dir="ltr">ALINK AI (ALINK)</li>
<li dir="ltr">Vivi (VIVI)</li>
<li dir="ltr">OptionBlitz (BLX)</li>
<li dir="ltr">ASTL (ASTL)</li>
<li dir="ltr">Kryptview (KVT)</li>
<li dir="ltr">Minima (WMINIMA)</li>
<li dir="ltr">Brickken (BKN)</li>
<li dir="ltr">EasyFeedback (EASYF)</li>
<li dir="ltr">WeSendIt (WSI)</li>
<li dir="ltr">Mintera (MNTE)</li>
</ol>
<h2 dir="ltr"></h2>
<h2 dir="ltr">1. Chancer (CHANCER) &mdash; Revolutionizing the betting industry</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">What is Chancer?</h3>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Chancer</a> is the world&rsquo;s first blockchain-based decentralized predictive markets app. Chancer aims to revolutionize the betting and gambling industry by removing the need for a bookmaker or house entirely. Chancer is a betting facilitator that allows people to make peer-to-peer (P2P) so the odds are equal and never stacked against users. Any type of bet can be made, from a small bet among friends, to viral bets on huge events such as the Superbowl or the Oscars. Unlike traditional bookies, bets aren&rsquo;t limited to just sports.</p>
<p dir="ltr">All bets and pay-outs are made in Chancer&rsquo;s native token, CHANCER. Additionally, users can earn CHANCER simply by using the platform and placing bets, presenting users with a great opportunity to earn a passive income. The rewards don&rsquo;t stop there; users can get discounts on bets, making it cost-efficient for frequent bettors.</p>
<p dir="ltr">CHANCER has great utility as a token as it fuels Chancer&rsquo;s entire platform. Given that the size of the betting and gambling industry was worth an eye-watering $64 billion last year, there&rsquo;s a real chance that Chancer will disrupt the market and take a sizeable chunk of it through its democratized, decentralized platform that puts bettors first. This makes Chancer a great investment with lots of potential for both betting and crypto enthusiasts.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>&gt;&gt;&gt; You can find more information, including how to buy Chancer </strong><a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong>here</strong></a><strong> &lt;&lt;&lt;</strong></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">2. Shiba Memu (SHIBA MEMU) &mdash; A meme coin with real utility</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">What is Shiba Memu?</h3>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Shiba Memu</a> is a brand new meme coin based on the adorable Japanese Shiba Inu dog. However, this deceptively cute coin has a marketing powerhouse behind it and aims to do the work of 100+ marketing agencies in real time. It&rsquo;s leveraging the power of both blockchain and AI technology to transform marketing, taking time-consuming tasks from marketers so they can focus their efforts elsewhere.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu learns from successful marketing strategies, writes its own PR and promotes itself across relevant forums and social networks. It will be able to generate content based on the data that its AI continually analyzes, publishing this on several online platforms. It will then monitor and analyze the success of its marketing efforts and adjust them accordingly, constantly learning and improving content in order to optimize results.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu will undoubtedly benefit from being a cute, funny meme. However, unlike other meme coins in the market which rely on initial hype and then drastically lose value because they have no long-term use, SHIBA MEMU has innate utility as it fuels the entire Shiba Memu platform. Meme fans and crypto enthusiasts looking to invest in a meme coin and see long-term returns should consider Shiba Memu.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>&gt;&gt;&gt; You can find more information, including how to buy Shiba Memu </strong><a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong>here</strong></a><strong> &lt;&lt;&lt;</strong></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">3. AltSignals (ASI) &ndash; Harnessing AI to Transform the Trading Industry</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">What is AltSignals?</h3>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://token.altsignals.io/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>AltSignals</u></a> is a trading signals provider that has established itself as an industry leader. Launched in 2017, AltSignals has issued over 1,500 calls in the forex, crypto, and stock market to over 1,400 VIP subscribers, with an average accuracy of 64%. It consistently produces outstanding returns each month; its Binance Futures signals for February netted a 2,163% return with a 90% win rate, while January generated 2,480% with 92% accuracy!</p>
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals&rsquo; impeccable Trustpilot scores back up these results. It&rsquo;s garnered almost 500 positive reviews, boasting an average star rating of 4.9/5. It&rsquo;s all been made possible by AltSignals&rsquo; team of advanced trading professionals and the cutting-edge <a href="https://www.altsignals.io/indicator" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>AltAlgo&trade;</u></a> Indicator. AltAlgo&trade; combines over 34 filters and strategies to help the AltSignals team determine the best trading opportunities.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Now, AltSignals is ready for the next step in its journey. It&rsquo;s launching the ASI token to fund the development of the ActualizeAI algorithm. It aims to leverage a full AI stack to bring the platform&rsquo;s accuracy rate above 80% while offering some incredible benefits to investors. This AI stack will use the latest developments in AI technology, like machine learning and natural language processing, to upgrade the existing <a href="https://www.altsignals.io/indicator" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>AltAlgo&trade;</u></a> algorithm.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">By owning ASI, prospective investors will be granted exclusive access to the ActualizeAI algorithm&rsquo;s signals, giving them an edge over others in the financial markets. Those purchasing 20,000 ASI tokens or more will be offered lifetime membership to the signals while gaining free access to the existing AltAlgo&trade; signals service.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">ASI will also offer investors eligibility to join the AI Members Club. This club will allow members to help shape the future of AltSignals and the ActualizeAI algorithm. As members, they can offer feedback, ideas, and contribute to the platform&rsquo;s development, earning additional ASI tokens as rewards. These tokens can be accumulated to upgrade their membership level, which can unlock even more features of the AltSignals AI ecosystem or be held for potential future gains.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Finally, ASI acts as a governance token, allowing holders to propose changes and decide on future updates made to the platform. This direct community engagement helps to ensure that the platform&rsquo;s goals and values align with the traders using its service. After raising $120k just 2 days after launch, it&rsquo;s safe to say that AltSignals is a crypto project ready for big things. You definitely won&rsquo;t want to miss out on the ASI token presale!</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>&gt;&gt;&gt; You can find more information, including how to buy AltSignals </strong><a href="https://token.altsignals.io/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong>here</strong></a><strong> &lt;&lt;&lt;</strong></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">4. Metacade (MCADE) &ndash; Playing a Vital Role in the Play-To-Earn Movement</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">What is Metacade?</h3>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=23" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade</u></a> is a play-to-earn (P2E) community hub aiming to shake up the GameFi landscape with its initial coin offering. It&rsquo;s an all-in-one solution where gamers, crypto enthusiasts, and developers can team up and explore the rapidly-expanding world of P2E gaming. While it&rsquo;ll have everything you&rsquo;d expect from a gaming hub, like sub-communities, spaces for real-time interaction, and game leaderboards, it&rsquo;s harnessing the power of blockchain technology to take things to the next level.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">For instance, to encourage the top minds in P2E to flock to the platform, it rewards anyone sharing reviews, tips, and other helpful content with MCADE tokens. Advanced players can earn by helping others find their GameFi edge. Meanwhile, players new to the P2E space can open up another source of income by sharing their thoughts on a new title they&rsquo;ve been playing.</p>
<p dir="ltr">There are also plans for regular tournaments, prize draws, and competitions where gamers can test their luck alongside other community members. Metacade intends to introduce a job and gig board in 2024, where users will discover roles ranging from casual game testing gigs to full-time salaried positions with Web3 and gaming leaders.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Most excitingly, Metacade is introducing the Metagrant scheme. Metagrants are expected to play a pivotal role in shaping the future of the P2E industry. They allow the community to vote and direct funds to the very best P2E titles in development.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Developers will submit their ideas to a pool of competing proposals, and MCADE holders will vote on their favorite. The one that wins is awarded financing from the Metacade treasury, with the final game being added to the platform&rsquo;s virtual arcade for anyone to log on and play. Not only does this foster a unique sense of community engagement, but it also has the potential to make Metacade a household name with P2E gamers.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>&gt;&gt;&gt; You can find more information, including how to buy Metacade </strong><a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=23" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong>here</strong></a><strong> &lt;&lt;&lt;</strong></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">5. ALINK AI (ALINK) &ndash; A Marketplace Ready for the Future of AI</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">What is ALINK AI?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">Following the recent rise of AI applications like ChatGPT, new AI-based crypto projects, and token sales have recently cropped up. One of the premier AI ICO campaigns is <a href="https://alink.ai/"><u>ALINK AI</u></a>, an all-in-one marketplace for AI services. It effectively allows anyone with an internet connection to request and offer services related to artificial general intelligence (AGI) in a blockchain-based marketplace.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">These services range from simple speech or image generation to complex predictive model building and industry-specific solutions. Developers can even launch and monetize self-governing AI software that interacts with other aspects of the ALINK network.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">ALINK also has a data marketplace built-in, where data can be bought, sold, and traded. Data providers can monetize their information by selling it to marketers, data analysts, research companies, etc. As the need for data to feed to AI solutions grows, ALINK will be ready to act as the intermediary between those with the data and those who need it to train their AI models.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The platform uses its native digital token, ALINK, as a medium of exchange in its marketplaces to raise money and incentivize its users to provide and improve ALINK&rsquo;s services. While AI tokens have yet to break into the mainstream crypto space, ALINK seems like a promising new cryptocurrency ready to pave the way. As such, it&rsquo;s one of the best crypto ICOs to invest in right now.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">6. Vivi (VIVI) &ndash; Decentralized Short-Form Video Sharing That Pays</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">What is Vivi?</h3>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://vivi-tech.io/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Vivi</u></a> is a decentralized platform that allows creators to share short videos and earn rewards while offering viewers a way to monetize their time spent on social media. Using its decentralized structure, Vivi ensures its users&rsquo; privacy and security while promoting a fair distribution of rewards.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Vivi is akin to a decentralized TikTok. Users can post short videos, like makeup or cooking tutorials, making it perfect for TikTok creators looking to move away from centralized social media platforms while maintaining their style.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">One of the unique features of Vivi is the use of non-fungible token (NFT) glasses. Users get a free NFT glasses when signing up and can use them to earn VRV rewards. Users who continue to watch videos and interact on the platform gain VRV, which can be swapped for the platform&rsquo;s governance token, VIVI. VIVI enables users to upgrade their glasses to earn even more VRV for their watch time.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Besides the main Vivi app, there&rsquo;s also Vivi Live, Vive Spot, and Vivi Academy, which each serve a specific purpose in the live streaming, sports, and educational niches. With the potential to become Web3&rsquo;s go-to decentralized short video platform in the crypto industry, Vivi is certainly a token sale worth considering.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">7. OptionBlitz (BLX) &ndash; A Unique Decentralized Derivatives Trading Platform</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">What is OptionBlitz?</h3>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://www.optionblitz.co/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>OptionBlitz</u></a> is a decentralized trading platform built on the Ethereum layer-2 scaling solution Arbitrum. It specializes in derivatives trading, particularly options trading. It uses Arbitrum to achieve fast transaction settlement times at virtually no cost to traders while maintaining complete decentralization. In its <a href="https://www.optionblitz.co/static/media/optionblitz_whitepaper.ce295a0d387dd3ce94b9.pdf" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>whitepaper</u></a>, OptionBlitz also promises zero slippage and zero spreads.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Like other decentralized trading platforms, OptionBlitz allows users to lock up their USDC in a liquidity pool to facilitate transactions for other traders in return for a share of the platform&rsquo;s revenue. OptionBlitz offers traders three distinct products: digital options, classic options, and Turbos, its flagship 200:1 leveraged offering that could be the next step in perpetual futures trading.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The markets it offers aren&rsquo;t just limited to crypto. Traders can access forex, commodity, and energy markets products, with pricing determined using the Chainlink decentralized oracle for maximum accuracy. Its options are incredibly flexible, with expiration times ranging from 10 seconds to 24 hours.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Overall, OptionBlitz is setting itself apart from other ICOs with a tremendously innovative offering. Its potential to become the most advanced decentralized derivatives platform can&rsquo;t be understated, so it&rsquo;s one of the best crypto presales to buy right now.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">8. ASTL (ASTL) &ndash; Raise Money and Generate Passive Income With ASTL</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">What is ASTL?</h3>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://astl.io/"><u>ASTL</u></a> is a passive income cryptocurrency project that aims to combine AI technology and crypto mining with helping its users generate returns well above what a bank will offer. ASTL uses a fleet of crypto miners, powered by green energy and optimized using AI, to mine the best tokens that maximize user profits.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Investors simply purchase their chosen number of ASTL tokens and then receive a reward in USDT proportional to their purchase. These returns can be as high as 11% APY, thanks to ASTL&rsquo;s mining diversification, and can be paid out daily if users purchase enough tokens.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Effectively, when investors buy ASTL, they buy a portion of the computing power in the project&rsquo;s mining fleet. Unlike regular cloud mining services, the return from ASTL doesn&rsquo;t change depending on the current happenings in the crypto market; the primary difference is that it promises a stable return that won&rsquo;t fluctuate. With its token offering currently underway, ASTL is one to consider if you want to invest in a passive income-focused ICO.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">9. Kryptview (KVT) &ndash; Pioneering Research-To-Earn With a User-Friendly Platform</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">What is Kryptview?</h3>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://kryptview.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Kryptview</u></a> is a blockchain-based platform that offers a unique approach to community research and insight-sharing on tokens and other cryptocurrencies. It employs a peer-to-peer model that rewards users for generating in-depth fundamental analysis of the latest cryptocurrencies. The data collected is automatically structured, then reviewed by the community, and posted to the platform for all users to take advantage of.</p>
<p dir="ltr">It has built-in fundamental analysis tools that allow users to assign scores to various areas, like a cryptocurrency project&rsquo;s team, competition, sustainability, and community. The reviews generated by Kryptview users are then used to build an overall score for a given token, which provides an at-a-glance view of which cryptocurrency projects are worth picking up.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The reward model of Kryptview is simple but effective. Analysts are ranked based on the quality of their contributions, which allows them to earn more for sharing analysis as they rank up. Meanwhile, reviewers can earn KVT tokens for reviewing research and validating scores. Contributors can post portfolios and generate KVT if their picks outperform the market. As a result, its upcoming ICO is hotly anticipated by many prospective investors.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">10. Minima (WMINIMA) &ndash; A Mobile-Based Blockchain Focused on Freedom</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">What is Minima?</h3>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://www.minima.global/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Minima</u></a> is one of the latest ICO projects to venture into the layer-1 crypto space. Its goal is to become the world&rsquo;s first fully decentralized network powered by mobile and Internet of Things (IoT) devices. Minima is designed to be accessible by as many participants as possible, meaning anyone with a mobile phone and an internet connection can run a Minima node.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Minima states its core purpose is to build a network that offers freedom to all who use it, where users can come together and create without restrictions or censorship. Like other leading layer-1 networks, it allows anyone to launch custom tokens, NFT projects, and decentralized applications (dApps). Minima also claims to have pending partnerships with companies in the automobile, telecommunications, and file-sharing industries.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">While there are fees during periods of high demand on the network, these fees aren&rsquo;t burnt, meaning the tokens are removed from the hard-capped total token supply. This, in turn, makes MNIMA a deflationary token. Minima&rsquo;s presale is for Wrapped Minima, a version of MINIMA that can interface with the Ethereum network.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">11. Brickken (BKN) &ndash; Taking on Traditional Company Fundraising</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">What is Brickken?</h3>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://www.brickken.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Brickken</u></a> is a blockchain-based platform that allows enterprises to tokenize their businesses and raise funds using security tokens. Its vision is to help global asset owners use a decentralized funding model, opening up income streams for companies and investors. Instead of going through an Initial Public Offering (IPO) and issuing stock, companies can undertake Security Token Offerings (STOs) to raise capital without intermediaries.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Asset tokenization has been a hot topic amongst crypto investors in recent years. Brickken aims to provide the tools and technology to allow anyone to put their assets on the blockchain, bridging the gap between Web2 and Web3. This is especially important for small-and-medium enterprises (SMEs), which can often only raise funds from venture capitalists. Brickken opens up a world of opportunity for these SMEs, allowing them to tap the vast retail investor market.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Brickken uses a proprietary dApp powered by smart contracts to issue and manage token securities while ensuring that every investor and securities issuer meets the regulatory requirements through stringent KYC and anti-money laundering checks. BKN, the project&rsquo;s native digital token, is fuel for Brikken&rsquo;s ecosystem, being used to invest in ongoing projects and issue STOs.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">12. EasyFeedback (EASYF) &ndash; Rewarding Users for Their Feedback</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">What is EasyFeedback?</h3>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://easyfeedbacktoken.io/en/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>EasyFeedback</u></a> is a company using blockchain technology to create the world&rsquo;s first feedback-to-earn protocol. Established in 2015, EasyFeedback allows anyone to send suggestions, congratulations, questions, complaints, and claims to any business worldwide &ndash; for free! It offers a suite of templates that can be adapted to the individual company, with feedback sent directly to company heads.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">With the EASYF token, users sending feedback to companies or institutions can be rewarded based on the feedback&rsquo;s usefulness. These EASYF tokens can be exchanged for products, services, and gift cards in the EasyFeedback marketplace or held in crypto wallets for future gains.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Those with relevant expertise can also become jurors, who evaluate the feedback and decide whether it&rsquo;s worth a reward. These jurors must undergo strict background checks to determine their knowledge and experience in their specialist sector and can earn EASYF tokens for validating feedback. EasyFeedback predicts that the use of its service will increase by 600% following the tokenization of its service, which could bode well for early investors.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">13. WeSendIt (WSI) &ndash; Established File Sharing Platform Venturing Into Web3</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">What is WeSendIt?</h3>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://wesendit.io/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>WeSendIt</u></a> is a file-sharing platform that, like AltSignals, has a reputation that precedes its entry into the crypto space. It&rsquo;s a Swiss company that emphasizes data protection and security while making large file transfers and storage simple. Now, WeSendIt is making its foray into Web3 with a custom-built decentralized solution.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">WeSendIt claims that, through decentralization, it can ensure its clients&rsquo; files stay 100% confidential while costing up to 80% less than regular cloud storage providers. Moreover, it says that data is stored redundantly across thousands of availability zones across the globe, meaning that the risk of losing data due to server failure is virtually eliminated.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Using the WSI digital coin means that users can achieve discounts on its Pro and Premium offers up to 60% cheaper than when paying via credit card or Paypal. Users can also earn WSI rewards for sending data. Finally, there&rsquo;s even a generous referral scheme that pays users in WSI to recruit more users into the ecosystem!</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">14. Mintera (MNTE) &ndash; A Green Project That Generates Passive Income</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">What is Mintera?</h3>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://mintera.co/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Mintera</u></a> is a climate-friendly cryptocurrency project that uses blockchain technology to impact the environment positively. While it believes that the development of blockchain-based projects has a beneficial effect on society, Mintera sees a problem with the waste in the crypto space. As a result, it&rsquo;s building an ecosystem of sustainable products, billing itself as &ldquo;the green digital investment bank of the future.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">At the heart of the Mintera ecosystem is the MNTE token, which offers potential investors access to a net-positive range of green investment products, revenue streams, and perks. One of the most exciting aspects of Mintera is the Green Mining Yield (GMY), which promises to return a stablecoin yield to investors through its long-running green mining operation. Mintera mines <a href="https://www.chia.net/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Chia</u></a>, which it terms an eco-friendly alternative to Bitcoin.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Yields depend on Chia&rsquo;s price, but Mintera claims to offer rates of anywhere between 5% and 100% per year. It also dedicates 50% of its profits to environmental organizations and stashes 6.5 million MNTE to fund green innovation. Overall, Mintera is an excellent choice for any ICO investor investing in a climate-positive project.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Buying Into an ICO</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">What To Look For in an ICO</h3>
<p dir="ltr">So how do you determine which ICOs are worth investing in? Here&rsquo;s a comprehensive list of what to consider when identifying successful ICOs.&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr"><strong>Legal Elements:</strong> Investors should ensure that the ICO complies with relevant regulations in its jurisdictions. Any potential legal risks should also be considered. Some tokens may be regarded as securities by the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), which could lead to scrutiny and legal action in the future.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr"><strong>Tokenomics:</strong> Evaluating the token economics in an initial coin offering is essential, including the token&rsquo;s supply, distribution, and use case. Pay special attention to how much of the token supply is allocated to the development team: too much or insufficient can be red flags. Around 5-15% is typical.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr"><strong>White Paper:</strong> Reviewing the white paper is crucial in understanding the project&rsquo;s goals, technology, and roadmap. Assess whether the project has a clear and achievable roadmap with realistic timelines before investing in an initial coin offering.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr"><strong>Partnerships and Terms:</strong> It&rsquo;s a good idea to evaluate any partnerships or collaborations the ICO company has secured and the terms of those agreements. These partnerships can bring value to the project and help it grow.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr"><strong>Team and Advisors:</strong> Assessing the team behind cryptocurrency projects is essential, including their experience and credentials in their specialized industry. Investors should also consider any notable advisors that can bring value to the project.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr"><strong>Community and Engagement:</strong> Evaluating the project&rsquo;s community, including its engagement and support, is essential. A strong community can make all the difference in whether an ICO is successful or not.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h3 dir="ltr">How Do I Know When New Coins Are Launched?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">Staying on top of the latest token sales in the fast-moving world of cryptocurrency and blockchain startups can be challenging. Fortunately, several resources are available that can help investors stay informed. One of the best places to start is on social media platforms such as Twitter and Reddit, where cryptocurrency enthusiasts and industry leaders often post news about new tokens.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Some coins are also launched exclusively on centralized exchanges through Initial Exchange Offerings (IEOs) or on decentralized exchanges with Initial Dex Offerings (IDOs). Lastly, there are many lists of active and upcoming ICOs out there. Search &ldquo;ICO list&rdquo; to find websites showcasing the latest token sales.&nbsp;</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Advantages of Initial Coin Offerings (ICOs)</h3>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Quick Funding: ICOs provide blockchain startups with a relatively fast and cost-effective way to raise funds. Unlike traditional fundraising methods, like IPOs, ICOs allow private companies to reach a global audience of investors without the need for financial institutions. Blockchain startups can raise funds faster and with fewer restrictions, allowing them to focus on developing their products and growing their businesses.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Potentially High Returns: Since ICOs often involve investing in new and innovative technologies, investors can benefit from being early adopters of new products and services. This can lead to significant price appreciation in the new tokens they hold, translating to high returns on their initial investment.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Community: ICOs typically look to build up a community around their new coins, which can help create a loyal following and promote adopting their new technology. For investors, this can provide an opportunity to connect with like-minded crypto enthusiasts and join a growing community of supporters.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h3 dir="ltr">Disadvantages of Initial Coin Offerings (ICOs)</h3>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Lack of Regulation: ICOs are still a relatively new fundraising method, so they&rsquo;re largely unregulated. This can make it difficult for investors to assess the legitimacy of a project and opens up a realm of possibility for projects to misuse funds received or even commit outright fraud, often with little repercussion.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Volatility: ICOs are highly speculative investments. Their potential for returns is usually higher than more established projects, which also comes with increased risk. Like many startups, even the best ICOs may face significant challenges in achieving their goals, and the value of their tokens can fluctuate rapidly due to market conditions or unexpected developments.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Technical Risks: ICOs usually involve investing in new and untested technologies, which can present significant technical risks. These risks can include vulnerabilities to hacking or other security breaches and potential flaws or weaknesses in the underlying technology. This can lead to the loss of investor funds and damage the project&rsquo;s future prospects.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr">Related Crypto FAQs</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">What are cryptocurrencies?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">Cryptocurrencies are digital assets that are usually highly decentralized and operate independently of governments and financial institutions. The most valuable cryptocurrency is Bitcoin, which is generally seen as a store of value. The second largest cryptocurrency is Ethereum, which offers smart contracts that can perform incredibly versatile functions.&nbsp;</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">What does ICO mean?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">ICO stands for Initial Coin Offering. It&rsquo;s a fundraising method blockchain startups use to raise capital by issuing digital currency, such as new tokens or coins, to investors in exchange for cryptocurrencies or fiat currency.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Are ICOs illegal?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">ICOs are not inherently illegal, but most would face scrutiny under securities laws in many jurisdictions, including by regulators at the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) in the US. This means ICOs must comply with relevant regulations to avoid legal issues with regulators.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Are ICO coins a good investment?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">The potential return on investment for an ICO coin can be high, but it also comes with increased risk due to the lack of regulation and the potential for volatility. Picking the right ICO can be tricky, and an ICO coin&rsquo;s performance ultimately depends on many factors.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Where can I buy an initial coin offering crypto?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">ICOs are usually bought directly from the startup itself or on ICO aggregator websites like Pinksale. Some ICOs take place on exchanges, where they&rsquo;re termed IEOs or IDOs.&nbsp;</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">What are the next big upcoming initial coin offerings in 2023?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">It&rsquo;s difficult to predict the next big ICO for 2023, as the market can be highly unpredictable. However, many of the tokens on this list have a strong chance of performing well, especially Chancer and Shiba Memu.&nbsp;</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">What is the main difference between an ICO and an IPO?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">The main difference between an ICO and an IPO is that an IPO is a traditional fundraising method established companies use to raise capital by issuing stocks to the public. In contrast, an ICO is used by startups to generate capital by issuing new tokens.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">What happens to an ICO&rsquo;s funds?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">Money raised by an ICO is typically used to fund the development and growth of specific features within the project, including hiring developers and marketing the project. The particular use of funds will likely be outlined in the ICO project&rsquo;s white paper.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/initial-coin-offerings-ico-in-2023-what-are-the-best-crypto-icos-to-buy-now/">Initial Coin Offerings (ICO) in 2023. What Are the Best Crypto ICOs To Buy Now?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
