<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 10:07:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>BP Stock Tanked Over 5% Despite Company Beating Q1 2023 Profit Expectations</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bp-stock-q1-2023-profit/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bp-stock-q1-2023-profit/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 10:07:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wall Street]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bernard looney]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bp stock]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=252930</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bp-stock-q1-2023-profit/">BP Stock Tanked Over 5% Despite Company Beating Q1 2023 Profit Expectations</a></p>
<p>Amid lower fossil fuel costs, BP's profits tanked in comparison to the bumper profits recorded in 2022. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bp-stock-q1-2023-profit/">BP Stock Tanked Over 5% Despite Company Beating Q1 2023 Profit Expectations</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bp-stock-q1-2023-profit/">BP Stock Tanked Over 5% Despite Company Beating Q1 2023 Profit Expectations</a></p>
<p>On Tuesday, May 2, oil major <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/bp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">British Petroleum</a> (BP) reported stronger-than-expected first-quarter (<a href="https://www.bp.com/en/global/corporate/investors/results-and-presentations/quarterly-results-and-webcast.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Q1 2023</a>) profits, and rising from the previous quarter i.e. Q4 2022. However, the numbers were down from the exceptional profits that the company recorded during a blockbuster 2022 when fossil fuel prices shot up significantly following Russia&#8217;s invasion of Ukraine.</p>
<h2>BP Q1 2023 Performance</h2>
<p>During the first quarter, the British energy giant reported an underlying replacement cost profit of $4.96 billion. This was higher than the $4.8 billion net profit in Q4 2022 but lower than the $6.2 billion profit recorded in Q1 2022. Analysts expected British Petroleum to report $4.3 billion in profit during the first quarter this year.</p>
<p>The first quarter results from British Petroleum reflect robust oil and gas trading. Speaking on the development, BP CEO Bernard Looney <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/02/bp-earnings-q1-2023.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“This has been a quarter of strong performance and strategic delivery as we continue to focus on safe and reliable operations. And importantly we continue to deliver for shareholders, through disciplined investment, lowering net debt and growing distributions.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>BP Stock Price and Share BuyBack</h2>
<p>During the earning morning trade on the London stock exchange, shares of BP tanked by more than 5% while slipping to the bottom of the pan-European Stoxx 600 index. The energy giant said that it expects to deliver a share buyback of $4 billion a year. This is still at the lower end of the company&#8217;s $14 billion to $18 billion capital expenditure range.</p>
<p>For the year 2022, BP reported annual profits of $27.7 billion, more than double recorded in the previous year. The last time, the oil major recorded this massive profit was in 2008. Despite a barrage of criticism, big oil giants have sought to defend their profits highlighting the importance of energy security as the world transitions away from fossil fuel. BP is among the first energy giants to announce reaching an ambition of net-zero emissions by 2050.</p>
<p>However, shareholders have shared disappointment with some of the UK&#8217;s biggest pension funds expressing deep frustration. Some 17% of the shareholders have voted in favor of a resolution put forward by Dutch Group Follow This. This resolution calls for BP to align its 2030 emission reduction targets with the landmark Paris Agreement.</p>
<p>In addition to BP, French oil major TotalEnergies also kicked off its earnings season for the first quarter in line with analyst expectations. Amid lower fossil fuel prices, the company reported a 27% drop in net income to $6.5 billion.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sothebys-art-selling-nft-marketplace/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bp-stock-q1-2023-profit/">BP Stock Tanked Over 5% Despite Company Beating Q1 2023 Profit Expectations</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bp-stock-q1-2023-profit/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sotheby’s Launches Secondary Art-selling NFT Marketplace for Collectors &amp; Artists</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sothebys-art-selling-nft-marketplace/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sothebys-art-selling-nft-marketplace/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 10:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sotheby's]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web3]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=252924</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sothebys-art-selling-nft-marketplace/">Sotheby’s Launches Secondary Art-selling NFT Marketplace for Collectors &#038; Artists</a></p>
<p>The new secondary art NFT marketplace by Sotheby’s also pays royalties from sales directly to the artists, from payments made by collectors.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sothebys-art-selling-nft-marketplace/">Sotheby’s Launches Secondary Art-selling NFT Marketplace for Collectors &#038; Artists</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sothebys-art-selling-nft-marketplace/">Sotheby’s Launches Secondary Art-selling NFT Marketplace for Collectors &#038; Artists</a></p>
<p>Sotheby’s has <a href="https://twitter.com/Sothebysverse/status/1653049950786265094" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">launched</a> an on-chain non-fungible token (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NFT</a>) marketplace that facilitates the sale of secondary digital art items. According to <a href="https://decrypt.co/138514/sothebys-launches-on-chain-nft-marketplace-for-secondary-art-sales" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Decrypt</a>, the New York-based auction house now supports secondary NFT sales, allowing artists to transact directly with collectors. For example, interested collectors can list and make offers on work from select artists.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="474" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">The next evolution of <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/SothebysMetaverse?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank">#SothebysMetaverse</a> is here! The most trusted and dynamic destination to collect, buy and sell remarkable digital works. </p>
<p>Explore: <a href="https://t.co/hZvYIkO3xx" target="_blank">https://t.co/hZvYIkO3xx</a> <a href="https://t.co/dCkaCKlXVm" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/dCkaCKlXVm</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Sotheby&#39;s Metaverse (@Sothebysverse) <a href="https://twitter.com/Sothebysverse/status/1653049950786265094?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank">May 1, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Sotheby’s Vice President and Head of NFTs and Digital Art, Michael Bouhanna, discussed the secondary NFT marketplace. According to Bouhanna, the offering marks an essential step in Sotheby’s evolution within the decentralized technology and Web3 space.</p>
<h2>More on Sotheby’s Secondary NFT Marketplace</h2>
<p>The Web3-embracing Sotheby’s peer-to-peer and fully on-chain secondary NFT initiative launched Monday on the auction house’s Metaverse platform. This latest addition supports NFT artwork minted on the Ethereum blockchain and scaling protocol Polygon. In a statement, Sotheby’s described both popular all-encompassing blockchains as the “networks of choice for NFT creators and collectors”.</p>
<p>Sotheby’s Metaverse secondary sales are wholly facilitated by automated smart contracts that accept <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ETH</a> and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/matic-network/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">MATIC</a> as payment for art collectibles. Powered by Serotonin-developed NFT tech and commerce suite Mojito, Sotheby’s Metaverse platform initially went live in October 2021. The popular auction house’s marketplace differs from OpenSea’s broad-scale, peer-to-peer NFT platform in terms of offerings. According to Sotheby’s, the value proposition of its NFTs is in the “rotating, curated selection of leading artists” carefully selected by its specialists. Furthermore, the British-founded American venture pointed out that its selection of secondary marketplace artists will change every few months.</p>
<p>Sotheby’s also revealed that its initial wave of artists would see collectors list and make offers on NFTs from 13 creators the company deems as pioneers. These digital art world leaders include Claire Silver, Tyler Hobbs, Sam Spratt, Diana Sinclair, Sofi Crespo, The Sarah Show, and XCOPY.</p>
<h2>Secondary Marketplaces &amp; On-chain Royalty Fees</h2>
<p>The secondary sales NFT marketplace is set up in a way that rewards artists via specified secondary on-chain royalty fees. Sotheby’s explained it will subtract a creator royalty fee from any secondary sales, typically 5% to 10% of the sale price. This fee is automatically paid into the artist’s wallet as broader discussions regarding NFT resale royalties take center stage.</p>
<p>For instance, in late March, generative art NFT platform Art Blocks debuted its NFT marketplace with enforced creator royalties. At the time, Art Blocks said it would not receive any platform fee for secondary trades through its marketplace. Instead, the company looked to honor artists’ own specified creator royalties.</p>
<p>In March, Art Blocks founder and chief executive officer Erick Calderon exposited further, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>“We are here to support the artists and the artists’ practices. How many artists had quit their jobs to be full-time artists because they were just thrilled with the idea of getting to pursue this?&#8230;The creator economy is empowering the creator with control over their own creation.”</p></blockquote>
<p>At the time, Calderon added that the most compelling thing in the secondary marketplace is a creator who provides a meaningful reward.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-chase-acquires-first-republic-bank/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sothebys-art-selling-nft-marketplace/">Sotheby’s Launches Secondary Art-selling NFT Marketplace for Collectors &#038; Artists</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sothebys-art-selling-nft-marketplace/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>JPMorgan Chase Acquires First Republic Bank After Months-Long Crisis</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-chase-acquires-first-republic-bank/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-chase-acquires-first-republic-bank/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 09:49:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Deals News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[first republic bank]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jamie dimon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jpmorgan chase]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=252940</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-chase-acquires-first-republic-bank/">JPMorgan Chase Acquires First Republic Bank After Months-Long Crisis</a></p>
<p>American multinational banking giant JPMorgan Chase has emerged as the lucky buyer of the embattled regional banking firm, First Republic Bank.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-chase-acquires-first-republic-bank/">JPMorgan Chase Acquires First Republic Bank After Months-Long Crisis</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-chase-acquires-first-republic-bank/">JPMorgan Chase Acquires First Republic Bank After Months-Long Crisis</a></p>
<p>As <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/01/first-republic-bank-failure.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reported</a> by CNBC, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/jpmorgan-chase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">JPMorgan Chase &amp; Co</a> (NYSE: JPM) acquired all of the deposits of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/first-republic-bank/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">First Republic Bank</a> (NYSE: FRC) and a substantial number of its shares. The acquisition was made possible after regulators took a hold of the bank on Monday. This notably placed the collapse of First Republic Bank as the worst in the US banking ecosystem since 2008. According to JPMorgan, it considers the acquisition as its own way of helping to maintain the integrity of the US financial ecosystem.</p>
<p>“Our government invited us and others to step up, and we did,” <a href="https://www.jpmorganchase.com/ir/news/2023/jpmc-acquires-substantial-majority-of-assets-and-assumes-certain-liabilities-of-first-republic-bank" target="_blank" rel="noopener">said</a> Chairman and Chief Executive Officer of JPMorgan Chase <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/jamie-dimon/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Jamie Dimon</a>. “Our financial strength, capabilities and business model allowed us to develop a bid to execute the transaction in a way to minimize costs to the Deposit Insurance Fund.”</p>
<p>According to JPMorgan Chase, the deal saw it scoop up $173 billion of loans and approximately $30 billion of securities belonging to First Republic Bank. The combined deposit value of FRC acquired by JPMorgan came in at $92 billion. Notably, this includes the $30 billion that was <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/first-republic-shares-bank-rescue/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">availed</a> to the collapsed bank by large financial institutions in the US. The firm said these deposits will be repaid in full before closing the deal.</p>
<p>“This acquisition modestly benefits our company overall, it is accretive to shareholders, it helps further advance our wealth strategy, and it is complementary to our existing franchise,” Dimon said.</p>
<p>There has been a lot of commentary with respect to the takeover of FRC by JPMorgan. While some have tagged the acquisition as a way in which the government is consolidating the financial system in readiness for a potential Digital Dollar, others believe the whole move reveals the fragility of the US banking system.</p>
<h2>Future of First Republic as a JPMorgan Offshoot</h2>
<p>JPMorgan is one of the biggest banking giants in the United States and for what it is worth, First Republic will benefit from the deep capital base the firm has, as well as its deep client base.</p>
<p>JPMorgan said that it expects the transaction to be “modestly EPS accretive and generate more than $500 million of incremental net income per year, not including the approximately $2.6 billion one-time post-tax gain or approximately $2.0 billion of post-tax restructuring costs expected over the course of 2023 and 2024.”</p>
<p>Despite the collapse of First Republic, it was acknowledged that the bank dealt with its clients with a high level of integrity. This, JPMorgan noted, will be beneficial to sustaining the bank’s business moving forward.</p>
<p>The shares of JPMorgan popped following the acquisition news. At the close of Monday’s trading session, JPM closed at 2.14% to $141.20. First Republic stock is down 45% in the after hours.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-market-q1-2023/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-chase-acquires-first-republic-bank/">JPMorgan Chase Acquires First Republic Bank After Months-Long Crisis</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-chase-acquires-first-republic-bank/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>European Market Shakes Off Recession Fears but Misses Q1 2023 Growth Estimates</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-market-q1-2023/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 13:44:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ecb]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=252849</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-market-q1-2023/">European Market Shakes Off Recession Fears but Misses Q1 2023 Growth Estimates</a></p>
<p>The European market recorded a gross domestic product (GDP) of  0.0 percent in the first quarter of 2023 compared with the fourth quarter of 2022.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-market-q1-2023/">European Market Shakes Off Recession Fears but Misses Q1 2023 Growth Estimates</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-market-q1-2023/">European Market Shakes Off Recession Fears but Misses Q1 2023 Growth Estimates</a></p>
<p>The European economy displayed market resilience during the first quarter despite being cut off from the Russian oil and gas supply since the invasion of Ukraine. The EU market was, however, marred by rising inflation amid bank deposits flight similar to the United States banking crisis. Nonetheless, the European Central Bank has continued to raise interest rates, with the recent update pushing by 50 basis points, to fight the high core inflation.</p>
<p>Notably, some ECB policymakers are working on further raising interest rates next week by about 25 basis points, which could push the core interest rate above 3 percent. The Euro Zone is currently fighting inflation of 6.9 percent and core inflation of about 5.7 percent.</p>
<h2>European Market Economic Outlook</h2>
<p>During the first quarter, the Euro Zone economy grew by 0.1 percent, according to preliminary figures released on Friday. The EU bloc missed analysts’ forecast on first quarter growth, which was expected at 0.2 percent, according to a poll conducted by Reuters. Nonetheless, the European economy expanded by approximately 1.3 percent on an annualized basis but still missed analysts&#8217; expectations of 1.4 percent.</p>
<p>According to a report by <a href="https://www.destatis.de/EN/Press/2023/04/PE23_169_811.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">destatis</a>, the European market recorded a gross domestic product (GDP) of  0.0 percent in the first quarter of 2023 compared with the fourth quarter of 2022. Additionally, data from the Federal Statistical Office (Destatis) showed that the final consumption expenditure of both households and the government declined at the beginning of 2023 in the Eurozone. Reportedly, positive contributions came from capital formation and exports in the European market during the first quarter.</p>
<p>Earlier this month, data from Eurostat showed a revision downward in the fourth-quarter 2022 GDP estimate for the eurozone from 0.1 percent quarterly growth to no growth, following a 0.4 percent growth during the third quarter of last year.</p>
<p>The European market was able to evade a much-feared recession during the first quarter of 2023. According to Carsten Brzeski, global head of macro at Dutch bank ING, the fall in wholesale energy prices, warmer-than-expected weather, and fiscal stimulus helped the European market dodge a widely-feared recession over the winter.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, Brzeski indicated that the data from individual countries will be crucial for the bloc&#8217;s future growth prospects. Moreover, the ongoing race between positive momentum in European countries and wage growth on the other hand has pushed the ECB to further monetary tightening policies.</p>
<p>As a result, the European Union regulators could be looking at diversifying leading economies like Germany, and France amid the looming United States feared recession in the second half of 2023.</p>
<p>Read other <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/markets/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">market news</a> on our website.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/h-c-wainwright-crypto-winter/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-market-q1-2023/">European Market Shakes Off Recession Fears but Misses Q1 2023 Growth Estimates</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Investment Bank H.C. Wainwright Believes Crypto Winter Is Over, Rates Coinbase Stock as ‘Buy’ </title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/h-c-wainwright-crypto-winter/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 13:05:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coin stock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase stock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[h c wainwright]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=252833</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/h-c-wainwright-crypto-winter/">Investment Bank H.C. Wainwright Believes Crypto Winter Is Over, Rates Coinbase Stock as ‘Buy’ </a></p>
<p>Analysts at H.C. Wainwright have said that the crypto winter of 2022 ceases to have any bearing on related stocks. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/h-c-wainwright-crypto-winter/">Investment Bank H.C. Wainwright Believes Crypto Winter Is Over, Rates Coinbase Stock as ‘Buy’ </a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/h-c-wainwright-crypto-winter/">Investment Bank H.C. Wainwright Believes Crypto Winter Is Over, Rates Coinbase Stock as ‘Buy’ </a></p>
<p>H.C. Wainwright believes that the crypto winter is over and has called for a buy on <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase</a> (NASDAQ: COIN) stock. According to the New York-based investment bank, Coinbase stands to benefit from global digital asset economy growth sooner rather than later. H.C. Wainwright released a <a href="https://hcwco.bluematrix.com/sellside/EmailDocViewer?encrypt=2b411f55-2386-4e7f-8f86-4cf9037b824d&amp;mime=pdf&amp;co=Hcwco&amp;id=jayson.derrick@investoogroup.com&amp;source=mail" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">statement</a> on Wednesday that underscored its bullishness on the prices of crypto assets.</p>
<p>The investment banking platform wrote:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Crypto asset prices have rallied 45% YTD, supported by a 67% increase in BTC prices, indicating to us that crypto winter is over and that we have likely now entered BTC’s next bull price cycle (not baked into current estimates), which has historically resulted in significant growth in total crypto market cap, incremental retail, and institutional adoption, and higher crypto trading volumes.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Summing up these key metrics as a driver of Coinbase’s operating results, including transaction revenues, H.C. Wainwright also said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“[As a leading exchange in the US and the world], we believe Coinbase is uniquely positioned to benefit from the large and rapidly growing global crypto economy given its trusted brand, easy-to-use products, and focus on compliance and regulation, and we expect the company to gain market share in 2023.”</p></blockquote>
<p>According to the bank, Coinbase’s revenues would become more “durable” over time due to its increasingly alternate revenue sources. Besides generating income from transaction-based fees, Coinbase has started leaning toward subscription and service revenues.</p>
<h2>H.C. Wainwright Analyst Identifies Coinbase as Only Exchange Valued at Over $10 Billion in Light of Crypto Winter</h2>
<p>H.C. Wainwright analyst Mike Colonnese posted a ‘Buy’ rating for Coinbase, explaining that “rewards outweigh risks at these prices.” Furthermore, the analyst stated that COIN, currently trading at $54.17, is a “scarce asset” unlikely to change over the near term. Colonnese also pointed out that the major crypto exchange is the only US publicly-listed crypto company with a market cap exceeding $10 billion. As a result, the analyst concluded that competition for investor capital remains extremely limited.</p>
<p>Although the Nasdaq-listed COIN closed 3% lower on Wednesday and at 85% lower than its November 2021 peak, Wainwright analysts opine the stock is still an attractive prospect. These analysts say Coinbase’s share price levels offer investors an attractive entry point because the stock trades at a 35% discount to historical highs.</p>
<h2>Coinbase vs SEC</h2>
<p>In other recent Coinbase news, the exchange sued the Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) over crypto regulatory guideline differences. In its lawsuit, the American exchange asked the court to require crypto clarity from the securities regulator. Coinbase called for the SEC to respond to its July 2022 petition promptly. In the previous petition, the exchange suggested that the Commission propose and adopt more explicit regulatory guidelines for the US crypto space via its formal rulemaking process. More than 1,700 individuals and entities have since submitted comments on Coinbase’s petition, also calling for more regulatory clarity from the SEC.</p>
<p>Yesterday, Coinbase <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-sec-wells-notice-securities/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">firmly responded</a> to a Wells Notice from the SEC last month, claiming no violation of securities laws. The exchange’s chief legal officer Paul Grewal accused the regulator of refusing to engage in meaningful dialogue regarding crypto regulations. Furthermore, Coinbase also suggested that the SEC had been intimidating several other exchanges over securities law violations. However, Coinbase expressed its intent to remain unshaken as it has not committed any wrongdoings.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-cloud-polygon-web3/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/h-c-wainwright-crypto-winter/">Investment Bank H.C. Wainwright Believes Crypto Winter Is Over, Rates Coinbase Stock as ‘Buy’ </a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Google Cloud Joins Hands with Polygon Labs to Boost Web3 Adoption</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-cloud-polygon-web3/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 12:56:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cloud Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[google cloud]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[polygon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[polygon labs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=252807</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-cloud-polygon-web3/">Google Cloud Joins Hands with Polygon Labs to Boost Web3 Adoption</a></p>
<p>As part of the partnership, Google will bring the Blockchain Node Engine, which is Google's fully managed node hosting service, to the Polygon ecosystem. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-cloud-polygon-web3/">Google Cloud Joins Hands with Polygon Labs to Boost Web3 Adoption</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-cloud-polygon-web3/">Google Cloud Joins Hands with Polygon Labs to Boost Web3 Adoption</a></p>
<p>In a recent development, Google Cloud announced its partnership with Polygon Labs and will thus make it easier for developers to build, launch, as well as grow their Web3 products and other decentralized applications on the Layer-2 scalability platform of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a>.</p>
<p>This strategic alliance will help in boosting the transaction throughput which will unlock several use cases in the sectors of supply chain, gaming, and decentralized finance (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-decentralized-finance-defi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">DeFi</a>) on the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/matic-network/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Polygon</a> blockchain.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="474" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/googlecloud?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank">@googlecloud</a> ☁️ <a href="https://twitter.com/0xPolygon?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank">@0xPolygon</a></p>
<p>Google Cloud will help accelerate adoption of core Polygon protocols w/ enterprise infrastructure &amp; tools.</p>
<p>🤝🏽 strategic alliance to increase transaction throughput enabling use cases in gaming, supply chain &amp; DeFi <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/onPolygon?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank">#onPolygon</a>🤗<a href="https://t.co/POKztinzKP" target="_blank">https://t.co/POKztinzKP</a> <a href="https://t.co/r5P94YaQDt" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/r5P94YaQDt</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Polygon (Labs) (@0xPolygonLabs) <a href="https://twitter.com/0xPolygonLabs/status/1651624482581217281?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank">April 27, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Also, as part of the partnership, Google will bring the Blockchain Node Engine, which is Google&#8217;s fully managed node hosting service, to the Polygon ecosystem. This will help developers to focus on building the protocol while retaining complete control over the nodes deployed. Also, developers will have no longer to worry about configuring and running their Polygon PoS nodes.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the Google Cloud marketplace is offering developers a simple one-click deployment of the Polygon PoS node for powering their dApps quickly and easily. Commenting on the development, Ryan Wyatt, President, Polygon Labs <a href="https://fortune.com/crypto/2023/04/27/google-cloud-partners-with-polygon-labs-adding-yet-again-to-its-growing-roster-of-web3-firms/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Google Cloud supporting all of the Polygon protocols is a step in the right direction to help onboard more people into Web3. Today&#8217;s announcement with Google Cloud aims to increase transaction throughput enabling use cases in gaming, supply chain management, and DeFi. This will pave the way for even more businesses to embrace blockchain technology through Polygon.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>Google Is Making Its Way Into the Web3 World with Polygon</h2>
<p>Google, which has dominated the Web2 market for a long, is now making to make a move into the rapidly emerging Web3 world. Much recently, Google launched its “Google for Startups Cloud Program” which will support startups and emerging projects in the Web3 space to scale their projects faster and even more securely.</p>
<p>Also, the Celo Foundation announced earlier this month that it would work with Google Cloud to offer workshops and other cloud computing services to developers and other Web3 founders building on Celo. Also, the tech powerhouse noted that its partnership with Polygon would help the protocol to take further its zero-knowledge innovation strategy. This will help in making the transactions even faster and cheaper.</p>
<p>The statement reads:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Initial tests to run Polygon zkEVM’s zero-knowledge proofs on Google Cloud, for instance, resulted in significantly faster and cheaper transactions as compared to the existing setup.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>It&#8217;s just last month that Polygon has released its zero-knowledge Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM) beta to the public.</p>
<p>Mitesh Agarwal, managing director of customer engineering and Web3 go-to-market, Asia Pacific of Google Cloud, said:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Google Cloud is helping the industry achieve escape velocity by directing our engineering efforts toward areas like improving data availability and enhancing the resilience and performance of scaling protocols like zero-knowledge proofs”.</p></blockquote>
<p>Reat other <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/technology/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">tech news</a> on Coinspeaker.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/findora-dapp-triple-masking-sdk/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-cloud-polygon-web3/">Google Cloud Joins Hands with Polygon Labs to Boost Web3 Adoption</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Findora Launches dApp Transaction Privacy-Focused Triple Masking SDK</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/findora-dapp-triple-masking-sdk/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 12:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[findora]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=252440</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/findora-dapp-triple-masking-sdk/">Findora Launches dApp Transaction Privacy-Focused Triple Masking SDK</a></p>
<p>Innovative Layer-1 blockchain Findora has introduced a Triple Masking SDK privacy-preserving solution for Web3. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/findora-dapp-triple-masking-sdk/">Findora Launches dApp Transaction Privacy-Focused Triple Masking SDK</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/findora-dapp-triple-masking-sdk/">Findora Launches dApp Transaction Privacy-Focused Triple Masking SDK</a></p>
<p><a href="https://findora.org/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Findora</a> has launched a Web3-focused Triple Masking SDK for developers to easily integrate zero-knowledge (ZK) proofs into their decentralized applications (dApps). According to the programmable privacy-enabled public blockchain, the Findora Triple Masking ZK SDK also enhances user transactions. For instance, users can now transact privately while remaining auditable and have multiple options regarding masked or transparent information.</p>
<p>Describing the development as a Web3 universal privacy-preserving solution, Findora added that the Triple Masking SDK offers plug-and-play privacy for dApps.</p>
<h2>Findora Developer CEO Sums Up Value Proposition of Triple Masking SDK</h2>
<p>Sam Harrison, chief executive officer of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ico/findora/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Findora</a> developer Discreet Labs, weighed in on the decentralized application facilitator, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Triple Masking fulfills a promise that blockchain technology made years ago: your financial status, your financial future, is no longer in the hands of some unknown, so-called &#8220;trusted&#8221; third party. It&#8217;s in your hands. This SDK simplifies the developer experience of implementing complicated ZK-proofs, which in turn enables more decentralized applications to offer the benefits of these ZK-proofs to their users.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Harrison also added:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Users tend to have to make a choice between privacy and convenience. And when they do, they usually pick convenience. I am excited to see what choices developers can offer their users when privacy and convenience are both attainable.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The Discreet Labs CEO explained that Triple Masking goes beyond simply encrypting information. According to him, Findora&#8217;s new offering can also trace assets in a regulatory and analytically compliant manner. As a result, Harrison pointed out that Triple Masking meets a professional institution&#8217;s privacy and compliance requirements.</p>
<h2>Zero-Knowledge Proofs &amp; SDK Applicability</h2>
<p>Financial institutions&#8217; requirements to safeguard privacy have been codified by regulation for decades. This also means consumers retain the right to keep their personal financial data from prying eyes. Although regulations emphasize financial customers&#8217; need to consent to private information-sharing, ZKs enhance the experience.</p>
<p>As cryptographic techniques, zero-knowledge proofs enable decentralized networks to hide transaction data while permitting the validation of the inherent information. Although this solution poses a computationally complex scenario, it also allows blockchain verification of a digital asset&#8217;s movement without requiring additional sensitive information. Such information includes details about the digital asset as well as its sender and receiver. Ultimately, ZK proofs lack the essential element that provides digital asset private transactions while ensuring minimal expenditure of said assets. It is this lapse that Findora&#8217;s Triple Masking initiative seeks to adequately address.</p>
<p>Supported on Findora&#8217;s network, the Triple Masking SDK offers full-privacy protection and anonymity for transactions instead of mere pseudonymity. With the SDK, developers are privy to ZK enablement and can access added transaction privacy at three levels. Although users can protect transactions from the rest of the public <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/crypto/blockchain-news/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">blockchain</a>, Findora said the SDK can trace assets. This means that while everybody else is oblivious to transactions, backend auditors can still monitor them.</p>
<p>Findora&#8217;s Triple Masking processes thousands of transactions significantly faster than the industry benchmark. Furthermore, the application&#8217;s compatibility with the secp256k1 curve enables better transaction signing by standard EVM wallets like MetaMask.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/a16z-100m-ai-pinecone/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/findora-dapp-triple-masking-sdk/">Findora Launches dApp Transaction Privacy-Focused Triple Masking SDK</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>a16z and Others Invest $100M in AI Startup Pinecone in Series B Funding</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/a16z-100m-ai-pinecone/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Babafemi Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 11:24:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[a16z]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[andreessen horowitz]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pinecone]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=252676</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/a16z-100m-ai-pinecone/">a16z and Others Invest $100M in AI Startup Pinecone in Series B Funding</a></p>
<p>The investment from a16z is a strong vote of confidence in Pinecone’s technology.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/a16z-100m-ai-pinecone/">a16z and Others Invest $100M in AI Startup Pinecone in Series B Funding</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/a16z-100m-ai-pinecone/">a16z and Others Invest $100M in AI Startup Pinecone in Series B Funding</a></p>

<p>California-based AI startup, Pinecone <a href="https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20230427005380/en/Pinecone-Raises-100M-in-Series-B-Funding-to-Provide-Long-Term-Memory-for-AI" target="_blank">has received</a> a $100 million investment from venture capital firm Andreessen Horowitz (a16z) in its series B funding. The round also featured ICONIQ Growth, Menlo Ventures, and Wing Venture Capital.</p>
<p>Following the investment, the company now has a market valuation of $750 million. With the investment, the vector database company will expand its team and improve its database further.</p>
<h2>Gaining Ground</h2>
<p>Pinecone creates vector databases that serve as long-term memory for AI models. These databases are a critical component of AI-powered applications. Since introducing its database in 2021, the firm has gained ground in the $110B Generative AI market.</p>
<p>In Q1 2023, the company saw increased adoption of its innovative technology across industries including consumer apps, e-commerce, fintech, insurance, media, and AI/ML. It also recorded an 8x growth in paid customers, including companies like Shopify, Gong, and Zapier.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/a16z/">A16z</a> General Partner, Peter Levine, noted how critical Pinecone has become to maintaining the AI stack. He said:</p>
<blockquote>
<p>“We&#8217;re thrilled to be partnering with Pinecone to support their vision of becoming the memory layer for AI applications.”</p>
</blockquote>
<h2>How AI Startup Pinecone Is Revolutionizing Machine Learning</h2>
<p>While current Large Language models (LLM) have been known to give wrong responses factually based on the vector embeddings they search through, the vector database company seeks to change all that.</p>
<p>“We created Pinecone and the vector database category to let all AI developers easily work with a scalable and cost-efficient database for this workload,” said Edo Liberty, CEO of Pinecone. Consequently, Pinecone provides an external database where developers can store relevant data for their LLM apps. These data can then be drawn on to improve the quality of AI search results</p>
<p>The investment from a16z is a strong vote of confidence in Pinecone’s technology. With the new funds raised, Pinecone will expand its reach and offer its technology to a wider range of customers. The firm will also hope to build more products.</p>
<p>According to Bob Wiederhold, President of Pinecone, the startup  “will capitalize on hypergrowth to transform every line of business and even create new ones, from AI search to AI chatbots and AI agents”.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cyberconnect-token-sale-coinlist/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/a16z-100m-ai-pinecone/">a16z and Others Invest $100M in AI Startup Pinecone in Series B Funding</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>CyberConnect Community Token Sale &amp; Registration on CoinList Announced</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/cyberconnect-token-sale-coinlist/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 11:14:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bnb]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bnb chain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[casper]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinlist]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cspr]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cyber]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cyberconnect]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cyberconnect wallet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cybertoken]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fil]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[filecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[matic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mina]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[polygon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sol]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[solana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sui]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sui Network]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=252798</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cyberconnect-token-sale-coinlist/">CyberConnect Community Token Sale &#038; Registration on CoinList Announced</a></p>
<p>The CyberConnect CYBER token initial coin offering takes place on CoinList on May 18th, three days after the registration deadline.  </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cyberconnect-token-sale-coinlist/">CyberConnect Community Token Sale &#038; Registration on CoinList Announced</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cyberconnect-token-sale-coinlist/">CyberConnect Community Token Sale &#038; Registration on CoinList Announced</a></p>
<p>CoinList recently announced the registration and sale of its CyberConnect Community tokens would soon be underway. In a <a href="https://blog.coinlist.co/announcing-the-cyberconnect-token-sale-on-coinlist/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">blog post</a>, the digital currency exchange said the sale of the user-empowering decentralized social network&#8217;s tokens begins on May 18th. The deadline for registration would be three days earlier on May 15th.</p>
<p>Priced at $1.80 per token, the CYBER tokens have an initial supply of 3,000,000 tokens, with an additional 2,000,000 that can be unlocked during the sale period. However, CoinList pointed out that unlocking the additional token supply would be at the team&#8217;s discretion.</p>
<p>The CyberConnect team <a href="https://twitter.com/CyberConnectHQ/status/1651633556123262979" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">took to Twitter</a> to announce the public sale of its native utility &amp; governance token.</p>
<h2>CyberConnect</h2>
<p>CyberConnect described itself as the biggest platform for users and developers since its 2021 launch as Web3&#8217;s earliest decentralized social network. It has challenged the Web2 status quo since inception, by establishing a community-owned platform that offers users control over their digital affairs. This includes ultimate ownership over their digital identity, data content, connections, and monetization channels.</p>
<p>In addition to providing a link between these digital assets, the decentralized social graph protocol offers a smart contract wallet. The CyberConnect Wallet securely stores the digital assets of users and developers and facilitates easy Web3 onboarding of these assets. This functionality sees CyberConnect&#8217;s decentralized data storage operate as a hybrid model combining on and off-chain advantages.</p>
<p>According to reports, over 50 projects already deploy CyberConnect&#8217;s decentralized social network infrastructure for numerous use cases. These include community-owned social networks, content curation, marketplaces, and discovery tools.</p>
<p>As of April, the CyberConnect protocol has over 875,000 CyberProfiles and roughly 327,000 monthly active wallets. These self-sovereign on-chain identities have completed more than 7.3 million cumulative transactions across numerous blockchains and decentralized protocols.</p>
<p>Currently on <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a>, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/matic-network/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Polygon</a>, and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/binance-coin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BNB</a> Chain, CyberConnect is designed to be multi-chain and scalable. The decentralized social graph protocol seeks to expand to other chains compatible with the Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM).</p>
<h2>Besides CyberConnect Development, CoinList Lists SUI</h2>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinlist-list-sui/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">In other news</a>, CoinList appears set to list Sui Blockchain native token SUI on May 3rd, coinciding with the Sui network mainnet launch. In a <a href="https://blog.coinlist.co/sui-network-sui-launching-soon-on-coinlist/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">blog post</a>, CoinList said:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Our mission at CoinList is to empower builders at any stage in their journey and connect them with high-quality early adopters of their products. Today, we are excited to announce that CoinList will be listing SUI, the native token of the highly anticipated Sui Blockchain, on Day 1 of its launch.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>At the time of the announcement two days ago, the token launchpad and trading platform also said that &#8220;as part of the SUI launch, CoinList will offer 48 hours of free trading on all SUI pairs on CoinList Pro and 1 month of fee-free staking to all eligible CoinList users.&#8221;</p>
<p>Ranked among the most functional token listing platforms in the decentralized space, CoinList has facilitated the popularity of several innovative blockchain protocols. These include  <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/solana/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Solana</a> (SOL), <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/filecoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Filecoin</a> (FIL), Casper (CSPR), and Mina.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-african-firm-bitcoin-fraud-us/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cyberconnect-token-sale-coinlist/">CyberConnect Community Token Sale &#038; Registration on CoinList Announced</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Head of South African Firm Slapped with $3.4B Fine for Bitcoin Fraud in US</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-african-firm-bitcoin-fraud-us/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sanaa Sharma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 11:02:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cftc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mti]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=252770</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-african-firm-bitcoin-fraud-us/">Head of South African Firm Slapped with $3.4B Fine for Bitcoin Fraud in US</a></p>
<p>The CFTC claimed that the firm had proprietary software that was expected to recognize significant trading gains for investors who contributed to the Bitcoin pool, but in reality, there was no such "bot" in use.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-african-firm-bitcoin-fraud-us/">Head of South African Firm Slapped with $3.4B Fine for Bitcoin Fraud in US</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-african-firm-bitcoin-fraud-us/">Head of South African Firm Slapped with $3.4B Fine for Bitcoin Fraud in US</a></p>
<p>The head of a South African firm has been slapped with a massive fine of $3.4 billion by a federal judge in Texas. The US commodities regulator claimed that this was the largest-ever fraud case revolving around <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> ever to be committed by a company.</p>
<p>The head, who goes by the name Cornelius Johannes Steynberg, was asked to pay $1.7 billion as a civil penalty, a record for any Commodity Futures Trading Commission case, according to the regulator. Steynberg, whose last known place of residing was in South Africa, hasn&#8217;t been responsive to the media.</p>
<h2>Details of This Bitcoin Fraud</h2>
<p>The <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/cftc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CFTC</a> had <a href="https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/us-cftc-charges-south-african-company-with-record-17-bln-bitcoin-fraud-2022-06-30/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reprimanded</a> Steynberg in July, claiming that the Mirror Trading demanded Bitcoin online from thousands of people to allegedly manage a commodity pool. The company also promised to trade off-exchange, retail foreign currency with users who were not allowed to trade. The Commodity Futures Trading Commission filed charges against Mirror Trading International Proprietary Limited.</p>
<p>Steynberg, who had been a fugitive from South African Law enforcement, was detained in Brazil last year on an INTERPOL arrest warrant.</p>
<p>Over a span of almost three years from 2018 to 2021, Steynberg received and stole at least 29,421 bitcoins worth more than $1.7 billion from over 23000 participants from the United States. The people of Texas were the worst affected by the heist that happened almost two years ago.</p>
<p>The judgment against Steynberg was rolled out by Judge Lee Yeakel in the Western District of Texas.</p>
<p>The CFTC claimed that the firm had proprietary software that was expected to recognize significant trading gains for investors who contributed to the Bitcoin pool, but in reality, there was no such &#8220;bot&#8221; in use. In reality, only a small portion of the pooled Bitcoin was invested, and that too at a loss. The remaining was &#8220;misappropriated&#8221;, according to the CFTC. The firm ended up filing for bankruptcy in 2021, closely after which South African regulatory official began its fraud investigation.</p>
<p>MTI is presently undergoing liquidation in South Africa. The order states that MTI is &#8220;liable for fraud in connection with retail foreign currency (forex) transactions, fraud by an associated person of a commodity pool operator (CPO), registration violations, and failure to comply with CPO regulations&#8221;.</p>
<p>In addition to the fine, Steynberg is permanently denied registering with the CFTC and trading in any markets regulated by them.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/intel-q1-2023/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-african-firm-bitcoin-fraud-us/">Head of South African Firm Slapped with $3.4B Fine for Bitcoin Fraud in US</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4673 metric#misses=43 metric#hit-ratio=99.1 metric#bytes=1302536 metric#prefetches=209 metric#store-reads=22 metric#store-writes=27 metric#store-hits=215 metric#store-misses=4 metric#sql-queries=34 metric#ms-total=211.47 metric#ms-cache=12.55 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.2615 metric#ms-cache-ratio=5.9 -->