<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 14:31:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse Criticizes ‘Double Standard’ in Wells Fargo Fine Case Compared to FTX Crash</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-ceo-wells-fargo-ftx/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-ceo-wells-fargo-ftx/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 14:31:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brad garlinghouse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[wells fargo]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=230363</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-ceo-wells-fargo-ftx/">Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse Criticizes ‘Double Standard’ in Wells Fargo Fine Case Compared to FTX Crash</a></p>
<p>The CEO of Ripple recently suggested that Wells Fargo did not receive the ‘FTX treatment’ despite exploiting its customers. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-ceo-wells-fargo-ftx/">Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse Criticizes ‘Double Standard’ in Wells Fargo Fine Case Compared to FTX Crash</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-ceo-wells-fargo-ftx/">Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse Criticizes ‘Double Standard’ in Wells Fargo Fine Case Compared to FTX Crash</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ripple-labs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ripple</a> CEO <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/brad-garlinghouse/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Brad Garlinghouse</a> recently likened the recent <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/wells-fargo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Wells Fargo</a> fund management fiasco to the collapse of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX.</a> However, Garlinghouse disapproved of what he perceived as a hypocritical reaction to Wells Fargo’s case. According to the Ripple CEO, the leading American bank’s $3.7 billion fine for mismanaging customers’ interests was on the same scale as FTX’s monumental fall. However, Garlinghouse says the outrage directed at Wells Fargo turned out to be barely noticeable compared to the sunken crypto exchange.</p>
<p>The Ripple CEO <a href="https://twitter.com/bgarlinghouse/status/1605658059228880897?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1605658059228880897%7Ctwgr%5E03c5519e02f27f376f675616a03349858f786725%7Ctwcon%5Es1_&amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fcointelegraph.com%2Fnews%2Fripple-ceo-compares-wells-fargo-billions-mismanagement-with-ftx-collapse" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">took to Twitter</a> to share his thoughts on the matter in a post that read:</p>
<blockquote><p>“The world is (appropriately) outraged by SBF and FTX’s fraud, but when Wells Fargo mismanages billions in customer funds as well, it’s barely a blip on the radar. Food for thought&#8230;”</p></blockquote>
<p>Garlinghouse’s tweet was accompanied by a popular comic book meme that alluded to the perceived double standard by government authorities.</p>
<h2>Twitter Users Chime In on Ripple CEO Scathing Assessment of Wells Fargo Case</h2>
<p>Garlinghouse’s criticism of the lack of attention directed towards Wells Fargo for its misdeeds garnered varied responses from Twitter observers. Although few questioned the meaning behind his verbal attack, a majority supported the Ripple CEO’s assessment of the Wells Fargo case. This majority support included insisting that relevant authorities should have extended the same FTX treatment to the prominent bank. In addition, some other users pointed out that the system favored traditional banking and finance over crypto-focused operations. Yet still, a few users also addressed the perceived double standard as proof that traditional banks’ own and control the government.’</p>
<h2>Recap of the Latest Wells Fargo Case</h2>
<p>Two days ago, the United States Consumer Financial Protection Bureau (CFPB) <a href="https://www.consumerfinance.gov/about-us/newsroom/cfpb-orders-wells-fargo-to-pay-37-billion-for-widespread-mismanagement-of-auto-loans-mortgages-and-deposit-accounts/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">demanded</a> that Wells Fargo pay a $3.7 billion fine. According to the consumer protection agency, Wells Fargo committed widespread mismanagement of auto loans, mortgages, and deposit loans. The CFPB also alleged that the San Francisco-based bank’s unethical conduct resulted in billions of dollars in financial harm to clients. This mismanagement also resulted in the wrongful foreclosure of homes and illegal repossession of vehicles, to name a few.</p>
<p>The CFPB’s hefty fine comprised over $2 billion in consumer redress and a $1.7 billion civil penalty.</p>
<p>Weighing in on Wells Fargo’s unlawful systematic fees and interest charges on its customers, CFPB Director Rohit Chopra stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Wells Fargo’s rinse-repeat cycle of violating the law has harmed millions of American families. The CFPB is ordering Wells Fargo to refund billions of dollars to consumers across the country.”</p></blockquote>
<p>In addition, Chopra suggested that this incident was not the first time the banking giant would violate the law. As he put it, “this is an important initial step for accountability and long-term reform of this repeat offender.”</p>
<p>According to reports, there are 16 million customers affected in the latest Wells Fargo case.</p>
<h2>Previous Wells Fargo Infraction</h2>
<p>In 2016, the multinational bank and financial services platform also received a $185 million fine from the CFPB. At the time, the agency accused Wells Fargo of creating countless fraudulent savings accounts for its customers without their consent. By 2020, the banking giant agreed to pay $3 billion to resolve all liabilities pertaining to the case.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-acquisition-blockfolio-ftt/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-ceo-wells-fargo-ftx/">Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse Criticizes ‘Double Standard’ in Wells Fargo Fine Case Compared to FTX Crash</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-ceo-wells-fargo-ftx/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>FTX Acquisition of Blockfolio Was Mostly Funded with FTT Tokens</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-acquisition-blockfolio-ftt/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-acquisition-blockfolio-ftt/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 11:54:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Deals News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockfolio]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTT Tokens]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=230347</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-acquisition-blockfolio-ftt/">FTX Acquisition of Blockfolio Was Mostly Funded with FTT Tokens</a></p>
<p>The FTT token was also a major factor in the implosion of FTX.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-acquisition-blockfolio-ftt/">FTX Acquisition of Blockfolio Was Mostly Funded with FTT Tokens</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-acquisition-blockfolio-ftt/">FTX Acquisition of Blockfolio Was Mostly Funded with FTT Tokens</a></p>
<p>New details about the investments of FTX Derivatives Exchange into BlockFolio, a crypto brokerage firm have been <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2022-12-22/ftx-paid-for-blockfolio-deal-mostly-in-ftt-token-it-invented?utm_source=website&amp;utm_medium=share&amp;utm_campaign=twitter&amp;sref=3REHEaVI" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">published</a> by Bloomberg. According to the media firm, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a> financed over 94% of the $84 million it paid for the platform using FTT, a digital token it created.</p>
<p>With the funds paid, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-acquires-blockfolio-150-million/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX took a 52% stake in BlockFolio</a> in 2020 and the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-exchange-files-for-bankruptcy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">bankrupt exchange</a> which at the time was only a year old had the option to buy up the rest of the smaller company. The insights shared by Bloomberg have shown some of the early financial impropriety Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF) committed that eventually set the stage for the implosion of his trading platform this November.</p>
<p>The interesting twist to the acquisition of BlockFolio was that media reports on it at the time never dug deep into the nature of equity paid down for the exchange. It was just reported that FTX paid in cash, crypto, and a combination of equity. Though the report from Bloomberg was backed by a document it reviewed, the claims have not been confirmed by any FTX representative.</p>
<p>The FTT token was also a major factor in the implosion of FTX as a report from Coindesk in early November showed that the digital currency occupies the bulk of the exchange’s balance sheet. That sent a signal that the valuation of the exchange and its ability to sustain the payment of liabilities is wholly dependent on the FTT tokens and this comes off as an unsettling push for investors.</p>
<p>The rush to the bankruptcy of the trading platform was catalyzed when Binance CEO, Changpeng “CZ” Zhao <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-ftx-tokens-ftt-alameda/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">announced</a> last month that he wants to sell the FTT coins he received as an equity contribution for investing in FTX.</p>
<h2>Beyond Blockfolio: Chronicles of Failed FTX Acquisitions</h2>
<p>At its very peak, the FTX trading platform was seen as a lender of last resort for most distressed crypto firms. Earlier this year, Terra (LUNA) plunged when its sister token, TerraUSD (UST) depegged from the USD, an event that lead to a liquidity crunch and the collapse of Three Arrows Capital (3AC).</p>
<p>Besides 3AC which had direct exposure to LUNA, other major Virtual Assets Service Providers (VASPs) like Celsius Network and Voyager Digital also went bankrupt following the collapse. At the time, FTX, through Alameda Research rose up to the occasion to bail out many of these firms and extend a <a href="https://blockworks.co/news/voyager-to-borrow-500m-from-alameda-amid-insolvency-rumors" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">line of credit worth $500 million</a> to Voyager Digital.</p>
<p>The cash injection was unable to keep the crypto lending from going bankrupt, and the exchange’s investment went almost to naught. FTX’s investments into BlockFi and other new entities were also reversed when the company filed for bankruptcy last month.</p>
<p>As it stands, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-creditors-1-million/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX has up to 1 million creditors</a> with over $10 billion in liabilities. The exchange’s top executives including Sam Bankman-Fried are facing Federal Fraud charges in the United States at the moment.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/huobi-visa-card/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-acquisition-blockfolio-ftt/">FTX Acquisition of Blockfolio Was Mostly Funded with FTT Tokens</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-acquisition-blockfolio-ftt/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Huobi Partners with Payment Giant Visa to Launch Huobi Visa Card</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/huobi-visa-card/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/huobi-visa-card/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 11:43:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FinTech News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[huobi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[visa]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=230311</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/huobi-visa-card/">Huobi Partners with Payment Giant Visa to Launch Huobi Visa Card</a></p>
<p>Huobi and Visa share similar goals in wanting to bridge the gap that exists between the crypto ecosystem and traditional finance.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/huobi-visa-card/">Huobi Partners with Payment Giant Visa to Launch Huobi Visa Card</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/huobi-visa-card/">Huobi Partners with Payment Giant Visa to Launch Huobi Visa Card</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/huobi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Huobi</a>, one of the world’s leading virtual assets exchanges, today <a href="https://www.huobi.com/support/en-us/detail/64926012577680" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announced</a> its partnership with the digital payment platform <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/visa-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Visa</a>. According to the post, the partnership will help the exchange to develop what it calls the &#8220;Huobi Visa Card&#8221;, and issue the same across the world.</p>
<h2>Huobi to Promote Adoption of Virtually Assets</h2>
<p>By all means, Huobi sees the plan as one that will bring more ease of access to crypto investors. This is because one of the main aims of the card is to create a more efficient fiat-to-crypto conversion gateway for its users.</p>
<p>Also, a partnership such as this one promises to help promote the popularity of the virtual asset industry at large. According to recent regulatory reports, Visa currently operates in at least 200 countries and boasts a customer base of about 3.3 billion people. Huobi will therefore be hoping to leverage Visa&#8217;s large customer base to help drive its plans of promoting the adoption of virtual assets worldwide. And on top of that, Huobi will also be hoping to contribute its quota to global financial inclusion with this partnership.</p>
<p>To that effect, Justin Sun, a member of Huobi&#8217;s Global Advisory Board shared his excitement about the milestone achievement. He then wrote in part:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Huobi and Visa are both prominent leaders in their respective industries. With the Huobi-branded card, we hope to contribute towards global financial inclusion.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Visa also shares similar goals with Huobi in wanting to bridge the gap between the crypto ecosystem and traditional finance. Cuy Sheffield, Head of Crypto at Visa shared this in a recent statement.</p>
<h2>The Huobi Visa Card</h2>
<p>Per the announcement, existing Huobi users may link the cards to their accounts. This implies that users may now purchase goods and services at any of the 80 million Visa merchant locations worldwide, using their virtual assets balances.</p>
<p>There are more benefits for users to derive from the Huobi Visa Card, says the exchange.  The benefits include and are not limited to sure-win coupon airdrops, cashback vouchers, APY booster coupons, and other privileges available in the Huobi Earn program.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-treasury-yields-lows/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/huobi-visa-card/">Huobi Partners with Payment Giant Visa to Launch Huobi Visa Card</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/huobi-visa-card/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>US Treasury Yields in Their Lows as Earlier Sell-Off Ends</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-treasury-yields-lows/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-treasury-yields-lows/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 11:38:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FOMC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[treasury]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[treasury yield]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=230331</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-treasury-yields-lows/">US Treasury Yields in Their Lows as Earlier Sell-Off Ends</a></p>
<p>As the Treasury yields bounce, the top market indices also have their share of mixed performance, and the crypto industry continues to wallow in losses.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-treasury-yields-lows/">US Treasury Yields in Their Lows as Earlier Sell-Off Ends</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-treasury-yields-lows/">US Treasury Yields in Their Lows as Earlier Sell-Off Ends</a></p>
<p>After recording a sell-off earlier in the week, the US Treasury yields have declined as investors return to the bond market. An unexpected move by the Bank of Japan in tweaking its yield curve controls sparked global bonds to sell off earlier in the week. Meanwhile, the financial institution took the step to shield the impact of protracted monetary stimulus measures. On the other hand, economics said the tweak was necessary.</p>
<h2>US Treasury Yields Fall</h2>
<p>US treasury yields dropped, with the 30-year Treasury bond falling 3.4 basis points to 3.7103%. Also, the 10-year Treasury note declined 3.9 basis points at 3.6452%. Also, the yield on the 2-year note dipped 1 point to 4.2037%.</p>
<p>Notably, the US treasury yields on a 2-year note slumped on Wednesday amid the surprise policy shift from the Bank of Japan, which stretched its target range for 10-year Japanese government bond yields. Additionally, the tweak in its yield curve control policy permits the yield on the 10-year Japanese government bond to move from 25 basis points to 50 basis points. The yield curve control came to light in 2016 with the central bank planning to move inflation to its 2% target. This is after a long period of ultra-low inflation and economic stagnation. According to the Bank of Japan, the recent tweak was to &#8220;improve market functioning and encourage a smoother formation of the entire yield, vehicle maintaining accommodative financial considerations.&#8221;</p>
<p>Coinspeaker recently <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/treasury-yields-stock-market-growth/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">wrote</a> about the Treasury yields rebound and setting the pace for the stock market growth. In addition to the Federal Open Market Committee (FOMC) raising interest rates to their highest level in 15 years at 50 basis points, the increment is affecting the government&#8217;s struggle to combat inflation in America. Before the 50 basis point rise, the Feds had increased the interest rates by 74 basis points on about 4 different occasions.</p>
<p>As the Treasury yields bounce, the top market indices also have their share of mixed performance, and the crypto industry continues to wallow in losses. With a market capitalization of about $324 billion, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> is currency down 0.07% to $16,855. Similarly, the second largest crypto asset <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a>, the cryptocurrency has shed 29.68% in its 24-hours trading volume and trades at $1,218.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-btc-eth-price-charts/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-treasury-yields-lows/">US Treasury Yields in Their Lows as Earlier Sell-Off Ends</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-treasury-yields-lows/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Twitter Introduces BTC and ETH Price Charts on App</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-btc-eth-price-charts/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-btc-eth-price-charts/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sanaa Sharma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 11:33:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[twitter]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=230319</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-btc-eth-price-charts/">Twitter Introduces BTC and ETH Price Charts on App</a></p>
<p>Soon after the announcement by the official Twitter account, Elon Musk retweeted the launch of this novel feature, claiming that this was one of the many product launches added to the Financial Twitter.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-btc-eth-price-charts/">Twitter Introduces BTC and ETH Price Charts on App</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-btc-eth-price-charts/">Twitter Introduces BTC and ETH Price Charts on App</a></p>
<p>Social media platform <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/twitter/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Twitter</a> has now introduced a new feature on the app which allows users to search the keywords to get the price rise and fall of Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a>) and Ether (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ETH</a>). This can be done easily by typing in the names or tickers on the search option.</p>
<p>This follows as an improvement of $Cashtags and was revealed by the Twitter Business account on December 21. The account explained that whenever tweets the symbol of a famous stock, exchange-traded fund, or cryptocurrency with a dollar sign ($), users will be able to view a clickable link that redirects them to look for results that will essentially comprise the pricing streak for those symbols. The ticker symbol search will also present the price graph of that particular entity.</p>
<p>Soon after the announcement by the official Twitter account, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/elon-musk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Elon Musk</a> retweeted the launch of this novel feature, claiming that this was one of the many product launches added to the Financial Twitter.</p>
<p>Having said that, Twitter Business claims to be expanding its range of symbols and enhancing user experience in the upcoming weeks. <a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/twitter-quietly-adds-btc-and-eth-price-indexes-to-search-function" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Cointelegraph</a> realized that several variations of Bitcoin like $Bitcoin, Bitcoin Price, and BTC price will also promote the price chart on Twitter, with associated searches presently working for ETH.</p>
<p>According to tech blogger Jane Mastodon Wong, the price charts are imported from the trading analysis platform TradingView.</p>
<p>The charts also comprise a &#8220;View on Robinhood&#8221; link that when selected at the bottom left corner, indicates that the American Financial Services firm has collaborated with Twitter on this project. The users are then redirected to Robinhood&#8217;s price graph which offers an additional link under &#8220;Sign Up to Buy Ethereum&#8221;. The same links are offered for Bitcoin also. However, no collaboration information has been revealed between Twitter and Robinhood.</p>
<p>Twitter&#8217;s price graph will surely lead to more viewership and traffic to Robinhood. According to data by BitInfoChart:- The bitcoin hashtag solely is tweeted more than a hundred and twenty thousand times per day.</p>
<p>Previously, rumors began to spread about Twitter introducing its very own cryptocurrency called the Twitter Coin that could be utilized for payments on the platform. The rumors started on December 4, approximately a week after Musk revealed what Twitter 2.0 would look like. This also talked about probable cryptocurrency-based payments on Twitter.</p>
<p>However, Musk&#8217;s future at Twitter seems on edge following his infamous poll wherein the controversial Businessman asked the users if he should step down as the head of Twitter. Almost sixty percent of the people who participated in the poll voted &#8216;Yes&#8217; as a result.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-token-ftt-security/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-btc-eth-price-charts/">Twitter Introduces BTC and ETH Price Charts on App</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-btc-eth-price-charts/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>US SEC Declares FTX’s Native Token FTT as Security</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-token-ftt-security/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-token-ftt-security/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 11:05:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Alameda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sam bankman-fried]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sbf]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=230254</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-token-ftt-security/">US SEC Declares FTX&#8217;s Native Token FTT as Security</a></p>
<p>The SEC stated that the operations of the FTT token and the buy-and-burn program initiated by crypto exchange FTX are synonymous with stock buyback and thus constitute the behavior of securities. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-token-ftt-security/">US SEC Declares FTX&#8217;s Native Token FTT as Security</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-token-ftt-security/">US SEC Declares FTX&#8217;s Native Token FTT as Security</a></p>
<p>In a complaint filed late Wednesday, December 21, the US Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) said that crypto exchange <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a> sold its native FTT tokens as an investment contract and is a &#8220;security&#8221;.</p>
<h2>Is FTT a Security?</h2>
<p>The massive selling of FTT tokens by <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a> and others triggered a major downfall for the crypto exchange FTX. Since the FTX crisis unfolded in early November, the price of FTT tokens collapsed by a staggering 98% so far. In its recent analysis, the US SEC <a href="https://www.sec.gov/litigation/complaints/2022/comp-pr2022-234.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener">noted</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;If demand for trading on the FTX platform increased, demand for the FTT token could increase, such that any price increase in FTT would benefit holders of FTT equally and in direct proportion to their FTT holdings. The large allocation of tokens to FTX incentivized the FTX management team to take steps to attract more users onto the trading platform and, therefore, increase demand for, and increase the trading price of, the FTT token.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The SEC made this claim in the complaint filed against Alameda Research CEO Caroline Ellison and FTX co-founder Gary Wang. The complaint filed by the SEC notes that crypto exchange FTX would use the proceeds from the token sale to fund the development, business operations, marketing, and growth of FTX. The SEC has clearly mentioned that FTT is an &#8220;investment&#8221; with profit potential.</p>
<p>&#8220;The FTT materials made clear that FTX’s core management team’s efforts would drive the growth and ultimate success of FTX,&#8221; said the SEC. Besides, the SEC has also mentioned the &#8220;buy and burn&#8221; program initiated by crypto exchange FTX.</p>
<p>The securities regulator said that this initiative was akin to many other crypto exchange tokens and similar to stock buyback where revenues from FTX would repurchase and burn FTT while increasing their value.</p>
<h2>Alameda CEO Pleads Guilty</h2>
<p>Alameda Research CEO Caroline Ellison and FTX co-founder Gary Wang <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ellison-wang-guilty-ftx/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">have pleaded guilty</a> to criminal charges by the US Southern District of New York. Damian Williams, the attorney for the Southern District of New York <a href="https://twitter.com/SDNYnews/status/1605745361842327552" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a> that Ellison and Wang were charged “in connection with their roles in the frauds that contributed to FTX’s collapse.”</p>
<p>Both have declared to cooperate with the prosecutors who are investigating the collapse of FTX and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/sam-bankman-fried/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Sam Bankman-Fried</a>. In action against SBF and his companies, the CFTC has also charged Ellison and Wang with charges of fraud.</p>
<p>At the same time, the SEC has charged the duo in a multi-year scheme of defrauding equity investors on FTX.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/paxful-delisting-ethereum/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-token-ftt-security/">US SEC Declares FTX&#8217;s Native Token FTT as Security</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-token-ftt-security/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Peer-to-Peer Trading Platform Paxful Delisting Ethereum</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/paxful-delisting-ethereum/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/paxful-delisting-ethereum/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mercy Tukiya Mutanya]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 11:01:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[paxful]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=230284</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/paxful-delisting-ethereum/">Peer-to-Peer Trading Platform Paxful Delisting Ethereum</a></p>
<p>The exchange added support for Ethereum in April last year, stating that “Ethereum gives users a different chance to claim their stake in the crypto world.”</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/paxful-delisting-ethereum/">Peer-to-Peer Trading Platform Paxful Delisting Ethereum</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/paxful-delisting-ethereum/">Peer-to-Peer Trading Platform Paxful Delisting Ethereum</a></p>
<p>Global peer-to-peer trading platform Paxful has <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2022/12/21/peer-to-peer-crypto-marketplace-paxful-removes-eth-from-platform/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announced</a> that it will delist <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a> from its platform. A newsletter sent to the platform&#8217;s 11.6 million users reveals that ETH trades will be halted on Thursday. A screenshot of the newsletter was shared in a tweet Paxful CEO Ray Youssef. In the letter, the CEO gives three reasons for his decision to delist Ethereum.</p>
<p>The first is Ethereum’s move from proof-of-work (PoW) to proof-of-stake (PoS). According to Youssef, PoW is what makes <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> “the only honest money” while PoS has turned Ethereum into a “digital form of fiat.” For the second reason, Youssef alleges that Ethereum is not decentralized and is instead run by a group of people. While acknowledging the cryptocurrency’s utility in areas such as credit and lending, the CEO noted that Ethereum now  “thrives because of tokenization,” adding that Ethereum-based tokens have been used to scam people out of ”billions.&#8221; Youssef opines that such tokens have “stolen valuable momentum away from Bitcoin and cost us years on our mission.”</p>
<p>The “mission,” according to Youssef is to free people, especially those in the “Global South” from “economic apartheid.” The CEO believes that the “crypto industry is under attack right now – which means our responsibility to protect our users is greater than ever before.”</p>
<p>Youssef first revealed plans to delist ETH on December 12 when he responded to a tweet by Jeremy Garcia, a software developer who state that the Ethereum project was headed for failure owing to its poor design and “a foundation of sand” as opposed to Bitcoin’s “foundation of granite.”</p>
<blockquote><p>https://twitter.com/raypaxful/status/1602111727944241152?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw</p></blockquote>
<p>The exchange added support for Ethereum in April last year, stating that “Ethereum gives users a different chance to claim their stake in the crypto world.”</p>
<p>Youssef is a known Bitcoin supporter and most recently, following the collapse of crypto exchange FTX, has been advocating for self-custody. He recently encouraged Paxful users to move their crypto to self-custody. Centralized exchanges (CEX) and self-custody have been major topics of discussion in the crypto industry following the FTX collapse.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ellison-wang-guilty-ftx/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/paxful-delisting-ethereum/">Peer-to-Peer Trading Platform Paxful Delisting Ethereum</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/paxful-delisting-ethereum/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Caroline Ellison and Gary Wang Plead Guilty in Ongoing FTX Investigation</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ellison-wang-guilty-ftx/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ellison-wang-guilty-ftx/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 10:52:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alameda research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Caroline Ellison]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gary Wang]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sam bankman-fried]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sbf]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=230282</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ellison-wang-guilty-ftx/">Caroline Ellison and Gary Wang Plead Guilty in Ongoing FTX Investigation</a></p>
<p>For their complicit role in how FTX went under, Federal prosecutors have filed a separate action against the duo for participating in the "multiyear scheme to defraud equity investors in FTX”.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ellison-wang-guilty-ftx/">Caroline Ellison and Gary Wang Plead Guilty in Ongoing FTX Investigation</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ellison-wang-guilty-ftx/">Caroline Ellison and Gary Wang Plead Guilty in Ongoing FTX Investigation</a></p>
<p>Caroline Ellison and Gary Wang, the two profile executives of the bankrupt FTX Derivatives Exchange and Alameda Research have <a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/caroline-ellison-gary-wang-plead-guilty-to-fraud-charges" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">pleaded guilty</a> to Federal fraud charges in the Southern District of New York (SDNY). The plea came as a part of the Department of Justice’s (DoJ) investigation into the circumstances that lead to the collapse of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a>, the crypto trading platform co-founded by Sam Bankman-Fried (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/sam-bankman-fried/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SBF</a>).</p>
<p>Gary Wang was a co-founder of FTX while Caroline Ellison served as the Chief Executive Officer of Alameda Research. Both of them are said to be cooperating with investigators and according to the DoJ, chances are that more developments like this are bound to show face in the near future.</p>
<p>“As I said last week, this investigation is ongoing and moving very quickly. I also said last week&#8217;s announcement would not be our last and let me be clear once again, neither is today&#8217;s,” said United States Attorney for the Southern District of New York (SDNY) Damian Williams, adding, “I&#8217;m announcing that SDNY has filed charges against Caroline Ellison [&#8230;] and Gary Wang [&#8230;] in connection with their roles in the frauds that contributed to FTX&#8217;s collapse. Both Ms. Ellison and Mr. Wang have pleaded guilty to those charges and both are cooperating with the SDNY.”</p>
<p>Since the implosion of FTX and the filing for bankruptcy, authorities in the Bahamas have been in charge of the case until <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-founder-us-extradition/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SBF signed extradition papers</a> earlier this week. Speaking to the Press, Attorney Williams confirmed that Sam Bankman-Fried is already in the custody of the Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI).</p>
<p>According to him, SBF is on his way back to the United States and he will be moved to the SDNY where an arrangement will be made for him to appear before a judge as soon as possible.</p>
<h2>Charges Levied on Caroline Ellison and Gary Wang in Relation to the FTX Case</h2>
<p>For their complicit role in how FTX went under, Federal prosecutors have <a href="https://www.sec.gov/news/press-release/2022-234" target="_blank" rel="noopener">filed a separate action</a> against the duo for participating in the &#8220;multiyear scheme to defraud equity investors in FTX.” The prosecutors are also poking their noses into other entities that might have a hand in the overall implosion of the trading platform.</p>
<p>&#8220;As part of their deception, we allege that Caroline Ellison and Sam Bankman-Fried schemed to manipulate the price of FTT, an exchange crypto security token that was integral to FTX, to prop up the value of their house of cards,&#8221; said SEC Chair Gary Gensler. &#8220;We further allege that Ms. Ellison and Mr. Wang played an active role in a scheme to misuse FTX customer assets to prop up Alameda and to post collateral for margin trading…”</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the bankruptcy proceedings of FTX Exchange are still ongoing, and the latest push from John Ray III is to <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-sell-4-subsidiaries/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">sell off some of the liquid offshoots</a> of the trading platform like LedgerX, FTX Europe, FTX Japan, and Embed Technologies.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ankr-former-employee-exploit/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ellison-wang-guilty-ftx/">Caroline Ellison and Gary Wang Plead Guilty in Ongoing FTX Investigation</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ellison-wang-guilty-ftx/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ankr Reveals Former Employee behind $5M Protocol Exploit, Looks to Beef Up Network Security</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ankr-former-employee-exploit/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ankr-former-employee-exploit/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 10:15:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ankr]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bnb]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=230269</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ankr-former-employee-exploit/">Ankr Reveals Former Employee behind $5M Protocol Exploit, Looks to Beef Up Network Security</a></p>
<p>Ankr announced that it has made sweeping changes to its security outlook following a protocol exploit by an ex-employee. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ankr-former-employee-exploit/">Ankr Reveals Former Employee behind $5M Protocol Exploit, Looks to Beef Up Network Security</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ankr-former-employee-exploit/">Ankr Reveals Former Employee behind $5M Protocol Exploit, Looks to Beef Up Network Security</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-decentralized-finance-defi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">DeFi</a> protocol Ankr has ascribed the recent malicious $5 million exploit it suffered to a former employee. The platform has stated that it would shore up its defenses to avert similar recurrences and that it has embarked on a recovery plan for affected users.</p>
<p>In a <a href="https://www.ankr.com/blog/after-action-report-our-findings-from-abnbc-token-exploit/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">blog post</a> from two days ago, the company explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>“A former team member (who is no longer with Ankr) acted maliciously to conduct a combination of a social engineering and supply chain attack, inserting a malicious code package that was able to compromise our private key once a legitimate update was made.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Ankr vowed to prosecute the ex-employee, revealing that it is already working with relevant authorities. In addition, the DeFi protocol said that it is working on beefing up security measures – including HR processes and safety measures.</p>
<h2>Ankr Details Ex-Employee Exploit</h2>
<p>Ankr also detailed how the infrastructure hack took place in the blog post. According to the company, the former employee instituted the supply chain assault by inputting a malicious code into future protocol updates. The package of future updates serves the team’s internal software. The malicious code created a security vulnerability in the Ankr protocol upon the update of said software. The attacker could then exploit this breach and steal the team’s deployer key from Ankr’s servers.</p>
<p>Following the attack, the perpetrator converted the minted ill-gotten gains for Binance Coin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/binance-coin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BNB</a>) before funneling them through crypto mixer Tornado Cash. The hacker then exchanged the BNB tokens for 5 million USDC.</p>
<p>Addressing the impact of the network hack and how it influences subsequent operational decisions, Ankr offered:</p>
<blockquote><p>“The exploit was possible partly because there was a single point of failure in our developer key. We will now implement multi-sig authentication for updates that will require signoff from all key custodians during time-restricted intervals, making a future attack of this type extremely difficult, if not impossible.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Ankr further explained that the implementation plans would enhance security for its new ankrBNB contract. The distributed node service operator added that using multi-sig authentication would secure all Ankr tokens.</p>
<h2>Ankr Makes Sweeping Changes in HR Practices</h2>
<p>Ankr also looks to improve its human resource practices, including “escalated” background checks for all staff. The company stressed that this practice would be holistic, thorough, and even extend to remote employees. Furthermore, Ankr stated that in the future, it would make sensitive data only accessible to workers who need it. In addition, the DeFi network also intends to implement a new notification system that alerts quickly in case of a breach.</p>
<h2>Recovery</h2>
<p>Following the exploit, Ankr has taken several measures to compensate users to “the full extent of their losses”. This agenda included deploying an Advanced API to locate every aBNBc holder within 10 seconds.</p>
<p>Reimbursement took place via airdropped ankrBNB and BNB tokens to all affected parties.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-thor-securities-ico-2018/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ankr-former-employee-exploit/">Ankr Reveals Former Employee behind $5M Protocol Exploit, Looks to Beef Up Network Security</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ankr-former-employee-exploit/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>SEC Charges Thor Technologies for Selling Unregistered Securities Thor Tokens in $2.6M ICO in 2018</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-thor-securities-ico-2018/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-thor-securities-ico-2018/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 09:33:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[thor]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[thor technologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[thor token]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=230260</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-thor-securities-ico-2018/">SEC Charges Thor Technologies for Selling Unregistered Securities Thor Tokens in $2.6M ICO in 2018</a></p>
<p>According to the SEC, Thor Technologies and its officials defrauded 1,600 investors out of which 200 of them were from the United States.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-thor-securities-ico-2018/">SEC Charges Thor Technologies for Selling Unregistered Securities Thor Tokens in $2.6M ICO in 2018</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-thor-securities-ico-2018/">SEC Charges Thor Technologies for Selling Unregistered Securities Thor Tokens in $2.6M ICO in 2018</a></p>
<p>The United States Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) under the leadership of Gary Gensler continues to hunt for cryptocurrency projects &#8211; including the failed Thor Technologies protocol &#8211;  accused of selling unregistered securities. According to SEC’s complaints filed on Wednesday, December 21, in the US District Court of San Francisco, Thor Technologies claimed it would “develop a software platform for ‘gig economy’ companies and workers”. However, the said platform was never completed.</p>
<h2>SEC vs Thor Technologies</h2>
<p>Notably, the SEC has scrutinized cryptocurrency exchanges for the 2018 ICO boom market. Back in June this year, the SEC announced that it was looking into <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a>’s 2017 Initial Coin Offerings (ICO).</p>
<p>According to the SEC, Thor Technologies defrauded 1,600 investors out of which 200 of them were from the United States.</p>
<p>“Thor marketed the Thor Tokens to investors who reasonably viewed the Thor Tokens as an investment vehicle that might appreciate in value based on Thor’s and Chin’s managerial and entrepreneurial efforts in developing the gig economy software platform,” the SEC noted.</p>
<p>In addition to charging the company, the SEC also charged David Chin, Thor&#8217;s co-founder and CEO, and Matthew Moravec, Thor&#8217;s co-founder and former CTO, for selling unregistered securities.</p>
<p>According to the SEC, Moravec has agreed to settle for a judgment against him imposing permanent and conduct-based injunctions, including a prohibition for three years from participating in any offering of a crypto asset security. Additionally, the settlement ordered him to remit $407,103, prejudgment interest of $72,209.45, and a civil penalty of $95,000. However, the settlement is subject to court approval.</p>
<h2>SEC Dismantles Crypto’s Gray Area</h2>
<p>The cryptocurrency market has attracted worldwide traders seeking huge profits with little investment. Furthermore, the rise of meme coins is a clear testament to greed in the industry. With the fall of Terra Luna and FTX &#8211; a combined loss of over $60 billion &#8211; the SEC has increased its manpower to scrutinize the crypto market.</p>
<p>To the surprise of many, the SEC recently won the LBRY Inc. battle on November 7, after the Judge deemed LBC tokens as unregistered severities.</p>
<p>Consequently, LBRY company sees no future hope of succeeding after losing the battle to SEC.</p>
<p>“We will likely be dead in the near future. We expect the LBRY mission to continue, but the company itself has been killed by legal and SEC debts,” the company <a href="https://decrypt.co/116081/lbry-killed-battle-with-sec" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">noted</a>.</p>
<p>As 2023 draws near, all eyes are on the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ripple-labs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ripple</a> vs SEC case, which will have a huge impact on the entire industry. Moreover, twelve crypto companies, including <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase Global Inc</a> (NASDAQ: COIN), have joined the Ripple vs SEC lawsuit via amici briefs.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-vasp-license-ireland/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-thor-securities-ico-2018/">SEC Charges Thor Technologies for Selling Unregistered Securities Thor Tokens in $2.6M ICO in 2018</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-thor-securities-ico-2018/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>