<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 10:10:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>OpenSea Announces New Trading Feature Dubbed Deals</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/opensea-trading-feature-deals/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/opensea-trading-feature-deals/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 10:10:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[opensea]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=263993</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/opensea-trading-feature-deals/">OpenSea Announces New Trading Feature Dubbed Deals</a></p>
<p>The OpenSea Deals feature is powered by Seaport protocol to enable P2P NFT trading at scale and securely.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/opensea-trading-feature-deals/">OpenSea Announces New Trading Feature Dubbed Deals</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/opensea-trading-feature-deals/">OpenSea Announces New Trading Feature Dubbed Deals</a></p>
<p>The NFT trading community on OpenSea now will have a new feature to enable P2P trading dubbed Deals. With the new trading feature, the OpenSea NFT trading community can offer a combo of digital artworks and sweeten the deal with Wrapped Ethers (WETH). The NFT marketplace announced that users no longer need to use sketchy DMs and websites to trade their digital artworks since OpenSea Deals provides a seamless platform.</p>
<p>Notably, the OpenSea Deals feature is powered by the Seaport protocol, which was introduced earlier last year. The Seaport protocol is a web3 marketplace project backed by OpenSea that is used for safely and efficiently buying and selling <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NFTs</a>. Moreover, the Seaport protocol uses open-source core smart contracts, which entail different items including <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ETH</a>, ERC20, ERC721,  and ERC1155.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="474" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Introducing Deals: offer your NFTs for theirs, securely on OpenSea.</p>
<p>👉 <a href="https://t.co/bTciJLUWDK">https://t.co/bTciJLUWDK</a> <a href="https://t.co/KR2MLbi7jh">pic.twitter.com/KR2MLbi7jh</a></p>
<p>&mdash; OpenSea (@opensea) <a href="https://twitter.com/opensea/status/1682077991029932032?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 20, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>With the Make a Deal OpenSea feature, users can offer one or more of their NFTs in return for another user’s NFTs. However, the user must first have a wallet address, and an ENS name or basically an OpenSea username for the person intended to make a deal with.</p>
<p>“Similar to Offers, the user accepting the Deal will pay gas. At this time, Deals transactions won’t include the OpenSea fee or any creator earnings. ERC-721 NFTs from badged collections that are visible in a user’s profile (not hidden) are eligible for Deals,” OpenSea <a href="https://support.opensea.io/hc/en-us/articles/18477733878803?_gl=1%2Aotc1ih%2A_ga%2AMzUyMzMwNDc1LjE2ODk5MTg4Mzk.%2A_ga_9VSBF2K4BX%2AMTY4OTkxODgzOS4xLjEuMTY4OTkyMDUxOC4wLjAuMA.." target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">noted</a>.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, OpenSea has been criticized for not being friendly to the community during the crypto bear market. According to Twitter user Aaron (@Aaronsage), the crypto industry currently needs value and not innovation. The Twitter user suggested that OpenSea could have easily launched a crypto token to give back to the community instead of announcing a trading platform since most people are holding their bags in anticipation of future bull rallies.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="474" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">&#8211; Disabling Creator Royalties<br />&#8211; OpenSea Pro<br />&#8211; NFT Trading</p>
<p>All things that this space doesn&#39;t CURRENTLY NEED</p>
<p>Yet, the braindead OpenSea team implemented them</p>
<p>&mdash; Aaron (@AaronSage) <a href="https://twitter.com/AaronSage/status/1682138205720829952?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 20, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2>OpenSea and Its Market Position</h2>
<p>The OpnSea NFT marketplace has enjoyed significant dominance in the digital artwork industry since its official Launch a few years ago. For instance, OpenSea collected revenue of about $600 million in 2022 despite the cryptocurrency industry battling the bear market effects. Nonetheless, the NFT trading volume has significantly declined as more traders recently moved to more promising digital assets like meme coins.</p>
<p>Consequently, OpenSea has been forced to continue innovating in a bid to remain on top of the NFT marketplace competition.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the rising use of NFTs in different industries including the luxury sector to eliminate counterfeit products has given OpenSea huge growth prospects. Furthermore, the use of phygital by different blockchains including Shiba Inu, and VeChain has increased the overall NFT traded volume. Additionally, the exponential growth of the metaverse and GameFi industry has given the NFT market more utility away from mere speculation.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sam-bankman-fried-ftx-attorneys/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/opensea-trading-feature-deals/">OpenSea Announces New Trading Feature Dubbed Deals</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/opensea-trading-feature-deals/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sam Bankman-Fried Faces Legal Action from FTX Attorneys</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sam-bankman-fried-ftx-attorneys/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sam-bankman-fried-ftx-attorneys/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 10:08:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sam bankman-fried]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=263985</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sam-bankman-fried-ftx-attorneys/">Sam Bankman-Fried Faces Legal Action from FTX Attorneys</a></p>
<p>Sam Bankman-Fried faces a slew of criminal allegations, including fraud, bribery, and campaign finance offenses.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sam-bankman-fried-ftx-attorneys/">Sam Bankman-Fried Faces Legal Action from FTX Attorneys</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sam-bankman-fried-ftx-attorneys/">Sam Bankman-Fried Faces Legal Action from FTX Attorneys</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/sam-bankman-fried/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Sam Bankman-Fried</a>, the former CEO of the now-defunct <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/">FTX</a> crypto exchange is embroiled in a legal battle with his former company’s lawyers.</p>
<p>The attorneys have <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/07/20/sam-bankman-fried-is-paying-defense-lawyers-with-ftx-funds-lawsuit.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reportedly</a> filed a lawsuit in Delaware bankruptcy court, accusing Bankman-Fried and members of his leadership team of stealing hundreds of millions of dollars from FTX and its sister hedge fund, Alameda Research.</p>
<h2>The $10 Million Gift Scandal</h2>
<p>The focal point of the legal battle lies in a transaction involving a substantial $10 million gift to Sam Bankman-Fried’s father, Joe Bankman. While gifting money to family members is not unlawful, this significant transaction, which allegedly occurred around January 2022 has sparked concerns.</p>
<p>FTX attorneys contend that the $10 million gift was essentially a ruse to divert company funds into the personal coffers of the former CEO’s family. The complaint contends that these funds are now being used to pay for Bankman-Fried’s criminal defense expenses, suggesting potential links to criminal activities related to the alleged misappropriation of funds.</p>
<p>In light of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-exchange-files-for-bankruptcy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX&#8217;s bankruptcy</a>, the lawyers for the exchange are determined to recover as much money as possible for the company&#8217;s creditors and investors. The allegations of embezzlement against Bankman-Fried and his leadership team are central to this mission.</p>
<p>Despite mounting questions, a representative for Bankman-Fried has opted not to comment on the matter, leaving stakeholders and the crypto community searching for answers. Should the court find them guilty of these financial misdeeds, they may be ordered to repay the misappropriated funds, along with facing potential fines and penalties.</p>
<h2>The Rise and Fall of FTX</h2>
<p>FTX, founded in 2019 by Sam Bankman-Fried and Gary Wang, quickly gained recognition as a pioneering crypto exchange. Bankman-Fried’s background in quantitative trading and his reputation as a savvy crypto investor played a significant role in propelling FTX to prominence.</p>
<p>The exchange stood out for its diverse offerings, including perpetual futures contracts, options trading, and other innovative financial products. FTX&#8217;s successful partnerships with renowned sports teams, celebrities, and institutions further solidified its position in the competitive crypto market.</p>
<p>However, the exchange’s success was short-lived, as liquidity dried up and customer withdrawal demands exceeded the company’s capacity. These financial difficulties became insurmountable, prompting FTX to declare bankruptcy late last year.</p>
<p>Sam Bankman-Fried faces a slew of criminal allegations, including fraud, bribery, and campaign finance offenses. The allegations point to possible corporate wrongdoing, with Bankman-Fried reportedly engaging in acts that contributed to FTX’s financial instability.</p>
<p>Alongside Sam Bankman-Fried, FTX and Alameda executives Caroline Ellison, Gary Wang, and Nishad Singh are also named as co-defendants in the case. Meanwhile, Bankman-Fried has maintained his innocence throughout the legal proceedings and pleaded not guilty to all charges.</p>
<p>As the trial is expected to <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-criminal-charges-ftx-sbf/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">commence later this year</a>, the industry will closely monitor the evidence presented and the arguments put forth by both the prosecution and the defense.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-shut-down-crypto-lending/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sam-bankman-fried-ftx-attorneys/">Sam Bankman-Fried Faces Legal Action from FTX Attorneys</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sam-bankman-fried-ftx-attorneys/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase Moves to Shut Down Crypto Lending Program</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-shut-down-crypto-lending/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-shut-down-crypto-lending/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Babafemi Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 10:05:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase borrow]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase prime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=263846</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-shut-down-crypto-lending/">Coinbase Moves to Shut Down Crypto Lending Program</a></p>
<p>Loan holders will have to clear their outstanding loan balances until November 20, 2023.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-shut-down-crypto-lending/">Coinbase Moves to Shut Down Crypto Lending Program</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-shut-down-crypto-lending/">Coinbase Moves to Shut Down Crypto Lending Program</a></p>

<p>An unnamed source has announced that <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase</a> will end its lending program, Coinbase Borrow, over the next few months.</p>
<p>Coinbase Borrow, a program that allowed customers to receive fiat loans of up to $1 million, began in November 2021. According to its website, users could borrow as much as 40% of their Bitcoin holdings at an 8.7% annual interest rate.</p>
<p>However, in May, Coinbase <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-stop-bitcoin-borrow/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">announced</a> that it would no longer allow new loans to be taken. It noted that it took the decision after re-evaluating the product’s prospects. At the same time, it promised that existing loan customers would not be affected. </p>
<h2>Coinbase to Wind Down Its Lending Service in November</h2>
<p>With the current development, loan holders will have until November 20, 2023, to clear their outstanding loan balances. It is unclear how many users this will affect</p>
<p>According to the source,  they “have notified impacted loan holders and are taking extra measures to ensure a smooth transition for them”. This measure includes priority access to customer support through Coinbase One and a four-month loan repayment period.</p>
<p>While Coinbase remains unclear as to its reason, there are indications the shutdown of the product may have been due to low demand. Others suggest that the exchange is simply doubling down on its essentials after attracting scrutiny from the SEC. Recall that the regulator <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-sec-coinbase-unregistered-exchange/">warned</a> Coinbase it could face enforcement action for supposedly offering unregistered securities. Possible targets of the enforcement action are the exchange’s spot wallet service, Coinbase Prime, and its Coinbase wallet.</p>
<h2>Exchange Advocates Update of Financial System</h2>
<p>Meanwhile, the crypto exchange has <a href="https://www.coinbase.com/blog/how-embracing-regulation-and-compliance-protects-our-customers" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">issued</a> a call for a clearer regulatory framework for crypto in the United States. The company noted that 1 in 5 Americans held crypto while the industry was attracting more interest from institutional investors. A lack of regulation, it said, was pushing Americans towards “unregulated” foreign exchanges.</p>
<p>Coinbase noted that blockchain and crypto had the potential to revolutionize the financial system but the US must stop its regulation-by-enforcement approach. “It’s time to allow for a faster, more affordable, and more transparent system to exist &#8211; that’s the promise of crypto,” it said.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/elon-musk-governance-ventures/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-shut-down-crypto-lending/">Coinbase Moves to Shut Down Crypto Lending Program</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-shut-down-crypto-lending/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Elon Musk Expanding His Ventures, Facing Scrutiny Over Governance Issues</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/elon-musk-governance-ventures/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/elon-musk-governance-ventures/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Darya Rudz]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 10:02:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Editor's Choice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon musk ai]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon musk governance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon musk sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon musk xai]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tesla]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xAI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xAI artificial intelligence]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=263940</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/elon-musk-governance-ventures/">Elon Musk Expanding His Ventures, Facing Scrutiny Over Governance Issues</a></p>
<p>Investors are wondering if there will be a devaluation of the Tesla giant since Elon Musk's initiatives might lead to competition between the EV maker and new ventures.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/elon-musk-governance-ventures/">Elon Musk Expanding His Ventures, Facing Scrutiny Over Governance Issues</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/elon-musk-governance-ventures/">Elon Musk Expanding His Ventures, Facing Scrutiny Over Governance Issues</a></p>
<p>Investors are raising concerns over the multiplying ventures of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/elon-musk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Elon Musk</a>. Recently, the billionaire <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/elon-musk-ai-company-xai/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">announced</a> the launch of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/xai/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">xAI</a> – a new company that focuses on <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/technology/artificial-intelligence-news/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">artificial intelligence</a> (AI) research and development. As a result, there is a risk of competition between <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/tesla/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tesla Inc</a> (NASDAQ: TSLA) and the new enterprise. Investors are wondering if there will be a devaluation of the EV giant. However, Elon Musk believes that xAI and its focus on AI would bring some value to Tesla.</p>
<p>Elon Musk <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/07/20/why-tesla-investors-should-care-about-elon-musks-multiplying-ventures.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">stated</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;There were just some of the world’s best AI engineers and scientists that were willing to join a startup but they were not willing to join a large, sort of relatively established company like Tesla. So I was like, OK well, better it’s a startup that I run than they go work somewhere else. That’s kind of the genesis of xAI.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Musk&#8217;s new xAI company aims to &#8220;understand reality&#8221; without any other details or explanation. It is also looking for ways to build an AI that is &#8220;truth-seeking&#8221; and that can &#8220;understand the nature of the universe&#8221;. The company is still in the early stages of bringing its plans to life, but is has already had an impact on competition and innovation in the field. It will definitely lead to advancements in AI technologies and applications, benefiting various industries. Besides, the launch of xAI will result in exploring alternative research directions and approaches.</p>
<p>As Musk has stated, xAI will compete with Google Bard and OpenAI’s ChatGPT in the future. Besides, xAI is planning to collaborate with Tesla on software and silicon alike.</p>
<h2>Governance Issues</h2>
<p>Last week, Senator Elizabeth Warren called the US Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) for investigating Tesla and its board of directors to determine if they violated securities laws after Elon Musk took over Twitter. As Elizabeth Warren stated in a letter to SEC, Musk&#8217;s responsibilities &#8220;have raised concerns about conflicts of interest, misappropriation of corporate assets, and other negative impacts to Tesla shareholders&#8221;. In particular, Warren found funneling Tesla resources into Musk’s Twitter takeover, conflicts of interest regarding advertising from other car companies, and possible labor law violations when conducting transfers of some Tesla employees to Twitter. Besides, Tesla’s board had not informed shareholders properly about the ways that the two companies have worked together, or might work together.</p>
<p>Back in May, Tesla face a similar issue, when a group of 17 investors who hold a total of $1.5 billion of Tesla stock raised concern that Tesla&#8217;s board of directors was &#8220;failing to adequately represent the interests of Tesla&#8217;s shareholders&#8221;. At that time, pension funds and other institutional investors urged Tesla&#8217;s board to improve corporate governance and oversee Elon Musk&#8217;s actions. Seems that things have not really improved since then, therefore, SEC Chair Gary Gensler got a letter from Elizabeth Warren.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ceo-caroline-ellison-alameda-research/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/elon-musk-governance-ventures/">Elon Musk Expanding His Ventures, Facing Scrutiny Over Governance Issues</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/elon-musk-governance-ventures/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Former CEO Caroline Ellison Reportedly Felt Ill-Suited to Run Alameda Research</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ceo-caroline-ellison-alameda-research/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ceo-caroline-ellison-alameda-research/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mercy Tukiya Mutanya]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 09:58:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alameda research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Caroline Ellison]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sam bankman-fried]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=263970</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ceo-caroline-ellison-alameda-research/">Former CEO Caroline Ellison Reportedly Felt Ill-Suited to Run Alameda Research</a></p>
<p>New FTX CEO John J Ray has stated that Alameda had access to FTX customer assets and could use them for its own purposes without proper oversight.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ceo-caroline-ellison-alameda-research/">Former CEO Caroline Ellison Reportedly Felt Ill-Suited to Run Alameda Research</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ceo-caroline-ellison-alameda-research/">Former CEO Caroline Ellison Reportedly Felt Ill-Suited to Run Alameda Research</a></p>
<p>Former Alameda  Research CEO Caroline Ellison has revealed that she did not feel well suited to leading the hedge fund. This is according to a Thursday <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2023/07/20/technology/ftx-caroline-ellison-bankman-fried.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">New York Post article</a> citing the former exec’s diary. Ellison was in December charged with fraud in relation to the November collapse of Alameda’s sister company <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a> crypto exchange.</p>
<p>Ellison, who was romantically linked to then FTX CEO Sam Bankman-Fried, has been named a key witness in the former’s October trial. She was hand-picked by Bankman-Fried, known in crypto circles as SBF, to run the hedge fund. According to the report, the day that the leading crypto exchange collapsed, Ellison made a diary entry that said it “feels great”. Ellison wrote:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Running Alameda doesn’t feel like something I’m that comparatively advantaged at or well suited to do.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Ellison’s Alameda Research was implicated in the FTX collapse because of the intermingling of funds between the companies. New FTX CEO John J Ray has stated that Alameda had access to FTX customer assets and could use them for its own purposes without proper oversight. According to Ray, whose previous experience includes helping manage Enron after the energy trader&#8217;s 2001 bankruptcy –  FTX’s failure was caused by “a very small group of grossly inexperienced and unsophisticated individuals”.</p>
<h2>FTX Sues Former  Executives in Bid to Recoup $1 Billion</h2>
<p>Meanwhile, the bankrupt crypto exchange is suing former executives in a bid to recover $1 billion that they allegedly misappropriated. The complaint, filed in Delaware bankruptcy court names <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/sam-bankman-fried/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Sam Bankman-Fried</a>, Caroline Ellison, former FTX technology chief Zixiao &#8220;Gary&#8221; Wang, and former FTX engineering director Nishad Singh. The suit alleges that the group used company funds to bankroll luxury accommodations, political donations, speculative investments, and other &#8220;pet projects&#8221;, all the while committing &#8220;one of the largest financial frauds in history&#8221;.</p>
<p>SBF is facing several criminal charges and has pleaded not guilty while Ellison, Wang, and Singh have pleaded guilty and agreed to assist prosecutors. According to the complaint by FTX, the illicit transfers include over $750 million of equity that FTX and SBF-controlled West Realm Shires awarded &#8220;without receiving any value in exchange&#8221;. A further $546 million was used by SBF and Wang to buy Robinhood Markets share while Ellison paid herself bonuses amounting to $28.8 million. The funds were allegedly misappropriated between February 2020 and November 2022. The complaint states that according to the US bankruptcy code, the transfers can be undone.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/united-kingdom-crypto-firms-fca/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ceo-caroline-ellison-alameda-research/">Former CEO Caroline Ellison Reportedly Felt Ill-Suited to Run Alameda Research</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ceo-caroline-ellison-alameda-research/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>United Kingdom Wants Crypto Firms to Be More Responsible as FCA Seeks More Regulatory Powers</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/united-kingdom-crypto-firms-fca/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/united-kingdom-crypto-firms-fca/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 09:53:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fca]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fca uk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United Kingdom]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=263948</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/united-kingdom-crypto-firms-fca/">United Kingdom Wants Crypto Firms to Be More Responsible as FCA Seeks More Regulatory Powers</a></p>
<p>The FCA has been continuosly warning firms that are linked with crypto to be cautious in their business dealings.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/united-kingdom-crypto-firms-fca/">United Kingdom Wants Crypto Firms to Be More Responsible as FCA Seeks More Regulatory Powers</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/united-kingdom-crypto-firms-fca/">United Kingdom Wants Crypto Firms to Be More Responsible as FCA Seeks More Regulatory Powers</a></p>
<p>The United Kingdom&#8217;s Financial Conduct Authority (FCA) is currently formulating a new set of requirements for crypto-based firms in the region. According to the regulator, it might no longer suffice that a firm has cleared anti-money laundering requirements and obtained an operational license.</p>
<p>So, to this end, the FCA is seeking to create new rules that will foster prudence among crypto firms. The FCA revealed the plans in its annual <a href="https://www.fca.org.uk/news/press-releases/financial-watchdog-cracks-down-problem-firms-and-supports-struggling-borrowers" target="_blank" rel="noopener">report</a> which was published Thursday.</p>
<p>However, the FCA also noted that the new prudential rules it intends to float will only come to light when the Treasury and Parliament eventually bring those activities under its regulatory authority.</p>
<p>As of publication, what timeline the FCA will receive this regulatory power remains unclear.</p>
<h2>United Kingdom Eyes Becoming a Global Crypto Hub</h2>
<p>Meanwhile, it is worth mentioning that the FCA has already put a <a href="https://www.fca.org.uk/publications/multi-firm-reviews/ifpr-implementation-observations#:~:text=The%20Investment%20Firms%20Prudential%20Regime%20(IFPR)%20is%20the%20new%20prudential,began%20on%201%20January%202022" target="_blank" rel="noopener">prudential regime</a> in place for investment firms. That includes asset managers, trading firms, and even fund managers spread across the United Kingdom.</p>
<p>The regime requires first that firms make certain that they have enough capital. Then, they identify risks to their business and show proof of adequate reserves to mitigate harm.</p>
<p>For what it&#8217;s worth, the FCA has been warning firms that are linked with crypto to be cautious in their business dealings. That includes those with direct or indirect exposure to crypto. And as a fact, the regulator <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fca-crypto-financial-scam-uk/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">issued</a> a warning statement to such firms last year, asking them to &#8220;have appropriate systems and controls to counter the risk of being misused for financial crime&#8221;.</p>
<p>Interestingly, the FCA has just been saddled with some new regulatory powers under a recently passed financial markets bill. And as it stands, the regulator might well be on the way to becoming the country&#8217;s key watchdog. That is as far as crypto is concerned.</p>
<p>More importantly, the various formulations will also help the country to achieve its aim of becoming a global crypto hub.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-account-uniswap-scam/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/united-kingdom-crypto-firms-fca/">United Kingdom Wants Crypto Firms to Be More Responsible as FCA Seeks More Regulatory Powers</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/united-kingdom-crypto-firms-fca/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Twitter Account of Uniswap Founder Hayden Adams Faces Breach, Promotes Scam</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-account-uniswap-scam/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-account-uniswap-scam/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 09:48:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cybersecurity News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[twitter]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[uni]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[uniswap]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=263937</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-account-uniswap-scam/">Twitter Account of Uniswap Founder Hayden Adams Faces Breach, Promotes Scam</a></p>
<p>The hackers posted malicious links from Adams's Twitter account driving people to scam websites. The Uniswap co-founder recently confirmed that the account is restored for now. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-account-uniswap-scam/">Twitter Account of Uniswap Founder Hayden Adams Faces Breach, Promotes Scam</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-account-uniswap-scam/">Twitter Account of Uniswap Founder Hayden Adams Faces Breach, Promotes Scam</a></p>
<p>Despite strong growth and maturity, hacks and theft incidents continue to plague the crypto industry. On Thursday, July 20, the crypto community found that the Twitter account of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/uniswap/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Uniswap</a> co-founder Hayden Adams has faced a major breach.</p>
<p>The hackers made several tweets from the account driving users to all scammy websites. On July 20, the &#8220;Web3 Security Alerts&#8221; channel on Telegram informed its followers about the compromise of Adams&#8217;s Twitter account. The compromised account of Uniswap&#8217;s founder and CEO, with over 254,000 followers, posted a false tweet claiming that the platform&#8217;s Permit2 contract had been impacted by an unknown exploit, putting users&#8217; tokens at risk. The tweet included a malicious link, encouraging people to click on it.</p>
<p>The initial scam tweet was taken down shortly after being posted, but several similar ones followed. Web3 Security Alerts revealed that Adams&#8217; accounts with MetaMask and Coinbase Wallet remain blocked.</p>
<p>Also, the message offering free $UNI tokens doesn&#8217;t appear anymore. However, the account continued to post tweets with scam links as late as 4:43 p.m. in New York.</p>
<h2>Uniswap Labs Issues Statement, Adams&#8217;s Twitter Account Restored</h2>
<p>Hours later, Uniswap Labs issued a statement confirming the hack of Hayden Adams&#8217;s account. It <a href="https://twitter.com/Uniswap/status/1682130018225225728" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">noted</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;@haydenzadams’ Twitter account has been hacked. Please do not click on any links. There is no giveaway, airdrop, or bounty. The Protocol has not been hacked or exploited. We will let you know when the issue is resolved.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>However, a few hours back, Haydem Adams stated that they have managed to restore the account again. &#8220;In control of my Twitter again. Appreciate everyone who helped out tonight, and the effort people put in to help with takedowns, warnings, etc,&#8221; he <a href="https://twitter.com/haydenzadams/status/1682198527236096000" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">wrote</a>.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s not new for scammers to use social media to trick people into giving away their cryptocurrency or money. Twitter&#8217;s Elon Musk announced on July 1 that they would limit the number of posts users can read each day to catch and stop fake accounts and bad actors.</p>
<p>Recently, Meta launched its new app Instagram Threads to compete with Twitter. Within days, the app gained over 100 million users. However, scammers have already started promoting fake nonfungible token projects and pretending to be other well-known crypto Twitter users.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-house-republicans-crypto-bill/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-account-uniswap-scam/">Twitter Account of Uniswap Founder Hayden Adams Faces Breach, Promotes Scam</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-account-uniswap-scam/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>US House Republicans Release New Crypto Oversight Bill for Investor Protection</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-house-republicans-crypto-bill/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-house-republicans-crypto-bill/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 09:37:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cftc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=263944</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-house-republicans-crypto-bill/">US House Republicans Release New Crypto Oversight Bill for Investor Protection</a></p>
<p>The bill, initially drafted in early June, aims to create a regulatory framework for crypto exchanges to register with the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-house-republicans-crypto-bill/">US House Republicans Release New Crypto Oversight Bill for Investor Protection</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-house-republicans-crypto-bill/">US House Republicans Release New Crypto Oversight Bill for Investor Protection</a></p>
<p>Over the last few months, US lawmakers have been actively working to form a clear regulatory framework in the country. On Thursday, July 20, the US House of Republicans introduced a new cryptocurrency oversight bill with the goal of having a regulatory framework for investor protection in the crypto industry.</p>
<p>The bill is part of several others trying to establish clear rules for digital assets. It comes at a time when the unclear regulations and aggressive actions from authorities are making some crypto businesses think about leaving the US. Also, crypto startups are hesitant to start their operations due to the lack of regulatory clarity. In a statement on Thursday, Chairman of the House Committee on Agriculture Rep. Glenn “GT” Thompson (R-Pa.) <a href="https://agriculture.house.gov/news/documentsingle.aspx?DocumentID=7672" target="_blank" rel="noopener">said</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Today&#8217;s introduction of the Financial Innovation and Technology for the 21st Century Act marks a significant milestone in the House Committees on Agriculture and Financial Services efforts to establish a much-needed regulatory framework that protects consumers and investors and fosters American leadership in the digital asset space.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The bill, initially drafted in early June, aims to create a regulatory framework for crypto exchanges to register with the US Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>). It would allow these exchanges to trade digital securities, commodities, and stablecoins all in one place.</p>
<p>“The crypto industry wants clarity and our collaborative bill gives both the CFTC and SEC a seat at the table. Our bill establishes clear principles to ensure financial security and certainty as digital asset developers continue to innovate,” said Dusty Johnson (R-S.D.) in the statement.</p>
<h2>Industry Experts Express Concern Over Revised Bill</h2>
<p>Although the Republican lawmakers have made an effort to push the crypto regulatory bill, some industry experts have shared their concerns. In the <a href="https://agriculture.house.gov/uploadedfiles/fit_for_the_21st_century_act_of_2023.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener">revised bill</a> on page 10, traditional securities like stocks, bonds, &#8220;transferable shares&#8221;, &#8220;certificates of interest or participation in any profit-sharing agreement&#8221;, and similar assets are excluded from the definition of &#8220;digital assets&#8221;.</p>
<p>According to Gabriel Shapiro, Delphi Labs&#8217; general counsel, a recent change in the bill significantly impacts its value proposition and could reintroduce ambiguity. This change could lead to increased regulation for various assets in the decentralized finance (DeFi) market, including Compound&#8217;s cTokens and Liquid Collective&#8217;s Liquid Staking Tokens, even if they are not currently regulated.</p>
<p>&#8220;The SEC can still go on the warpath&#8230;all they have to do is argue that a token is a &#8216;transferable share&#8217; &#8216;a profit interest&#8217; etc.,&#8221; he warned.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-us-unemployment-fed/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-house-republicans-crypto-bill/">US House Republicans Release New Crypto Oversight Bill for Investor Protection</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-house-republicans-crypto-bill/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Barely Scathed by High Impact of US Unemployment Claims as Fed Continues with Monetary Tightening Policies</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-us-unemployment-fed/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-us-unemployment-fed/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 08:36:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blackrock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fednow]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=263938</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-us-unemployment-fed/">Bitcoin Barely Scathed by High Impact of US Unemployment Claims as Fed Continues with Monetary Tightening Policies</a></p>
<p>Bitcoin dropped by just around 1 percent to trade around $29.9k on Friday despite the US unemployment claims coming in lower than expected.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-us-unemployment-fed/">Bitcoin Barely Scathed by High Impact of US Unemployment Claims as Fed Continues with Monetary Tightening Policies</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-us-unemployment-fed/">Bitcoin Barely Scathed by High Impact of US Unemployment Claims as Fed Continues with Monetary Tightening Policies</a></p>
<p>The Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a>) market was arguably less concerned with the high-impact news from the United States Department of Labor regarding the unemployment claims on Thursday. Notably, the United States unemployment claims came in at 228k, which was lower than the previous and forecasted by a significant margin. As the US dollar currency index (DXY) showed some slight improvement compared to other global currencies, Bitcoin price too was slightly impacted by dropping about 1 percent in the past 24 hours. However, experts believe the Bitcoin market is facing a bigger challenge from the rising altcoin market, especially after the SEC vs Ripple judgment ruling.</p>
<h2>Impact of US Unemployment Claims on Bitcoin and Altcoin Market</h2>
<p>Moreover, the TOTAL3 market cap, which represents altcoins excluding <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a>, had its macro wedge breakout confirmed in the past few days. Essentially, crypto cash flow is expected to move from Bitcoin and Ethereum to lower and medium-cap altcoins in the coming weeks.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the Fed&#8217;s policies in fighting high inflation seem to be playing out in favor of the dollar. Economists highly anticipated the Fed raising the interest rates by 25 basis points on July 26 in a bid to further fight inflation.</p>
<p>In a bid to counter the rise of digital assets and the high demand from institutional investors, the United States Federal Reserve announced the launch of FedNow, an instant payment service. Reportedly, more than 35 banks have enlisted to the FedNow services with thousands more expected to join later.</p>
<p>“Over time, as more banks choose to use this new tool, the benefits to individuals and businesses will include enabling a person to immediately receive a paycheck, or a company to instantly access funds when an invoice is paid,” Fed Chair Jerome Powell <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/07/20/fed-officially-launches-new-fednow-instant-payments-service.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Performance</h2>
<p>The Bitcoin market continued to flex its muscles against most global assets amid heightened demand from institutional investors. In the past few weeks, several fund managers led by <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/blackrock/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BlackRock Inc</a> (NYSE: BLK), and Valkyrie, have filed for a Bitcoin ETF, with the SEC expected to either approve, deny, or delay one filed by Cathie Wood’s Ark Invest. In a recent interview, BlackRock CEO of BlackRock described Bitcoin as digitizing gold and its mainstream adoption is imminent.</p>
<p>Notably, the Bitcoin market capitalization is about $580 billion compared to that of gold at nearly $11 trillion. Interestingly, US presidential candidate Robert F. Kennedy, Jr has promised to back the greenback with Bitcoin if elected for the highest office next year. Notably, Kennedy has also indicated that the digital dollar will not happen under his watch.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the cryptocurrency market remains an integral part of the investment industry not only in the United States but around the world.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/johnson-johnson-q2-2023-earnings/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-us-unemployment-fed/">Bitcoin Barely Scathed by High Impact of US Unemployment Claims as Fed Continues with Monetary Tightening Policies</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-us-unemployment-fed/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Johnson &amp; Johnson Reports Better than Expected Q2 2023 Earnings, JNJ Shares Up Slightly</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/johnson-johnson-q2-2023-earnings/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/johnson-johnson-q2-2023-earnings/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 15:03:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wall Street]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jnj]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jnj stock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[johnson & johnson stock]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=263919</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/johnson-johnson-q2-2023-earnings/">Johnson &#038; Johnson Reports Better than Expected Q2 2023 Earnings, JNJ Shares Up Slightly</a></p>
<p>The pharmaceutical segment reported the highest sales with about $13.71 billion, followed by MedTech with a total sales of about $7.78 billion, and the remaining accrued from the consumer health segment.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/johnson-johnson-q2-2023-earnings/">Johnson &#038; Johnson Reports Better than Expected Q2 2023 Earnings, JNJ Shares Up Slightly</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/johnson-johnson-q2-2023-earnings/">Johnson &#038; Johnson Reports Better than Expected Q2 2023 Earnings, JNJ Shares Up Slightly</a></p>
<p>One of the oldest American pharmaceutical and consumer packaged goods companies, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/johnson-and-johnson/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Johnson &amp; Johnson</a> (NYSE: JNJ) announced its second quarter (Q2) 2023 earnings on July 20, which ostensibly beat Wall Street expectations. According to the company’s announcement, the second quarter sales grew by about 6.3 percent and the operational growth excluding the COVID-19 vaccine jumped by 8.9 percent. Meanwhile, the company’s Joaquin Duato, Chairman of the Board and Chief Executive Officer highlighted that the future is bright for its vast products, especially as it moves ahead to split its shares.</p>
<p>“We are entering the back half of the year from a position of strength with numerous catalysts, including becoming a two-sector company focused on Pharmaceutical and MedTech innovation,” Duato <a href="https://www.jnj.com/johnson-johnson-reports-q2-2023-results" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">noted</a>.</p>
<h2>Johnson &amp; Johnson Q2 2023 Financial Highlights</h2>
<p>During the second quarter of 2023, the company announced adjusted earnings per share of $2.80 compared to $2.62 expected by analysts surveyed by Refinitiv. Additionally, Johnson &amp; Johnson announced revenue of about $25.53 billion compared to the $24.62 billion expected by analysts surveyed by Refinitiv. Splitting the sales, the company announced that it collected about $13.44 billion from the United States market and the remaining $22 billion from the international market.</p>
<p>The pharmaceutical segment reported the highest sales with about $13.71 billion, followed by MedTech with a total sales of about $7.78 billion, and the remaining accrued from the consumer health segment. Although the company is facing several headwinds including some legal proceedings, it highlighted that the coming quarters could as well be profitable as the prior one.</p>
<p>As a result, the company announced that it will be increasing its 2023 full-year guidance midpoints for adjusted operational sales excluding the COVID-19 vaccine and the adjusted operating earnings per share. Notably, the company is forecasting its full-year sales to come in between $98.80 billion to $99.80 billion, which is about $1 billion higher than the guidance issued in April. Additionally, the company’s full-year earnings outlook is expected to come in between $10.70 to $10.80 per share, which is higher than the prior one issued in April between $10.60 to $10.70 per share.</p>
<p>Amid the legal litigations most centered on allegations that its pharmaceutical products are causing cancer to its users, the company has focused on splitting its pharma segment and MedTech segment for future growth prospects.</p>
<h2>Market Outlook</h2>
<p>The $413 billion valued company has been on the receiving end in the past two years. According to the latest stock market data, JNJ shares have dropped approximately 7.3 percent and 10 percent in the last year and YTD respectively. Nonetheless, 21 analysts are still optimistic about the company’s future performance having given the JNJ market an average rating of Over.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/american-airlines-outlook-2023/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/johnson-johnson-q2-2023-earnings/">Johnson &#038; Johnson Reports Better than Expected Q2 2023 Earnings, JNJ Shares Up Slightly</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/johnson-johnson-q2-2023-earnings/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4200 metric#misses=61 metric#hit-ratio=98.6 metric#bytes=1058464 metric#prefetches=198 metric#store-reads=45 metric#store-writes=18 metric#store-hits=219 metric#store-misses=22 metric#sql-queries=51 metric#ms-total=1657.77 metric#ms-cache=9.71 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.1566 metric#ms-cache-ratio=0.6 -->