<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
>

<channel>
	<title>CoinCu News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://coincu.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coincu.com</link>
	<description>Coin and Crypto Infomation Update</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 06:37:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/cropped-Screen-Shot-2022-05-31-at-14.56.39-32x32.png</url>
	<title>CoinCu News</title>
	<link>https://coincu.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>TOKEN2049 Singapore Set To Be World’s Largest Web3 Event With Over 10,000 Attendees </title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/208143-token2049-singapore-largest-web3-event/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Foxy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 06:36:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Releases]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[# Cryptocurrencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[#Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Asia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto event]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Event]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Token2049]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web3]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=208143</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[TOKEN2049 will take place from 13-14 September 2023 at Marina Bay Sands, ahead of the Formula 1 Singapore Grand Prix 2023 race weekend. <p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/208143-token2049-singapore-largest-web3-event/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>Not only Asia’s largest Web3 event, this year’s conference is expected to be the world’s largest of its kind</em></li>



<li><em>TOKEN2049 has already surpassed last year’s registration and sponsorship numbers with numbers steadily climbing ahead of September</em></li>



<li><em>Speaker highlights include prolific entrepreneur Balaji Srinivasan; Ethereum Co-Founder Joe Lubin; Galaxy Digital CEO Mike Novogratz</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>SINGAPORE — 6 June 2023 — <a href="https://www.asia.token2049.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">TOKEN2049</a>, Asia’s premier Web3 and crypto conference, has announced its first batch of high-profile title sponsors<em> </em>and headline speakers for its much-anticipated Singapore return. TOKEN2049 will take place from 13-14 September 2023 at <a href="https://www.marinabaysands.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Marina Bay Sands</a>, ahead of the <a href="https://www.formula1.com/en/racing/2023/Singapore.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Formula 1 Singapore Grand Prix 2023</a> race weekend.&nbsp;</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/TOKEN2049-SG_Banner_1.png"><img decoding="async" width="1024" height="577" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/TOKEN2049-SG_Banner_1-1024x577.png" alt="TOKEN2049 Singapore Set To Be World’s Largest Web3 Event With Over 10,000 Attendees " class="wp-image-208145" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/TOKEN2049-SG_Banner_1-1024x577.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/TOKEN2049-SG_Banner_1-300x169.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/TOKEN2049-SG_Banner_1-768x433.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/TOKEN2049-SG_Banner_1-1536x865.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/TOKEN2049-SG_Banner_1-2048x1154.png 2048w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/TOKEN2049-SG_Banner_1-750x423.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/TOKEN2049-SG_Banner_1-1140x642.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="TOKEN2049 Singapore Set To Be World’s Largest Web3 Event With Over 10,000 Attendees  1"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p><a href="https://coincu.com/192593-token2049-singapore-set-be-worlds-largest/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">TOKEN2049</a> is set to welcome over 10,000 attendees from over 3,500 companies, making it the largest event of its kind this year. With the conference taking place in Singapore once more, this speaks to the enduring importance of Asia as a driver of growth and vibrancy of innovation in the global digital asset ecosystem. Following the resounding success of its record-breaking Singapore 2022 event, TOKEN2049 will feature an expansive programme of over 300 side events and networking opportunities taking place from 11-17 September throughout the city-state.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Celebrating the event’s triumphant return to Singapore, <strong>Alex Fiskum, Co-Founder of TOKEN2049 </strong>said: “We’ve seen unprecedented traction and interest amid a record number of ticket registrations to date and confirmed speakers, sponsors and partners in our line-up. We expect TOKEN2049 Singapore to be the largest crypto event of the year, an unforgettable experience that will surpass our previous editions in terms of size, activity, and overall excitement.”</p>



<p>Gathering global industry leaders, top decision makers and innovators, new additions in the 2023 agenda include hacker houses, technical workshops, and NFT galleries among others. The 2023 edition of the conference has already surpassed last year’s attendance, sponsorship and speaker milestones, with numbers rapidly rising ahead of September.</p>



<p>This year’s agenda spans the ever-evolving regulatory landscape, the rise of AI, Web3 gaming, NFTs and the metaverse, DeFi, scalability, interoperability, and many more. The impressive speaker line-up includes Balaji Srinivasan, Founder, Investor and Author of The Network State; Joe Lubin, Co-Founder of Ethereum and Founder of ConsenSys; Stani Kulechov, Founder and CEO of Aave; Mike Novogratz, CEO of Galaxy Digital; Sandeep Nailwal, Co-Founder of Polygon; and Brad Garlinghouse, CEO of Ripple, along with a range of leading industry figureheads.&nbsp;</p>



<p>“This is the second year for us to combine TOKEN2049 and Singapore Grand Prix where we’ll unveil the new McLaren OKX custom livery. The event is a great starter to the weekend and to bring crypto and F1 fans together in a big way. This year has been about helping people see the future of Web3 through our latest “rewrite the system” campaign and Singapore will be a prime venue for us to amplify our efforts,” said <strong>Haider Rafique, Chief Marketing Officer at OKX.</strong></p>



<p>The diversity of this year’s title sponsors for TOKEN2049 Singapore speaks to the inherent vigour of the industry. This includes leading cryptocurrency spot and derivatives exchange <strong>OKX</strong>; global financial technology firm <strong>Circle Internet Financial (Circle)</strong>; world’s largest cryptocurrency exchange <strong>Binance</strong>; global digital asset market maker and multi-stage Web3 investment firm<strong> DWF Labs</strong>; open-source blockchain technology firm <strong>EOS Network Foundation</strong>; DeFi asset management protocol <strong>Tranchess</strong>; top cryptocurrency exchange platform <strong>Kucoin</strong>; the world’s largest multichain ecosystem <strong>Polkadot</strong>; all-in-one, institutionally-focused digital asset platform <strong>Fireblocks</strong>; leading decentralised blockchain operating system <strong>TRON DAO</strong>; world’s largest crypto copy trading platform <strong>Bitget</strong>; open-source public blockchain <strong>Klaytn</strong>; and the world’s first Sharia-compliant crypto asset <strong>Islamic Coin</strong>.</p>



<p>For more information and continued updates on TOKEN2049 Singapore, please visit: <a href="https://www.asia.token2049.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://www.asia.token2049.com/</a></p>



<p><strong>ABOUT TOKEN2049</strong></p>



<p>TOKEN2049 is a premier Web3 event, organised annually in Singapore, where decision-makers in the global crypto ecosystem connect to exchange ideas, network, and shape the industry. TOKEN2049 is a global meeting place for entrepreneurs, institutions, industry insiders, investors, builders, and those with a strong interest in the crypto and blockchain industry.</p>



<p><strong>Media Contact</strong></p>



<p><a href="mailto:token2049sg@wachsman.com">token2049sg@wachsman.com</a> </p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER:&nbsp;</em></strong><em>The Information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>
<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/208143-token2049-singapore-largest-web3-event/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/foxy-2023-13-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>KuCoin Halts BTC And LTC Mining Pools To Pursuit Futuristic Business Strategy</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/208132-kucoin-halts-btc-and-ltc-mining-pools/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Harold]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 04:57:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kucoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mining pool]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[New York Attorney General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=208132</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[KuCoin to suspend BTC and LTC mining pools on Aug 15, 2023.<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/208132-kucoin-halts-btc-and-ltc-mining-pools/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>KuCoin to suspend BTC and LTC mining pools on Aug 15, 2023.</em></li>



<li><em>Users are urged to back up data and switch to alternative pools by Aug 27.</em></li>



<li><em>Suspension aligns with KuCoin&#8217;s evolving business strategy.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>KuCoin, a well-known cryptocurrency exchange, recently <a href="https://www.kucoin.com/announcement/zh-announcement-kucoin-pool-to-temporarily-suspend-operations" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">disclosed</a> its decision to suspend mining pools supporting Bitcoin (BTC) and Litecoin (LTC) mining, effective August 15, 2023. In light of the forthcoming suspension, the platform&#8217;s users have been urged to back up and maintain their mining records before August 27, 2023.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-208-1024x567.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="567" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-208-1024x567.png" alt="KuCoin Halts BTC And LTC Mining Pools To Pursuit Futuristic Business Strategy" class="wp-image-208139" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-208-1024x567.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-208-300x166.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-208-768x425.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-208-750x416.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-208-1140x632.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-208.png 1500w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="KuCoin Halts BTC And LTC Mining Pools To Pursuit Futuristic Business Strategy 2"></a></figure></div>


<p>The exchange clarified that this move is aligned with its evolving business strategy, aimed at redirecting resources to core business operations, enhancing user experience, and ensuring the platform&#8217;s long-term sustainability. As a result, KuCoin mining pool users are advised to transition their miners to alternative pools before the suspension date.</p>



<p>It&#8217;s essential to note that while the mining pool operations are set to be temporarily halted, other services offered by <a href="https://coincu.com/207640-kucoin-bolsters-security-certificate-update/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">KuCoin</a>, including its exchange operations, remain unaffected. The exchange has assured its community that users&#8217; assets will continue to be safe and secure on the platform throughout the suspension period.</p>



<p>KuCoin&#8217;s BTC and LTC mining pools have been acknowledged as top-performing pools, contributing significantly to the respective networks. As of press time, the exchange&#8217;s BTC and LTC pools account for 7.7 EH/s and 3.33 TH/s of the total network hash rate, respectively.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-209.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="575" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-209-1024x575.png" alt="KuCoin Halts BTC And LTC Mining Pools To Pursuit Futuristic Business Strategy" class="wp-image-208141" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-209-1024x575.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-209-300x169.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-209-768x432.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-209-750x421.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-209.png 1050w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="KuCoin Halts BTC And LTC Mining Pools To Pursuit Futuristic Business Strategy 3"></a></figure></div>


<p>This decision comes shortly after KuCoin <a href="https://coincu.com/205917-kucoin-faces-profit-woes-surround/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">refuted</a> rumors about possible layoff plans. CEO Johnny Lyu emphasized that the company is undergoing restructuring to maintain its competitive edge and adapt to the dynamic crypto market.</p>



<p>The suspension of mining pool activities could be linked to a legal issue involving the New York Attorney General over <a href="https://coincu.com/172664-kucoin-sued-asks-permanent-ban-eth-security/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">alleged</a> non-compliance with KYC rules. Consequently, KuCoin has ramped up its <a href="https://coincu.com/198648-kucoin-mandatory-kyc-verification/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">KYC procedures</a>, which reportedly led to a decrease in trading activity and revenue.</p>



<p>During the suspension, KuCoin&#8217;s users will retain complete access and control over their assets. The exchange has recommended that miners transition their BTC and LTC miners to alternative pools well ahead of the suspension date to ensure uninterrupted earnings.</p>



<p>While the suspension has been described as &#8220;temporary&#8221; in Kucoin&#8217;s official statement, the exchange has not specified a fixed timeline for the potential restart of mining pool services. Instead, it intends to evaluate market conditions and user demand to make this decision in the future.</p>



<p>As of recent data from <a href="https://btc.com/stats/pool" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">BTC.com</a>, KuCoin&#8217;s mining pool is ranked as the ninth-largest in terms of hash rate share, contributing approximately 1.2% of the total network hash rate over the past three days.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER: </em></strong><em>The information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>
<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/208132-kucoin-halts-btc-and-ltc-mining-pools/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-207-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Direxion Joins Trend With Bitcoin And Ethereum Futures ETF Application</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/208130-direxion-bitcoin-ethereum-futures-etf/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Foxy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 04:53:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[# Cryptocurrencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[#Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[#Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETF Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=208130</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Direxion filed an application for Bitcoin and Ether futures products with the US SEC on Wednesday.<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/208130-direxion-bitcoin-ethereum-futures-etf/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>On Wednesday, direxion filed a Bitcoin and Ether futures product application with the SEC.</em></li>



<li><em>Prior to that, Volatility Shares, Bitwise, VanEck, Roundhill, ProShares, and Grayscale had filed an Ether ETF application with the SEC.</em></li>



<li><em>The first ether futures ETF could go live on October 12 if the SEC doesn&#8217;t reject the application.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>According to <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/08/02/tradfi-giant-direxion-joins-crypto-etf-race-by-filing-for-combined-bitcoin-and-ether-futures-fund/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Coindesk</a>, U.S. primary leveraged and reversible ETF provider Direxion filed an application for Bitcoin and Ether futures products with the US SEC on Wednesday.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-205.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="576" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-205-1024x576.png" alt="Direxion Joins Trend With Bitcoin And Ethereum Futures ETF Application" class="wp-image-208133" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-205-1024x576.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-205-300x169.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-205-768x432.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-205-750x422.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-205-1140x641.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-205.png 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Direxion Joins Trend With Bitcoin And Ethereum Futures ETF Application 4"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>Should authorities accept the product, the Direxion Bitcoin Ether Strategy ETF will invest in bitcoin and ether futures contracts, according to a filing with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). Additional ETFs having exposure to futures products may be purchased through the program.</p>



<p>In addition to ProShares, Volatility Shares, Grayscale Investments, VanEck, Bitwise, and Roundhill Investments filed for an ETH futures ETF this past week.</p>



<p>The SEC has traditionally rejected spot bitcoin futures and ETFs, although nearly 10 applications have been filed before. However, if approved, the Ether ETF will launch 75 days after the application, and Volatility Shares will be the first application on October 12 and the funds to follow.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-206.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="890" height="404" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-206.png" alt="Direxion Joins Trend With Bitcoin And Ethereum Futures ETF Application" class="wp-image-208134" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-206.png 890w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-206-300x136.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-206-768x349.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-206-750x340.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 890px) 100vw, 890px" title="Direxion Joins Trend With Bitcoin And Ethereum Futures ETF Application 5"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>The excitement in the crypto market around crypto-related ETFs was triggered after a wave of spot bitcoin ETF registrations came into focus, especially after BlackRock filed for the first time on June 15.</p>



<p>The win for futures ETFs could be promising, as the SEC previously allowed bitcoin futures ETFs to come to market in 2021. The first ETF to launch, the ProShares Bitcoin Strategy ETF (BITO), obtained $1 billion in assets under management in the first few days.</p>



<p>On the other hand, experts assess that concerns surrounding the current level of ether futures liquidity, as well as the lack of clarity on whether ether is considered a security or a commodity, are possible reasons why the SEC may refuse.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER:&nbsp;</em></strong><em>The Information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>
<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/208130-direxion-bitcoin-ethereum-futures-etf/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/foxy-2023-12-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Artificial Intelligence Will Dominate The US Economy, Outpacing Electricity And PCs: Goldman Sachs</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/208115-artificial-intelligence-will-dominate-us/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Harold]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 04:22:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Goldman Sachs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OpenAI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Altman]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web3]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Worldcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=208115</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Goldman Sachs predicts artificial intelligence's impact to surpass that of electricity and personal computers on the US economy.<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/208115-artificial-intelligence-will-dominate-us/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>Goldman Sachs predicts artificial intelligence&#8217;s impact to surpass that of electricity and personal computers on the US economy.</em></li>



<li><em>Artificial intelligence could attract $200 billion in global investments by 2025, potentially contributing up to 4% of US GDP.</em></li>



<li><em>Generative AI has massive economic potential, but significant upfront investments are required for its full transformation.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Goldman Sachs economists <a href="https://www.goldmansachs.com/intelligence/pages/ai-investment-forecast-to-approach-200-billion-globally-by-2025.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">foresee</a> that artificial intelligence (AI) will have a greater financial impact on the American economy than both electricity and personal computers. The investment report suggests that by 2025, artificial intelligence could attract $200 billion in global investments, with half of that expected to flow into the United States, significantly boosting the country&#8217;s gross domestic product (GDP).</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/1x-1-3-scaled.jpg"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="683" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/1x-1-3-1024x683.jpg" alt="Artificial Intelligence Will Dominate The US Economy, Outpacing Electricity And PCs: Goldman Sachs" class="wp-image-208123" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/1x-1-3-1024x683.jpg 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/1x-1-3-300x200.jpg 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/1x-1-3-768x512.jpg 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/1x-1-3-1536x1024.jpg 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/1x-1-3-2048x1365.jpg 2048w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/1x-1-3-750x500.jpg 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/1x-1-3-1140x760.jpg 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Artificial Intelligence Will Dominate The US Economy, Outpacing Electricity And PCs: Goldman Sachs 6"></a></figure></div>


<p>While past tech booms resulted in a 2% increase in GDP with the introduction of electricity and personal computers, <a href="https://coincu.com/192663-goldman-sachs-12-bitcoin-in-may/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Goldman Sachs</a> estimates that artificial intelligence could contribute up to 4% of GDP in the US and 2.5% in other nations heavily investing in artificial intelligence.</p>



<p>The core of this economic potential lies in generative AI, exemplified by <a href="https://coincu.com/184654-openai-attracts-300m-from-top-vc-firms/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">OpenAI</a>&#8216;s chatbot, ChatGPT, and other transformative tools like Midourney (image creation) and Eleven Labs (text-to-speech). Once widely adopted, these AI technologies could drive global labor productivity up by over 1 percentage point annually for a decade. Recently, <a href="https://coincu.com/207931-worldcoin-faces-suspension-in-kenya/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Worldcoin</a>, a cryptocurrency project founded by OpenAI CEO <a href="https://coincu.com/189924-sam-altmans-crypto-company-raises-115m/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Sam Altman</a>, launched last week.</p>



<p>However, reaping these benefits requires substantial upfront investments in physical, digital, and human capital. Goldman Sachs projects global AI-related investments to reach $200 billion by 2025, occurring before efficiency gains lead to significant productivity growth.</p>



<p>The US holds an advantageous position as a market leader in artificial intelligence technology, with American companies expected to be early adopters. While other AI-leading nations like China may also experience similar effects, the impact on investments will likely be smaller and delayed.</p>



<p>Though the timing of the artificial intelligence investment cycle remains uncertain, business surveys suggest that its impact will be felt in the second half of this decade. Larger firms in information, professional, scientific, and technical services are expected to be at the forefront of AI adoption.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-204-1024x720.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="720" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-204-1024x720.png" alt="Artificial Intelligence Will Dominate The US Economy, Outpacing Electricity And PCs: Goldman Sachs" class="wp-image-208121" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-204-1024x720.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-204-300x211.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-204-768x540.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-204-750x527.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-204-1140x802.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-204.png 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Artificial Intelligence Will Dominate The US Economy, Outpacing Electricity And PCs: Goldman Sachs 7"></a></figure></div>


<p>Market interest in artificial intelligence is surging, with a significant increase in the number of companies mentioning the technology on earnings calls. A large portion of this surge followed the release of ChatGPT in late 2022. Goldman Sachs&#8217; previous research indicates that such mentions typically precede increased company-level capital spending.</p>



<p>Goldman Sachs credits much of the anticipated gains to the rapid advancements in generative AI. While early signs of artificial intelligence adoption are apparent in some industries, the broader macroeconomic effects are expected to take a few more years to fully materialize.</p>



<p>The combination of artificial intelligence and blockchain is poised to revolutionize the Web3 landscape, making projects more efficient and productive. Blockchain&#8217;s decentralized governance offers a safeguard against AI&#8217;s misinformation challenges. Additionally, AI-powered trading bots optimize crypto trading, increasing liquidity and market efficiency. Together, artificial intelligence and blockchain promise a bright and innovative future for decentralized technologies.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER: </em></strong><em>The information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>
<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/208115-artificial-intelligence-will-dominate-us/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Final-Thumb-1-1-1024x731.jpg" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/jpeg" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Curve Finance Stops CRV Rewards For Liquidity Pools Affected By Attacks</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/208104-curve-finance-stops-crv-rewards-pools-attacks/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Foxy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 04:17:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[# Cryptocurrencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[#Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CRV]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Curve]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Liquidity Pools]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=208104</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Curve Finance's emergency multi-sig feature ended the CRV rewards of many liquidity pools affected by recent attacks.<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/208104-curve-finance-stops-crv-rewards-pools-attacks/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>Curve Finance has terminated CRV rewards for liquidity pools affected by Curve and Multichain mining.</em></li>



<li><em>This decision affects pools for alETH+ETH, msETH-ETH, pETH-ETH, crvCRVETH, Arbitrum Tricrypto, and multibtc3CRV.</em></li>



<li><em>Rewards are paused to avoid encouraging further participation in these compromised groups.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Gabriel Shapiro, General Counsel of Delphi Labs, tweeted that Curve Finance&#8217;s emergency multi-sig feature ended the CRV rewards of many liquidity pools affected by recent attacks.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-203.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="576" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-203-1024x576.png" alt="Curve Finance Stops CRV Rewards For Liquidity Pools Affected By Attacks" class="wp-image-208119" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-203-1024x576.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-203-300x169.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-203-768x432.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-203-750x422.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-203-1140x641.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-203.png 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Curve Finance Stops CRV Rewards For Liquidity Pools Affected By Attacks 8"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>Lending protocol Curve Finance has terminated governance token rewards for liquidity pools affected by recent hacks, including those affected by Vyper compiler mining on Curve and multiBTC pools affected by Multichain mining. This action was taken to avoid further user involvement in these compromised liquidity pools.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">ATTENTION, FROM A CURVE E-DAO SIGNER: <br><br>The <a href="https://twitter.com/CurveFinance?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener">@CurveFinance</a> emergency multisig has terminated CRV rewards (gauges) to the liquidity pools affected by recent exploits, including pools affected by the recent Vyper compiler exploit and the multiBTC pool affected by the recent…</p>&mdash; _gabrielShapir0 (@lex_node) <a href="https://twitter.com/lex_node/status/1686802793275813902?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener">August 2, 2023</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>As mentioned in previous Coincu News articles, On July 6, more than $100 million in cryptocurrency was <a href="https://coincu.com/200802-multichain-130m-assets-withdrawn-unknown-cause/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">withdrawn</a> from several bridges that are part of the Multichain protocol. Then, on July 30, Curve Finance was the victim of a <a href="https://coincu.com/207193-curve-finances-liquidity-pools/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">re-attack</a>. More than $47 million in cryptocurrencies were lost during the mining process.</p>



<p>The termination of the reward is carried out by the Curve Emergency decentralized autonomous organization (Curve E-DAO), which is composed of selected members of the Curve DAO governing body. Affected groups include alETH+ETH, msETH-ETH, pETH-ETH, crvCRVETH, Arbitrum Tricrypto, and multibtc3CRV. However, it is important to note that the decision could be reversed in the future if the Curve DAO proceeds with a total vote.</p>



<p>After almost 1 day of being hacked, a white hat hacker <a href="https://coincu.com/207221-hacker-returns-5-4m-to-curve-finance/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">managed </a>to get around 2,879 ETH worth about $5.4 million from a miner and return it to the protocol. However, this is only a tiny amount of the total damage suffered by the protocol.</p>



<p>Curve is one of the largest DEXs of the crypto market today, with TVL (Total Value Locked) <a href="https://defillama.com/protocol/curve-finance" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">reaching</a> $1,811. The total amount hacked accounted for about 4% of its TVL at the time, which is considered a significant hack. As a result, this hack caused ripples throughout the entire cryptocurrency sector and raised questions about the strength of the decentralized financial ecosystem.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER:&nbsp;</em></strong><em>The Information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>
<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/208104-curve-finance-stops-crv-rewards-pools-attacks/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/foxy-2023-11-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hong Kong Now Welcomes Compliant Crypto Exchanges For Retail Investors</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/208101-hong-kong-welcomes-compliant-crypto-exchanges/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Harold]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 03:59:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hash Blockchain Limited]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[HashKey Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[HashKey Group]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hong kong]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OSL]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sfc]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=208101</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Hong Kong approves compliant crypto exchanges for retail investors.<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/208101-hong-kong-welcomes-compliant-crypto-exchanges/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>Hong Kong approves compliant crypto exchanges for retail investors.</em></li>



<li><em>HashKey Group gains clearance for off-platform virtual asset trading.</em></li>



<li><em>New regulatory regime positions Hong Kong as a major player in the crypto industry.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>In a recent development, the Hong Kong Securities Regulatory Commission has given its approval to compliant exchanges, enabling them to offer services to retail investors. This marks a significant step forward for the crypto industry in the region.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/190705113107-hong-kong-flag-2-edited.jpg"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1799" height="1012" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/190705113107-hong-kong-flag-2-edited.jpg" alt="Hong Kong Now Welcomes Compliant Crypto Exchanges for Retail Investors" class="wp-image-208111" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/190705113107-hong-kong-flag-2-edited.jpg 1799w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/190705113107-hong-kong-flag-2-edited-300x169.jpg 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/190705113107-hong-kong-flag-2-edited-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/190705113107-hong-kong-flag-2-edited-768x432.jpg 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/190705113107-hong-kong-flag-2-edited-1536x864.jpg 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/190705113107-hong-kong-flag-2-edited-750x422.jpg 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/190705113107-hong-kong-flag-2-edited-1140x641.jpg 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1799px) 100vw, 1799px" title="Hong Kong Now Welcomes Compliant Crypto Exchanges For Retail Investors 9"></a></figure></div>


<p>Until now, only two compliant exchanges, Hashkey Pro and OSL, were operational, providing spot transactions for major cryptocurrencies such as BTC, ETH, USDT, and USDC.</p>



<p>The approval comes as a result of <a href="https://coincu.com/188649-hashkey-group-to-raise-funds/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">HashKey Group</a>, a prominent digital asset financial services provider based in <a href="https://coincu.com/206575-hong-kong-and-saudi-arabia/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Hong Kong</a>, obtaining clearance from the Securities and Futures Commission of Hong Kong (SFC) in February. This permission allowed the firm to facilitate off-platform virtual asset trading through its subsidiary, Hash Blockchain Limited (HBL).</p>



<p>HashKey Group COO Livio Weng <a href="https://twitter.com/0xLivio/status/1686920195200454658" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">announced</a> on Twitter that HashKey Exchange is very close when approval is passed.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true"><p lang="zh" dir="ltr">一张好&quot;牌&quot;，即将到来 <a href="https://t.co/S6AIgiuJgb" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/S6AIgiuJgb</a></p>&mdash; Livio Weng 七爷 (@0xLivio) <a href="https://twitter.com/0xLivio/status/1686920195200454658?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener">August 3, 2023</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>HashKey&#8217;s statement emphasized that this approval opens the door for HBL to act as an intermediary in facilitating trades between parties, even for tokens not listed on the exchange&#8217;s order book. The company&#8217;s commitment to providing a secure and transparent trading environment for its clients played a vital role in securing the green light from the <a href="https://coincu.com/191124-sfc-hong-kong-principles-for-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">SFC</a>.</p>



<p>Notably, the regulatory landscape for digital assets in Hong Kong underwent a significant transformation on June 1, when a new regulatory regime was implemented. The new rules and licensing guidelines were finalized just one week before they took effect, a mere eight months after being proposed in October 2022.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/HashKey.jpg"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="576" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/HashKey-1024x576.jpg" alt="Hong Kong Now Welcomes Compliant Crypto Exchanges for Retail Investors" class="wp-image-208112" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/HashKey-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/HashKey-300x169.jpg 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/HashKey-768x432.jpg 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/HashKey-1536x864.jpg 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/HashKey-750x422.jpg 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/HashKey-1140x641.jpg 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/HashKey.jpg 1920w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Hong Kong Now Welcomes Compliant Crypto Exchanges For Retail Investors 10"></a></figure></div>


<p>The updated exchange regime introduces a clear and definitive structure for centralized cryptocurrency exchanges to operate and offer their services to retail investors. This radical shift has garnered attention due to Hong Kong&#8217;s substantial financial market, making it an essential player in the crypto industry.</p>



<p>Under this program, providers were permitted to offer crypto trading services solely to professional investors with portfolios of at least HK$8 million ($1 million). Although Hong Kong witnessed the founding of notable crypto exchanges like Crypto.com and FTX, they eventually shifted their base away from the country and were not part of the local licensing regime.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-202-1024x576.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="576" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-202-1024x576.png" alt="Hong Kong Now Welcomes Compliant Crypto Exchanges for Retail Investors" class="wp-image-208113" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-202-1024x576.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-202-300x169.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-202-768x432.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-202-750x422.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-202-1140x641.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-202.png 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Hong Kong Now Welcomes Compliant Crypto Exchanges For Retail Investors 11"></a></figure></div>


<p>Paul Chan, the Financial Secretary of Hong Kong, has been a vocal advocate for digital assets and Web3 technologies. Earlier in January, he praised Hong Kong as an attractive destination for digital asset corporations, citing the city&#8217;s robust regulatory framework that adheres to international standards. He viewed virtual assets as &#8220;unstoppable new financial innovations&#8221; and stressed the need for Hong Kong to embrace them.</p>



<p>As the regulatory landscape continues to evolve, the approval of additional compliant exchanges is expected to bolster Hong Kong&#8217;s position in the global crypto market, creating new opportunities for both investors and businesses in the region. With a commitment to maintaining high standards of transparency, security, and integrity, the city looks set to further solidify its place as a leading player in the digital asset space.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER: </em></strong><em>The information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>
<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/208101-hong-kong-welcomes-compliant-crypto-exchanges/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-201-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Genesis Extends Final Reconciliation Period With Creditors, Ends Before August 16</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/208098-genesis-extends-reconciliation-period-creditors/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Foxy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 03:45:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[# Cryptocurrencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[#Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Creditors]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Lending]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DCG]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gemini]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reconciliation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=208098</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bankruptcy cryptocurrency company Genesis has extended a two-week extension to its main creditors, ending by August 16.<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/208098-genesis-extends-reconciliation-period-creditors/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>Bankruptcy crypto company Genesis has extended a two-week extension to its main creditors.</em></li>



<li><em>The lawyer said that if the parties fail to reach an agreement by August 16, the crypto lender will continue with its existing bankruptcy plan.</em></li>



<li><em>The company has been conciliating with critical stakeholders, including parent company Digital Currency Group (DCG) and Gemini Trust Co., since May.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>According to <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-08-02/genesis-says-mediation-will-end-soon-regardless-of-deal-status?utm_campaign=socialflow-organic&amp;utm_content=crypto&amp;utm_source=twitter&amp;utm_medium=social#xj4y7vzkg" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Bloomberg</a>, attorneys for bankrupt crypto lender <a href="https://coincu.com/194910-genesis-amends-reorganization-plan/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Genesis</a> said at Wednesday&#8217;s hearing that the company extended its settlement period with creditors for the last time and ended on August 16.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-200.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="976" height="549" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-200.png" alt="Genesis Extends Final Reconciliation Period With Creditors, Ends Before August 16" class="wp-image-208102" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-200.png 976w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-200-300x169.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-200-768x432.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-200-750x422.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 976px) 100vw, 976px" title="Genesis Extends Final Reconciliation Period With Creditors, Ends Before August 16 12"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>&#8220;If we do not make substantial progress with respect to a deal in principle in the next two weeks, we do not believe that we will be seeking to extend the mediation further,&#8221; company lawyer Sean O&#8217;Neal told US Bankruptcy Judge Sean Lane. As a result, the talks will have to wrap up by August 16.</p>



<p>Attorneys said if the parties fail to reach an agreement by August 16, Genesis will continue with its existing bankruptcy plan, subject to certain modifications. Reconciliation is one of the final barriers preventing Genesis from going bankrupt.</p>



<p>The company&#8217;s largest creditor is 340,000 Gemini Earn customers who owe $795.5 million. Those clients formed a &#8220;special&#8221; committee represented by the law firm Kirkland &amp; Ellis. Another group of about 60 institutional creditors, represented by Proskauer Rose, owes $1.5 billion.</p>



<p>The bankrupt crypto firm is understood to have been conciliating with key stakeholders, including parent company Digital Currency Group (DCG) and Gemini Trust Co., since May. They were trying to salvage the bankruptcy plan proposed by DCG, but the official committee of unsecured creditors rejected the plan.</p>



<p>Attorneys for Genesis Global Holdco filed a term sheet in February outlining a settlement agreement with creditors indicating that DCG will shoulder the heavy burden of restructuring the already established bankrupt crypto lending firm. The original settlement was backed by creditors representing more than $2 billion in claims against Genesis, including Gemini Trust Co.</p>



<p>The company&#8217;s lending arm filed for Chapter 11 protection in January following the collapse of crypto exchange FTX, which triggered an &#8220;unprecedented&#8221; wave of withdrawals that caused affiliates to withdraw. They have to suspend lending and borrowing.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER:&nbsp;</em></strong><em>The Information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>
<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/208098-genesis-extends-reconciliation-period-creditors/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/foxy-2023-10-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>IRS And Treasury Required To Issue Tax Regulations For Cryptocurrency Brokers</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/208089-irs-treasury-required-issue-tax-regulations/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Foxy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 03:22:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[# Cryptocurrencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[#Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Brokers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elizabeth Warren]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[IRS]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Issue]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=208089</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[US Democratic senators have urged the IRS and the Treasury Department to issue tax regulations for crypto brokers and then do so vigorously.<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/208089-irs-treasury-required-issue-tax-regulations/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>Democrats are urging the IRS and the Treasury Department to issue tax regulations for crypto brokers.</em></li>



<li><em>Lawmakers are referring to the directives elaborated in the bill that was formulated almost 2 years ago.</em></li>



<li><em>Although the White House has approved it, the Treasury Department and the IRS have not yet announced it to the public despite the deadline for implementation.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Democratic US senators signed a <a href="https://www.warren.senate.gov/imo/media/doc/2023.08.01%20Letter%20to%20Treasury%20and%20IRS%20re%20Crypto%20Tax%20Reporting%20Requirements.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">letter</a> with Bernie Sanders on Tuesday, urging the <a href="https://coincu.com/207546-irs-issues-crypto-tax-ruling/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">IRS</a> and Treasury Department to issue tax regulations for crypto brokers and then do so vigorously.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-198.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="538" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-198-1024x538.png" alt="IRS And Treasury Required To Issue Tax Regulations For Cryptocurrency Brokers" class="wp-image-208093" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-198-1024x538.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-198-300x158.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-198-768x403.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-198-750x394.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-198-1140x599.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-198.png 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="IRS And Treasury Required To Issue Tax Regulations For Cryptocurrency Brokers 13"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>US Democratic Senators Elizabeth Warren, Bob Casey, and Richard Blumenthal addressed the directives in the Senate&#8217;s $1.2 trillion infrastructure bill in August 2021, opening existing tax reporting requirements for businesses operating as crypto brokers including exchanges.</p>



<p>Warren and other senators contend that the need for the adjustment is immediate since crypto users&#8217; yearly losses from tax evasion amount to billions of dollars. The regulations seek to close financial loopholes by requiring significantly more extensive crypto tax reporting.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote has-small-font-size">
<p class="has-small-font-size">&#8220;Research suggests that crypto tax evaders are cheating the IRS out of at least $50 billion a year &#8211; but the figure may be much higher,&#8221;</p>
<cite>The law appeals.</cite></blockquote>



<p>According to the party members&#8217; argument, given the opportunity, tax evaders and cryptocurrency intermediaries willing to assist them will continue to play games on the system, exploit vulnerabilities and extract billions of dollars every year from the US government.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-199-1024x656.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="656" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-199-1024x656.png" alt="IRS And Treasury Required To Issue Tax Regulations For Cryptocurrency Brokers" class="wp-image-208094" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-199-1024x656.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-199-300x192.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-199-768x492.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-199-750x481.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-199-1140x731.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-199.png 1250w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="IRS And Treasury Required To Issue Tax Regulations For Cryptocurrency Brokers 14"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>The lawmakers pointed out that even though the Infrastructure Investment and Jobs Act of 2021 required new reporting requirements for cryptocurrency trading, the White House ended its review in May this year. Still, the Treasury Department and Internal Revenue Service (IRS) have yet to create the rules to implement them, despite a deadline set by Congress later this year. Experts say this is an unusual delay in tax regulations.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote has-small-font-size">
<p class="has-small-font-size">&#8220;Nearly two years have passed since the law was enact, and the implementation deadline is less than six months away—but Treasury has yet to publish proposed rules,&#8221;</p>
<cite>The letter read.</cite></blockquote>



<p>If implemented by the Treasury Department, the new rules would require third parties such as Binance and Coinbase to report information about individuals&#8217; cryptocurrency transactions, including gains and losses, to the IRS. This is considered to generate potential legal action for cryptocurrency service providers, especially in this sensitive time Binance and Coinbase are both appearing in SEC and CFTC lawsuits.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER:&nbsp;</em></strong><em>The Information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>
<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/208089-irs-treasury-required-issue-tax-regulations/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/foxy-2023-9-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Robinhood&#8217;s Crypto Revenue Declines 18% In Q2 Amidst Fewer Trades</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/208069-robinhoods-crypto-revenue-declines-18/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Harold]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 02:45:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robinhood]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=208069</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Robinhood's Q2 crypto revenue dropped 18% to $31 million due to reduced customer trades.<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/208069-robinhoods-crypto-revenue-declines-18/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>Robinhood&#8217;s Q2 crypto revenue dropped 18% to $31 million due to reduced customer trades.</em></li>



<li><em>Despite the decline, Robinhood reported a net income of $25 million, a significant improvement from the previous quarter&#8217;s loss.</em></li>



<li><em>The company plans to introduce a non-custodial wallet to offer customers greater control over their crypto assets.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Robinhood, the California-based online brokerage platform, <a href="https://investors.robinhood.com/overview/default.aspx" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">reported</a> an 18% decrease in transaction-based revenue from cryptocurrencies during the second quarter. The drop was primarily due to a decline in customer trading activity, as stated in the company&#8217;s latest earnings report.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-195.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="614" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-195-1024x614.png" alt="Robinhood&#039;s Crypto Revenue Declines 18% In Q2 Amidst Fewer Trades" class="wp-image-208087" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-195-1024x614.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-195-300x180.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-195-768x461.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-195-750x450.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-195-1140x684.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-195.png 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Robinhood&#039;s Crypto Revenue Declines 18% In Q2 Amidst Fewer Trades 15"></a></figure></div>


<p>Revenue related to crypto activities fell to $31 million, down from $38 million in the previous quarter. This decline was accompanied by a 6% decrease in the number of customers placing crypto trades, while notional volumes per trader declined by 15%, according to supplementary data provided by the company.</p>



<p>Nevertheless, Robinhood is continuing to explore opportunities within the crypto space. The firm has announced its plans to introduce a non-custodial wallet later this year, which would grant customers more control over their digital assets.</p>



<p>Despite the dip in crypto-related revenue, <a href="https://coincu.com/197978-robinhood-lays-off-7-of-its-workforce/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Robinhood</a> managed to exceed Wall Street estimates in its overall financial performance for the quarter. The company reported adjusted earnings of $0.03 per share, outperforming analysts&#8217; expectations of a $0.02 loss. Additionally, Robinhood&#8217;s total revenue of $486 million surpassed the estimated $472 million. However, the number of monthly active users fell short of estimates, with 10.8 million reported compared to the expected 11.7 million.</p>



<p>Other transaction-based revenues were also affected, with options revenue dropping 5% to $127 million and equities revenue declining 7% to $25 million. Over the past year, total revenue decreased by 4%, falling from $202 million in June of the previous year to $193 million.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-197.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="639" height="426" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-197.png" alt="Robinhood&#039;s Crypto Revenue Declines 18% In Q2 Amidst Fewer Trades" class="wp-image-208090" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-197.png 639w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-197-300x200.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 639px) 100vw, 639px" title="Robinhood&#039;s Crypto Revenue Declines 18% In Q2 Amidst Fewer Trades 16"></a></figure></div>


<p>Despite the decrease in revenue, Robinhood recorded a net income of $25 million in Q2, marking a significant turnaround from the net loss of $511 million reported in the first quarter of the year. This positive outcome is attributed to the company&#8217;s efforts to optimize total operating expenses, with a notable decrease of $45 million.</p>



<p>Earlier this year, Robinhood witnessed a significant decline in crypto trading volume, which <a href="https://coincu.com/194416-robinhood-crypto-trading-volume/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">dropped</a> by 43% in May compared to April. May&#8217;s trading volume was 68% lower than the same month in the previous year, as stated in the company&#8217;s previous statement.</p>



<p>However, it&#8217;s not all bleak for Robinhood. The firm&#8217;s total assets under custody experienced a 13% increase, reaching $89 billion in the last quarter. This growth was driven by higher equity valuations and continued net deposits. Over the first half of 2023, Robinhood also saw a slight increase in crypto assets under custody, rising from $8.431 billion in December 2022 to $11.503 billion in June 2023.</p>



<p>In the second quarter, Robinhood recorded a net deposit of $4.1 billion, reflecting an annualized growth rate of 21% relative to assets under custody in the first quarter of the year. Over the past 12 months, net deposits amounted to $16.1 billion, indicating a growth rate of 25% over the year.</p>



<p>Earlier this year, Robinhood took a decisive step by <a href="https://coincu.com/192803-robinhood-sol-ada-and-matic-after-sec/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">ending support</a> for all tokens listed as securities in the SEC lawsuits against crypto exchanges <a href="https://coincu.com/208039-binance-may-be-accused-of-fraud/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Binance</a> and Coinbase. These tokens included Cardano, Polygon, and Solana. Currently, the trading platform offers access to trading 15 different cryptocurrencies.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-196.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="576" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-196-1024x576.png" alt="Robinhood&#039;s Crypto Revenue Declines 18% In Q2 Amidst Fewer Trades" class="wp-image-208088" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-196-1024x576.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-196-300x169.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-196-768x432.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-196-1536x864.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-196-750x422.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-196-1140x641.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-196.png 1920w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Robinhood&#039;s Crypto Revenue Declines 18% In Q2 Amidst Fewer Trades 17"></a></figure></div>


<p>Despite the challenges faced in the crypto space, Robinhood remains optimistic about its future prospects. The firm aims to leverage its expanding suite of products and continued innovation to adapt to changing market dynamics and customer preferences.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER: </em></strong><em>The information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>
<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/208069-robinhoods-crypto-revenue-declines-18/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-194-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>LeetSwap Recovers 314 ETH, New Measures Being Tested to Resume Trading</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/208077-leetswap-recovers-314-eth-resume-trading/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Foxy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 02:38:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[# Cryptocurrencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[#Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BALD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[base]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LeetSwap]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[recover]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=208077</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[DEX LeetSwap on the Base chain said on Twitter that the platform had recovered a total of 314 ETH from the problematic liquidity pool.<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/208077-leetswap-recovers-314-eth-resume-trading/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>DEX platform Leetswap recovered 314 ETH from the hack.</em></li>



<li><em>New solutions are being tested in preparation for the resumption of transactions.</em></li>



<li><em>There are a number of liquidity pools that cannot be bailed out due to limits imposed by some custom tax token contracts.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The official announcement from DEX LeetSwap on the Base chain said on Twitter that the platform had <a href="https://coincu.com/207859-leetswap-recovered-about-220-eth-hacked/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">recovered</a> a total of 314 ETH from the problematic liquidity pool.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-191.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="576" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-191-1024x576.png" alt="LeetSwap Recovers 314 ETH, New Measures Being Tested to Resume Trading" class="wp-image-208080" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-191-1024x576.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-191-300x169.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-191-768x432.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-191-750x422.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-191-1140x641.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-191.png 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="LeetSwap Recovers 314 ETH, New Measures Being Tested to Resume Trading 18"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>It then started using custom logic to look at failed tax tokens during recovery. The platform has managed to save the ETH of some tokens directly into the tax wallet of some of these tokens. The codes of all these tokens need to be checked one by one. That&#8217;s why trading pairs with so many tokens on the DEX take such a long time.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">The funds we recovered from the locked/stuck liquidity of vulnerable pools now amount to 314 ETH.<br><br>Then we started looking at those tax tokens with custom logic on which our recovery procedure failed. We managed to rescue the ETH of some tokens directly to the tax wallet of some…</p>&mdash; LeetSwap (@LeetSwap) <a href="https://twitter.com/LeetSwap/status/1686885814146396160?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener">August 2, 2023</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>New solutions are being tested in preparation for the resumption of transactions. It will then send ETH to the rescued liquidity pool deployers so their developers can restart. There are a number of liquidity pools that cannot be bailed out due to limits imposed by some custom tax token contracts.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote has-small-font-size">
<p class="has-small-font-size">&#8220;Finally, we will resume trading as there are pools that cannot be rescued due to the limits imposed by some of the custom tax token contracts.&#8221;</p>
<cite>Notice <a href="https://twitter.com/LeetSwap/status/1686885814146396160" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">written</a></cite></blockquote>



<p>According to previous news on August 1st, the axlUSD/WETH pool in LeetSwap was hit by a price manipulation attack and the damage amounted to around $620,000.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-192.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="859" height="484" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-192.png" alt="LeetSwap Recovers 314 ETH, New Measures Being Tested to Resume Trading" class="wp-image-208081" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-192.png 859w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-192-300x169.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-192-768x433.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-192-750x423.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 859px) 100vw, 859px" title="LeetSwap Recovers 314 ETH, New Measures Being Tested to Resume Trading 19"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>The liquidity hack is the second-biggest LeetSwap mining after a project creator (believed to be Sam Bankman-Fried) withdrew $12.5 million from a Layer 2 Base meme coin, BALD. Launched in 2022, LeetSwap is the largest decentralized exchange on Coinbase&#8217;s Base network, which aims to provide higher transaction speeds and lower fees than Ethereum.</p>



<p>Experts say a Reentrancy bug in the compiler for Vyper, the language used in some Curve smart contracts, triggered the attack. The smart contract compiler changes a programmer&#8217;s human-readable language into instructions that the blockchain can understand.</p>



<p>As one of the pillars of DeFi, Curve Finance&#8217;s hack has been causing a lot of turmoil. Curve&#8217;s core features are critical to the liquidity of stablecoins used in several other DeFi projects.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER:&nbsp;</em></strong><em>The Information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>
<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/208077-leetswap-recovers-314-eth-resume-trading/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/foxy-2023-8-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
