<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 10:28:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Argentina Launches Investigation into Worldcoin over Privacy Concerns</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/argentina-investigation-worldcoin/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/argentina-investigation-worldcoin/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mercy Tukiya Mutanya]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 10:28:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[openai]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sam altman]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[worldcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266619</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/argentina-investigation-worldcoin/">Argentina Launches Investigation into Worldcoin over Privacy Concerns</a></p>
<p>Besides the criticism of its method and storage of data collection, the project has also been subject to scrutiny over its onboarding of early adopters.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/argentina-investigation-worldcoin/">Argentina Launches Investigation into Worldcoin over Privacy Concerns</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/argentina-investigation-worldcoin/">Argentina Launches Investigation into Worldcoin over Privacy Concerns</a></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Argentina joins Germany, France, and Kenya on the list of governments to investigate the cryptocurrency project <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/worldcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Worldcoin</a> over privacy concerns. The country’s Agency for Access to Public Information (AAIP) <a href="https://www.argentina.gob.ar/noticias/la-aaip-investiga-el-tratamiento-de-datos-personales-de-worldcoin-en-argentina" target="_blank" rel="noopener">announced</a> on August 8 that it was looking into the collection, storage, and use of user data at Worldcoin to ensure that it is handled in line with privacy regulations. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Worldcoin started as a way to distinguish people from bots online and uses retinal scans to verify users, a method that has raised privacy concerns.  The project&#8217;s WRLD token was launched on July 24 with over 2 million accounts already signed up.   </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The AAIP stated that the project has garnered “public notoriety in recent weeks due to the procedure of scanning the faces and irises of numerous individuals in exchange for financial compensation at different locations in Buenos Aires City and the provinces of Buenos Aires, Córdoba, Mendoza, and Río Negro.” It stated that Argentinians “have the right, whenever personal data is provided, to have clear and accessible information in relation to the assignment, use and purpose for which the data is collected and processed, especially with regard to sensitive data, such as biometric data.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Expressing similar sentiments, Kenya’s government, through its minister of internal security, announced on August 2 that it was suspending Worldoin operations pending an investigation into the potential risk to citizens. Local media reports state that Kenyan law enforcement raided a Worldcoin office and seized equipment suspected to contain user data. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In Germany, the Bavarian State Office for Data Protection Supervision revealed that it was investigating the project over privacy concerns. The French National Commission on Informatics and Liberty has also described Worldcoin’s data collection methods as “questionable.” The United Kingdom’s Information Commissioner’s Office has also expressed similar concerns, stating that it would examine the project to ensure compliance with data laws. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">However, in a </span><a href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/08/10/worldcoin-regulatory-scrutiny-grows-as-argentina-opens-investigation/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">statement to CoinDesk</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, Worldcoin stated that “the project complies with all laws and regulations governing the processing of personal data in the markets where Worldcoin is available, including but not limited to Argentina&#8217;s Personal Data Protection Act 25.326.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Worldcoin was co-founded by OpenAI CEO Sam Altman and raised $115 million in funding in May from Andreessen Horowitz, Bain Capital Crypto, and Distributed Global.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Besides the criticism of its method and storage of data collection, the project has also been subject to scrutiny over its onboarding of early adopters. A </span><a href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2022/04/06/1048981/worldcoin-cryptocurrency-biometrics-web3/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">study</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> conducted by MIT Technology asserts that Worldcoin’s first 1 million users were obtained by “deception, cash handouts and exploiting workers” in developing countries. </span></p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-gas-prices-surge-40/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/argentina-investigation-worldcoin/">Argentina Launches Investigation into Worldcoin over Privacy Concerns</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/argentina-investigation-worldcoin/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>European Gas Prices Surge Almost 40% amid Supply Concerns</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-gas-prices-surge-40/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-gas-prices-surge-40/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Darya Rudz]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 10:24:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Commodities & Futures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[australia gas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[australia gas strikes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chevron]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dutch title transfer facility]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[europe gas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[european gas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gas Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[natural gas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[woodside energy group]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266578</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-gas-prices-surge-40/">European Gas Prices Surge Almost 40% amid Supply Concerns</a></p>
<p>Prices on the Dutch Title Transfer Facility, the European benchmark, rose to more than €43 per megawatt-hour, reaching an intraday record high. On Thursday, the price slightly fell to €39.82.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-gas-prices-surge-40/">European Gas Prices Surge Almost 40% amid Supply Concerns</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-gas-prices-surge-40/">European Gas Prices Surge Almost 40% amid Supply Concerns</a></p>
<p>On Wednesday, the prices of European natural gas soared by almost 40%, for the first time since June. The price levels reached more than €40 per megawatt-hour, driven by fears over possible supply disruption in Australia. There, workers of major liquefied natural gas plants were reportedly planning strike action in a fight for higher salaries and better job security. On top of that, some traders closed out their bets that gas prices would fall, which also fueled price movements.</p>
<p>Callum Macpherson, head of commodities at Investec, <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/08/10/european-gas-prices-expected-to-rise-amid-australia-lng-supply-fears.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">stated</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;A fear that an outage in Australia could increase demand from Asia buyers for LNG that might otherwise come to Europe, has led to today&#8217;s spike in prices.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>John Evans, an analyst at brokerage PVM, commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Australia is now the highest exporter of LNG, beating Qatar and the US, but with production issues and compromised gas fields, European buyers are fearful of security in supply and have resorted to tank filling from the cash market before the onset of winter.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Prices on the Dutch Title Transfer Facility, the European benchmark, rose to more than €43 per megawatt-hour, reaching an intraday record high. On Thursday, the price slightly fell to €39.82. As of the press moment, the gas price at the Dutch Title Transfer Facility makes up €36.16.</p>
<h2>What Is Happening in Australia?</h2>
<p>Over the past decade, Australia’s LNG exports have grown exponentially, making it the country with the largest operating LNG export capacity in the world. Last year, Australia recorded an all-time high in liquefied natural gas export earnings, with volumes and prices driven by the energy security crisis that followed the outbreak of the war between Russia and Ukraine. As per the Australian Petroleum Production &amp; Exploration Association (APPEA), the record export income led to support for thousands of jobs, substantial direct government revenues, and significant expenditure locally.</p>
<p>However, it turns out that revenue generated from gas export does not mean benefits for those involved in the working processes. Currently, there are high risks of potential strikes at three major liquefied natural gas facilities in Australia that could disrupt about 10% of global exports of fuel. The owners of the facilities, Chevron and Woodside Energy Group, are now holding talks with unions to avoid the protests.</p>
<p>&#8220;We will continue to engage our employees and their representatives as we seek outcomes that are in the interests of both employees and the company,&#8221; said a Chevron representative.</p>
<p>Unions representing 700 workers at the LNG facilities have been complaining about low pay and bad working conditions. As a result, they have applied for &#8220;protected action ballot orders&#8221; that give them the right to hold votes on strike action. According to those familiar with the matter, the ongoing negotiations with Woodside and Chevron are at different stages. But considering how the processes are run, industrial action is likely to take place towards the end of August and could carry on for months if not resolved. The talks will continue until next Tuesday.</p>
<p>Read other <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/markets/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">market news</a> on Coinspeaker.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-cpi-inflation-surge-markets/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-gas-prices-surge-40/">European Gas Prices Surge Almost 40% amid Supply Concerns</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-gas-prices-surge-40/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>US CPI Inflation Surge at 3.2% Below Forecast, Markets React Positively</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-cpi-inflation-surge-markets/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-cpi-inflation-surge-markets/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 10:16:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Indices]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cpi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[federal reserve]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gdp]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266576</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-cpi-inflation-surge-markets/">US CPI Inflation Surge at 3.2% Below Forecast, Markets React Positively</a></p>
<p>The decelerating inflation reduces some of the pressure from the Fed, however, remains high over the central bank's 2% target. Thus, the Fed is less to announce rate cuts anytime soon. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-cpi-inflation-surge-markets/">US CPI Inflation Surge at 3.2% Below Forecast, Markets React Positively</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-cpi-inflation-surge-markets/">US CPI Inflation Surge at 3.2% Below Forecast, Markets React Positively</a></p>
<p>On Thursday, August 10, 2023, the Bureau of Labor Statistics reported the US CPI data for the month of July at 3.2% showing clear signs of receding inflation numbers. Also, the annual inflation rate was below the 3.3% forecast.</p>
<p>However, it was still higher than the month of June, and the first increase in more than a year&#8217;s time. Excluding the volatile prices of food and energy, the core Consumer Price Index (CPI) also rose by 0.2% in the month. This was in alignment with expectations and resulted in a year-over-year rate of 4.7%, marking the lowest level since October 2021. The annual rate for the core CPI was slightly below the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-the-dow-jones-industrial-average-index-djia/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Dow Jones</a> consensus estimate of 4.8%.</p>
<p>Markets reacted positively with Dow Jones futures shooting up by 200 points and Treasury yields moving lower. Sung Won Sohn, chief economist at SS Economics said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“It is not quite ‘mission accomplished’ yet, but significant progress on the inflation front has been made. On balance, the inflation picture has improved significantly. The Federal Reserve will stop raising the interest rate soon.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Sectors Affecting US CPI Inflation Data</h2>
<p>The majority of the monthly increase in inflation was due to higher shelter costs, which experienced a 0.4% rise, resulting in a 7.7% increase over the past year. Within the shelter category, rents also rose by 0.4%. This category accounted for over 90% of the overall increase and holds about one-third of the CPI weighting.</p>
<p>Food prices saw a 0.2% increase during the month, while energy prices only rose by 0.1%, despite notable surges in crude oil prices and pump prices.</p>
<p>Prices for used vehicles declined by 1.3%, while medical care services experienced a 0.4% decrease. Airline fares, which had seen a substantial surge during the early days of the Covid pandemic, fell by 8.1% in the month. This is the same decrease as in June, thus resulting in an overall decline of 18.6% from a year ago.</p>
<h2>The Fight Against Inflation Continues</h2>
<p>Collectively, the most recent set of data demonstrates that although inflation has significantly decreased from its peak in mid-2022, it remains notably higher than the Federal Reserve&#8217;s desired 2% threshold. This level of inflation makes it unlikely that there will be any interest rate cuts in the near future.</p>
<p>However, the decelerating inflation levels are taking off some pressure from the Fed. Seema Shah, chief global strategist at Principal Asset Management <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/08/10/cpi-inflation-july-2023-.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“While inflation is moving in the right direction, the still-elevated level suggests that the Fed is some distance from cutting rates. Indeed, disinflation is unlikely to be smooth and will require some additional economic pain before the 2% target comes sustainably into view.”</p></blockquote>
<p>The increased interest rates have yet to impact economic growth significantly: GDP recorded growth of 2% and 2.4% in the first two quarters of 2023, while the Atlanta Fed forecasts a third-quarter growth rate of 4.1%. Although payroll gains have slowed down, they remain robust, and unemployment is at its lowest level since late 1969.</p>
<p>Having raised benchmark interest rates 11 times since March 2022, central bank officials are widely anticipated to pause in September. However, there is an ongoing debate about the next course of action. Policymakers have expressed varying opinions in public comments leading to confusion.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/circle-1b-reserve-competition/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-cpi-inflation-surge-markets/">US CPI Inflation Surge at 3.2% Below Forecast, Markets React Positively</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-cpi-inflation-surge-markets/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Circle Relies on $1B Cash Reserve to Fight Competition</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/circle-1b-reserve-competition/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/circle-1b-reserve-competition/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 08:46:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[circle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[paypal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[usd coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[usdc]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266609</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/circle-1b-reserve-competition/">Circle Relies on $1B Cash Reserve to Fight Competition</a></p>
<p>Circle revealed that it is actively pursuing partnerships to promote the adoption of USD Coin.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/circle-1b-reserve-competition/">Circle Relies on $1B Cash Reserve to Fight Competition</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/circle-1b-reserve-competition/">Circle Relies on $1B Cash Reserve to Fight Competition</a></p>
<p>Prominent Stablecoin issuer <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/circle/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Circle</a> is demonstrating its commitment to adaptability and resilience as it faces renewed competition from unexpected players.</p>
<p>As non-crypto giants such as <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">PayPal Holdings Inc</a> (NASDAQ: PYPL) <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-paypal-usd-stablecoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">enter</a> the field, Circle’s CEO <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/jeremy-allaire/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Jeremy Allaire</a> revealed in an <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-08-10/circle-usdc-stablecoin-issuer-says-1-billion-cash-to-counter-paypal-binance?in_source=embedded-checkout-banner" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">interview</a> with Bloomberg that the company is relying on a substantial cash cushion exceeding $1 billion to weather the storm while addressing a decline in the market share of its stablecoin.</p>
<h2>Circle Reserve and USDC Market Share Slump</h2>
<p>At the beginning of the year, Circle&#8217;s USD Coin (USDC) was riding high with a circulation of approximately $45 billion. However, that figure has since plummeted to around $26 billion. This downward trajectory stands in stark contrast to the growth of Tether (USDT), the largest stablecoin by market capitalization, during the same period.</p>
<p>Jeremy Allaire reiterated that various &#8220;tail-risk events&#8221; in the crypto industry have had an impact on USD Coin’s adoption. He highlighted that the fall of Terra, Binance&#8217;s conversion shift, the FTX crisis, and regional bank failures all led to Circle&#8217;s difficulties.</p>
<p>Despite these obstacles, Circle&#8217;s revenue production model has proven resilient, particularly through interest income generated by assets backing the stablecoin, such as dollar deposits and short-term Treasuries. Circle is now in a position to gain from rising interest rates.</p>
<p>Circle&#8217;s financial performance in the first half of the year reflects its resilience. With $779 million in revenue, Circle surpassed its total revenue of $772 million for the entire preceding year.</p>
<p>In addition, adjusted earnings before interest, taxes, depreciation, and amortization (EBITDA) reached $219 million, outpacing the $150 million achieved in the previous year. Bolstered by a substantial cash reserve exceeding $1 billion as of June, Circle is well-equipped to forge ahead with its strategic plans.</p>
<p>Allaire emphasized that the vision for Circle&#8217;s future is grounded in the mainstream adoption of stablecoins, envisaging them as the financial medium of the Internet era. He views PayPal&#8217;s recent announcement as just the initial step in this journey.</p>
<p>He expects a greater range of financial services companies and online payment firms to enter the stablecoin arena, increasing competition and accelerating the sector&#8217;s progress.</p>
<h2>The Future Ahead of Circle</h2>
<p>Circle revealed that it is actively pursuing partnerships to promote the adoption of USD Coin. The company is also enhancing transparency by sharing financial reports and collaborating with Deloitte as an auditor.</p>
<p>The company said it is also looking into partnerships for greater adoption of its USDC. However, Circle&#8217;s approach focuses on collaboration without adopting the white-label model used by competitors such as Paxos Trust Co.</p>
<p>Even as the Federal Reserve considers decreasing interest rates, Allaire remains bullish about Circle’s prospects, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/circle-usdc-reserves-us-default/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">noting</a> that historically, a low-rate environment has boosted crypto activity.</p>
<p>Circle’s development of new revenue sources, like the recent launch of a crypto wallet service following the acquisition of CYBAVO in 2022, demonstrates the company’s dedication to innovation and diversification.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/vc-andreessen-horowitz-zero-knowledge/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/circle-1b-reserve-competition/">Circle Relies on $1B Cash Reserve to Fight Competition</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/circle-1b-reserve-competition/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>VC Firm Andreessen Horowitz Delves into Crypto Tech Research, Unveils New Tools to Bolster Zero-Knowledge Proofs</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/vc-andreessen-horowitz-zero-knowledge/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/vc-andreessen-horowitz-zero-knowledge/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 08:39:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investors News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[a16z]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[andreessen horowitz a16z]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[andresseen horowitz]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[zero knowledge proofs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[zk]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266580</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/vc-andreessen-horowitz-zero-knowledge/">VC Firm Andreessen Horowitz Delves into Crypto Tech Research, Unveils New Tools to Bolster Zero-Knowledge Proofs</a></p>
<p>This move by a16z signals the firm's intent to actively partake in the development of some of the core tech that power the companies it backs with its venture dollars.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/vc-andreessen-horowitz-zero-knowledge/">VC Firm Andreessen Horowitz Delves into Crypto Tech Research, Unveils New Tools to Bolster Zero-Knowledge Proofs</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/vc-andreessen-horowitz-zero-knowledge/">VC Firm Andreessen Horowitz Delves into Crypto Tech Research, Unveils New Tools to Bolster Zero-Knowledge Proofs</a></p>
<p>Venture Capital (VC) giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/a16z/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Andreessen Horowitz</a> has unveiled two new tools aimed at improving the core tech behind some of today&#8217;s biggest blockchains. That tech is the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-zero-knowledge-proof-zkp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">zero-knowledge</a> (ZK) technology.</p>
<p>In line with this, it introduced ‘Lasso’ and ’Jolt’ on Thursday, which are essentially a pair of open-source software projects that are based on the Succinct Non-interactive Arguments of Knowledge, or SNARKs.</p>
<p>ZK protocols are designed in a way that allows one party to verify the truth of a statement to another party without disclosing anything beyond the fact. The technology is very essential to ZK-rollups, a prevalent Layer 2 scaling solution within the blockchain domain.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, it may seem that this move by a16z signals the firm&#8217;s intent to actively partake in the development of some of the core tech that powers the companies it backs with its venture dollars. And on a broader scale, might also be an indicator that venture firms are beginning to exert more control over the companies they fund.</p>
<h2>Lasso and Jolt in Details</h2>
<p>According to a16z research papers, the two new tools are a far more effective approach to SNARK. That is in the sense that they are faster and more easily understandable for developers.</p>
<p>Lasso, which is a16z&#8217;s main innovation, proposes a “<a href="https://a16zcrypto.com/posts/article/introducing-lasso-and-jolt/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">lookup argument</a>” method to speed up ZK systems. About Lasso, the team wrote in a statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Lasso introduces a streamlined approach to verifying SNARKs, avoiding tedious hand-optimized circuits by performing lookups against massive structured tables.”</p></blockquote>
<p>The team has released code for Lasso under an open-source license. And that means that outside developers may also use it in their own projects.</p>
<p>Jolt, on the other hand, introduces a type of zero-knowledge virtual machine (zkVM) that uses Lasso. As of press time, Jolt is still just a research paper. However, a16z confirms that it has forward plans to also release a version of it in code soon. That is, also under an open-source license.</p>
<h2>What Does Andreessen Horowitz Aim to Achieve with Its New Tools?</h2>
<p>It is a known fact that most of the companies in a16z&#8217;s portfolio rely on ZK tech. So, by directly contributing to this technology, the firm is ultimately helping its clients to be successful. More so, open-source contributions undoubtedly boost its reputation, especially among developers and builders. Therefore, with the new tools, a16z may have put itself in an advantaged position over its counterparts when it comes to leading deals.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-curve-5m-recovery-hack/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/vc-andreessen-horowitz-zero-knowledge/">VC Firm Andreessen Horowitz Delves into Crypto Tech Research, Unveils New Tools to Bolster Zero-Knowledge Proofs</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/vc-andreessen-horowitz-zero-knowledge/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Labs Supports Curve Finance with $5M Investment to Aid Recovery from Recent Hack</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-curve-5m-recovery-hack/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-curve-5m-recovery-hack/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 08:09:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Binance News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance labs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bnb]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bnb chain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crv]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[curve]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[defi]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266581</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-curve-5m-recovery-hack/">Binance Labs Supports Curve Finance with $5M Investment to Aid Recovery from Recent Hack</a></p>
<p>The injection of $5 million from Binance Labs transcends a simple financial transaction; it represents a collaborative effort focused on strengthening Curve's security infrastructure and aiding the protocol in recovering its stability.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-curve-5m-recovery-hack/">Binance Labs Supports Curve Finance with $5M Investment to Aid Recovery from Recent Hack</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-curve-5m-recovery-hack/">Binance Labs Supports Curve Finance with $5M Investment to Aid Recovery from Recent Hack</a></p>
<p>Binance Labs, the investment arm of the world&#8217;s largest crypto exchange <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a>, has committed a substantial $5 million investment in Curve DAO Token (CRV). The strategic move comes as a response to a recent security breach that rattled the Curve ecosystem. Binance Labs said in its <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/blog/ecosystem/binance-labs-invests-$5m-in-curve-dao-token-crv-and-supports-curve-deployment-to-bnb-chain-4372009526169554266" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announcement</a> on August 10 that the investment demonstrates its commitment to shaping the future of the decentralized finance (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-decentralized-finance-defi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">DeFi</a>) sector.</p>
<p>The funds will be used to support Curve&#8217;s native token, CRV, which serves as a utility token that regulates all the activities in the Curve protocol. The DeFi platform is renowned as the largest stableswap and the industry&#8217;s second-largest decentralized exchange (DEX). With this infusion of funds from Binance Labs, the protocol can further strengthen its foothold and ensure that the platform is tightly packed with security features that make it impenetrable to hackers.</p>
<p>Curve faced a setback due to a vulnerability in its underlying programming language, Vyper. Cybercriminals exploited this vulnerability on July 30, losing $73.5 million from its stable pools. However, the DeFi platform has since recovered around 73% of the stolen funds worth around $52.3 million. The platform recently <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/curve-finance-bounty-exploiter/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">issued</a> a $1.85 million bounty hunter seeking to expose the hacker who claimed he was smarter than the protocol in an on-chain message on <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum.</a></p>
<p>&#8220;I&#8217;m refunding you, not because you can find me. It&#8217;s because I don&#8217;t want to ruin your project. I&#8217;m smarter than all of you, f**k!!,&#8221; reads the message.</p>
<h2>Curve Finance Receives Support from Binance Labs after Hack</h2>
<p>The DeFi platform has now received financial support from Binance Labs to help recover from the attack. The injection of $5 million from Binance Labs transcends a simple financial transaction, it represents a collaborative effort focused on strengthening Curve&#8217;s security infrastructure and aiding the protocol in recovering its stability. This investment is not solely aimed at addressing vulnerabilities but is geared toward amplifying the platform&#8217;s functionalities.</p>
<p>Yi He, Co-Founder of Binance and Head of Binance Labs, referenced the attack while noting that the platform had significantly impacted the adoption of the DeFi apps in 2023.</p>
<p>&#8220;Curve is the largest stableswap, and as a key protocol in DeFi, it has contributed to the steady growth of the space in 2023. Given the recent events that have impacted the protocol, Binance Labs has offered our full support to Curve through our investment and strategic collaboration. We view this cooperation as a starting point and look forward to working together to propel the growth of the DeFi ecosystem further.&#8221;</p>
<h2>Curve to Deploy on BNB Chain</h2>
<p>As part of the collaboration with Binance Labs, Curve plans to explore BNB Chain. According to the announcement, the DeFi protocol, which currently operates across several chains, will expand its protocol to the BNB ecosystem. The move will further propel the growth of the BNB Chain DeFi ecosystem.</p>
<p>&#8220;BNB Chain has earned a significant presence in DeFi and is well positioned to deploy Curve&#8217;s current and future products on its chain. We look forward to collaboratively fostering innovation and growth across the DeFi ecosystem,&#8221; said Michael Egorov, founder of Curve.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gemini-xrp-deposits-xrpl/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-curve-5m-recovery-hack/">Binance Labs Supports Curve Finance with $5M Investment to Aid Recovery from Recent Hack</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-curve-5m-recovery-hack/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gemini Opens XRP Deposits after Announcing Support for XRPL</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/gemini-xrp-deposits-xrpl/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/gemini-xrp-deposits-xrpl/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 07:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gemini]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpl]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266585</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gemini-xrp-deposits-xrpl/">Gemini Opens XRP Deposits after Announcing Support for XRPL</a></p>
<p>Gemini highlighted that XRP will be available for trading under several currency pairs including USD, GBP, EUR, CAD, SGD, HKD, and AUD.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gemini-xrp-deposits-xrpl/">Gemini Opens XRP Deposits after Announcing Support for XRPL</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gemini-xrp-deposits-xrpl/">Gemini Opens XRP Deposits after Announcing Support for XRPL</a></p>
<p>Following the court&#8217;s ruling earlier last month on the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a> vs Ripple case, cryptocurrency exchange <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/gemini/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Gemini</a> announced on Thursday that it has now added the support of XRPL and its native digital asset <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/xrp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">XRP</a>. According to the announcement, XRP is now available for trading on the company’s API/FIX and ActiveTrader applications for USD pairs. Additionally, the company announced that the Gemini Mobile App and website users can trade XRP pairs in USD, GBP, EUR, CAD, SGD, HKD, and AUD. The announcement was welcomed by the XRP and Ripple community as it means enhanced liquidity for the digital asset.</p>
<p>“Adding XRP Ledger to our list of supported crypto networks is an important step on our mission to unlock the next era of financial, creative, and personal freedom,” Gemini noted in the <a href="https://www.gemini.com/blog/gemini-adds-support-for-xrp" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announcement</a>.</p>
<p>The crypto exchange, however, noted that XRP can only be stored in its exchange wallet before it is made available for the Gemini Custody. The company additionally advised its users that they must upgrade to the latest version of its mobile app to deposit XRP.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="474" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Be sure to update your Gemini mobile app to version 23.808.0 to deposit XRP</p>
<p>Read more here ⤵️<a href="https://t.co/ib7lvQkz1r">https://t.co/ib7lvQkz1r</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Gemini (@Gemini) <a href="https://twitter.com/Gemini/status/1689634983609057280?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 10, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2>Market Implications for Gemini Listing Ripple-backed XRP</h2>
<p>The support of XRPL and XRP on the Gemini cryptocurrency exchange is a mutual benefit that extends the interaction of both communities. Notably, XRP is globally traded and adopted by a wide range of institutional investors tapping Ripple&#8217;s cross-border payment infrastructure like On-Demand Liquidity (ODL), and RippleNet. According to the latest crypto market data, the XRP digital asset has a market capitalization of approximately $33.4 billion and a 24-hour trading volume of about $1.147 billion.</p>
<p>Gemini exchange, on the other hand, is available to over 70 countries through regulated means and has facilitated over $200 billion in traded volume. The company has several products in the market including staking, credit card, eOTC, and custody for institutional investors. The company has made strategic partnerships along the way to help accelerate the mainstream adoption of digital assets. Among the companies in Gemini’s portfolio as partners, there are Samsung, Nifty Gateway, and Brave, among others.</p>
<p>As a New York-based crypto company, Gemini is regulated by the New York State Department of Financial Services (NYSDFS) to provide its services. With millions of crypto traders already using Gemini exchange and XRP offering deep liquidity, experts believe the integration is strategic for their future growth prospects.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the announcement did not have a major positive effect on the XRP price in the past day. According to market data provided by Coingecko, XRP price trades around 63 cents, down approximately 5.1 percent in the last week. Nevertheless, XRP price has gained approximately 83 percent YTD fueled by regulatory clarity and several listings.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bittrex-24m-sec-exchange/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gemini-xrp-deposits-xrpl/">Gemini Opens XRP Deposits after Announcing Support for XRPL</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/gemini-xrp-deposits-xrpl/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bittrex Agrees to Pay $24M to Settle with SEC for Failing to Register as National Securities Exchange</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bittrex-24m-sec-exchange/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bittrex-24m-sec-exchange/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 07:36:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bittrex]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cftc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fdic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[occ]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266579</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bittrex-24m-sec-exchange/">Bittrex Agrees to Pay $24M to Settle with SEC for Failing to Register as National Securities Exchange</a></p>
<p>The US SEC filed a complaint against Bittrex on April 17 with the US District Court for the Western District of Washington alleging the exchange listed unregistered securities.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bittrex-24m-sec-exchange/">Bittrex Agrees to Pay $24M to Settle with SEC for Failing to Register as National Securities Exchange</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bittrex-24m-sec-exchange/">Bittrex Agrees to Pay $24M to Settle with SEC for Failing to Register as National Securities Exchange</a></p>
<p>The United States Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) counted another win against the cryptocurrency market on Thursday after digital asset exchange Bittrex agreed on a $24 million settlement for allegedly listing unregistered securities in the name of crypto assets trading. However, the SEC noted that the defendants agreed on the settlement under the condition that the former neither admits nor denies the allegations. Nonetheless, the SEC counted it as a win after a recent blow in the Ripple case, which the agency intends to appeal.</p>
<h2>SEC vs Bittrex Litigation</h2>
<p>Earlier this year, the United States SEC filed a complaint against the Bittrex crypto exchange and its former CEO William Shihara for allegedly operating an unregistered national securities exchange, broker, and clearing agency. The SEC highlighted that Bittrex has earned at least $1.3 billion from 2017 through 2022 by charging transaction fees from investors.</p>
<p>The SEC further complained that Bittrex and Shihara, who was the company’s CEO from 2014 to 2019, coordinated with crypto issuers to first delete from public channels certain problematic statements that the exchange believed would lead to regulatory scrutiny. As a result, the SEC <a href="https://www.sec.gov/news/press-release/2023-78" target="_blank" rel="noopener">argued</a> that the exchange chose profits over investor protection.</p>
<p>Having been cornered without further argument based on existing laws, Bittrex and Bittrex Global agreed to pay a joint disgorgement fee of about $14.4 million, prejudgment interest of $4 million, and a civil penalty of $5.6 million, thereby bringing the total penalty to about $24 million. Notably, the settlement is subject to the court’s approval</p>
<p>“Today’s settlement makes clear that you cannot escape liability by simply changing labels or altering descriptions because what matters is the economic realities of those offerings. I am grateful to the SEC staff for aggressively pursuing non-compliance in the crypto industry, resolving this matter, and bringing additional relief to harmed investors,” Gurbir S. Grewal, Director of the SEC’s Division of Enforcement, <a href="https://www.sec.gov/news/press-release/2023-150" target="_blank" rel="noopener">noted</a>.</p>
<p>The US SEC has already filed similar complaints against several crypto exchanges including Binance US and also Coinbase Global, Inc. (NASDAQ: COIN). However, the SEC has been accused of overstepping its mandate as some argue that the crypto market is not under its jurisdiction.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="474" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Today we announced that crypto asset trading platform Bittrex Inc. and its co-founder and former CEO, William Shihara, agreed to settle charges that they operated an unregistered national securities exchange, broker, and clearing agency.</p>
<p>&mdash; U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (@SECGov) <a href="https://twitter.com/SECGov/status/1689741781481504768?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 10, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2>Bigger Picture</h2>
<p>The cryptocurrency market in the United States is expected to experience heavy regulatory onslaught from several agencies including the Fed, SEC, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/cftc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CFTC</a>, FDIC, and OCC. Notably, Congress too has made swift progress in regulating the crypto industry more so the stablecoins market in a bid to ensure a safe adoption of the digital dollar, which in turn helps the greenback retain its status as the global reserve currency.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/india-sign-documents-crypto/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bittrex-24m-sec-exchange/">Bittrex Agrees to Pay $24M to Settle with SEC for Failing to Register as National Securities Exchange</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bittrex-24m-sec-exchange/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>India Launches Open Competition to Build Web Browser Using Crypto to Digitally Sign Documents</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/india-sign-documents-crypto/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/india-sign-documents-crypto/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 14:08:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital rupee]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[goldman sachs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[iwbdc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[rbi]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266523</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/india-sign-documents-crypto/">India Launches Open Competition to Build Web Browser Using Crypto to Digitally Sign Documents</a></p>
<p>The competition, which has a submission deadline in July next, will allow tech enthusiasts add to crypto innovation in India.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/india-sign-documents-crypto/">India Launches Open Competition to Build Web Browser Using Crypto to Digitally Sign Documents</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/india-sign-documents-crypto/">India Launches Open Competition to Build Web Browser Using Crypto to Digitally Sign Documents</a></p>
<p>India is looking to launch a new web browser that allows people to digitally sign documents using crypto tokens. According to an official <a href="https://pib.gov.in/PressReleaseIframePage.aspx?PRID=1947243" target="_blank" rel="noopener">press release</a>, the Ministry of Electronics and Information Technology (MeitY) launched the Indian Web Browser Development Challenge (IWBDC) to build the app.</p>
<p>The press release explains that the IWBDC is an open competition to inspire tech enthusiasts, developers, and innovators looking to build the browser. The announcement also expects that the browser would come equipped with tight security and data privacy protection.</p>
<p>“Proposed browser would also focus on accessibility and user-friendliness, ensuring built-in support for individuals with diverse abilities. Moreover, the browser envisions the ability to digitally sign documents using a crypto token, bolstering secure transactions and digital interactions,” reads the announcement.</p>
<p>The browser is expected to fully support Web3 and similar functionalities. The MeitY has also announced a $400,000 prize for the winner and has set the submission deadline for July 1, 2024.</p>
<h2>Crypto in India</h2>
<p>India has tried repeatedly to ban cryptocurrency in the country but has not had much success. While there is no direct ban on cryptocurrencies in India, the unregulated nature suggests that authorities oppose the widespread adoption of digital assets in the Southeast Asian country. There are also no official guidelines for using crypto and no government-backed recourse for problems arising from crypto investment and related issues.</p>
<p>Last year, India launched the Digital Rupee, a crypto version of its national currency, after initially proposing the asset in 2017. Now, the Reserve Bank of India (RBI) is hoping that the Digital Rupee would help significantly with cross-border transactions.</p>
<p>The RBI has <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/india-rbi-central-banks-digital-rupee/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">engaged nearly 20 central banks</a> all over the world, seeking ways through which the central bank digital currency (CBDC) will support cross-border payments. According to RBI Governor Shaktikanta Das, India is a vibrant market for trade and receives a large number of cross-border payments from citizens working in other countries. However, there have been setbacks.</p>
<p>Das explains that access to the United States dollar is an increasingly difficult problem for traders in most countries looking to import goods. He states that while India has no shortage of dollars, many other countries have these problems and are affected by the scarcity.</p>
<p>The RBI Governor explains there is a market for the Digital Rupee as a tool for cross-border payments since many popular options have seen reduced patronage because of the increased adoption of Bitcoin and many other cryptocurrencies. Using the Digital Rupee, the RBI Governor assures that cross-border transactions and payments will be cheaper, easier, and much faster. India hopes to counter the dependence on USD and make the Digital Rupee the preferred cross-border payment option instead of Bitcoin and other digital assets.</p>
<h2>India’s Economy</h2>
<p>Last month, Goldman Sachs <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/goldman-sachs-india-2075/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">said</a> India would become the world’s second-largest economy by 2075. The firm states India will overtake large economies like Germany, China, and Japan.</p>
<p>Goldman’s India economist Santanu Sengupta also added that India’s dependency ratio would become one of the lowest sometime in the next 20 years. A dependency ratio compares the number of a country’s working population with its dependent sector.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/france-crypto-firms-mica-regulation/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/india-sign-documents-crypto/">India Launches Open Competition to Build Web Browser Using Crypto to Digitally Sign Documents</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/india-sign-documents-crypto/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>France Modifies Regulatory Requirements for Crypto Firms to Align with MiCA Regulation</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/france-crypto-firms-mica-regulation/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/france-crypto-firms-mica-regulation/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 14:03:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[amf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eu mica]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[france]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mica]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mica crypto regulation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266476</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/france-crypto-firms-mica-regulation/">France Modifies Regulatory Requirements for Crypto Firms to Align with MiCA Regulation</a></p>
<p>The "enhanced" registration requirements will be effective from January 1, 2024.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/france-crypto-firms-mica-regulation/">France Modifies Regulatory Requirements for Crypto Firms to Align with MiCA Regulation</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/france-crypto-firms-mica-regulation/">France Modifies Regulatory Requirements for Crypto Firms to Align with MiCA Regulation</a></p>
<p>In a bid to conform to the recently finalized Markets in Crypto Assets (MiCA) regulation, France has just revised its requirements for crypto firms. The country&#8217;s financial regulator AMF <a href="https://www.amf-france.org/en/news-publications/news/digital-assets-amf-amends-it-general-regulation-and-its-policy-dasp-light-enhanced-registration-and#xts=607212&amp;xtor=RSS-3&amp;type=RSS" target="_blank" rel="noopener">revealed</a> this on Thursday, as countries in the European Union (EU) stand in line to implement the new rule which will take effect in about one and a half years.</p>
<p>For what it&#8217;s worth, France already has a seemingly robust licensing regime for crypto firms. Therefore, it has been a place of high interest to many firms looking to register ahead of implementing MiCA. That is considering that firms that have duly registered under the current licensing regime may not have any need to be MiCA-compliant when the rule takes effect.</p>
<h2>MiCA Regulation: How&#8217;s the AMF Preparing?</h2>
<p>According to AMF, the &#8220;enhanced&#8221; registration requirements will be effective from Jan. 1, 2024. And, it will be mandatory for &#8220;new players&#8221; that may want to offer any digital assets services. About the old players, however, the regulator said:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;As a reminder, DASPs that obtained a simple registration before Jan. 1, 2024 benefit from a &#8220;grandfather&#8221; clause and continue to be subject to the framework applicable before this date.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Per the AMF, the amendment to its rule covers diverse areas that seek to ensure that digital asset service providers conduct their businesses in good faith. Its revised rule, for instance,  bans crypto firms from using client assets without their express permission. Also, it requires that digital asset service providers issue clear and non-misleading information about their operations. That is as it pertains to their pricing policies, custody provisions ( proper differentiation between client assets and own assets), and security and control systems. And, lastly, the amended rule also seeks for these firms to establish systems for managing conflicts of interest.</p>
<p>Although <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-approval-france/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a> and Hex Trust are registered with the AMF, they were recently joined by Societe Generale&#8217;s crypto division which recently bagged the license as well.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-q1-2024-revenue-growth/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/france-crypto-firms-mica-regulation/">France Modifies Regulatory Requirements for Crypto Firms to Align with MiCA Regulation</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/france-crypto-firms-mica-regulation/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4204 metric#misses=47 metric#hit-ratio=98.9 metric#bytes=1107356 metric#prefetches=215 metric#store-reads=25 metric#store-writes=4 metric#store-hits=222 metric#store-misses=8 metric#sql-queries=36 metric#ms-total=138.21 metric#ms-cache=6.38 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.2278 metric#ms-cache-ratio=4.6 -->