<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 13:18:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Shiba Memu presale hits $902k as popular meme tokens stalls</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memu-presale-hits-902k-as-popular-meme-tokens-stalls/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memu-presale-hits-902k-as-popular-meme-tokens-stalls/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 13:18:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memu-presale-hits-902k-as-popular-meme-tokens-stalls/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>At press time, Shiba Memu had sold 30,951,646 tokens raising $902,439.72. The Shiba Memu presale has continued gathering steam as popular meme tokens stall. Popular meme tokens including Pepe have seen their value decline in the past 24 hours. A majority of popular meme tokens on Monday saw significant price declines as the Shiba Memu [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memu-presale-hits-902k-as-popular-meme-tokens-stalls/">Shiba Memu presale hits $902k as popular meme tokens stalls</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>At press time, Shiba Memu had sold 30,951,646 tokens raising $902,439.72.</li>
<li>The Shiba Memu presale has continued gathering steam as popular meme tokens stall.</li>
<li>Popular meme tokens including Pepe have seen their value decline in the past 24 hours.</li>
</ul>
<p>A majority of popular meme tokens on Monday saw significant price declines as the <a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news">Shiba Memu</a> presale continued to gather steam. <a href="https://coinjournal.net/dogecoin/what-is-dogecoin/">Dogecoin (DOGE)</a> has dropped by 3.6%, <a href="https://coinjournal.net/shiba-inu/what-is-shiba-inu/">Shiba Inu (SHIB)</a> by 3.4%, PEPE by 4.1%, and FLOKI by 4.5%.</p>
<p>Going by the hype that the Shiba Memu (SHMU) is receiving, the new Shiba-themed meme token is slowly putting up a spirited fight to become a major meme token player.</p>
<h2>Shiba Memu could be the next PEPE</h2>
<p>PEPE, a new meme token, has outperformed Shiba Inu and Dogecoin this year although there is a rider as covered in a previous article <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/as-pepe-crypto-price-surges-beware-of-a-bull-trap/">here</a>. Pepe&rsquo;s value has increased by more than 300% in the last three months while Shiba Inu&rsquo;s value has decreased by more than 25%.</p>
<p>Pepe gained support as investors began concentrating on more recent meme coins as more established ones lost favour. In fact, this year has seen pressure on Floki Inu, Dogecoin, and Dogelon Mars. As news of new millionaires spread, Pepe, on the other hand, benefited from the fear of missing out (FOMO).</p>
<p>Overall, Pepe has grown from nothing to one of the largest cryptocurrencies in the world in a matter of months. The token&rsquo;s daily volume has increased, and its market capitalization has increased to over $605 million. In addition, Pepe is frequently one of the most popular tokens on CoinMarketCap and in social media.</p>
<p>However, the last few weeks have also seen Pepe&rsquo;s popularity dwindle and a new entrant by the name of Shiba Memu could become the next big thing in cryptocurrency. Shiba Memu is currently conducting a presale of its SHMU token and has raised $902,439 in less than three weeks.</p>
<p>The sudden surge in SHMU&rsquo;s popularity is partly because of the fact that its price is rising every few hours thanks to its innovative token sale strategy. At the time of writing, one SHMU was going for 0.013825 USDT and was scheduled to appreciate to 0.014050 USDT in the next four hours. Shiba Memu can be purchased <a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news">here</a>.</p>
<p>It is important to note that investors are flocking to the Shiba Memu project even as one of its main rivals, Shiba Inu, developers work on the layer-2 network called Shibarium to be released in August.</p>
<h2>What is Shiba Memu?</h2>
<p>Shiba Memu is a brand-new and ground-breaking meme token. It is a distinctive and alluring investment because of its self-sufficient marketing abilities, which are supported by AI technology.</p>
<p>Shiba Memu will develop its own marketing strategies, write its own PR, and advertise itself in pertinent forums and social networks, unlike other meme tokens that depend heavily on human teams&rsquo; marketing efforts to gain traction.</p>
<p>Shiba Memu developers want to build a marketing powerhouse that is unstoppable and self-sufficient. They want to create a platform that can consistently produce more content than a tabloid by utilising AI. A variety of media will publish this content.</p>
<p>The team aims at launching the Shiba Memu token on the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/what-is-ethereum/">Ethereum</a> blockchain and Binance Smart Chain (BSC), conclude its native token presale, provide the initial liquidity for trading on a decentralized exchange, and launch a staking program to encourage community participation and engagement by the end of Q3, 2023. This will be followed by the development of its AI Marketing Dashboard in Q4, 2023 before launch in Q1, 2024.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memu-presale-hits-902k-as-popular-meme-tokens-stalls/">Shiba Memu presale hits $902k as popular meme tokens stalls</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memu-presale-hits-902k-as-popular-meme-tokens-stalls/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Coin (BNB) price forms a bearish flag as the plot thickens</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-coin-bnb-price-forms-a-bearish-flag-as-the-plot-thickens/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-coin-bnb-price-forms-a-bearish-flag-as-the-plot-thickens/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 12:42:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance Coin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-coin-bnb-price-forms-a-bearish-flag-as-the-plot-thickens/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>BNB coin has become heavily shorted in the perpetual futures market. It has also formed a bearish flag pattern on the daily chart. Binance Coin has come under intense pressure in the past few weeks as short bets in the futures market increased. BNB token was trading at $244 on Monday, lower than last week&#8217;s [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-coin-bnb-price-forms-a-bearish-flag-as-the-plot-thickens/">Binance Coin (BNB) price forms a bearish flag as the plot thickens</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">BNB coin has become heavily shorted in the perpetual futures market.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">It has also formed a bearish flag pattern on the daily chart.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/binance-coin/"><u>Binance Coin</u></a> has come under intense pressure in the past few weeks as short bets in the futures market increased. BNB token was trading at $244 on Monday, lower than last week&rsquo;s high of $261. In all, it has dropped by over 31% from the highest level this year.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">BNB loses momentum</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Most&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/cryptocurrencies/"><u>cryptocurrencies</u></a> jumped sharply last week after the conclusion of the Ripple vs SEC case. BNB coin, on the other hand, remained in a tight range. It jumped to a high of $261.40 and then erased most of those gains.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Binance Coin has remained under pressure mostly because of the ongoing case, which was brought about by the&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-response-to-sec-lawsuit/"><u>Securities and Exchange Commission</u></a> (SEC). The SEC accused Binance of committing over 10 crimes, including operating a broker-dealer in the United States without following the law.</p>
<p dir="ltr">It is too early to predict how the lawsuit will develop and how long it will take. Legal experts I have talked to say that the SEC has a relatively solid case against Binance.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Another reason why BNB price is struggling is a recent report that Binance had fired over 1,000 employees recently. Like other crypto companies, Binance has gone through major challenges because of the crypto winter.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Despite this, there is a likelihood that the company&rsquo;s finances are improving as cryptocurrencies recover. Binane has also seen inflows in the past few weeks. According to DeFi Llama, it has had over $2.9 billion in inflows in the past 30 days. Its assets now stands at over $64 billion.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Meanwhile, data shows that many players in the perpetual futures market are short the BNB coin. Data compiled by CoinGlass shows that open interest is weighted heavily towards the short-sellers. In a note, an analyst told Coindesk:</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;The sentiment has worsened due to the recent high-profile staff exits, inconsistencies related to BCH withdrawals from Binance.US and the pending Department of Justice case against Binance&rsquo;s CEO Changpeng &ldquo;CZ&rdquo; Zhao.&rdquo;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">BNB price prediction</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/17/1689597732514-fcf7fd11-d135-478a-a972-3f898eb2d3f6.png" style="width: 661px;height: 321.687px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="661" height="321.687"></p>
<p dir="ltr">The daily chart shows that the BNB crypto price has been in a strong bearish trend in the past few months. Most recently, the coin has formed what looks like a bearish flag pattern. In price action analysis, this pattern is usually a bearish sign.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">BNB coin has moved below the 50-day and 25-day moving averages. Therefore, because of the descending flag pattern, the coin will likely have a bearish breakout in the near term. If this happens, the next level to watch will be at $220.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy Binance Coin</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>


<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=MTQ2NTAy&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy BNB with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    CEX.IO</h3>


<p>
    <a href="/visit/cex-crypto?guid=MTQ2NTAy&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy BNB with CEX.IO today            </a>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-coin-bnb-price-forms-a-bearish-flag-as-the-plot-thickens/">Binance Coin (BNB) price forms a bearish flag as the plot thickens</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-coin-bnb-price-forms-a-bearish-flag-as-the-plot-thickens/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chancer sells over 2 million tokens as Bitcoin’s price stabilises</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-sells-over-2-million-tokens-as-bitcoins-price-stabilises/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-sells-over-2-million-tokens-as-bitcoins-price-stabilises/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 11:53:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-sells-over-2-million-tokens-as-bitcoins-price-stabilises/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways Chancer has sold more than two million tokens so far in its presale, raising nearly $800,000 in the process. Bitcoin continues to maintain its value above $30k as more investors become bullish.&#160; The cryptocurrency market rallied last week following the news that XRP is not considered a security. Several cryptocurrency exchanges, including Coinbase [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-sells-over-2-million-tokens-as-bitcoins-price-stabilises/">Chancer sells over 2 million tokens as Bitcoin’s price stabilises</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Chancer has sold more than two million tokens so far in its presale, raising nearly $800,000 in the process.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin continues to maintain its value above $30k as more investors become bullish.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">The cryptocurrency market rallied last week following the news that XRP is not considered a security. Several cryptocurrency exchanges, including Coinbase and Kraken,&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/page/2/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>relisted XRP</u></a> on their platforms afterwards.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin, the world&rsquo;s leading cryptocurrency by market cap, continues to maintain its value above the $30k level. This has allowed other cryptocurrencies to experience positive performance.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer, still in its presale stage, is also setting new records, with nearly $800,000 raised by the team so far.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitcoin maintains its price above $30k</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin has been trading between the $29k-$31k region over the past three weeks. Following Ripple&rsquo;s partial win in court, Bitcoin rallied close to the $32k level before retracing towards $29k on Friday.</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, Bitcoin is now trading above $30k once again as investors remain optimistic about the medium and long-term outlook of the market. At press time, the&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>price of Bitcoin</u></a> stands at $30,165 per coin.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Chancer?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The total cryptocurrency market cap has stayed above $1 trillion for more than a month, indicating that interest in the market remains strong.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">With the market experiencing a pullback following Ripple&rsquo;s judgement last week, investors might be looking at some new and exciting projects. Chancer is one of the exciting and new projects currently in the cryptocurrency space.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Chancer</u></a> is a unique Web3 peer-to-peer (P2P) custom betting platform designed to enable users to live stream betting events.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">In an age where everything is becoming decentralised, Chancer is looking to do the same to the betting industry. Chancer has adopted a decentralised method of betting and online gambling.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Another exciting feature of Chancer is that it allows users to bet on a wide range of events, beyond traditional sports and casino bets.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The project is in its presale stage, and the first stage is almost over. The team aims to raise $1 million in the first presale stage and has so far raised $794k. The developers will use the funds raised from the various funding rounds to build a P2P betting platform.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to their whitepaper, Chancer would allow users to enjoy numerous features, including, betting markets in real-time and based on user interests, social media connections, and expertise.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Furthermore,&nbsp;<a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Chancer</u></a> claims that it wants to solve the problems associated with using bookmakers when betting. Users would be allowed to set up their custom P2P betting markets.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">One of the biggest selling points of Chancer is that users can bet on various activities. It doesn&rsquo;t matter if it is an official event or not. The bet can range from sporting events and even non-sporting ones amongst friends.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">You can bet on the first one in your group to finish a specific task or to achieve a certain milestone.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Chancer&rsquo;s first presale stage is 80% completed</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer&rsquo;s presale event will take place in stages, and the first one is nearly 80% completed. So far, the team has raised nearly $800k.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The development team will use the funds to develop its suite of products. The team intends to carry out 12 presale events, with a target of $15 million.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">CHANCER is the native token of the Chancer ecosystem. At the moment, CHANCER is going for $0.01 BUSD per token.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to the team, the token will power various activities on the Chancer platform. Users that hold CHANCER can create markets and invest in markets created by other users.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">In addition to that, holding CHANCER would allow users to create, participate in, and profit from their very own predictive markets.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Currently, Chancer supports numerous wallets for the presale, including, Trust Wallet, MetaMask, Coinbase Wallet, and Rainbow.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Visit the Chancer website</u></a> to get more information about the presale.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Should you invest in Chancer now?</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Chancer</u></a> could be one of the best new projects to enter the market this year. By decentralising the betting ecosystem, Chancer could gain massive adoption over the next few months and years.</p>
<p dir="ltr">If Chancer gains massive adoption, its native token could experience a surge in price in the medium and long term. In addition to that, CHANCER&rsquo;s price could also rally higher if the broader cryptocurrency market continues its positive performance in the coming months.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-sells-over-2-million-tokens-as-bitcoins-price-stabilises/">Chancer sells over 2 million tokens as Bitcoin’s price stabilises</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-sells-over-2-million-tokens-as-bitcoins-price-stabilises/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>zkSync unveils new proof system dubbed Boojum</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/zksync-unveils-new-proof-system-dubbed-boojum/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/zksync-unveils-new-proof-system-dubbed-boojum/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 11:42:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/zksync-unveils-new-proof-system-dubbed-boojum/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Boojum upgrade is live as zkSync Era transitions to a new STARK-powered proof system. The new proof system is designed to power world-class performance on regular consumer-grade hardware. zkSync is rolling out the feature in phases as it tests out its security and functionality. zkSync Era, a zero knowledge (ZK) proofs layer 2 protocol for [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/zksync-unveils-new-proof-system-dubbed-boojum/">zkSync unveils new proof system dubbed Boojum</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Boojum upgrade is live as zkSync Era transitions to a new STARK-powered proof system.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The new proof system is designed to power world-class performance on regular consumer-grade hardware.</li>
<li dir="ltr">zkSync is rolling out the feature in phases as it tests out its security and functionality.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">zkSync Era, a zero knowledge (ZK) proofs layer 2 protocol for <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/">Ethereum</a>, has announced its high-performance proof system called Boojum.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to the team, the upgrade is not only to scale network performance but also significantly improve on its overall decentralisation by allowing for the use of consumer-grade hardware.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Say hello to Boojum &#128075;: zkSync Era&rsquo;s new high-performance proof system for radical decentralization. Boojum is an upgrade that will transition zkSync Era to a STARK-powered proof system, providing world-class performance on consumer-grade hardware.</p>
<p>&#128161;&nbsp;Learn more:&hellip; <a href="https://t.co/1GrwJ5Y07A">pic.twitter.com/1GrwJ5Y07A</a></p>
<p>&mdash; zkSync &#8718; (@zksync) <a href="https://twitter.com/zksync/status/1680820952991408129?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 17, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">New zkSync Era upgrade</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Boojum is a Rust-based arithmetization and constraint library that zkSync is transitioning to from its SNARK-based prover system. The protocol noted in an<a href="https://zksync.mirror.xyz/HJ2Pj45EJkRdt5Pau-ZXwkV2ctPx8qFL19STM5jdYhc" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">&nbsp;<u>announcement</u></a> on Monday that the new proof system will power the platform&rsquo;s upgraded version of ZK circuits.</p>
<p dir="ltr">While zkSync Era can currently process over 100 transactions per second (TPS), Boojum is expected to considerably bump this up. On top of that, the team targets near-real-time and cheap transactions.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>Our current SNARK-based system, while effective for today, won&rsquo;t scale to the high-volume, near real-time transactions the ZK Stack, where zkSync Era operates as a Hyperchain, aims to support in the coming years. The future we imagine for these systems is one in which proofs are generated and verified cheaply and quickly, allowing for fast finality and interoperability between Hyperchains</em>,&rdquo; the zkSync Era team wrote.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In terms of reducing hardware requirements, Boojum will allow for GPU provers with as little as 16 GB of RAM. The move to have such a low barrier is crucial to supporting an increasingly decentralised ecosystem.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Today&rsquo;s rollout of Boojum upgrade will incorporate a phased out integration into mainnet. While live on the mainnet, the upgrade&rsquo;s first implementation is in &ldquo;shadow mode&rdquo;. It means the team will run the new proof system in tandem with the current one.</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, while Boojum will be in testing mode, &ldquo;shadow proofs&rdquo; will be generated and verified from real production data on Mainnet blocks. zkSync will continually work on the ecosystem to fine-tune the upgrade&rsquo;s functionality as it moves closer to full migration.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/zksync-unveils-new-proof-system-dubbed-boojum/">zkSync unveils new proof system dubbed Boojum</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/zksync-unveils-new-proof-system-dubbed-boojum/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kalima Secures $10 Million Investment Commitment and Announces Private Sale and DEX Listing</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/kalima-secures-10-million-investment-commitment-and-announces-private-sale-and-dex-listing/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/kalima-secures-10-million-investment-commitment-and-announces-private-sale-and-dex-listing/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire &#160;]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 11:17:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=146475</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Dubai, United Arab Emirates, July 17th, 2023, Chainwire Delegated proof-of-stake blockchain Kalima has entered into an agreement with ABO Digital, a private alternative funding group based in the Bahamas and Dubai. This significant partnership involves a commitment of US$10 million into the French-based blockchain company. Kalima has also released details of its KLX token sale. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/kalima-secures-10-million-investment-commitment-and-announces-private-sale-and-dex-listing/">Kalima Secures $10 Million Investment Commitment and Announces Private Sale and DEX Listing</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Dubai, United Arab Emirates, July 17th, 2023, Chainwire</strong></p>
<p>Delegated proof-of-stake blockchain <a href="https://www.kalima.io/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Kalima</a> has entered into an agreement with ABO Digital, a private alternative funding group based in the Bahamas and Dubai. This significant partnership involves a commitment of US$10 million into the French-based blockchain company. Kalima has also released details of its KLX token sale.</p>
<p>Kalima is a rapidly growing ecosystem that allows businesses, developers, and startups to build web3 enterprise and data governance applications, with a focus on IoT (Internet of Things) data in order to solve real-world problems.</p>
<blockquote><p>Kalima CEO Andr&eacute; Legendre said: &ldquo;The funding commitment from ABO Digital marks a significant milestone for Kalima, which plans to utilize the funds to further innovate and refine IoT solutions to revolutionize industries and drive digital transformation. The arrangement with ABO Digital will enable Kalima to enhance its IoT blockchain solutions for industrial companies and bolster strategic partnerships within the IoT and blockchain ecosystem.&rdquo;</p></blockquote>
<blockquote><p>&ldquo;We are excited to work with the Kalima team going forward,&rdquo; said Amine Nedjai, CEO of ABO Digital. &ldquo;Kalima&rsquo;s innovative approach and expertise in web3 enterprise applications align perfectly with our commitment to driving technological advancements in enterprise blockchain solutions.&rdquo;</p></blockquote>
<p>The Kalima team has also announced a 24-hour private sale of its KLX token on Pinksale. The event will provisionally take place on July 19. A general purpose utility token, KLX can be used to pay for transactions and access blockchain services on the Kalima protocol.</p>
<p>To support the growth of the KLX token, on July 10 Kalima Blockchain Governance created several proposals. These include bridging the KLX token from Polygon to the Ethereum network and proposing the 24-hour token sale on Pinksale. Following completion of the private sale event, KLX will be made available for trading on Uniswap, where a KLX-ETH pair will be established.</p>
<p>The primary objective of the private sale, which will have a hard cap of 300 ETH, is to create a sufficiently deep liquidity pool on Uniswap. The Uniswap listing of the KLX token is planned for July 21.</p>
<h3>About Kalima</h3>
<p><a href="https://www.kalima.io/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Kalima</a> is a low-consumption layer one blockchain for enterprises and IoT. It provides an interconnected blockchain for achieving decentralization and increasing scalability, adopting a framework popularized by blockchains such as Cosmos and Polkadot. Kalima can be embedded into very small IoT devices and allows AI inferences to be executed at the network&rsquo;s edge using its native smart contracts.</p>
<h3>About ABO Digital</h3>
<p>ABO Digital is an investment firm providing alternative financing solutions to cryptocurrency projects around the world. As part of the Alpha Blue Ocean group, which has executed more than $2B in financing commitments for publicly listed companies since its inception in 2017, ABO Digital brings institutional-grade expertise and flexible financing solutions for blockchain developers worldwide.</p>
<h3>Contact</h3>
<p>Head of PR, Yousef Batter, White Label Strategy, yousef.batter@whitelabelstrategy.io, +971559356531</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/kalima-secures-10-million-investment-commitment-and-announces-private-sale-and-dex-listing/">Kalima Secures $10 Million Investment Commitment and Announces Private Sale and DEX Listing</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/kalima-secures-10-million-investment-commitment-and-announces-private-sale-and-dex-listing/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple technical analysis update following last week&#8217;s landmark federal ruling</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/ripple-technical-analysis-update-following-last-weeks-landmark-federal-ruling/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/ripple-technical-analysis-update-following-last-weeks-landmark-federal-ruling/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mircea Vasiu]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 10:40:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/ripple-technical-analysis-update-following-last-weeks-landmark-federal-ruling/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A US federal judge ruled last week that Ripple is a security when sold to institutional investors Ripple&#8217;s price jumped by more than 30% Only a close above parity would invalidate the bearish bias Ripple squeezed higher last week following a landmark decision from a federal judge ruling that it is a security when sold [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ripple-technical-analysis-update-following-last-weeks-landmark-federal-ruling/">Ripple technical analysis update following last week&#8217;s landmark federal ruling</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>A US federal judge ruled last week that Ripple is a security when sold to institutional investors</li>
<li>Ripple&rsquo;s price jumped by more than 30%</li>
<li>Only a close above parity would invalidate the bearish bias</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p>Ripple squeezed higher last week following a landmark decision from a federal judge ruling that it is a security when sold to institutional investors. If crypto is a security or not has been the subject of many debates lately.</p>
<p>The ruling is a major victory for Ripple, even though the same judge ruled that Ripple is not a security when sold to retail investors. Nevertheless, Ripple&rsquo;s price bounced from its long-term consolidation area, up over 30% in one single day.</p>
<p>For technical traders, the question is whether the higher spike is enough to break the bearish trend. As it turns out, bulls will have to push some more for Ripple&rsquo;s bearish trend to end.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/17/1689589909591-979dd710-cd6b-4aef-9029-b2d49dc2935b.jpg" style="width: 1800px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="1800" height="490"></p>
<p><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XRPUSD/?exchange=CRYPTO">Ripple chart by TradingView</a></p>
<h2>Ripple should trade above parity with the US dollar for the bearish bias to end</h2>
<p>Despite the spike higher, Ripple&rsquo;s price remains under pressure unless it manages to climb above parity with the US dollar.</p>
<p>In other words, it remains sensitive to US dollar news, and any dollar strength should result in Ripple giving up more of its recent games.</p>
<p>However, it would all change if the market climbs above parity. This area has provided resistance since the start of 2022 and still does &ndash; after all, it contained the price action following last week&rsquo;s news.</p>
<p>The good part for bulls is that breakout came at the end of a bullish triangle. The said triangle acted as a reversal pattern, and triangles like these usually appear at the end of bearish trends.</p>
<p>All in all, the bias remains bearish unless more strength leads to Ripple trading above parity. Until then, look for US dollar news to drive the price action.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ripple-technical-analysis-update-following-last-weeks-landmark-federal-ruling/">Ripple technical analysis update following last week&#8217;s landmark federal ruling</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/ripple-technical-analysis-update-following-last-weeks-landmark-federal-ruling/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Memu’s presale nears $800k as XRP rallies on court rulling</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memus-presale-nears-800k-as-xrp-rallies-on-court-rulling/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 10:40:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memus-presale-nears-800k-as-xrp-rallies-on-court-rulling/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways XRP rallied by more than 70% on Thursday following favourable ruling in Ripple&#8217;s legal case against the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). Shiba Memu&#8217;s presale nears $800k as more investors enter the market. The cryptocurrency market has been extremely bullish over the past 24 hours, with the prices of most coins and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memus-presale-nears-800k-as-xrp-rallies-on-court-rulling/">Shiba Memu’s presale nears $800k as XRP rallies on court rulling</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">XRP rallied by more than 70% on Thursday following favourable ruling in Ripple&rsquo;s legal case against the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu&rsquo;s presale nears $800k as more investors enter the market.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">The cryptocurrency market has been extremely bullish over the past 24 hours, with the prices of most coins and tokens in the green zone.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu&rsquo;s presale has also been performing excellently and is now set to reach the $800k level as more investors enter the market.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">XRP and XLM rally to new highs</h2>
<p dir="ltr">XRP, the native coin of the Ripple ecosystem, rallied by more than 70% on Thursday, thanks to a favourable ruling in the ongoing Ripple vs. SEC legal case.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The U.S. District Court of the Southern District of New York&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ripple-wins-sec-case-xrp-not-a-security/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>ruled</u></a> a few hours that the sale of Ripple&rsquo;s XRP tokens on exchanges and through algorithms did not constitute investment contracts.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, the judge also ruled that the institutional sale of the tokens did violate federal securities laws.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Ripple&rsquo;s partial victory was welcomed by the cryptocurrency ecosystem, with XRP rallying to a one-year high of $0.84 on Thursday, adding more than 70% to its value in the process. At press time, the&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/ripple/#:~:text=The%20price%20of%20XRP%20today,trading%20volume%20of%20%24622.39M." rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>price of Ripple</u></a> stands at $0.7857</p>
<p dir="ltr">XLM, the native coin of the Stellar Lumen ecosystem, also soared by more than 50% following the Ripple announcement. BTC, ETH, Solana, and Polygon also recorded excellent gains over the last 24 hours.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Shiba Memu?</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Shiba Memu</u></a>, although still in its presale stage, is included in the ongoing market rally. Shiba Memu&rsquo;s presale reached a new level a few hours ago as more investors entered the market.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu is a cryptocurrency token that combines AI and blockchain technology to create an unstoppable, entirely self-sufficient marketing powerhouse.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In their whitepaper, the team explained that Shiba Memu is a project that could do the work of 100 marketing agencies. However, as an AI-based platform, Shiba Memu is also active.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The platform is always working to find the best work going on in creative advertising, eating it up and spitting it back out, but better.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu is riding on the recent popularity of meme coins, which have become a multi-billion dollar sector within the cryptocurrency industry. Over the last three years, the market cap of meme coins grew from practically $0 to reach the $20 billion mark in 2022.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, Shiba Memu differs from the hundreds of other meme coins in the market in that it has utility and will solve real-world problems for users.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to their whitepaper, Shiba Memu has self-sufficient marketing capabilities powered by AI technology, making it a unique and attractive investment.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Shiba Memu</u></a> will develop its own marketing strategies, write its own PR, and promote itself in relevant forums and social networks.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Currently, the project operates on Ethereum and BNB Chain, the two leading DeFi and smart contract blockchains in the cryptocurrency space.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Shiba Memu&rsquo;s presale nears $800k</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu&rsquo;s presale investment has more than tripled over the past seven days. Last week, Shiba Memu&rsquo;s presale investment stood at $215,000, and it currently stands at $798,247.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The surge in investment can be attributed to an increase in investors entering the market and investing in the project.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Shiba Memu team said they would use the funds generated from the presale to develop some of their products. Most of the funds would be used to develop Shiba Memu&rsquo;s AI technology.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Click here to find out more about&nbsp;<a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Shiba Memu&rsquo;s presale event</u></a>.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Should you invest in Shiba Memu today?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The cryptocurrency market has experienced an excellent performance since the start of the year, with the prices of most coins and tokens up by nearly 50% during that period.</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, the market is still down by more than 50% from the all-time high set in 2021. Market analysts are now expecting Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies to rally in the medium to long term.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The decision to invest in a token depends on the investor. However,&nbsp;<a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Shiba Memu</u></a> could be a big winner once the project launches and the token gets listed on cryptocurrency exchanges.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu will be combining the powers of AI and blockchain technology to ease marketing strategies for companies and organisations. If the project gets the right level of adoption, its SHMU token could rally higher over the next few months and years.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memus-presale-nears-800k-as-xrp-rallies-on-court-rulling/">Shiba Memu’s presale nears $800k as XRP rallies on court rulling</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Katie Haun: SEC “unlikely” to appeal XRP decision</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/katie-haun-sec-unlikely-to-appeal-xrp-decision/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/katie-haun-sec-unlikely-to-appeal-xrp-decision/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 09:39:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Policy and Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/katie-haun-sec-unlikely-to-appeal-xrp-decision/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Katie Haun is the founder and CEO of Haun Ventures and also a former US Department of Justice prosecutor. In a tweet on Sunday, Haun said the SEC is unlikely to appeal as the agency wouldn&#8217;t want to lose on appeal. XRP price rose significantly after the judge&#8217;s summary ruling. Katie Haun, the founder and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/katie-haun-sec-unlikely-to-appeal-xrp-decision/">Katie Haun: SEC “unlikely” to appeal XRP decision</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Katie Haun is the founder and CEO of Haun Ventures and also a former US Department of Justice prosecutor.</li>
<li dir="ltr">In a tweet on Sunday, Haun said the SEC is unlikely to appeal as the agency wouldn&rsquo;t want to lose on appeal.</li>
<li dir="ltr">XRP price rose significantly after the judge&rsquo;s summary ruling.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Katie Haun, the founder and CEO of Haun Ventures and former prosecutor at the US Department of Justice, believes the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) is unlikely to seek an &ldquo;immediate appeal&rdquo; of the court ruling that effectively declared&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/xrp/"><u>XRP</u></a> not a security.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">SEC immediate appeal &ldquo;unlikely&rdquo;</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Haun, who sees the win for&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/ripple/"><u>Ripple</u></a> after its tussle with the agency as a great outcome for crypto, shared her opinion via tweeted remarks on Sunday. The comments follow last week&rsquo;s summary court ruling that was largely welcome across the industry.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>I&rsquo;ve spoken with trusted legal colleagues (including @HaunVenturesv advisors Steve Engel and James Burnham) and the consensus is that the court drew a reasonable line&mdash;distinguishing between XRP itself (not an investment contract and thus not a security) and certain XRP transactions in which institutional investors paid money to Ripple directly and Ripple made contractual commitments in exchange, creating an investment contract under Howey</em>,&rdquo; Haun tweeted.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to her, the distinction has offered the crypto industry an avenue to explore in cases the SEC has brought against some of the top exchanges. The argument here is that &ldquo;tokens are never &ldquo;investment contracts&rdquo; on their own.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>Only binding contracts imposing post-sale obligations on the seller can constitute investment contracts and hence tokens traded on exchanges or secondary markets would almost never qualify</em>.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">On whether the SEC will appeal the court&rsquo;s decision, Haun notes that there&rsquo;s a possibility it could. However, it&rsquo;s unlikely to be an immediate appeal. On why this could be the case, the former a16z fund manager explained:</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;&hellip; <em>an immediate appeal seems unlikely both because the agency would have to ask the court to split this decision from the portion going to trial and because I&rsquo;m skeptical the SEC actually wants legal clarity. The Commission benefits from the current confusion and losing these issues on appeal would jeopardize its entire enforcement agenda. So I&rsquo;d be surprised if the SEC tried to appeal now</em>.&rdquo;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Congress needs to step in </h2>
<p dir="ltr">XRP price skyrocketed more than 100% as a result, hitting highs of $0.94. However, the coin&rsquo;s value is hovering near $0.75. &nbsp;The partial win for Ripple could be key in pushing XRP above the $1 supply wall.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Some observers have&nbsp;<a href="https://twitter.com/JohnReedStark/status/1679904748273532936"><u>opined</u></a> that the court&rsquo;s decision could be reversed on appeal, while some&nbsp;<a href="https://twitter.com/nic__carter/status/1679882709718519808"><u>say</u></a> Ripple faces a significant penalty in case of settlement. The overall sentiment though is that while the ruling delivered a blow to the SEC, what remains to be seen is what it does for the broader question of regulation.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Can Congress step in? Haun says it&rsquo;s imperative they do so.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>Even if the outcome here was positive overall, the complexity of the court&rsquo;s reasoning suggests that existing laws and jurisprudence may be ill-equipped to contend with all the important policy concerns at play. The major questions doctrine seems built for crypto at this moment: major decisions on policy like this are for Congress, not unelected agencies,</em>&rdquo; she noted.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/katie-haun-sec-unlikely-to-appeal-xrp-decision/">Katie Haun: SEC “unlikely” to appeal XRP decision</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/katie-haun-sec-unlikely-to-appeal-xrp-decision/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto prices rising and sentiment flipping but liquidity &#038; macro picture are ominous</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-prices-rising-and-sentiment-flipping-but-liquidity-macro-picture-are-ominous/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dan Ashmore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 09:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-prices-rising-and-sentiment-flipping-but-liquidity-macro-picture-are-ominous/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key Takeaways Crypto prices are rising sharply, with Bitcoin up 20% in the last three weeks The filing of a number of high-profile Bitcoin ETFs has pushed optimism in the market Under the hood, liquidity remains low and some worrisome trends emerge, however The regulatory woes are still present, with Coinbase and Binance facing a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-prices-rising-and-sentiment-flipping-but-liquidity-macro-picture-are-ominous/">Crypto prices rising and sentiment flipping but liquidity &amp; macro picture are ominous</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2 dir="ltr">Key Takeaways</h2>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Crypto prices are rising sharply, with Bitcoin up 20% in the last three weeks</li>
<li dir="ltr">The filing of a number of high-profile Bitcoin ETFs has pushed optimism in the market</li>
<li dir="ltr">Under the hood, liquidity remains low and some worrisome trends emerge, however</li>
<li dir="ltr">The regulatory woes are still present, with Coinbase and Binance facing a murky future</li>
<li dir="ltr">The macro picture also remains uncertain, with the prospect of a lagged impact via tightening monetary policy looming large</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p dir="ltr">It wouldn&rsquo;t be like crypto markets to get overly excited. In the past couple of weeks, positivity has returned to the space, led by the seminal filings for a Bitcoin spot ETF by two of the world&rsquo;s biggest asset managers, Blackrock and Fidelity.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Additionally, Fidelity were among a cohort of large trad-fi operators, including Schwab and Citadel Securities, to back the new exchange EDX, which offers trading for Bitcoin, Ether, Litecoin and Bitcoin Cash.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin is up 20% in the last three weeks, breaching past the $30,000 mark, while Ether is up 16% in the same timeframe, approaching the $2,000 mark once more. A glance at the <a href="https://alternative.me/crypto/fear-and-greed-index/"><u>Fear and Greed</u></a> index, an interesting metric which gauges overall sentiment in the space, shows it is markedly in the &ldquo;greed&rdquo; sector with a score of 61 (0 represents extreme fear, 100 represents extreme greed).&nbsp;</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/05/1688557574714-e61e6782-a3ef-4b4a-9f4f-a101fbbe3e8d.png" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="600" height="535">And yet, a look under the hood betrays some concern. Firstly, if the filing of the ETFs is the reason for the recent ramp, as it appears to be, is a 20% jump justified? The SEC has declared the recent filings as &ldquo;inadequate&rdquo;, according to the WSJ, informing the Nasdaq and CBOE (who filed the paperwork on behalf of the asset managers) that there is not enough detail with respect to &ldquo;surveillance-sharing agreements&rdquo;. The SEC had previously said that sponsors of a Bitcoin trust are required to enter into a surveillance-sharing agreement with a regulated market of significant size.</p>
<p dir="ltr">While the applications can be updated and refiled (and the CBOE did indeed refile theirs since, with Nasdaq likely soon to follow) the development hints at how difficult it has been to get the much-coveted spot ETF over the line. There is no guarantee that these are approved, despite the big names involved &ndash; the SEC even rejected an application from Fidelity in the past, turning it away in January 2022.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">In truth, it feels inevitable that Bitcoin spot ETFs will one day be traded freely, but a 20% jump on a mere filing in the last couple of weeks is a massive ramp when considering what else has happened in the space, and the state of markets, which we will delve into now.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Liquidity</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Liquidity continues to lag, a factor which cannot be overstated &ndash; and indeed one which the eventual approval of spot ETFs should help.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Looking at centralised exchanges per data from Kaiko as we close out the second quarter of 2023, volume over the past three months was lower again, coming in at the lowest number since 2020, before Bitcoin and crypto embarked on their inexorable price rises and took the financial world by storm.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/05/1688557591169-492d05de-add9-47cf-86fa-47539ff38e28.png" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="600" height="324"></p>
<p dir="ltr">But with lower liquidity, moves to both the upside and downside are exacerbated. This has perhaps contributed to Bitcoin&rsquo;s steep rise in the past few weeks, and also year-to-date, with it currently up 83%.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">But liquidity and volumes being so low should be alarming for market participants. Much of the inroads made during the pandemic, with regard to Bitcoin taking its place next to bona-fide asset classes from a trading perspective, have slowed if not reversed &ndash; at least from a liquidity perspective.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">As further evidence of this, in the below chart, I&rsquo;ve presented the total balance of stablecoins across exchanges, which has fallen a staggering 60% in the past six months &ndash; an outflow of $26 billion.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14290288">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">Having said that, there are pockets of optimism which hint at a brighter future if/when these spot ETFs do get approved. Looking at volume in derivatives markets, it has been rather consistent. In fact, it is markedly up on the second half of 2022. Perhaps this means the spot market has been greater affected by the regulatory crackdown. Either way, it&rsquo;s a less gruesome picture than what we are seeing in spot markets.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/05/1688557591126-4dee794c-aab5-4225-8275-f59e55c418c3.png" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="600" height="327"></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Regulation</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Right now, with regard to crypto-specific risk, it really all comes back to regulation. We have discussed the ETF filings, but June also brought two seminal moments: formal charges brought against Coinbase and Binance.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The two cases are extremely different, mind you. Binance&rsquo;s lawsuit <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/opinion-binance-sued-by-sec-an-inevitable-but-ominous-day-for-crypto/"><u>could not be less surprising</u></a>, with the exchange constantly skirting guidelines and laws. The charges amount to a laundry list of different offences, including trading against customers, manipulating trade volume, encouraging users to circumvent geographical restrictions and securities violations.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">It is the latter charge which is the centre of the suit against Coinbase, however, and the most pivotal of the lot. It is also why the Coinbase suit is <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-and-cryptos-fate-hangs-by-a-string-a-deep-dive/"><u>far more intriguing</u></a>. Do not forget that the allegations are coming from the SEC, the same body which presided over Coinbase&rsquo;s IPO in April 2021. Why did the SEC let an unregistered securities exchange float on a US stock exchange? You tell me.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">But let&rsquo;s get back to the point: what this all means for crypto markets. While Bitcoin appears to be carving its own place out in the eyes of the law, a slew of other tokens were named as securities by the SEC. Despite this, they have risen sharply since off the Bitcoin ETF news. Does this make sense?&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Conclusion</h2>
<p dir="ltr">At the end of the day, crypto is going to crypto. Prices move, and trying to pinpoint reasons is often a fool&rsquo;s errand. The last month, however, feels like we have seen an extremely aggressive price rise despite some bad news on the regulatory front.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Additionally, the macro picture has not changed much, even with the pause at the last Fed meeting. Fed chair Jerome Powell&rsquo;s comments made it clear that this was a pause rather than an about-turn in policy.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;Looking ahead, nearly all committee participants view it as likely that some further rate increases will be appropriate this year,&rdquo; Powell said when announcing the pause.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The market believes him. I backed out probabilities from Fed futures in the next chart, which show that there is currently an 86% chance of a 25 bps hike at the next Fed meeting in three weeks time, with only a 14% chance of rates being left unchanged again. I have presented this next to the same probabilities conveyed by the market exactly a month ago (Bitcoin is up 20% in the time since), showing softer forecasts do not explain the sharp price (the chance of no hike has actually come down).&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14349271">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">As I said, crypto going to crypto. But with assets as notoriously volatile as what we see in this sector, it would be wise to stop and think about whether the sudden wave of positivity is justified. When considering the liquidity picture and the regulatory trouble, there are plenty of reasons to hesitate.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Then when one layers in the macro picture, the picture becomes murkier again. Let us not forget that we are in the midst of one of the swiftest rate hiking cycles in modern history, with rates rising all the way from zero to above 5%, and the prospect of them rising even further later this month.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Monetary policy operates with a lag, and the scale of that tightening is enormous. Sentiment may feel like it has flipped dramatically, but there is a long road ahead yet.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-prices-rising-and-sentiment-flipping-but-liquidity-macro-picture-are-ominous/">Crypto prices rising and sentiment flipping but liquidity &amp; macro picture are ominous</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
