<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 01:16:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Anthony Pompliano expects SEC to eventually approve a Spot Bitcoin ETF</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/anthony-pompliano-sec-approve-spot-bitcoin-etf/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wajeeh Khan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 01:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Interview]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=145078</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Pompliano says underlying fundamentals of Bitcoin are strengthening. He expects a Spot Bitcoin ETF to be a meaningful catalyst for BTC. Bitcoin is currently up a whopping 85% versus the start of the year. Anthony Pompliano agrees that Bitcoin could see friction in the near term but remains bullish on the digital asset for the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/anthony-pompliano-sec-approve-spot-bitcoin-etf/">Anthony Pompliano expects SEC to eventually approve a Spot Bitcoin ETF</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Pompliano says underlying fundamentals of Bitcoin are strengthening.</li>
<li>He expects a Spot Bitcoin ETF to be a meaningful catalyst for BTC.</li>
<li>Bitcoin is currently up a whopping 85% versus the start of the year.</li>
</ul>
<p>Anthony Pompliano agrees that <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> could see friction in the near term but remains bullish on the digital asset for the long term.</p>
<h2>Pompliano shares his view on Bitcoin</h2>
<p>The Founder of Pomp Investments is constructive because the underlying fundamentals related to the world&rsquo;s largest cryptocurrency by market cap are improving.</p>
<blockquote><p>Bitcoin is anti-fragile. We see hash rate hitting all-time highs. We see adoption hitting all-time highs. People are realizing its value and they&rsquo;re putting all sorts of capital into the network.</p></blockquote>
<p>The total supply of Bitcoin is slated to <a href="https://coinjournal.net/learn/what-is-bitcoin-halving/">halve</a> in April of 2024 which has historically served as a catalyst for its price.</p>
<p>At writing, BTC is already up about 85% versus the start of the year.</p>
<h2>Is a Spot Bitcoin ETF coming soon?</h2>
<p>Pompliano is also convinced that the U.S. SEC will eventually <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/secs-spot-bitcoin-etf-approval-fairly-high-bernstein/">approve</a> a Spot Bitcoin ETF which will likely be another tailwind for the cryptocurrency.</p>
<p>His comments follow a recent wave of applications for such an exchange-traded fund that the regulator has already dubbed <a href="https://www.afr.com/markets/currencies/us-regulator-pushes-back-against-wave-of-spot-bitcoin-etf-filings-20230701-p5dkyt" target="_blank" rel="noopener">inadequate</a>. Still, Pompliano said today on CNBC&rsquo;s &ldquo;<a href="https://www.cnbc.com/video/2023/07/03/bitcoin-is-anti-fragile-says-pomp-investments-anthony-pompliano.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Squawk Box</a>&rdquo;:</p>
<blockquote><p>It&rsquo;s a small detail that is more of a formality. We&rsquo;re watching Wall Street saying we want access to BTC. So, when it [spot bitcoin ETF] happens, a lot of people will pour capital into it.</p></blockquote>
<p>He&rsquo;s confident in particular because among notable names that have recently filed for a Spot Bitcoin ETF is <a href="https://decrypt.co/147177/blackrock-spot-bitcoin-etf-filing-sec-coinbase-surveillance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BlackRock</a> that has a history of going for an exchange-traded fund only when it&rsquo;s convinced it will get approval.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/anthony-pompliano-sec-approve-spot-bitcoin-etf/">Anthony Pompliano expects SEC to eventually approve a Spot Bitcoin ETF</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>SEC’s spot Bitcoin ETF approval “fairly high”: Bernstein</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/secs-spot-bitcoin-etf-approval-fairly-high-bernstein/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/secs-spot-bitcoin-etf-approval-fairly-high-bernstein/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 19:10:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Policy and Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/secs-spot-bitcoin-etf-approval-fairly-high-bernstein/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>$650 billion asset manager Bernstein believes there&#8217;s a good chance of a spot Bitcoin ETF approval. The SEC&#8217;s argument for denial of a spot ETF while approving futures ETFs is unlikely to convince the court in the Grayscale vs SEC case. The regulator is likely to approve a spot ETF by a regulated Wall Street [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/secs-spot-bitcoin-etf-approval-fairly-high-bernstein/">SEC’s spot Bitcoin ETF approval “fairly high”: Bernstein</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">$650 billion asset manager Bernstein believes there&rsquo;s a good chance of a spot Bitcoin ETF approval.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The SEC&rsquo;s argument for denial of a spot ETF while approving futures ETFs is unlikely to convince the court in the Grayscale vs SEC case.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The regulator is likely to approve a spot ETF by a regulated Wall Street giant than deal with OTC products like GBTC, analysts at Bernstein noted.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">On July 2, Gemini co-founder Cameron Winklevoss&nbsp;<a href="https://twitter.com/cameron/status/1675302282915610624"><u>tweeted</u></a> that it has been 10 years since the Winklevoss twins filed the first spot Bitcoin ETF. Over the decade, the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/sec/">SEC</a> has denied multiple proposals, a scenario that continues even as the crypto market&rsquo;s outlook shifts increasingly optimistic.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The case is even more pronounced after a flurry of applications involving mainstream Wall Street giants like BlackRock, Fidelity and Invesco.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Among those to voice the latest optimistic tone over the approval of a <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/bitcoin-etf/">spot Bitcoin ETF</a> is brokerage firm Bernstein, CoinDesk reported today.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to experts at the firm, who shared their insights in a research report, the SEC&rsquo;s approval of futures Bitcoin ETFs and the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/btc-hits-31k-as-sec-approves-first-leveraged-futures-bitcoin-etf/">leveraged futures ETF allowed last week</a>, all leave the regulator with little room to maneouvre in terms of continuing to deny a spot ETF.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">The case for a spot ETF</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The SEC&rsquo;s contention that futures pricing is from regulated exchanges such as the CME, as opposed to spot prices that come from crypto exchanges like Coinbase, remains. However, with major asset managers signaling towards market surveillance agreements to address possible manipulation, basically puts the SEC in the spot.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Grayscale&rsquo;s case against the SEC, which relates to the regulator&rsquo;s disapproval of a proposal to convert the Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC) into a spot Bitcoin ETF, is another reason why an approval is highly likely. &nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">[Read more: <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/fully-committed-to-launching-a-bitcoin-etf-grayscale/">Grayscale to convert its GBTC to a Bitcoin ETF</a>]</p>
<p dir="ltr">Analysts at Bernstein say that the court is likely not to be &ldquo;<em>convinced that the futures price is not derived from the spot price</em>.&rdquo; They also opine that allowing the futures ETFs and not disapproving spot ones could be &ldquo;<em>a difficult pill to swallow for the court</em>s.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Their report sums up the outlook thus:</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>SEC would rather bring in a regulated bitcoin ETF led by more mainstream Wall Street participants and with surveillance from existing regulated exchanges, than having to deal with a Grayscale OTC product filling the institutional gap</em>.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Market experts see the SEC&rsquo;s recent quick feedback on recently filed proposals, which has seen Cboe BZX refile spot ETFs for several firms naming Coinbase as the exchange they are having a surveillance sharing agreement with, as a good first step.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Nasdaq has also refiled BlackRock&rsquo;s ETF proposal, naming Coinbase as the crypto exchange with the SSA.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">JUST IN: BlackRock has re-filed for spot bitcoin ETF, the resubmission was dated 6/29, Nasdaq just posted tho. They just added Coinbase like everyone else. <a href="https://t.co/UGq46DdLgu">pic.twitter.com/UGq46DdLgu</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Eric Balchunas (@EricBalchunas) <a href="https://twitter.com/EricBalchunas/status/1675926078177550336?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 3, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/secs-spot-bitcoin-etf-approval-fairly-high-bernstein/">SEC’s spot Bitcoin ETF approval “fairly high”: Bernstein</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/secs-spot-bitcoin-etf-approval-fairly-high-bernstein/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Thailand introduces new digital asset service providers’ regulations</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/thailand-introduces-new-digital-asset-service-providers-regulations/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/thailand-introduces-new-digital-asset-service-providers-regulations/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 16:50:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto adoption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/thailand-introduces-new-digital-asset-service-providers-regulations/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Thailand&#8217;s SEC has introduced new regulations ensuring investor protection from digital asset service providers. Digital asset providers will also not be able to provide digital assets deposited by users for loans or investments. The new regulations require providers to clearly disclose the risks that may arise from trading cryptocurrencies. In order to prioritize investor protection, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/thailand-introduces-new-digital-asset-service-providers-regulations/">Thailand introduces new digital asset service providers’ regulations</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Thailand&rsquo;s SEC has introduced new regulations ensuring investor protection from digital asset service providers.</li>
<li>Digital asset providers will also not be able to provide digital assets deposited by users for loans or investments.</li>
<li>The new regulations require providers to clearly disclose the risks that may arise from trading cryptocurrencies.</li>
</ul>
<p>In order to prioritize investor protection, Thailand&rsquo;s Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) introduced <a href="https://t.co/ObNncgrJLa">new rules</a> for companies that provide services for digital assets. </p>
<p>The rules now require crystal-clear risk warnings for <a href="https://coinjournal.net/cryptocurrencies/trade/">cryptocurrency trading</a>. A clear warning about the possible risks associated with trading digital assets must also be provided by providers of digital assets in accordance with the new regulations.</p>
<p>The Thai SEC stated that the warning message, along with the disclosure of the outcomes of the investment suitability assessment and appropriate asset allocation, must be displayed prominently. According to the rules, service providers must make sure customers consent and understand the risks before using their services.</p>
<h2>Restrictions on lending and deposit services</h2>
<p>The new guidelines place restrictions on the deposit and lending services provided by digital asset businesses in addition to risk disclosure. With the exception of certain pre-approved promotional activities, these rules forbid the provision or support of such services beginning on August 30.</p>
<p>According to the Thai SEC&rsquo;s guidelines, it is strictly forbidden for any entities other than businesses dealing in digital assets to promote or otherwise influence deposit-taking and lending services.</p>
<p>On September 1, 2022, the Thai SEC approved the requirement that cryptocurrency business operators disclose security warnings about the risks of trading cryptocurrencies, starting a dialogue on investor protection regulations.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/thailand-introduces-new-digital-asset-service-providers-regulations/">Thailand introduces new digital asset service providers’ regulations</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/thailand-introduces-new-digital-asset-service-providers-regulations/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Revolut to delist Polygon, Solana and Cardano</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/revolut-to-delist-polygon-solana-and-cardano/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/revolut-to-delist-polygon-solana-and-cardano/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 16:40:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Policy and Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Revolut]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US regulation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/revolut-to-delist-polygon-solana-and-cardano/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Revolut is taking the step after its US-based partner Bakkt recently delisted the tokens. MATIC, ADA and SOL will however still be available on Revolut across other markets. Robinhood and eToro have recently also announced similar token delistings. Revolut will end support for three major cryptocurrencies, the crypto-friendly bank has told its customers in the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/revolut-to-delist-polygon-solana-and-cardano/">Revolut to delist Polygon, Solana and Cardano</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Revolut is taking the step after its US-based partner Bakkt recently delisted the tokens.</li>
<li dir="ltr">MATIC, ADA and SOL will however still be available on Revolut across other markets.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Robinhood and eToro have recently also announced similar token delistings.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Revolut will end support for three major cryptocurrencies, the crypto-friendly bank has told its customers in the United States.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The company said in a notice emailed to US customers that it will be delisting <a href="https://coinjournal.net/cardano/">Cardano (ADA)</a>, <a href="https://coinjournal.net/polygon/">Polygon (MATIC)</a> and Solana (SOL). The &ldquo;financial super app&rdquo; <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/uk-bank-revolut-adds-support-for-11-new-crypto-tokens/">added</a> a host of tokens in early 2021 as demand skyrocketed amid the crypto bull market.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Revolut&rsquo;s US partner delisted the tokens</h2>
<p dir="ltr">London-based Revolut&rsquo;s decision to delist ADA, MATIC and SOL comes as the company responds to the prevailing <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/us-regulation/">regulatory environment in the US</a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The past few months have seen the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) up its regulatory crackdown on multiple crypto platforms.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Last month&rsquo;s lawsuits against Binance and Coinbase highlighted the tough regulatory landscape crypto businesses faced in the US as the industry continued to fight for clarity from relevant authorities.</p>
<p dir="ltr">After the agency, led by Chair Gary Gensler, alleged the above coins and many others were securities, Revolut&rsquo;s US partner Bakkt moved to delist Polygon, Cardano and Solana. The publicly-listed crypto custodian announced the delistings in mid-June.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Revolut has advised customers to sell their holdings on the app before September 18, after which any unsold assets will be sold and the cash deposited in users&rsquo; fiat accounts.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Notably, the delisting only affects US-based users, meaning support will continue across other markets. There has also been other platforms that moved to remove various crypto tokens, including Robinhood and eToro.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/revolut-to-delist-polygon-solana-and-cardano/">Revolut to delist Polygon, Solana and Cardano</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/revolut-to-delist-polygon-solana-and-cardano/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Celo price goes parabolic amid rapid ecosystem growth</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/celo-price-goes-parabolic-amid-rapid-ecosystem-growth/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/celo-price-goes-parabolic-amid-rapid-ecosystem-growth/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 16:31:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CELO News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/celo-price-goes-parabolic-amid-rapid-ecosystem-growth/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Celo crypto price has gone parabolic in the past few days.&#160; The network&#8217;s ecosystem growth has continued to accelerate. Celo recently integrated Chainlink in its ecosystem. Celo price has made a spectacular comeback this month, making it one of the best-performing cryptocurrencies in the industry. The token soared to a high of $0.6736 on Monday, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/celo-price-goes-parabolic-amid-rapid-ecosystem-growth/">Celo price goes parabolic amid rapid ecosystem growth</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Celo crypto price has gone parabolic in the past few days.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The network&rsquo;s ecosystem growth has continued to accelerate.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Celo recently integrated Chainlink in its ecosystem.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/celo/"><u>Celo</u></a> price has made a spectacular comeback this month, making it one of the best-performing cryptocurrencies in the industry. The token soared to a high of $0.6736 on Monday, the highest level since April 19th. It has jumped by more than 85% from the lowest level in June.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Celo user growth continuing</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Celo is a fast-growing blockchain that is gaining traction among developers and users. The platform is used to build quality dApps in all industries, including DeFi and non-fungible tokens (NFTs). It is able to handle about 11.99 blocks per second.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Celo&rsquo;s ecosystem growth has continued. According to DeFi Llama, the total value locked (TVL) jumped to more than $116 million. The biggest DeFi apps in the ecosystem are Mento, Curve DEX, Uniswap V3, and Moola Market among others.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The main reason why Celo price is soaring is that the number of active users in the ecosystem is growing. For example, data compiled by Dune Analytics shows that the number of transactions in the ecosystem has jumped to over 228 million.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Celo has handled over 20.15 million blocks over the years while the number of active addresses jumped to over 2.4 million. It has handled over 12.1 million contracts.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Celo seems to be popping off. Impressive user and transaction growth numbers lately.</p>
<p>Anyone know what's driving this? <a href="https://t.co/0yhA0fpjSS">pic.twitter.com/0yhA0fpjSS</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Haseeb &#65310;|&#65308; (@hosseeb) <a href="https://twitter.com/hosseeb/status/1674848704241729537?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 30, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">The other important Celo news is that the developers recently integrated&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/chainlink/"><u>Chainlink</u><strong><u>&rsquo;s</u></strong></a><strong>&nbsp;</strong>data feeds. Chainlink, the biggest oracle network in the world. An oracle is a platform that connects off-chain data to the on-chain. In an announcement, the head of ecosystem growth at Celo said:</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;Chainlink Data Feeds will empower Celo developers, providing critical access to oracle data and services and bolster Celo&rsquo;s dApps to drive real-world impact and solutions.&rdquo;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Celo price prediction</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/03/1688401819607-967798be-320e-4934-a338-58afca6b4a0a.png" style="width: 616px;height: 299.267px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="616" height="299.267"></p>
<p dir="ltr">The 4H chart shows that the CELO crypto price has made a strong bullish trend in the past few weeks. As it jumped, the token rose above the key resistance point at $0.5686, the highest level on June 3rd. It has moved above the 25-day and 50-day moving averages.</p>
<p dir="ltr">A the same time, the Relative Strength Index (RSI) moved to the overbought level. The MACD has jumped to the highest level in months. Therefore, with the coin being overbought, there is a likelihood that Celo will retreat and retest the support at $0.5686.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy Celo</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>


<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=MTQ1MDU0&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy CELO with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    Binance.US</h3>


<p>
    <a href="/visit/binance-us-crypto?guid=MTQ1MDU0&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy CELO with Binance.US today            </a>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/celo-price-goes-parabolic-amid-rapid-ecosystem-growth/">Celo price goes parabolic amid rapid ecosystem growth</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/celo-price-goes-parabolic-amid-rapid-ecosystem-growth/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Largest crypto ATM operator Bitcoin Depot debuts on Nasdaq after SPAC merger</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/largest-crypto-atm-operator-bitcoin-depot-debuts-on-nasdaq-after-spac-merger/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 16:03:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto adoption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/largest-crypto-atm-operator-bitcoin-depot-debuts-on-nasdaq-after-apac-merger/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin Depot has merged with special purpose acquisition company (SPAC) GSR II Meteora (GSRM). Bitcoin Depot went ahead to also debut on Nasdaq after the merger. Bitcoin Depot shares more than doubled after debut. Following a merger with special purpose acquisition company (SPAC) GSR II Meteora (GSRM), which was valued at $885 million in August, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/largest-crypto-atm-operator-bitcoin-depot-debuts-on-nasdaq-after-spac-merger/">Largest crypto ATM operator Bitcoin Depot debuts on Nasdaq after SPAC merger</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitcoin Depot has merged with special purpose acquisition company (SPAC) GSR II Meteora (GSRM).</li>
<li>Bitcoin Depot went ahead to also debut on Nasdaq after the merger.</li>
<li>Bitcoin Depot shares more than doubled after debut.</li>
</ul>
<p>Following a merger with special purpose acquisition company (SPAC) GSR II Meteora (GSRM), which was valued at $885 million in August, shares of Bitcoin Depot, the largest crypto ATM operator in the world, more than doubled on their Nasdaq debut Monday.</p>
<p>Bitcoin Depot, situated in Atlanta, Georgia, and trading under the ticker &ldquo;BTM,&rdquo; is the first provider of cryptocurrency ATMs to be listed on a significant American stock exchange.</p>
<p>In pre-market trading, BTM shares climbed as high as $6.60, more than double GSRM&rsquo;s closing price on Friday, before tumbling to $3.39, which is still up 5% from Friday&rsquo;s price.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Depot controls a 20% market share of ATMs</h2>
<p>According to <a href="https://coinatmradar.com/">information</a> from Coin ATM Radar, Bitcoin Depot operates approximately 6,000 of these machines, holding a 20% market share of ATMs in the United States and a 17.6% global share.</p>
<p>There is a lot of space for consolidation in the cryptocurrency ATM business because it is &ldquo;highly fragmented,&rdquo; according to Bitcoin Depot CEO Brandon Mintz. The company is now focusing on this area.</p>
<p>According to Mintz, after installing crypto ATMs in more than 2,000 Circle K convenience stores over the last two years, Bitcoin Depot is pursuing analogous installation deals with other &ldquo;household name retailers.&rdquo;</p>
<p>With the help of crypto ATMs, customers purchase cryptocurrency with cash or debit cards and wire the tokens directly to a specific wallet without using a <a href="https://coinjournal.net/compare/best-cryptocurrency-exchanges/">cryptocurrency exchange</a>. However, scammers who advertise things on websites like eBay or Craigslist with instructions for buyers to pay by depositing actual cash at an ATM have also used them.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/largest-crypto-atm-operator-bitcoin-depot-debuts-on-nasdaq-after-spac-merger/">Largest crypto ATM operator Bitcoin Depot debuts on Nasdaq after SPAC merger</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alex The Doge (ALEX) Aims to Emulate Bitcoin Cash (BCH) Rally Upon Launch</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/alex-the-doge-alex-aims-to-emulate-bitcoin-cash-bch-rally-upon-launch/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/alex-the-doge-alex-aims-to-emulate-bitcoin-cash-bch-rally-upon-launch/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire &#160;]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 14:14:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=145013</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Frankfurt, Germany, July 3rd, 2023, Chainwire The team behind Alex The Doge (ALEX), the memecoin powering the GameFi ecosystem of the same name, are hoping the token can emulate BCH upon launch. Currently in its presale phase, hopes are high that ALEX will hit the market with a bang, making the sort of headline-grabbing moves [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/alex-the-doge-alex-aims-to-emulate-bitcoin-cash-bch-rally-upon-launch/">Alex The Doge (ALEX) Aims to Emulate Bitcoin Cash (BCH) Rally Upon Launch</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Frankfurt, Germany, July 3rd, 2023, Chainwire</strong></p>
<p>The team behind Alex The Doge (ALEX), the memecoin powering the GameFi ecosystem of the same name, are hoping the token can emulate BCH upon launch. Currently in its presale phase, hopes are high that ALEX will hit the market with a bang, making the sort of headline-grabbing moves that Bitcoin Cash (BCH) has recorded lately.</p>
<p>The recent surge in price of Bitcoin Cash (BCH) has caught the attention of the cryptocurrency community. The Proof of Work cryptocurrency is up 160% over the past month. At the same time, interest in another digital asset that has yet to debut, Alex The Doge (ALEX), has been ramping up.</p>
<p>Alex The Doge (ALEX) is a unique project that combines the appeal of memecoins with the utility of decentralized finance (DeFi) and play-to-earn gaming. Its presale phase, during which early supporters can acquire ALEX tokens ahead of the token&rsquo;s DEX launch, has generated strong interest that augurs well for the project&rsquo;s prospects.</p>
<p>Alex The Doge aims to revolutionize the gaming industry by creating a digital gaming world called the Miracle Verse. This ecosystem will enable users to engage in play-to-earn gaming, social trading, and DeFi activities.</p>
<p>Built on the Polygon blockchain for scalability and security, Alex The Doge (ALEX) has positioned itself as a promising GameFi player in the crypto space. Its comprehensive roadmap, whitepaper, and strong community support have contributed to its growing popularity.</p>
<p>Once the token launches, the Alex The Doge roadmap will advance to its next phase, introducing key milestones including the Miracle Verse, complete with the opportunities this holds for gaming, social interaction, and DeFi, all powered by ALEX.</p>
<h3>About ALEX</h3>
<p><a href="https://alexthedoge.live/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">ALEX</a>&nbsp;is the newest Doge on the block, Welcome to the future of Play-To-Earn Gaming and Social-Fi! Alex The Doge is a community project with a focal point on the end user experience, ALEX will revolutionize P2E gaming and expand our ecosystem to alternative gaming communities using cross chain compatibility and creating a fluid transition between gaming credits and digital assets.</p>
<p><strong>For more information about Alex The Doge (ALEX) presale:&nbsp;</strong></p>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://alexthedoge.live/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><strong>Website</strong></a></li>
<li><a href="https://t.me/alexthedoge" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><strong>Telegram</strong></a></li>
<li><a href="https://twitter.com/AlexTheDoge_p2e" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><strong>Twitter</strong></a></li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Contact</strong></p>
<p>Community lead<br>
Zack Anderson<br>
Alex The Doge<br>
support@alexthedoge.live</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/alex-the-doge-alex-aims-to-emulate-bitcoin-cash-bch-rally-upon-launch/">Alex The Doge (ALEX) Aims to Emulate Bitcoin Cash (BCH) Rally Upon Launch</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/alex-the-doge-alex-aims-to-emulate-bitcoin-cash-bch-rally-upon-launch/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Punk Domains partners with Flare to boost Its newly-launch domain extensions</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/punk-domains-partners-with-flare-to-boost-its-newly-launch-domain-extensions/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/punk-domains-partners-with-flare-to-boost-its-newly-launch-domain-extensions/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 14:05:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/punk-domains-partners-with-flare-to-boost-its-newly-launch-domain-extensions/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways Punk Domains Partners with Flare to boost its domain extensions. The newly-launched domain extensions are .SGB (Songbird Domains) and .FLR (flr.domains).&#160; This means that users can use their web3 domains as social media handles.&#160; Punk Domains Partners With Flare Web3 domain name protocol Punk Domains, announced on Monday, July 3rd, that it has [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/punk-domains-partners-with-flare-to-boost-its-newly-launch-domain-extensions/">Punk Domains partners with Flare to boost Its newly-launch domain extensions</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Punk Domains Partners with Flare to boost its domain extensions.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The newly-launched domain extensions are .SGB (Songbird Domains) and .FLR (flr.domains).&nbsp;</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">This means that users can use their web3 domains as social media handles.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr">Punk Domains Partners With Flare</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Web3 domain name protocol Punk Domains, announced on Monday, July 3rd, that it has partnered with the Flare blockchain, gaining thousands of registrations for its newly-launched domain extensions, .SGB (Songbird Domains) and .FLR (flr.domains).&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">In a press release shared with Coinjournal, the team said the domains could represent personal usernames, profiles, and identities in the fast-growing web3 world.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Thanks to this latest development, users can use their web3 domains as social media handles, attach data to them, and simplify the process of sending tokens by using a domain rather than a long string of alphanumeric characters.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Following this latest development, Punk Domains said it plans to integrate the domains into the Bifrost wallet. This would allow Flare users to mint their domains and transfer funds in a much easier way.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Flare Time Series Oracle To Be Integrated Into Punk Domains</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The team also revealed that the Flare Time Series Oracle (FTSO) will also be integrated to ensure fixed domain pricing regardless of SGB and FLR price deviations.</p>
<p dir="ltr">While commenting on this <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>latest cryptocurrency news</u></a>, Punk Domains&rsquo; co-founders Techie.flr and Tekr.flr, stated that;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;When we launched our protocol on Songbird, the community welcomed us warmly and with great excitement. Their support touched us deeply and inspired us to create even more tools in this ecosystem. We&rsquo;re eagerly looking forward to what lies ahead as we continue building on Flare and Songbird.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p dir="ltr">Before the launching of .SGB and .FLR, Punk Domains created a number of domain services, including .smol in the Arbitrum-based Smolverse and .klima domains alongside klimaDAO.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Punk Domains also created an open-source decentralized social network built on Songbird, SGB Chat. The network supported a wide range of DeFi tools that allow users to access token swaps and other DeFi features without leaving the platform.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Flare has been making big strides despite the bear market. In May, Flare&rsquo;s API Portal <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/flares-api-portal-launches-on-the-google-cloud-marketplace/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>launched on the Google Cloud Marketplace</u></a>. This means that blockchain data from Flare&rsquo;s nodes and Connected Chain nodes can be accessed by developers using Google Cloud Marketplace to perform easy blockchain transactions and read up-to-date states.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Punk Domains is a permissionless, decentralized domain name service running on multiple blockchains. The Web3 venture allows users to register a domain name that serves as a human-readable label for blockchain addresses, representing personal usernames, profiles, and identities.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Meanwhile, Flare is the blockchain for data: the only Layer 1 focused on providing developers with information at scale in a decentralized manner. Flare is EVM based and has data acquisition protocols built into the blockchain rather than on top of it, so it can offer inexpensive and highly scalable access to more types of quality data.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/punk-domains-partners-with-flare-to-boost-its-newly-launch-domain-extensions/">Punk Domains partners with Flare to boost Its newly-launch domain extensions</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/punk-domains-partners-with-flare-to-boost-its-newly-launch-domain-extensions/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Belarus planning to ban P2P crypto transactions</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/belarus-planning-to-ban-p2p-crypto-transactions/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/belarus-planning-to-ban-p2p-crypto-transactions/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 09:54:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/belarus-planning-to-ban-p2p-crypto-transactions/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Belarusian President Alexander Lukashenko in 2022 signed a decree allowing free circulation of cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin in the country. The announcement somewhat seems to contradict the previous stand that Belarus has had on cryptocurrencies. If effected, Belarusians will not be allowed to use peer-to-peer crypto exchanges. The foreign ministry of Belarus is drafting new legislation [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/belarus-planning-to-ban-p2p-crypto-transactions/">Belarus planning to ban P2P crypto transactions</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Belarusian President Alexander Lukashenko in 2022 signed a decree allowing free circulation of cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin in the country.</li>
<li>The announcement somewhat seems to contradict the previous stand that Belarus has had on cryptocurrencies.</li>
<li>If effected, Belarusians will not be allowed to use peer-to-peer crypto exchanges.</li>
</ul>
<p>The foreign ministry of Belarus is drafting new legislation to outlaw peer-to-peer (P2P) cryptocurrency transactions of cryptocurrencies like <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/what-is-bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a>.</p>
<p>On July 2, the Republic of Belarus&rsquo; Ministry of Foreign Affairs (MFA) made a formal announcement on Telegram regarding the new legislation that will outlaw peer-to-peer (P2P) cryptocurrency transactions for individuals.</p>
<p>Belarus&rsquo; Ministry of Foreign Affairs (MFA) announcement runs somewhat afoul of the recent laws that Belarus has passed. President Alexander Lukashenko of Belarus officially endorsed the free circulation of cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin in 2022.</p>
<h2>Belarus cites high rate of cybercrime</h2>
<p>The authorities cited Belarus&rsquo; high rate of cybercrime and claimed that since the year&rsquo;s beginning, local prosecutors have stopped 27 citizens from offering &ldquo;illegal crypto exchange services.&rdquo;</p>
<p>The total earning from illicit earnings totalled about 22 million Belarusian rubles ($8.7 million).</p>
<p>According to the foreign ministry, cryptocurrency P2P services are &ldquo;in demand among thieves who cash out and convert stolen funds and transfer money to criminal scheme organizers or participants.&rdquo;</p>
<p>The MFA will forbid individuals from P2P and only permit them to exchange cryptocurrencies only through <a href="https://coinjournal.net/compare/best-cryptocurrency-exchanges/">cryptocurrency exchanges</a> registered with Belarus Hi-Tech Park in order to eradicate such illicit activity (HTP). It also stated that it intends to implement a practice that will make it &ldquo;impossible to withdraw money obtained from illegal activity,&rdquo; similar to the process for exchanging foreign currencies.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/belarus-planning-to-ban-p2p-crypto-transactions/">Belarus planning to ban P2P crypto transactions</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/belarus-planning-to-ban-p2p-crypto-transactions/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
