<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 07:06:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Cathie Wood&#8217;s Ark Invest buys another $3.2 million worth of Coinbase shares</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/cathie-woods-ark-invest-buys-another-3-2-million-worth-of-coinbase-shares/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/cathie-woods-ark-invest-buys-another-3-2-million-worth-of-coinbase-shares/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 07:05:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ARK Investment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/cathie-woods-ark-invest-buys-another-3-2-million-worth-of-coinbase-shares/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ark Invest has invested another $3.2 million in Coinbase, bringing its total shares to 5.8 million. COIN is up by nearly 4% during Thursday&#8217;s pre-market trading session. Coinbase has underperformed this year and could record losses by the end of the year. Ark Invest purchases $3.2 million worth of Coinbase shares Cathie Wood&#8217;s Ark Invest [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/cathie-woods-ark-invest-buys-another-3-2-million-worth-of-coinbase-shares/">Cathie Wood&#8217;s Ark Invest buys another $3.2 million worth of Coinbase shares</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Ark Invest has invested another $3.2 million in Coinbase, bringing its total shares to 5.8 million.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">COIN is up by nearly 4% during Thursday&rsquo;s pre-market trading session.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Coinbase has underperformed this year and could record losses by the end of the year.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Ark Invest purchases $3.2 million worth of Coinbase shares</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Cathie Wood&rsquo;s Ark Invest revealed a few hours ago that it had purchased $3.2 million worth of Coinbase shares (COIN). The investment firm continues to increase its exposure to the company despite the ongoing bear market.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Following this latest development, Ark Invest now holds 5.8 million COIN shares, worth approximately $228 million. COIN is a part of its tech-focused ARK Innovation ETF (ARKK) as the company doubles down on investments during the bear market.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The latest investment comes a few days after&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ark-invest-purchases-over-78k-coinbase-shares-despite-sliding-prices/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Ark Invest purchased 78,982 shares</u></a> of Coinbase shares at $3,184,554.24.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">COIN has responded positively to the news of Ark Invest&rsquo;s latest investment. The stock price is up by 3.8% during Thursday&rsquo;s pre-market trading session and is now trading at $40.19.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>COIN is down by 83% YTD</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Despite performing well over the past few hours, COIN has underperformed since the start of the year. Year-to-date (YTD), COIN has lost 83% of its value, thanks to the broader cryptocurrency market experiencing a bearish trend.</p>
<p dir="ltr">COIN began the year trading at $251 per share but is now trading just above $40 per share. Bitcoin and the other leading cryptocurrencies have lost more than 75% of their value over the last 12 months, a major factor that affected COIN&rsquo;s performance.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Brian Armstrong, the CEO of Coinbase, revealed earlier this month that he expects the company&rsquo;s 2022&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-fy2022-revenue-to-be-less-than-half-of-fy2021-revenue-says-brian-armstrong/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>revenue to decline by 50% or more</u></a> compared to what they recorded in 2021. He said;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;Last year in 2021, we did about $7 billion of revenue and about $4 billion of positive EBITDA, and this year with everything coming down, it&rsquo;s looking, you know, about roughly half that or less.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p dir="ltr">In 2021, the company generated around $7 billion in revenue, but market analysts expect the figure to drop to $3.2 billion in 2022.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/cathie-woods-ark-invest-buys-another-3-2-million-worth-of-coinbase-shares/">Cathie Wood&#8217;s Ark Invest buys another $3.2 million worth of Coinbase shares</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/cathie-woods-ark-invest-buys-another-3-2-million-worth-of-coinbase-shares/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Expert panel: what are the 3 most important things to look out for when choosing a crypto platform to sign up to?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/expert-panel-what-are-the-3-most-important-things-to-look-out-for-when-choosing-a-crypto-platform-to-sign-up-to/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/expert-panel-what-are-the-3-most-important-things-to-look-out-for-when-choosing-a-crypto-platform-to-sign-up-to/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dan Ashmore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 17:42:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Interview]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/expert-panel-what-are-the-3-most-important-things-to-look-out-for-when-choosing-a-crypto-platform-to-sign-up-to/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>It has been a scary year in the crypto markets.&#160; It feels like every week has brought a new scandal. There was the death spiral of the Terra ecosystem in May, which sparked a wave of contagion across the industry.&#160; Down went crypto lenders Celsius and Voyager Digital, among others.&#160; Then, even more spectacularly, was [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/expert-panel-what-are-the-3-most-important-things-to-look-out-for-when-choosing-a-crypto-platform-to-sign-up-to/">Expert panel: what are the 3 most important things to look out for when choosing a crypto platform to sign up to?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">It has been a scary year in the crypto markets.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">It feels like every week has brought a new scandal. There was the death spiral of the Terra ecosystem in May, which sparked a wave of contagion across the industry.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Down went crypto lenders Celsius and Voyager Digital, among others.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Then, even more spectacularly, was the collapse of former tier-1 exchange FTX, with $8 billion of customer assets lost. This has led to the bankruptcy of BlockFi and a range of other firms, with more contagion likely still to come.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Against this backdrop, it has never been more important to choose your crypto platform wisely. On this note, we sat down with a few industry experts to get their thoughts on an important question, as part of our series asking expert panels for advice in crypto:</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em><strong>What are the 3 most important things to look out for when choosing a crypto platform to sign up to?</strong></em></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Ramani Ramachandran, CEO and Co-Founder of <a href="https://www.routerprotocol.com/"><u>Router Protocol</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Trading on crypto platforms is certainly alluring to new Web 3.0 users, but the sheer number of platforms often acts as roadblocks for making the first trade. In my opinion, if you want to judge the merit of a crypto platform these are the 3 things to look out for.&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Security: Look at features like two-factor authentication, password recovery options, and multiple different factors that can determine if a platform has security measures in place or not. Moreover, since the ecosystem is still relatively young, you can&rsquo;t ignore the possibility of a hack entirely, so you should also look at the terms and conditions to see what is insured and what&rsquo;s not if a hack takes place.&nbsp;</li>
<li dir="ltr">Regulatory Compliances: The good thing about Web 3.0 is that everyone is invited to build and scale. However, when it comes to crypto exchanges, you should take an additional step to know if the team behind the crypto exchange is firstly complying with basic regulations like KYC and anti-money laundering checks. And secondly, check if the team is from a politically stable state that can hold them accountable if they engage in any malpractice.&nbsp;</li>
<li dir="ltr">Variety of Tokens and liquidity: Contrary to popular belief, not every exchange has the same tokens and networks as part of their trading ethos. Generally speaking, you should always opt for trading platforms that provide the most number of tokens and networks for you to trade and also have sufficient liquidity for these pairs</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr"></h2>
<h2 dir="ltr">Stefan Rust, CEO of <a href="https://www.lagunalabs.io/"><u>Laguna Labs</u></a>, says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Crypto platforms have evolved tremendously over the past 5 years &ndash; they come in all shapes and sizes offering all kinds of different assets and trading strategies. And so, the first thing to do is figure out what you want &ndash; just a bit of Bitcoin, or Bitcoin derivatives? Or do you want to get into DeFi staking or borrowing? The answers to these questions will lead you to your platform. Secondly, you&rsquo;ll want to consider your jurisdiction and any tax or regulatory implications and then, finally, how reputable the platform and team behind it is.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Marius Ciuboatriu, co-founder of <a href="https://hubbleprotocol.io/"><u>Hubble Protocol</u></a>, says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">If you&rsquo;re new to crypto, then it&rsquo;s really important to choose a platform that is transparent, has a strong community, and takes security seriously. Read everything in their docs, read their blogs, and read everything you can find out about the platform&mdash;then join the platform&rsquo;s community on Telegram or Discord and start asking questions. Is it easy to understand how everything works? If they are offering yield, where does the yield come from? Finally, is the platform audited by a trusted security firm? If a platform isn&rsquo;t willing to get a security audit, or even multiple audits after changes are made, then that&rsquo;s a huge red flag.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Tom Norwood, CEO of <a href="https://www.loop.markets/"><u>Loop Finance</u></a>, says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">When looking for a new crypto platform, 1: Look for one selling what you want to buy, and for the right price! If it&rsquo;s undiscovered NFTs you&rsquo;re after, for example, OpenSea is unlikely to be your huckleberry. Then, 2: Choose one that has strong backing from its community. The beauty of crypto is that members of the community can really tell you a lot about a project or protocol. Finally, 3: Think about whether a platform is centralized or decentralized. If the former, you are subject to the decisions (and mistakes) of a select few founders. If the latter, you have total control of your assets.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Dan Ashmore, data analyst at <a href="https://coinjournal.net/author/dan-ashmore/"><u>Coinjournal</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Safety is the biggest. Make 100% sure the platform is reputable. No other factor is anywhere near as important as this. Venturing outside the bigger names should only be done by those more familiar with the industry.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The second most important is reducing the cost. That means ensuring you are paying the lowest fees possible &ndash; deposit fees, FX fees, trading fees etc. Finally, a platform which offers a good range of coins (or specifically, the ones you seek) is preferable.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Martin Lee, Data Journalist at <a href="https://www.nansen.ai/"><u>Nansen</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">For exchanges the main things are:</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">App stability during peak periods (Coinbase known to lag or go down during large moves in the market)</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Trading fees and spot price used during swaps/trades. Some exchanges claim to have no fees but when you use their swap/trading functions you&rsquo;ll realize that the spot price used in the trades is a few percentage points higher than other exchanges.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">General trustworthy-ness of the platform &ndash; do they have coverage/insurance against hacks, public perception, founders background etc.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr">Lars Seier Christensen, chairman of <a href="https://concordium.com/"><u>Concordium</u></a> and founder of <a href="https://www.home.saxo/"><u>Saxo Bank</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">First of all, I would like to say that I have spent nearly all my professional life dealing with mostly semi-professional and sophisticated clients dealing in speculative investments. Foreign exchange, futures, CFDs, leveraged trading. And out of all of these, I consider crypto to be the most risky and volatile asset class I have ever dealt with. So before even opening an account, people have to educate themselves thoroughly on what they are getting into. If in doubt, stay out.</p>
<p dir="ltr">If they still want to engage and open a brokerage or exchange crypto account, they should choose a provider that is regulated in a solid jurisdiction. They should start with CEXes, rather than DEXes and not start in opaque DeFi schemes. They should check the financial solidity of who they deal with and they should look for people that are open and transparent about their management and their experience. Who is responsible? And are they qualified?</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Yang Lan, founder of <a href="https://fiat24.com/"><u>Fiat24</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Crypto platforms can refer to many things &ndash; cryptocurrencies, wallets, exchanges, lending protocols, etc.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Regardless, the top 3 things to look out for are to look for signs that it is trustworthy (white papers, roadmaps, community, transparency, the team behind it); research to understand its potential value in the future (market cap, historical performance, tokenomics, etc); and finally, try to place it in the larger scheme of the space right now (the competition, trends, new technologies, external factors).&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Dmitry Gooshchin, COO and Co-Founder of <a href="https://endotech.io/"><u>EndoTech</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The three most important things to look out for when choosing a crypto platform are reputation, functionality, and fees.&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Reputation: you want your investment to succeed or fail on its own merits, not on the wallet you choose. Therefore, it&rsquo;s important to understand that we are in a new era and there are many fly-by-night companies. You want to make sure you have a business that has adequate regulatory and security oversight.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Functionality: while you may start with a simple buy/sell, you&rsquo;ll likely want to grow into more advanced solutions like trading algorithms and AltCoins. Make sure your wallet can grow in sophistication with you.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Fees: too many people make this their #1 criteria. While it does add up in the end, it&rsquo;s more important to have a reputable and functional wallet for your investments.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bobby Pham &ndash; CMO <a href="https://kardiachain.io/"><u>KardiaChain</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">I&rsquo;m assuming the question when asking about the platform is regarding an exchange or wallet.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The 3 most important factors to consider when deciding which platform to sign up for are:</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Security. The crypto industry is still in its infant stages. Thus, security issues, bugs, and hacks are still common within the industry. Evaluate the security of a platform when you&rsquo;re deciding which to sign up for. Essentially, the more checks and requirements a platform asks of you to sign up, the more secure it is.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Insurance Policy. Even the most secure platforms can be prone to hacks and risks, so the next factor in evaluating is a platform&rsquo;s insurance policy. If the platform is hacked, how much money do they have to restore users&rsquo; lost funds? For example, Coinbase has an insurance policy of up to $225 Million in its reserves if users&rsquo; funds are hacked. Having the peace of mind of knowing that your funds are safe even in the event of a hack is another factor to consider.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Customer Support. A strong, available customer support system is a green flag of a trusted platform. While great improvements have been made in the ease and simplicity of using crypto platforms, it&rsquo;s still confusing for many new to the space. Crypto platforms that have a strong and available customer support team in place is indicative of a brand that cares about its users.</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr"></h2>
<h2 dir="ltr">Joerg Hansen, CEO of <a href="https://caizcoin.com/"><u>Caiz Development GmbH</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The most important thing to look out for when choosing a crypto platform is the high-security standard of a crypto exchange. Rule of thumb: the harder it is to create an account at a particular exchange and the more checks they do, the better it is. Trustworthiness is important, to protect and be able to track and manage your digital assets anytime. As the crypto community loves to say: &ldquo;Not your keys, not your coins. So either store cryptos in your own (preferably cold) wallet with your own keys, or only entrust your assets to regulated and reputable institutional providers.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The second most important thing when choosing a crypto platform is to be aware of fees and pairs. Most crypto exchanges will include some type of fee for any transactions which is based on the size of the transaction or dependent upon your level of activity or membership. Do you plan to be highly active, making transactions every day? If so, perhaps consider an exchange with a lower per-transaction fee.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The third important thing in choosing a crypto platform is the volume of a crypto coin or a crypto pair. If you see a coin that&rsquo;s appreciating on the back of high volume, it&rsquo;s more likely to be a sustainable move. Logically, when more money is moving into a cryptocurrency, it means there is more demand for the crypto coin and for the crypto platform.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Lang Mei, CEO of <a href="https://airdao.io/"><u>AirDAO</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Unfortunately, the decentralization-focused crypto industry has a long history of centralized exchanges misappropriating users&rsquo; funds. Infamously, Mt. Gox exchange went insolvent after a hacker stole funds deposited by customers, and the hack resulted in a near-decade legal battle that still hasn&rsquo;t been fully resolved yet. You must learn from the past and ask yourself whether you can trust the crypto exchange you are going to use:</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Research whether the exchange you plan to use has a good reputation.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Get a hardware wallet to safely withdraw your assets immediately after purchase instead of leaving them on a centralized exchange.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Look into DeFi as an alternative to using centralized exchanges.</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Vlad Totia, Research Analyst at <a href="http://www.zilliqa.com/"><u>Zilliqa</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Maturity: Crypto has come a long way since truly gaining mainstream attention back in 2017. Although there are still many scams around, a good portion of the space has matured. One of the best indicators of this is the growth of centralized exchanges, like Binance, Coinbase, Kucoin, or ByBit becoming reasonably well-regulated and established.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Security: Even though it&rsquo;s a nuisance every time a deposit or withdrawal gets done, features like 2FA, email, or SMS confirmation are very important for the safety of users&rsquo; funds. Whether it&rsquo;s using a personal cold wallet, a browser wallet, or staying only within the confines of an exchange, it&rsquo;s very good practice to get used to security checks.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Diversity of assets and services: At this stage, most of the big exchanges have grown into their role and offer quite a broad variety of tokens, as well as features to trade, borrow, earn, or stake. Given this &lsquo;one-stop shop&rsquo; reality, it makes the most sense to use only one large exchange when getting started and then become a more advanced user from there.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Hristiyan Hristov, Account Management Team Lead at <a href="https://nexo.io/"><u>Nexo</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">First, identify what your needs are and find the platform that is the best fit for what you require. That&rsquo;ll depend on what you&rsquo;re looking to do, which could be earning interest, trading, borrow/margin, or secure custody. I would strongly recommend finding a place where most of your needs could be accommodated in one place. This will come in handy when the temperature heats up and the market is volatile. In those situations, it might be very slow to move assets around &ndash; due to network congestions and other circumstances &ndash; which can prevent you from achieving the best results and protecting your funds.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Second tip: If you&rsquo;re planning on moving assets from a cold wallet to a custodial one, security should take center stage in your research. You must diligently check if the platform you&rsquo;re planning to move funds to has had any issues in the past and what practices it follows. Check whether it has reputable partners, licenses and registrations, are its financials audited, and is there any insurance. 2FA authentication, in particular, is an absolute must, no matter the amount of money you are holding.</p>
<p dir="ltr">And now, number three: sustainability. &nbsp;Don&rsquo;t be attracted to the glamour of abnormally high yields or low interest rates. As a general rule, if something looks too good to be true, it usually is. Always ask yourself if the offered rates and services are sustainable in the long term, and compare them to what other market participants are offering. Any serious outliers from the &ldquo;normal&rdquo; range should have you raising an eyebrow.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Wolfgang R&uuml;ckerl, Co-Founder and CEO of <a href="https://istari.vision/en/"><u>Istari Vision</u></a> and <a href="https://entity.global/"><u>Entity</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">When deciding where to invest your crypto, it&rsquo;s crucial to choose a platform with a healthy trading volume. This is an indicator of both the available liquidity and the reputation of the platform, since low volume means that big money investors do not trust a given exchange. A high volume shows that an exchange is trusted, and also means there are more fees to reward liquidity providers.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Investors must also assess whether a platform supports a range of different tokens. Bigger platforms tend to have a bigger selection, which presents more options for investors and leads to greater capital flows.</p>
<p dir="ltr">It is also crucial to pay attention to the global availability and legal status of exchanges. Some platforms are restricted in certain countries, which limits the potential user base. Furthermore, some platforms might even operate without a license in some jurisdictions. This is a red flag that an exchange is not serious about regulatory compliance.&rdquo;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Nimantha Siriwardana, Co-Founder and CTO of <a href="https://metacask.com/"><u>Metacask</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The first thing new crypto users need to look out for is whether it&rsquo;s a legitimate company. Do they have a history? Check that they have a legitimate business address and real people working there. There are plenty of fraudulent exchanges and websites that pretend to be existing exchanges. It&rsquo;s a relatively new and unregulated industry, so there are plenty of scoundrels out there looking to take your hard-earned cash.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Users also need to be aware of how simple or difficult it is to deposit and withdraw their fiat currency (USD, GBP, EUR). Check your bank&rsquo;s stance on cryptocurrencies &ndash; some banks are less crypto-friendly than others and will not accept deposits from crypto exchanges.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In addition, users should check the exchange fees &ndash; platforms charge varying transaction fees, so if you&rsquo;re making lots of transactions, these can quickly add up.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Tahem Verma, Co-Founder and CEO of <a href="https://www.mesha.club/"><u>mesha</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Security and trust are vital when choosing a crypto platform. Investors need to be aware of where their funds will be held and whether the platform has suffered any hacks. Checking the reviews is also an easy way to get an inside look into existing users&rsquo; experiences. The chosen crypto platform should be regulated and have the proper licenses in place. In addition, investors should review the platform&rsquo;s pricing in terms of their fees and spreads.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Andrew Levine, CEO and Co-Founder of <a href="https://koinos.group/"><u>Koinos Group</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">When choosing a crypto platform to sign up for, one should always ask &lsquo;What is the unique value proposition of the platform?&rsquo; Basically, how is the platform advancing the field? Besides looking into the monetary potential of a platform, investors should evaluate if the platform will contribute in a meaningful way and what the growth potential of the proposed technology is.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Additionally, a potential investor should examine how easy it is to develop applications on the blockchain. Will the blockchain require frequent updates or hard forks that will disrupt the flow of innovation? When looking to invest in a new crypto platform, an investor should predict whether there is a fluid way to develop dApps. The technology should support innovation.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Another important factor is how pleasant the user experience is. Will developers actually want to build on the platform? This goes back to the ability for the blockchain to evolve and the upgradability of the platform. It&rsquo;s also important to note if the platform is accessible to new users or if there are many barriers to entry.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Pannathorn Lorattawut, CEO of VUCA Digital, from the <a href="https://crowntoken.io/"><u>CROWN Token Project</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The first thing you need to consider is the credibility of the company, the team, and their projects. When you sign up for something, you give personal information to that platform. Doing due diligence on the reputation and security of the platform will help mitigate the risk. You can also check whether they have customer support and a channel to contact them if something goes wrong.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Next, consider the real growth opportunities of the projects. You should understand the purposes and products of the platform, its sources of revenue, and key drivers that support the growth. This will help you evaluate the platform&rsquo;s sustainability and see whether the returns from its products are reasonable.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Lastly, look at the features of the platform and its project. Each platform may provide different solutions, for example, functions, flexibility, security, fee, and return. The platform&rsquo;s current features and its roadmap will help answer whether it is what you&rsquo;re looking for.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Richa Joshi, Co-Founder of <a href="https://push.org/"><u>Push Protocol</u></a> says:</h2>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr"><strong>Existing Adoption.&nbsp;</strong>There is certainly opportunity to be found by interacting with a crypto platform in its earliest days &mdash; especially if there are token incentives involved, such as LPing in DeFi protocols. However, early adopters also shoulder significant risk; volatility risk and security risk. Seeking out projects that have a proven track record of adoption is a more assured way of interacting with web3 in a secure manner.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr"><strong>Partners &amp; Supporters.&nbsp;</strong>Though web3 is a space where an individual can go far, many of the most impressive protocols have a strong network of partners and supporters. These can include investors, technical partners, and customers. Seeking projects that have a &ldquo;wall&rdquo; of supporters and partners that <em>you&nbsp;</em>also trust is typically good practice when choosing a protocol.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr"><strong>Community Sentiment.&nbsp;</strong>Spend some time in the communities of the projects you&rsquo;re considering &mdash; mainly Discord and Twitter. How are those community members interacting with the protocol? Are they combative or supportive? Is there an over-emphasis on token price, or does there appear to be general consensus that the technology and utility of the project is more interesting? A community makes a project, so look for the best communities out there.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr">Joshua Tobkin, CEO and Co-Founder of <a href="https://supraoracles.com/"><u>SupraOracles</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">When choosing a crypto platform to sign up to, be sure to check that the site is reputable, and that the URL is spelled exactly as it is meant to be spelled (beware of copycat sites that are run by scammers). Also, look for an exchange that offers as many of the tokens you are looking to trade as possible. Lastly, make sure there is a high enough trading volume to ensure you get the proper value for the tokens you are exchanging. I would suggest starting with CEXs and probably only the top 10 you can find on CoinGecko/CoinMarketCap.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Valentin Pletnev, CEO of <a href="https://www.quasar.fi/"><u>Quasar</u></a> says:</h2>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Understanding what risks apply to you. If you choose a custodial provider, you&rsquo;re not only exposed to DeFi risk, you&rsquo;re also exposed to their financial situation and runway management. Not your keys, not your assets.&nbsp;</li>
<li dir="ltr">Team track record &amp; focus on the mission that is being tackled. Professionalism, active development and clear goals are underappreciated in crypto, pick winners</li>
<li dir="ltr">Take the time to understand the foundational knowledge that the crypto platform is built on top of and only choose things you have a clear and immediate need for. Doing your own research is critical and a key principle in crypto.</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Mario Baxter, CTO at <a href="http://www.fun.xyz"><u>Fun</u></a> says:</h2>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Understand what custody looks like. There are 2 main types: externally-custodied and self-custodied. Externally-custodied means that the control of the account resides with the custodian, for example Coinbase. Self-custodied means that you have full control over the account via the storing of a private key or recovery phrase. With great power comes great responsibility, as they say, and this is especially true with regard to crypto custody. If you choose to self-custody your assets (congrats! you are self-sovereign), you need to be extremely careful with how you store your private keys &mdash; if these are lost or compromised you will lose access to all of your funds.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Look into trading fees as well as the features offered. Some platforms offer additional functionality aside from simply being a medium for holding crypto assets. They can offer staking, lending and borrowing, as well as direct integrations with DeFi protocols, just to name a few.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Look into the jurisdictions where the platform is authorized to operate. Some platforms will be geographically bound, meaning that a platform intended for European users may not be accessible in the United States.</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">David Schwed, Chief Operating Officer of <a href="https://halborn.com/"><u>Halborn</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Many may hear the statement &ldquo;not your keys, not your crypto&rdquo;, which means they should hold the information (private key) necessary to effectuate a transaction as opposed to a third party like an exchange. While I fundamentally agree, I think for new crypto users, the safest option is to buy/sell/hold crypto on a centralized exchange. When selecting an exchange, I would look at the following criteria:</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Security, security, security. &nbsp;What security controls have the exchange implemented that help protect your crypto. At a minimum, there should be multi-factor authentication methods besides using a phone number for texting. On the more secure side would be a hardware key or a time-based one-time password.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Jurisdiction is critical. Since many exchanges/companies rise to jurisdictions where there is little to no regulatory oversight, check to see where they are registered and what laws/regulations they have to comply with. Based on that information select an exchange in an area that has strong regulatory oversight.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Thirdly, check if there have been any notable security events in the past 36 months and see what corrective actions have been taken.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr">Limaris Torres, Security Advisor at <a href="https://halborn.com/"><u>Halborn</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">I think, for the newcomers the key things to look at when choosing a crypto platform are usability, security and service. As users, we all have a variety of different skills and our own preferences, so people new to this space should look for something that&rsquo;s easy to use and have simple functionality that can get you started. This means visually easy to navigate but also flexible in terms of web app or mobile app. The best platform for anyone will always be the one they can and do use consistently.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Second and most important is security, there&rsquo;s always risk with investing but the risk should be related to your strategy and not the lack or broken approach to security of the platform. Users should be able to trust that their assets will be safe, the two factor authentication by default should be a norm on any platform.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Lastly, users should look at support and customer service capability of the platform. Mistakes happen and things break. I&rsquo;d suggest paying attention to and choosing a platform with excellent customer service to help you with all your logistical needs.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Paulina J&oacute;&#347;k&oacute;w, Head of Business Development at <a href="https://ramp.network/"><u>Ramp</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">It&rsquo;s all about trust. And as the old adage says, trust arrives on foot and leaves on horseback. But how can you trust a platform with your money and with your crypto? In addition to the obvious suspects (like online reviews, checking age and activity of web properties and social media, etc), here are some things to look out for:</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr"><strong>Transparency</strong>: how upfront and transparent are they &ndash; about their fees, costs, and especially about their team? Don&rsquo;t get me wrong, anonymous teams have built some amazing things. But if you have an issue with your money, would you really prefer to chase after a funny monkey JPEG anon on Discord instead of a registered company?</li>
<li dir="ltr"><strong>Compliance</strong>: the crypto space is maturing and increasingly subject to laws and regulations. Is the platform you&rsquo;re dealing with compliant with global and local regulations? Are they authorised to offer services to your region? If not, this can lead to a host of legal issues to them and you.</li>
<li dir="ltr"><strong>Security history</strong>: it&rsquo;s not just about if a platform has been hacked before (many great ones have, only to emerge stronger). But what caused the attack? What was the platform&rsquo;s response to users, and how honest/transparent were they during the process? And finally, what measures did they take to avoid another similar issue? These answers can tell very different stories, from unfortunate zero-day exploits that got immediately patched, to tales of repeated negligence by irresponsible founders.</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Gabriella Kusz, CEO of the <a href="https://global-dca.org/"><u>Global Digital Asset and Cryptocurrency Association</u></a> says:</h2>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Has the exchange been vetted by a reputable third party? Firms like Digital Asset Research have methodologies that evaluate the quality of an exchange and can be useful in decision making <a href="https://www.digitalassetresearch.com/digital-asset-research-announces-july-2022-crypto-exchange-vetting-results/">https://www.digitalassetresearch.com/digital-asset-research-announces-july-2022-crypto-exchange-vetting-results/</a></li>
<li dir="ltr">Disclosures &ndash; transparency of terms and conditions and user agreement for using the platform should be easy to locate and understand.&nbsp;</li>
<li dir="ltr">Is it regulated? &ndash; Exchanges that are regulated have certain standards to adhere to and oversight. NY State BitLicense is one such example as are state level Money Transmitter Licenses.&nbsp;</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Rashid Ali, co-founder and CEO of <a href="https://exarta.com/"><u>Exarta</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">I guess we are talking about crypto exchanges. For me personally, it&rsquo;s about the crypto options they have as not all platforms have all tokens listed for various reasons. However, more and more, we need to start asking what they are doing about security as exchanges are a prime target, although I would recommend holding any long term crypto in secure cold storage.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Security is becoming an area where exchanges need to show they take it seriously. We have seen many hacks over the years, and I doubt they will stop anytime soon.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Peter Eberle, President and CIO of <a href="https://www.castlefunds.com/"><u>Castle Funds</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Are they legally doing business in your jurisdiction? Though crypto is largely unregulated, in the United States regulations do exist to protect consumers. Through the internet users can access web sites around the world it is important not to circumvent laws as your assets could be frozen.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Fees &ndash; All exchanges have different cost structures. Dig beyond just the commissions. There are fees for moving fiat on and off exchange, commissions, and various other fees.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Liquidity &ndash; The more popular the platform the greater the liquidity. Why does liquidity matter? The spread between bid and offer (where you can buy or sell crypto) can be large or small but even if the spread is small, it might be for only a small amount so if you are trying to buy a larger quantity the spread might be quite large. See how much liquidity there actually is.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Paolo Ardoino, CTO of <a href="https://www.bitfinex.com/"><u>Bitfinex</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">For exchanges the main things are:</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Security, check if an exchange has had any previous incidents and how these incidents were resolved. Also be sure to check what the recourse is for you if your funds in yourwallet have been compromised. It is also helpful to check the liquidity of the exchange and possible issues faced in the past or ongoing with regard to liquidity Very closely aligned to this is to check if the platform has a verification or Know Your Customer (KYC) process &ndash; which serves to protect against fraudulent account creation by verifying that account holders are who they say they are.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Cyber scammers are always looking for new ways to commit fraud. Scammers are increasing in their sophistication. One example is cryptojacking &ndash; where hackers implant a piece of software that mines cryptocurrencies on a victim&rsquo;s computer &ndash; further demonstrates that the ingenuity of cybercrooks should never be underestimated. Unsuspecting victims are left perplexed as their devices slow down to a snail&rsquo;s pace, unaware of the criminal activity and where it emanates from. Whether you are a retail user or a business, you need to remain in a perpetual state of vigilance to guard against such threats. To keep your account safe look at combining password protection and basic anti-phishing controls, which may add resiliency to cryptojacking attempts.</li>
<li dir="ltr">It may seem obvious but users need to check the jurisdiction that the exchange operates in and whether they are able to make use of it and last but not least:</li>
<li dir="ltr">Trading fees and spot price used during swaps/trades. These can sometimes be overlooked, however, certain exchanges claim to have zero fees but when using their swap/trading functions you realize that the spot price used in the trades is a few percentage points higher than other exchanges.</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Jake Yocom-Piatt, Co-Founder and Project Lead of <a href="https://decred.org/"><u>Decred</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The first step is to choose a reputable exchange that supports the right fiat currencies, cryptocurrencies, and customer jurisdictions. Many exchanges only support particular fiat currencies, cryptocurrencies, and customer jurisdictions. &nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Spend time doing your own independent research to find a well-known and well-reviewed exchange that fits your needs. As this is becoming an increasingly common problem, make certain the exchange supports deposits and withdrawals in your cryptocurrencies of choice and not just deposits. &nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Some exchanges only allow deposits and not withdrawals in a given cryptocurrency, and some do not allow either deposits or withdrawals in a given cryptocurrency. The last thing to look out for is being patient. The account registration process at most cryptocurrency exchanges that process fiat can take several days or weeks to complete in a worst-case scenario. &nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Be prepared to submit information similar to what you would submit to open a bank account and for it to take time to verify that information. &nbsp;If you are registering an account during a bull market, account registration delays can be significant.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Charmyn Ho, head of crypto insights at <a href="https://www.bybit.com/"><u>Bybit</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Security, product range and integrity.</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">The number one question the average trader should ask is &ndash; are your assets safe? Exchanges are infrastructure projects that compete on technical expertise. Hence it is important to start with a wallet you can trust on a platform that values security.</li>
<li dir="ltr">More likely than not, your crypto journey will evolve at a fast pace. While everyone&rsquo;s learning curve is different, a beginner may soon find that basic platforms are unable to meet their needs. Hence, you may wish to save your time and money by choosing an exchange with diverse product offerings which also has an increasing number of trading pairs and project listings, as well as more sophisticated products you&rsquo;ll need down the road. Even if you are starting with spot trading a handful of mainstream coins, trading on exchanges with advanced offerings and an edge in derivatives now will save you the hassle of switching later on.</li>
<li dir="ltr">When you consider the platform, the technology it deploys and the company behind it, integrity is critical to your success. To start with, find an exchange with a track record of reliability and a sizable user base. Exchanges with integrity value transparency, fairness and customer support, but more importantly it is able to provide better market depth, liquidity, and resilience in volatile times.&nbsp;</li>
</ul>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/expert-panel-what-are-the-3-most-important-things-to-look-out-for-when-choosing-a-crypto-platform-to-sign-up-to/">Expert panel: what are the 3 most important things to look out for when choosing a crypto platform to sign up to?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/expert-panel-what-are-the-3-most-important-things-to-look-out-for-when-choosing-a-crypto-platform-to-sign-up-to/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto winter may not end anytime soon</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-winter-may-not-end-anytime-soon/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-winter-may-not-end-anytime-soon/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dan Ashmore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 17:41:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-winter-may-not-end-anytime-soon/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key Takeaways Crypto is one year into a vicious bear market This is the first time crypto has experienced a bear market in the wider economy, too With too many negative macro variables, and the zero-interest rate era over, it seems na&#239;ve to think crypto can bounce significantly in the short-term &#160; Anyone betting on [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-winter-may-not-end-anytime-soon/">Crypto winter may not end anytime soon</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>Key Takeaways</h2>
<ul>
<li>Crypto is one year into a vicious bear market</li>
<li>This is the first time crypto has experienced a bear market in the wider economy, too</li>
<li>With too many negative macro variables, and the zero-interest rate era over, it seems na&iuml;ve to think crypto can bounce significantly in the short-term</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>&nbsp;</strong></p>
<p>Anyone betting on a swift recovery in the crypto markets might want to reassess.</p>
<p>If you are familiar with my analysis, you will know I have been bearish for a while. This mainly comes down to the macro setup, as the economy reels in the face of this new paradigm of high-interest rates.</p>
<p>Crypto represents one of the highest-risk asset classes around, and hence was always going to the struggle once the rug was pulled out from under it. And that is what has happened, with Jerome Powell and the Federal Reserve pulling that rug out mercilessly.</p>
<p>With this macro backdrop in this position, there is a ceiling in place. Crypto will not rise until inflation is beaten and interest rates peak. Currently, T-bills are trading at 4%, but this will likely rise to 5% in early 2023.</p>
<p>There is still concern that inflation, which does seem as if it has peaked, will nonetheless persist for some time. The labour market has yet to feel real tightness, while demand has been subdued but not significantly.</p>
<h2><strong>More bad news </strong></h2>
<p>This landscape what was led me to declare that crypto could be <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/is-bitcoin-one-event-away-from-a-world-of-pain/">one bad event away</a> from a &nbsp;meltdown. It was range-bound at the $20,000 mark for too long, unable to break out while restrained by the bearish sentiment in the wider markets.</p>
<p>I didn&rsquo;t expect that event to be quite so seismic, however. <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ftx-insolvent-what-next-for-crypto/">FTX&rsquo;s implosion</a> represents a watershed moment for crypto. I believe it will cause even greater harm than what most forecast.</p>
<p>We saw credit agency Moody&rsquo;s place Coinbase&rsquo;s bonds on review for downgrade, hinting at the detrimental action that could follow the exchange&rsquo;s insolvency. I wrote a <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-flows-out-of-exchanges-marketwide-following-ftx-collapse/">piece</a> analysing the deluge of <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/what-is-bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> flowing out of exchanges, showing that trust had been broken and was at an all-time low.</p>
<p>In fact, a pretty staggering <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/a-net-flow-of-200000-bitcoins-leaves-exchanges-following-ftx-collapse-as-trust-broken/">200,000 bitcoins flowed out</a> of exchanges less than a month after the FTX collapse. And even Cathie Wood is <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/even-cathie-wood-admits-institutional-adoption-of-crypto-will-fall-off/">warning</a> of a pullback in institutional adoption.</p>
<pre>        <div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/12032894">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    </pre>
<pre>&nbsp;</pre>
<p>They say &ldquo;be greedy when others are fearful&rdquo;, but I&rsquo;m not sure that applies here. Cryptocurrency is at a fork in the road. It has never existed during a bear market in the wider economy before &ndash; remember, Bitcoin was launched in 2009, and hence has experienced nothing but an explosive bull market in financial assets.</p>
<p>Now, it is different. Contagion is again swirling, crypto&rsquo;s reputation is in tatters and the money printer is no longer propping everything up. Times are tough.</p>
<h2><strong>Previous crypto winters</strong></h2>
<p>Against this context, this environment is unprecedented for crypto. This is why I believe that extrapolating past cycles to current conditions is na&iuml;ve. It is a lot easier to bounce back when interest rates are at 0% and the rest of the economy is booming. Not only that, but the scale of the capital destruction this time around is much greater, given crypto grew so much during the pandemic years.</p>
<p>Having said that, there will come a time when inflation is beaten. There will come a time when interest rates are no longer being hiked. This is the cyclical world we live in, and hence risk assets will rise again.</p>
<p>I just believe that this time, the winter may last a little longer than a lot are expecting. And when looking at previous cycles, the winters lasted long then, too. The below chart plots the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/what-is-bitcoin/">Bitcoin price</a> back to 2014, showing this well.</p>
<pre>        <div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/12143615">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    </pre>
<p>Following the peak of close to $20,000 in December 2017, it was not until Q4 of 2020, deep into the pandemic, that Bitcoin once again breached this mark. That marked a near 3-year fallow period, where investors failed to enjoy any significant gains in the crypto world.</p>
<p>We are one year into this bear market now, both in crypto and financial assets in general. Forecasting the future in crypto will only ever end with you looking silly, but I&rsquo;ll try anyway. I would be surprised if we were beyond halfway through this bear market.</p>
<p>As the winter snap hits hard in Europe and people feel those high energy prices, the war in Ukraine rages on, and inflation continues to persist stubbornly, it just feels na&iuml;ve to think crypto could rise anytime soon.</p>
<p>Of course, that could theoretically change in an instant. Positive news out of Ukraine could send markets north in an instant, but that is impossible to predict. I think the base case, however, is a longer period of pain ahead than a lot of people realise. &nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-winter-may-not-end-anytime-soon/">Crypto winter may not end anytime soon</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-winter-may-not-end-anytime-soon/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>US Senator Toomey on FTX and SBF: the code committed no crime</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/us-senator-toomey-on-ftx-and-sbf-the-code-committed-no-crime/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/us-senator-toomey-on-ftx-and-sbf-the-code-committed-no-crime/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 17:22:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/us-senator-toomey-on-ftx-and-sbf-the-code-committed-no-crime/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>FTX filed for bankruptcy in November and Senator Patrick Toomey says Congress should move to provide regulatory clarity on crypto, adding that FTX&#8217;s collapse has nothing to do with cryptocurrency. According to the lawmaker, cryptocurrency is software that has nothing instrinsically good or evil about it. He says the &#8216;code committed no crime&#8217; and that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/us-senator-toomey-on-ftx-and-sbf-the-code-committed-no-crime/">US Senator Toomey on FTX and SBF: the code committed no crime</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>FTX filed for bankruptcy in November and Senator Patrick Toomey says Congress should move to provide regulatory clarity on crypto, adding that FTX&rsquo;s collapse has nothing to do with cryptocurrency.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>According to the lawmaker, cryptocurrency is software that has nothing instrinsically good or evil about it.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><strong><em>He says the &lsquo;code committed no crime&rsquo; and that the US cannot ban crypto &nbsp;as that only pushes it offshore.</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">US Senator Patrick &ldquo;Pat&rdquo; Toomey Jr., a crypto-friendly lawmaker who believes regulatory clarity can benefit the sector, says the FTX case is about the crimes committed by Sam Bankman-Fried and others, and that the saga has nothing to do with <a href="https://coinjournal.net/cryptocurrencies/">cryptocurrency</a> or the underlying technology.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Toomey, who said in an interview with CNBC&rsquo;s &lsquo;<em>Squawk Box</em>&rsquo; on Tuesday that the indictment of the former FTX CEO should not be an indictment of crypto, maintains that the &lsquo;<em>code committed no crime</em>.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">He was <a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1603050838288609280" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">commenting</a> on FTX&rsquo;s implosion following a House Committee hearing.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>The wrongful behaviour that occurred here is not specific to the underlying asset. What appears to have happened here is the complete breakdown in the handling of those assets,</em>&rdquo; he said.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">&lsquo;Nothing intrinsically good or evil about software&rsquo;</h2>
<p dir="ltr">According to Senator Toomey, handling of the saga going forward should not involve calls to ban crypto altogether until regulations are in place. Indeed, his view is that FTX would not have happened if Congress had moved to offer the regulatory guidelines necessary to promote the ecosystem and help robust, well-regulated US-based exchanges take root.</p>
<p dir="ltr">That hasn&rsquo;t happened, and it&rsquo;s important to note that there&rsquo;s a difference between crypto as the underlying software and the companies built on top of it &ndash; like FTX. He added:</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>There&rsquo;s nothing intrinsically good or evil about software&hellip;it&rsquo;s about what people do with it. And with this analogy in mind, what we should all understand here is one simple thing &ndash; the code committed no crime. FTX and cryptocurrency are not the same thing</em>.&rdquo;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">No one banned mortgages after 2008</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The lawmaker also stated that it&rsquo;s the FTX founder and his team that were &lsquo;opaque&rsquo; and dishonest. Not the crypto.</p>
<p dir="ltr">He referenced the 2008 financial crisis, noting that no one moved to ban mortgages following the crisis, nor the US dollar when certain individuals mismanaged customer funds. Likewise, it would be inconceivable for people to suggest a ban on crypto &ndash; as the problem is clearly FTX and the misuse of customer funds.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Pause crypto! Toomey says &lsquo;no way&rsquo;, and that would only succeed in pushing the industry offshore.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>Short of enacting draconian, authoritarian policies, cryptocurrency cannot be stopped. If we try, the technology will simply migrate offshore. Cryptocurrency does not need brick and mortar facilities to operate</em>.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">To help streamline the crypto sector and have properly regulated American crypto exchanges, he points to Congress.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">The collapse of FTX is not an indictment of crypto. It&rsquo;s an indictment of those who misused customer assets.</p>
<p>As I&rsquo;ve said for months, Congress needs to give regulatory clarity so business flows to prudent, sensible, well-regulated American crypto exchanges. <a href="https://t.co/oXKZdawO0m">pic.twitter.com/oXKZdawO0m</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Senator Pat Toomey (@SenToomey) <a href="https://twitter.com/SenToomey/status/1603035390658727944?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 14, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">Senator Toomey&rsquo;s remarks on Wednesday come after Bankman-Fried&rsquo;s arrest in the Bahamas. The former FTX CEO faces several criminal charges from the US Department of Justice, US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC).&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">As <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ftx-committed-old-fashioned-embezzlement-says-new-ceo-john-j-ray-iii/">reported earlier</a>, new FTX CEO John J Ray III believes what happened at FTX is &lsquo;old-fashioned embezzlement.&rsquo;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/us-senator-toomey-on-ftx-and-sbf-the-code-committed-no-crime/">US Senator Toomey on FTX and SBF: the code committed no crime</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/us-senator-toomey-on-ftx-and-sbf-the-code-committed-no-crime/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chainlink Automation launches on Arbitrum One</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/chainlink-automation-launches-on-arbitrum-one/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/chainlink-automation-launches-on-arbitrum-one/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 15:39:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chainlink]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/chainlink-automation-launches-on-arbitrum-one/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Chainlink Automation will make it easier for developers to build dApps on Arbitrum One. COTI and Armadillo, Cask, and DeFiEdge have already integrated Chainlink Automation. Arbitrum One is an optimistic rollup for the Ethereum blockchain. Arbitrum One developers now have access to Chainlink Automation Chainlink, the most widely used oracle services provider, and Arbitrum announced [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chainlink-automation-launches-on-arbitrum-one/">Chainlink Automation launches on Arbitrum One</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Chainlink Automation will make it easier for developers to build dApps on Arbitrum One.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">COTI and Armadillo, Cask, and DeFiEdge have already integrated Chainlink Automation.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Arbitrum One is an optimistic rollup for the Ethereum blockchain.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Arbitrum One developers now have access to Chainlink Automation</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Chainlink, the most widely used oracle services provider, and Arbitrum announced the launch of Chainlink Automation on Arbitrum One on Wednesday, December 14th.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>latest cryptocurrency news</u></a> comes as some projects, including COTI and Armadillo, Cask, and DeFiEdge, have integrated Chainlink Automation into their dApps to reliably trigger key smart contract functions on Arbitrum One.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Chainlink revealed that it has helped drive the rapid growth of the DeFi ecosystem on Arbitrum One. with the launch of Chainlink Automation on Arbitrum One, developers can now access reliable and performant automation to help them build advanced&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/glossary/decentralized-applications-dapps/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>decentralised applications</u></a>.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Developers would be able to take advantage of a decentralised network of nodes that monitor smart contracts and then execute functions using Chainlink&rsquo;s battle-tested transaction manager, which takes care of nonce-management, gas spikes, and network re-orgs, the team added.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">While commenting on this latest development, Niki Ariyasinghe, Head of Blockchain Partnerships at Chainlink Labs, said;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;We&rsquo;re excited to support the Arbitrum ecosystem with the native integration of Chainlink Automation, enabling developers to build highly scalable and low-cost smart contract applications that are automated end to end. With the enhanced uptime and security guarantees provided by Chainlink Automation, Arbitrum developers can build the next generation of decentralized applications and help reliably scale the Web3 ecosystem.&rdquo;</em></p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Developers can now build advanced dApps on Arbitrum One</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">The teams explained that Arbitrum One is an optimistic rollup for Ethereum that powers high-throughput, low-cost dApps, while Chainlink Automation is a smart contract automation solution.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Combining these two makes it possible for developers to build advanced, feature-rich dApps that can scale at an ever-lower cost.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">&nbsp;A.J. Warner, Chief Strategy Officer of Offchain Labs, added that;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;DeFi apps have experienced tremendous growth on the Arbitrum One, which allows them to scale in a secure manner. Similarly, Chainlink Automation helps dApps reliably scale by enabling them to automate DevOps and maintenance tasks without having to rely on centralized scripts or worry about single points of failure.&rdquo;&nbsp;</em></p>
<p dir="ltr">Chainlink is the industry standard for building, accessing, and selling oracle services needed to power hybrid smart contracts on any blockchain. Chainlink oracle networks provide smart contracts with a way to reliably connect to any external API and leverage secure off-chain computations for enabling feature-rich applications.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Offchain Labs is a venture-backed and Princeton-founded company that is behind Arbitrum, a suite of scaling technologies for Ethereum. Arbitrum is the leading scaling provider for Ethereum and has two live chains &mdash; Arbitrum One, the scaling solution of choice for DeFi and NFTs and Arbitrum Nova, the newly announced gaming and social platform.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chainlink-automation-launches-on-arbitrum-one/">Chainlink Automation launches on Arbitrum One</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/chainlink-automation-launches-on-arbitrum-one/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Over $933k Tokens Sold In Metacades Beta Presale, only 12% remaining before it sells out</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/over-933k-tokens-sold-in-metacades-beta-presale-only-12-remaining-before-it-sells-out/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice Davies]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 15:26:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/over-933k-tokens-sold-in-metacades-beta-presale-only-12-remaining-before-it-sells-out/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto investors are rushing into the Metacade beta stage presale to buy tokens at their lowest price. The world&#8217;s first play-to-earn arcade Metacade opened its presale with 1 MCADE token for $0.008. The blockchain gaming newcomer has received an electric welcome from the crypto community with over $933k worth of MCADE tokens sold in the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/over-933k-tokens-sold-in-metacades-beta-presale-only-12-remaining-before-it-sells-out/">Over $933k Tokens Sold In Metacades Beta Presale, only 12% remaining before it sells out</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Crypto investors are rushing into the <a href="https://metacade.co/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade</u></a> beta stage presale to buy tokens at their lowest price. The world&rsquo;s first play-to-earn arcade Metacade opened its presale with 1 MCADE token for $0.008. The blockchain gaming newcomer has received an electric welcome from the crypto community with over $933k worth of MCADE tokens sold in the beta stage in under 18 days</p>
<p dir="ltr">Once the beta stage closes the MCADE price will rise to $0.01 per token &ndash; a 25 percent increase. By the end of the presale, the token price will have increased by over 2.5x to $0.02 per MCADE.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As of writing, a phenomenal $933k has already been poured into the project since the Metacade presale opened. There are only 12 percent of tokens left before stage one begins, so it&rsquo;s crucial to purchase MCADE tokens now before the price leaps.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Metacade?&nbsp;</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade is the next big thing in the metaverse and P2E gaming. The platform will be home to a tremendous array of arcade-style games where players can earn, compete and connect with fellow gamers.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade will also be home to the hottest gaming alpha and reviews, leaderboards of what&rsquo;s trending on the platform and across the GameFi space, and a hub where users can chat in real time with like-minded gamers. &nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade isn&rsquo;t just for hardcore gamers: the platform offers something for everyone. Investors can stake MCADE tokens to earn rewards. Entrepreneurs and developers can build games on the platform, supported by a funding initiative known as Metagrants. Job seekers can find their new roles in Web3. &nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The community-driven blockchain gaming platform will take the GameFi platform by storm with its huge array of Web3-forward features that allow players to truly take control of their gaming experience, leaving traditional gaming far behind.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The platform&rsquo;s ultimate goal is to build a platform that gamers want and allow its community to shape the future of gaming and earn as they do so. Ultimately, Metacade will transition into a DAO, allowing the dedicated community to fully control and continue building the platform they love.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy $MCADE tokens&nbsp;</h2>
<p dir="ltr">MCADE tokens can be purchased on <a href="https://metacade.co/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade.co</u></a>. Here are some easy steps to get your hands on your Metacade tokens before the token hits the major exchanges and the price shoots up.&nbsp;</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">STEP 1&nbsp;</h3>
<p dir="ltr">Set up a crypto wallet. Metacade is built on the Ethereum blockchain, so ensure that you have a wallet that is compatible with ETH. The <a href="https://explorer.walletconnect.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>wallets supported by Wallet Connect</u></a> are suitable. The Metacade team recommends&nbsp;<a href="https://metamask.io/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metamask</u></a> for a smooth buy experience.&nbsp;</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">STEP 2&nbsp;</h3>
<p dir="ltr">Get some crypto. Metacade can be purchased with ETH and USDT, so ensure you have enough of one of these currencies in your wallet before buying MCADE.&nbsp;</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">STEP 3&nbsp;</h3>
<p dir="ltr">Connect your wallet to the Metacade website and <a href="https://metacade.co/dex" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>access the DEX</u></a>. You&rsquo;ll be given the option to swap your ETH for $MCADE. Enter the amount you&rsquo;d like to purchase and click &ldquo;buy&rdquo;.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Here are some further details on <a href="https://metacade.co/how-to-buy" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>how to purchase $MCADE</u></a>.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Metacade presale is off to a flying start&nbsp;</h2>
<p dir="ltr">With beta presale tokens selling fast, there&rsquo;s never been a better time to get in on a phenomenal GameFi project on the ground floor.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Find out more on <a href="https://metacade.co/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade.co</u></a>.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/over-933k-tokens-sold-in-metacades-beta-presale-only-12-remaining-before-it-sells-out/">Over $933k Tokens Sold In Metacades Beta Presale, only 12% remaining before it sells out</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Expert panel: what mistakes should users avoid when attempting to buy cryptocurrencies</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/expert-panel-what-mistakes-should-users-avoid-when-attempting-to-buy-cryptocurrencies/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/expert-panel-what-mistakes-should-users-avoid-when-attempting-to-buy-cryptocurrencies/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dan Ashmore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 14:38:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Interview]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/expert-panel-what-mistakes-should-users-avoid-when-attempting-to-buy-cryptocurrencies/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We all make mistakes.&#160; Look no further than the crypto market for this, when the entire space seemed to get a little bit over-excited, shall we say, during the pandemic years of 2020 and 2021.&#160; The year 2022 has exposed a lot of overvalued investments as the economy has flipped and capital has flowed out [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/expert-panel-what-mistakes-should-users-avoid-when-attempting-to-buy-cryptocurrencies/">Expert panel: what mistakes should users avoid when attempting to buy cryptocurrencies</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">We all make mistakes.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Look no further than the crypto market for this, when the entire space seemed to get a little bit over-excited, shall we say, during the pandemic years of 2020 and 2021.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The year 2022 has exposed a lot of overvalued investments as the economy has flipped and capital has flowed out of the space. Many investors are hurting bad, so perhaps it is a good time to take stock of errors and see whether these can be avoided in future.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">On this note, we sat down with a few industry experts to get their thoughts on an important question, as part of our series asking expert panels for advice in crypto:</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em><strong>What mistakes should users avoid when attempting to buy cryptocurrencies?</strong></em></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Ramani Ramachandran, CEO and Co-Founder of <a href="https://www.routerprotocol.com/"><u>Router Protocol</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">There are so many common and often preventable mistakes that new traders make. Some of the most common ones are, sending your assets to the wrong wallet. As a trader, you must understand that every single transaction in blockchain is immutable. If you accidentally send the tokens to the wrong address, it can&rsquo;t be undone.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Secondly, committing trades without looking at gas fees. If you want to execute an urgent transaction, then paying high gas fees makes sense. But if you can wait for the transaction to take place then make sure to execute the transaction when the gas fees are low. You can use tools like Ethereum&rsquo;s GasNow to find a time when the gas is on the lower end of the spectrum.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Stefan Rust, CEO of <a href="https://www.lagunalabs.io/"><u>Laguna Labs</u></a>, says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Again, knowing why you are buying crypto and what for can help you avoid the biggest mistakes. Are you looking to make a quick buck when the market is hot, or are you brave enough to face the bear market and buy low to hold over the long term? Or are you looking for stablecoins that hold their value and that you can use to buy things? PIck your poison and then &ndash; crucially &ndash; do your research.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Marius Ciuboatriu, co-founder of <a href="https://hubbleprotocol.io/"><u>Hubble Protocol</u></a>, says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Avoid hype. When someone trades into a crypto project&rsquo;s token or starts depositing on a decentralized finance platform without knowing how it really works, it&rsquo;s called &ldquo;apeing,&rdquo; and it&rsquo;s like throwing money like an ape at something because of hype or what someone said instead of doing due diligence. Avoid &ldquo;apeing&rdquo; into crypto projects if you don&rsquo;t have enough knowledge about the project to make an informed decision. Remember that all of these tokens represent projects that are trying to do something with incredibly new technologies, and if you don&rsquo;t understand what they are trying to do, then it&rsquo;s like wading into the dotcom bubble in the late nineties. A lot of internet projects either oversold their promises or had nothing new to offer other than having a website, but Google and Amazon made it through the bubble, because they worked and had real utility for users. &nbsp; &nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Tom Norwood, CEO of <a href="https://www.loop.markets/"><u>Loop Finance</u></a>, says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Sadly, there&rsquo;s almost nobody in crypto that doesn&rsquo;t have a horror story about buying a token at the wrong time or even getting pulled into a scam. It can be quite tricky to always make the right decisions in this space, but doing your own research, never believing something that&rsquo;s too good to be true (because most of the time, if it sounds too good to be true, it is!) and ensuring you never invest anything you can&rsquo;t afford to lose is going to safeguard you against making the biggest mistakes.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Dan Ashmore, data analyst at <a href="https://coinjournal.net/author/dan-ashmore/"><u>Coinjournal</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Avoid FOMO and reckless, emotion-bound investing. A lot of cryptocurrencies are hugely volatile, as is the sector at large. Investing needs always be done as part of a responsible portfolio allocation, with a key emphasis on diversification.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The vast majority of cryptos should be viewed as gambles rather than investments &ndash; always ensure you are investing in accordance with your risk tolerance.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Martin Lee, Data Journalist at <a href="https://www.nansen.ai/"><u>Nansen</u></a> says:</h2>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Avoid chasing hype and feeling like you need to catch every wave.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Don&rsquo;t overly rely on influencers or &ldquo;educational&rdquo; content creators for alpha. Do your own research and form your own opinion of a project before investing.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">There&rsquo;s sometimes a perception that buying BTC/ETH means that you won&rsquo;t be able to do well and you have to make more risky bets but historically having a portfolio that&rsquo;s largely BTC/ETH gets you the best returns unless you&rsquo;re able to ride the different waves well of course.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr">Lars Seier Christensen, chairman of <a href="https://concordium.com/"><u>Concordium</u></a> and founder of <a href="https://www.home.saxo/"><u>Saxo Bank</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">They should avoid leverage in their trading and they should avoid very short term trading. Day traders nearly all lose money as they cannot beat the constant cost of spreads and commissions. Research thoroughly on projects and accumulate for the longer term, looking for projects with solid use cases that eventually will be profitable. Buy on dips, not after big rallies, and don&rsquo;t fall for hype. There is a lot of hype out there, and relatively few solid projects with long term potential. Look out for the liquidity of the tokens and coins, how easy is it to get in and out, not least in volatile conditions.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Yang Lan, founder of <a href="https://fiat24.com/"><u>Fiat24</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Don&rsquo;t just buy cryptocurrencies that are &ldquo;Trending&rdquo; or have a lot of hype &ndash; do your own research and look out for coins which also have utility and are connected to upstanding projects.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Dmitry Gooshchin, COO and Co-Founder of <a href="https://endotech.io/"><u>EndoTech</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">One of the biggest mistakes that investors make is frequently changing their investment strategy. Investors often come into the market with a thesis about a coin&rsquo;s value or the market itself. That is the bedrock of the investment. However, too often, a new piece of regulation or tweet can set off emotional reactions and cause them to change their investment strategy.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bobby Pham &ndash; CMO <a href="https://kardiachain.io/"><u>KardiaChain</u></a> says:</h2>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Buy crypto from trusted sources. There are TONs of methods to purchase crypto. If you&rsquo;re just starting out, buy from trusted platforms, sources, or people you personally know. Even though the industry has been around for over 10 years, it&rsquo;s still filled with scammers and unethical users. Thus, if you&rsquo;re just starting out, be sure to buy crypto from large trusted brands like Coinbase, Binance, FTX, or from your personal relationships.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Stick to buying blue-chip crypto projects in the Top 25. There are over 21,000 cryptocurrencies. 99.9% are worthless and will likely disappear within the next 3 years. Investing into these is high-risk, and there&rsquo;s a big chance you&rsquo;ll lose most of your investment if you don&rsquo;t have much experience investing in crypto yet. If you look at the Top 10 crypto projects by market cap from the last 4 years, half of them have largely remained the same: Bitcoin, Ethereum, Ripple, Binance Coin, ChainLink. If a crypto project survives past the 5-year mark, it&rsquo;s likely a solid project that&rsquo;ll be around long-term. If you&rsquo;re a beginner, stick to buying blue-chip crypto projects while you gain experience.</li>
<li dir="ltr">In the beginning, only invest a small portion (less than 10%) of your liquid savings. You should initially expect to lose money as you learn how to buy crypto. Knowing this, you want to keep your learning mistakes small and inexpensive.</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Joerg Hansen, CEO of <a href="https://caizcoin.com/"><u>Caiz Development GmbH</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Don&rsquo;t focus too much on the price of a cryptocurrency. Crypto is one part, but the blockchain behind it is the key and bigger part of understanding the difference between a good cryptocurrency and a bad cryptocurrency. If you know what makes Bitcoin so unique, you will understand the future.&nbsp;Getting into crypto is mostly an investment in your future. By getting your feet wet carefully (without getting sucked into greed-driven frantic trading or leveraging) you can make sure you will be part of the new future of money rather than being left behind.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Lang Mei, CEO of <a href="https://airdao.io/"><u>AirDAO</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">I think the most common mistakes are:</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Not having strong passwords for crypto exchanges</li>
<li dir="ltr">Sending funds to the wrong wallet address</li>
<li dir="ltr">Losing private keys for wallets</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">New users should research how to avoid these mistakes.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Vlad Totia, Research Analyst at <a href="http://www.zilliqa.com/"><u>Zilliqa</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">One of the most common mistakes new users make is falling for promises of extremely high profit if they purchase a specific token. While crypto has definitely made many people rich, it has caused many more to lose their investments. Doing even a minimum amount of research before buying a cryptocurrency is a very good habit to have as it can filter out a good portion of bad projects.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Another common mistake is using small unproven exchanges as wallets. The phrase &lsquo;not your keys, not your crypto&rsquo; is popular for a reason. If a user wants to purchase a large amount of a little-known token, they should at least store it in a personal cold wallet as opposed to delegating the keys to it to an obscure exchange with a nice UI.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Hristiyan Hristov, Account Management Team Lead at <a href="https://nexo.io/"><u>Nexo</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Avoid following somebody else&rsquo;s advice from Youtube, Reddit, online articles, etc. Always do your own research and have in mind that many people are paid to promote assets and projects online and it isn&rsquo;t always immediately obvious when this is the case. This will help you build critical thinking in an industry where this is crucial to your success and &ldquo;survival&rdquo;. You&rsquo;ll learn a lot, and knowing you can rely on your own &ldquo;crypto smarts&rdquo; is incredibly empowering in long run.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Wolfgang R&uuml;ckerl, Co-Founder and CEO of <a href="https://istari.vision/en/"><u>Istari Vision</u></a> and <a href="https://entity.global/"><u>Entity</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">A typical mistake for new investors is buying tokens without first researching and understanding the project. The acronym &lsquo;DYOR,&rsquo; meaning &lsquo;Do Your Own Research,&rsquo; represents a critical process for making smart investment decisions. A related mistake is buying into over-hyped coins after the price has already skyrocketed.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Another common mistake in crypto investing is buying into projects that only have a litepaper but do not have any form of working product. While it takes time to develop software, most trustworthy projects will at least have a testnet version of their product before they begin fundraising. If a startup has a fully-functional mainnet product, that is an even better sign for investors.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Finally, many new investors fail to properly secure their crypto after purchasing it. Users should always protect their seed or recovery phrase, which is the key to accessing their blockchain assets. You should write these phrases down on paper in a secure location and never share them with anyone. Investors should also never connect their wallet to websites that they don&rsquo;t fully trust. Savvy investors will even use a &lsquo;cold wallet,&rsquo; which is a piece of physical hardware that keeps your crypto secure from hackers.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Nimantha Siriwardana, Co-Founder and CTO of <a href="https://metacask.com/"><u>Metacask</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Many people go into crypto thinking that they will make their fortune overnight. This is not the case. Plan for the long term. Find a project that you believe in and that aligns with your values. And don&rsquo;t make the mistake of not doing your own research.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Going all in is a rookie error. Only &lsquo;invest&rsquo; what you can afford to lose. Crypto is extremely volatile, and as with all investments, there are winners and losers &ndash; unfortunately, many will lose. &nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The worst mistake a user can make is panic buying and selling. Have a plan, and stick to it. As a wise person once said&hellip; plan the trade and trade the plan.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Tahem Verma, Co-Founder and CEO of <a href="https://www.mesha.club/"><u>mesha</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Users should avoid listening to crypto &lsquo;influencers&rsquo; and letting the fear of missing out drive their decision-making. One of the biggest mistakes a new crypto user can make is not doing their own research.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Andrew Levine, CEO and Co-Founder of <a href="https://koinos.group/"><u>Koinos Group</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Instead of trying to get rich quick, people interested in buying cryptocurrencies should find communities of like-minded individuals who share their values and want to solve important problems. Blockchain is an incredible technology with the potential to solve big problems in our world. Investors should shift their focus from the monetary value of a blockchain to its ability to support new technology.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Pannathorn Lorattawut, CEO of VUCA Digital, from the <a href="https://crowntoken.io/"><u>CROWN Token Project</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Users should avoid buying anything that promises unreasonably high returns. Also, chasing after the next 1000x coins is a very high-risk strategy, almost like making a bet.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Richa Joshi, Co-Founder of <a href="https://push.org/"><u>Push Protocol</u></a> says:</h2>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr"><strong>FOMO.&nbsp;</strong>FOMO is inevitable in web3. Prices start to fluctuate, floors start to creep up, APYs come and go. Remember that an emotional rationale for an economic choice is rarely the best route, and return to the technology, the adoption, and the community to make your decisions.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr"><strong>Custody.&nbsp;</strong>There are many forms of custody, and none of them are inherently a <em>mistake.&nbsp;</em>However, not understanding which custody you&rsquo;re signing up for can be a mistake. Understand the trade-offs between purchasing on a centralized exchange vs. a decentralized exchange and determine where you&rsquo;d rather have your money sitting.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr"><strong>Short-term Vision.&nbsp;</strong>Rome wasn&rsquo;t built in a day, and neither has any major technology movement. Web3 trends will come and go, bull and bear markets will cycle, and waves of people will enter and exit. Always look to the long-term, and when you can avoid getting caught up in short-term emotional choices.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr">Joshua Tobkin, CEO and Co-Founder of <a href="https://supraoracles.com/"><u>SupraOracles</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">If you&rsquo;re attempting to buy cryptocurrencies, it&rsquo;s essential to do your own research first. Gain an understanding of how blockchains function, and which tokens have very strong utility for the long term. Be sure to write down your confidence level and time frame you&rsquo;re willing to wait. Bull markets come and go with long bears in between. Remember that the market ebbs and flows, don&rsquo;t be dissuaded if your investment crashes at some point if you actually have done proper fundamental analysis.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Valentin Pletnev, CEO of <a href="https://www.quasar.fi/"><u>Quasar</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Avoid being driven by emotion and social trends. As with any financial endeavor, it is human nature to give into irrational behavior even in the most subtle ways. Cryptocurrency markets are no different.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Mario Baxter, CTO at <a href="http://www.fun.xyz"><u>Fun</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Don&rsquo;t buy anything that you don&rsquo;t understand.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">David Schwed, Chief Operating Officer of <a href="https://halborn.com/"><u>Halborn</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Avoid the hype. If you are new to crypto and hear about the &ldquo;next big thing/coin/project&rdquo; then you are most likely on the losing side of the cycle and would be buying as the original holders are selling. Start with small amounts and practice the process of buying/selling/transferring.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Limaris Torres, Security Advisor at <a href="https://halborn.com/"><u>Halborn</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Crypto by its very nature is volatile so avoid buying in one chunk. The Dollar Cost Average (DCA) is a great strategy to implement on any large purchase. This method helps reduce the influence of volatility over their investment and, therefore, reduce their risk exposure by breaking a larger amount into multiple smaller purchases.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Paulina J&oacute;&#347;k&oacute;w, Head of Business Development at <a href="https://ramp.network/"><u>Ramp</u></a> says:</h2>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Lack of research when picking an exchange or on-ramp. Picking a bad apple can be costly (hidden fees, expensive withdrawals), or worst case, turn out to be an outright scam.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Hurrying into a purchase. It&rsquo;s easy to create tokens with very similar names, and for users to buy the wrong one by accident, especially when using decentralized exchanges with little to no vetting on tokens that get added.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Going all-in on a low-liquidity crypto asset. Whatever the motivation behind your purchase, avoid placing all your eggs into one basket &ndash; especially for low-liquidity, infrequently-trading assets.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr">Gabriella Kusz, CEO of the <a href="https://global-dca.org/"><u>Global Digital Asset and Cryptocurrency Association</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Biggest mistake to avoid &ndash; Following the hype &ndash; always do your own research and invest in crypto like any other asset class.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Rashid Ali, co-founder and CEO of <a href="https://exarta.com/"><u>Exarta</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Believing the hype about one particular crypto, do your own research as there are many negative forces that build the hype only to dump it later.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Never share your private keys or any sensitive information.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Peter Eberle, President and CIO of <a href="https://www.castlefunds.com/"><u>Castle Funds</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Putting too much of your savings into any asset is a mistake, especially a volatile asset. If someone is losing sleep over their investments, it is clear that they have allocated too much capital to that investment. &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Beware of the experts! Twitter, Youtube and other social media is filled with &ldquo;experts&rdquo; promising huge returns. Why would they share this information if it was real? Wouldn&rsquo;t they just invest their own and their family and friends&rsquo; money? In reality many are pumping coins that they already own and are trying to unload their investments.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Paolo Ardoino, CTO of <a href="https://www.bitfinex.com/"><u>Bitfinex</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Firstly,it is wrong to think that crypto is easy money, or a means of getting rich quickly.</p>
<p dir="ltr">You need to understand the markets and how to use exchanges.</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Be sure to understand the fees of the platform and read the fine print.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Buying simply as a result of the price being low &ndash; users need to educate themselves about the crypto market in order to avoid the possibility of suffering a loss.</li>
<li dir="ltr">If you are very new to the market ensure that you always remember your private key or seed phrase. It is critically important that you keep this information in a secure, safe place.</li>
<li dir="ltr">And while it may seem obvious it&rsquo;s easy to follow the trend or current hype &ndash; but know what your goal is for your portfolio and stick to it. Also be sure to check your wallet address and keep that information safe. This is critical to keeping your assets safe.</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Jake Yocom-Piatt, Co-Founder and Project Lead of <a href="https://decred.org/"><u>Decred</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Avoid buying a large amount of cryptocurrency all at one time and price, it is best to dollar cost average and gradually buy and sell cryptoassets. &nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Since cryptocurrency markets are highly volatile relative to typical fiat financial markets, managing the psychological strain that comes with this volatility is important. If prices drop, your cost-averaged price tracks it downwards, reducing psychological strain.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">&nbsp;Use a hardware wallet, e.g. Trezor or Ledger, and withdraw your purchased cryptoassets from the exchange. &nbsp;You can easily redeposit the assets at an exchange if/when you are ready to sell. &nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">If an exchange gets hacked and its assets are stolen, this will not affect your withdrawn self-custodied assets. &nbsp;Remember &ldquo;not your keys, not your coins&rdquo;.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Charmyn Ho, head of crypto insights at <a href="https://www.bybit.com/"><u>Bybit</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Fraud risk remains high whether it is in DefI or TradFi. Reputable exchanges can help you navigate uncertainties and complexities by filtering out the noise and providing industry-strength fund custodial services.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Moving too fast, too quickly is also an easy mistake to make in crypto. But it is also one that is also easy to avoid. Being responsible, doing due diligence and taking time to &nbsp;watch, listen, and learn are key when attempting to buy cryptocurrencies. There are vast amounts of educational material readily available online and via exchanges &ndash; be sure to make use of them. (can we include links to Crypto Insights here?)</p>
<p dir="ltr">Building a portfolio is a gradual process. Crypto is an emerging economy with an enormous untapped potential and there is no need to submit to FOMO. &nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Another common mistake that is often overlooked are &ldquo;wrong address&rdquo; transactions. Retrieving assets or even locating assets sent to the wrong address, sometimes to a different blockchain, takes tremendous efforts that often end in vain.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Understand the basics of how blockchains work and how different exchanges support them before you execute a transaction, or simply access the readily available trading options on trusted exchanges.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/expert-panel-what-mistakes-should-users-avoid-when-attempting-to-buy-cryptocurrencies/">Expert panel: what mistakes should users avoid when attempting to buy cryptocurrencies</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/expert-panel-what-mistakes-should-users-avoid-when-attempting-to-buy-cryptocurrencies/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Expert panel: what is your biggest tip for a user just getting into crypto?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/expert-panel-what-is-your-biggest-tip-for-a-user-just-getting-into-crypto/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dan Ashmore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 14:20:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Interview]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/expert-panel-what-is-your-biggest-tip-for-a-user-just-getting-into-crypto/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>It has been a wild few years in the cryptocurrency industry.&#160; Only a few years ago, crypto was still a niche and enigmatic concept to most, yet today it is firmly in the mainstream. During the pandemic years especially, there was a massive influx of new users into the industry. But the industry is a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/expert-panel-what-is-your-biggest-tip-for-a-user-just-getting-into-crypto/">Expert panel: what is your biggest tip for a user just getting into crypto?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">It has been a wild few years in the cryptocurrency industry.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Only a few years ago, crypto was still a niche and enigmatic concept to most, yet today it is firmly in the mainstream.</p>
<p dir="ltr">During the pandemic years especially, there was a massive influx of new users into the industry. But the industry is a volatile one &ndash; look no further than 2022 for evidence of that, when a lot of pandemic gains have been given up.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Today we are in a completely different financial landscape, with the world economy reeling, inflation high and a wealth of uncertainty present. For movie investors, therefore, it is perhaps an even more intimidating time than usual to get into cryptocurrency.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">On this note, we sat down with a few industry experts to get their thoughts on an important question, as part of our series asking expert panels for advice in crypto:</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em><strong>What is your biggest tip for a user just getting into crypto?</strong></em></p>
<p dir="ltr">This is what they said:</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Ramani Ramachandran, CEO and Co-Founder of <a href="https://www.routerprotocol.com/"><u>Router Protocol</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">My biggest tip is to not give in to FOMO. Invest in Web 3.0 projects not by just looking at their graphs and listening to a few analysts. Really go in depth to understand the problem the project is solving. Understand the utility of the token, and try to gauge if their solution will be significant to the evolution of the whole ecosystem. Since Web 3.0 is relatively young and has attracted many major players, it is bound to go through periods of extreme volatility. But projects that are building with a vision will thrive regardless of market conditions.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Stefan Rust, CEO of <a href="https://www.lagunalabs.io/"><u>Laguna Labs</u></a>, says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The most important thing for anyone getting into crypto is to be brave &ndash; doing something new is always scary, but if you apply the right safety measures it&rsquo;s usually a rewarding experience. Get curious, do some homework, ask questions, and then get involved. Just like any kind of purchase or investment, make sure you&rsquo;re not using funds reserved for rent and mortgage payments. Beyond that, though, just give it a try.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Marius Ciuboatriu, co-founder of <a href="https://hubbleprotocol.io/"><u>Hubble Protocol</u></a>, says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">As with everything, it&rsquo;s really important to understand what you&rsquo;re getting into with crypto. It&rsquo;s possible that, in the future, use cases for crypto will become so broad that people will be interacting with blockchains without even knowing it. But right now, in the same way that you spend a lot of time and energy thinking about what phone to buy, you need to spend even more time and energy understanding crypto. It&rsquo;s an emerging market that pivots on a dime, so narratives are always changing, and you need to pay attention to make sure you&rsquo;re on the right track. &nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Tom Norwood, CEO of <a href="https://www.loop.markets/"><u>Loop Finance</u></a>, says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">If you&rsquo;re new to crypto, the most important thing is to really think about what you&rsquo;re doing before you do it. Some people get involved because they think they should, or because their friend told them that they could make a lot of money, but really it&rsquo;s best if you care about what&rsquo;s going on &ndash; or at least are excited by it beyond making a quick buck &ndash; and are willing to put in a bit of time and research to understand it. That&rsquo;s not to say crypto isn&rsquo;t for everyone, because it is. But it is never a waste of time to really understand where you&rsquo;re putting your time, money, and energy.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Dan Ashmore, data analyst at <a href="https://coinjournal.net/author/dan-ashmore/"><u>Coinjournal</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Start slow and small &ndash; don&rsquo;t go jumping into alt coins or investing significant amounts of money before you get up to speed. As a complete beginner, I would suggest getting up to speed first on other asset classes like equities, before trying to wrap one&rsquo;s head around crypto.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Once there, don&rsquo;t believe half of what you see online. The space is packed with scams, paid promotions acting as honest advice, clickbait headlines, boasting and lots of other noise. Search for objective opinions and unbiased news that is not afraid to criticise, until you build up a good understanding.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Martin Lee, Data Journalist at <a href="https://www.nansen.ai/"><u>Nansen</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Don&rsquo;t rush into it, take your time to learn and understand the space. Start with the basics i.e. What is a blockchain, what is Ethereum, what is Bitcoin, what are NFTs, what is DeFi etc, and work your way up to doing protocol specific deep dives.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Lars Seier Christensen, chairman of <a href="https://concordium.com/"><u>Concordium</u></a> and founder of <a href="https://www.home.saxo/"><u>Saxo Bank</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Do deep research on the business model, the longer term potential, the quality on the people and pick reasonably priced investments that you truly believe in for the long term. Don&rsquo;t buy and sell aggressively on a short term basis. It is a fool&rsquo;s game and nearly always ends in tears. Never, ever invest with money you can&rsquo;t afford to lose or would seriously damage your economy if you did. I don&rsquo;t think it is advisable to place more than a small part of your portfolio in crypto.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Yang Lan, founder of <a href="https://fiat24.com/"><u>Fiat24</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Take the time to learn &ndash; this cannot be stated enough! Fortunately, there are many resources online now in various formats (written, videos, courses, webinars) which can provide the fundamentals needed before starting to invest. Education is key and does take time, but is certainly well worth it.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Dmitry Gooshchin, COO and Co-Founder of <a href="https://endotech.io/"><u>EndoTech</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Small steps. Like any new investment class, you&rsquo;ll need to learn the dynamics. In crypto, it&rsquo;s no different. When you dip your toe in the water, you&rsquo;ll get a sense of the market volatility and your true risk appetite. Once you&rsquo;ve gained some comfort with cryptocurrencies, you&rsquo;ll be better able to evaluate more advanced investment considerations like leverage, futures, trading bots, and AltCoins. Start small, gain comfort and adjust. You want to get acclimatized so you can be a long-term investor.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bobby Pham &ndash; CMO <a href="https://kardiachain.io/"><u>KardiaChain</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Expect to lose money in the beginning, but aim to learn.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The worst thing that can happen is you make a lot of money immediately.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Making money fast and luckily teaches you nothing except to constantly chase luck.</p>
<p dir="ltr">During a bull market, it&rsquo;s super-easy to make money.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The challenge is keeping it.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Thus, in the beginning, keep your initially trading bankroll small and go into crypto with the expectation to learn.</p>
<p dir="ltr">If you make some money, great! &nbsp;Take some of the profits and save it.</p>
<p dir="ltr">But the biggest tip for a user just getting into crypto is to focus on learning in the beginning.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Joerg Hansen, CEO of <a href="https://caizcoin.com/"><u>Caiz Development GmbH</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">I know Lenin is not popular with everyone, but in my childhood, my father always quoted him saying: &ldquo;Trust is good, control is better&rdquo;. This means always doing your research first before you buy cryptocurrencies. Also start very small and find your footing before going in deeper. As an investor or potential &ldquo;hodler&rdquo; you never want to be exposed to high risk you can&rsquo;t handle or afford. Therefore, you should keep educating yourself, reading about tokenomics and the technology behind a certain cryptocurrency or project. Only invest in what you understand. Try to ask questions from all angles to really be sure about your investment and the risks involved. Be aware of fear and greed and don&rsquo;t buy a cryptocurrency only because it&rsquo;s super cheap or popular. Behind every technology is an opportunity for a long bright future, but be sure to always keep an active eye on your holdings. And: don&rsquo;t forget your crypto passwords or seed phrases!</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Lang Mei, CEO of <a href="https://airdao.io/"><u>AirDAO</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Keep an open mind, be willing to learn, and have a long-term mindset.</p>
<p dir="ltr">There are a lot of exciting and revolutionary projects in Crypto that have the potential to make a lasting impact on the world if successful, and most of them are not well known. Keep an open mind about the possibilities and the long-term vision of the teams involved. Be willing to step out of your comfort zone and try something new, whether it is a new DeFi project or a new layer-one blockchain that you might not have heard of before.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Also, a lot of new users think they are late to Crypto. There is an old Chinese proverb, &ldquo;The best time to plant a tree was twenty years ago. The second best time is now.&rdquo; Satoshi mined the first Bitcoin block in 2009. The history of traditional finance dates back thousands of years. In comparison, Crypto has barely begun &mdash; so think in terms of years and decades instead of weeks and months.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Vlad Totia, Research Analyst at <a href="http://www.zilliqa.com/"><u>Zilliqa</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Research, research, research. Always keep learning. Crypto changes fast, and it is unrelenting when it comes to separating beginners from their hard-earned money. The best way to understand the space is to get familiar with what current protocols or trends are popular and then go towards the basics from there. Learning by doing is arguably the best mantra in the space.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Hristiyan Hristov, Account Management Team Lead at <a href="https://nexo.io/"><u>Nexo</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Learn how the Bitcoin blockchain works. That&rsquo;s always a good start! The crypto space is vast and you might get lost, so I would recommend you find what interest you, be it DeFi, the metaverse, or Layer 1 &nbsp;blockchains, and dig deeper.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Wolfgang R&uuml;ckerl, Co-Founder and CEO of <a href="https://istari.vision/en/"><u>Istari Vision</u></a> and <a href="https://entity.global/"><u>Entity</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">My biggest tip for users starting out in crypto is to start small. Rather than go all in from the beginning, it is wiser to dollar-cost average in slowly. This means spreading out your purchases over time so that your price paid is less affected by market timing. Another way to start small is to focus on well-established projects that you fully understand. This is safer than trying to hit a home run right away by investing in a smaller, more speculative project.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Nimantha Siriwardana, Co-Founder and CTO of <a href="https://metacask.com/"><u>Metacask</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Don&rsquo;t believe the hype. Fear of missing out is real, but don&rsquo;t give in to it. There are plenty of folks on Twitter shouting about the next big thing, but you shouldn&rsquo;t listen to the noise. Always do your own research on the project that you&rsquo;re interested in to ensure it&rsquo;s legitimate. And don&rsquo;t stop there &ndash; research its team members, their history, and so on.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Tahem Verma, Co-Founder and CEO of <a href="https://www.mesha.club/"><u>mesha</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">It&rsquo;s impossible to time the market, so always make an investment based on your research, beliefs, and conviction. Another tip would be not to panic buy and sell.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Andrew Levine, CEO and Co-Founder of <a href="https://koinos.group/"><u>Koinos Group</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">For someone who is just entering the crypto space, they should look for value instead of quick financial gains. Investors should buy crypto from companies whose missions they identify with. Basing investments on the values and goals of a company, not what&rsquo;s a &lsquo;hot&rsquo; buy or not, will help new investors feel good about where their money is going. This approach also accounts for the long-term potential of a company, which can pay off in the future.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Pannathorn Lorattawut, CEO of VUCA Digital, from the <a href="https://crowntoken.io/"><u>CROWN Token Projec</u></a>t says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Crypto has a high volatility, generally with higher risk, and a higher return. However, the investment principles remain the same for both traditional and crypto assets. You should not put all your eggs in one basket. It&rsquo;s always important to have a good mix of asset allocations based on your risk tolerance level.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Richa Joshi, Co-Founder of <a href="https://push.org/"><u>Push Protocol</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>Learn the Fundamentals.&nbsp;</strong>A general sentiment among those building and using web3 today is that in many years we hope for web3 to be so ubiquitous that it doesn&rsquo;t &ldquo;feel&rdquo; like interacting with new tools in our daily use of the internet or money. That, however, isn&rsquo;t the reality today. There is still so much core work and innovation happening today. To get into crypto and thrive in this space, it&rsquo;s still crucial to learn the fundamentals of web3. How is it situated in the broader evolution of the internet? How have layer 1s evolved over time, and what are the core challenges they face? What types of issues can web3 actually solve, and how? Generally, how do different consensus mechanisms work? With a strong grasp of blockchain fundamentals, most of the innovation and work being done today can be contextualized, helping you make more informed decisions.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Joshua Tobkin, CEO and Co-Founder of <a href="https://supraoracles.com/"><u>SupraOracles</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">This cannot be stated strongly enough: Investing in any asset class on the cutting edge of modern technology comes with inherent risks; be sure to never invest more than you are willing to lose. We often hear about those who made big gains in the market, but what we don&rsquo;t hear about as often are those who didn&rsquo;t fare so well. Be sure to keep the risk to reward ratio in the forefront of your mind, and do what&rsquo;s most beneficial for you depending on your own personal financial situation.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Valentin Pletnev, CEO of <a href="https://www.quasar.fi/"><u>Quasar</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Learn as much as you can everyday to take agency in your financial future and be a sovereign individual. Reach out to others in the community and form strong knowledge networks because the space is vast and takes time to grasp.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Mario Baxter, CTO at <a href="http://www.fun.xyz"><u>Fun</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Join the crypto ecosystem for the technology, philosophy, and community &mdash; not to speculate and try to make money. If you&rsquo;re only in it for the money, and don&rsquo;t understand the underlying technology and use-cases, chances are that you&rsquo;ll get rekt.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">David Schwed, Chief Operating Officer of <a href="https://halborn.com/"><u>Halborn</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Curiosity followed by education and your own research. There are so many different projects and use cases for crypto, many learning platforms and well written content available online for free. While it can get a bit overwhelming, the trick to not getting discouraged easily is to start slowly with areas that you&rsquo;re naturally drawn to.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Limaris Torres, Security Advisor at <a href="https://halborn.com/"><u>Halborn</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">First, learn to filter the noise from the useful information. Educate yourself using multiple sources but be careful, just because it is on the internet doesn&rsquo;t mean it is true. Trust but validate everything you stumble upon before jumping into anything within crypto. Knowledge is power and the more you know, the more informed your decisions will be and the more confident you can be in your investments.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Paulina J&oacute;&#347;k&oacute;w, Head of Business Development at <a href="https://ramp.network/"><u>Ramp</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">There&rsquo;s not even a close second to this one: research is your best friend.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Learn the minimum about what you&rsquo;re getting involved in, especially when it comes to spending your money. Don&rsquo;t just take financial advice for random influencers in social media without research.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Nowadays there&rsquo;s no lack of good resources to get started. In fact, the opposite is sometimes the case &ndash; there&rsquo;s just too much advice around, not all of it good.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The best places to start your research are usually the ones where there&rsquo;s some accountability. Crypto news outlets, like CoinJournal, Coindesk, Cointelegraph, The Defiant, and Messari, tend to have reputable information put together by journalists and with checked sources.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Regulated crypto businesses are also accountable for their content and thus have more to lose than an anonymous Youtuber if they ever mislead their audience.</p>
<p dir="ltr">When starting your learning journey, ask yourself when dealing with any source of information: what does this source stand to win by pushing an agenda? What are they not saying?</p>
<p dir="ltr">Even if you found a source that looks good, look for alternatives. Use more than one source to do your research, and don&rsquo;t give away your money (or personal data) without digging further.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Finally, when you&rsquo;re ready to take the leap and purchase your first cryptocurrency, make sure you know what you&rsquo;re doing. Better yet, using a reputable crypto on-ramp like Ramp makes the entire process easier and straightforward, and reduces the potential risk of mistakes.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Gabriella Kusz, CEO of the <a href="https://global-dca.org/"><u>Global Digital Asset and Cryptocurrency Association</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Read Satoshi Nakamotos white paper &ndash; it is a wealth of infuriation and a great way to begin to understand blockchain and crypto. &nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Rashid Ali, co-founder and CEO of <a href="https://exarta.com/"><u>Exarta</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Read, learn and research &ndash; not everything that shines is gold.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Only invest what you can afford to lose. It&rsquo;s very easy to get carried away just as if you were at the casino. If you can control your emotions, know when to stop and know your limits, you are in a good place. If you are the opposite then you are in danger of losing everything.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Peter Eberle, President and CIO of <a href="https://www.castlefunds.com/"><u>Castle Funds</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Don&rsquo;t expect 1000% returns, be realistic.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Paolo Ardoino, CTO of <a href="https://www.bitfinex.com/"><u>Bitfinex</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Most important is how to securely store your Bitcoin and cryptocurrency holdings. This should be done in cold storage using a ledger or similar hard wallet device.</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Do your research, understand the basics and how exchanges and wallets work.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Understand the larger environment and the impact it may have on the industry as a whole.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Do your best to ensure that you know the risks associated with the market including understanding what&rsquo;s happening in traditional markets and secure your wallet. There is no such thing as too much security.</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Jake Yocom-Piatt, Co-Founder and Project Lead of <a href="https://decred.org/"><u>Decred</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Avoid letting hype and a false sense of urgency drive your decisions.Take your time, do your own research, and try to understand what you&rsquo;re investing in before you buy it. &nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Cryptocurrency has many nuances and is substantially different than investing in fiat-based financial instruments. &nbsp;If a project was a good purchase a week ago, it will still be a good purchase a few weeks later. Fads come and go, but fundamentals do not.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Charmyn Ho, Head of Crypto insights at <a href="https://www.bybit.com/"><u>Bybit</u></a> says:</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Find a reputable exchange with a strong technology foundation. The digital asset class is built on technology. Be smart and take advantage of the many automated and AI tools available. Like other advanced platforms, Bybit makes AI-powered bots easily accessible for traders of all levels. Users can automate trades and put their assets to work 24/7, follow trading pros with the copy trading bot, and generate yield by staking their assets.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Keep an open mind and unlearn some of the habits you may have gained through traditional investing. In crypto, there are no middlemen, no quarterly financial reports or 2-hour long investor calls, but the wealth of free resources and knowledge transfer that takes place in the crypto community will serve as your best financial advisors. If you invest your time in researching and learning about the use cases, potential and tokenomics of digital assets, you will find projects that make sense to you and start to fortify your financial portfolio for the future. (can we insert a link back to Crypto Insights here too?)</p>
<p dir="ltr">The crypto world may seem overwhelming, but a strong supportive community, vast sources of educational materials, and the latest technology and tools, all readily available and all free, make experiencing the future far easier than traditional trading will ever be.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/expert-panel-what-is-your-biggest-tip-for-a-user-just-getting-into-crypto/">Expert panel: what is your biggest tip for a user just getting into crypto?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Brazil Central Bank plans to launch CBDC in 2024</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/brazil-central-bank-plans-to-launch-cbdc-in-2024/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/brazil-central-bank-plans-to-launch-cbdc-in-2024/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 13:04:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Policy and Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brazil]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/brazil-central-bank-plans-to-launch-cbdc-in-2024/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Brazil Central Bank is planning to launch a CBDC in 2024. According to the president of the central bank, digital assets could drive participation. Brazil will join the likes of China, the Bahamas, and Nigeria as nations with individual CBDCs. The president of the Brazil Central Bank, Roberto Campos Neto has today revealed in a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/brazil-central-bank-plans-to-launch-cbdc-in-2024/">Brazil Central Bank plans to launch CBDC in 2024</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Brazil Central Bank is planning to launch a CBDC in 2024.</li>
<li>According to the president of the central bank, digital assets could drive participation.</li>
<li>Brazil will join the likes of China, the Bahamas, and Nigeria as nations with individual CBDCs.</li>
</ul>
<p>The president of the Brazil Central Bank, Roberto Campos Neto has today revealed in a <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GcS1-Zn5n3E">press conference</a> that the bank is planning to launch a <a href="https://coinjournal.net/glossary/central-bank-digital-currency-cbdc/">Central Bank Digital Currency</a> in 2024.</p>
<p>Neto also revealed that the bank is planning to conduct a pilot program alongside other financial institutions prior to the full implementation of the CBDC. He also went on to give the benefits of implanting a digital currency issued by the central bank notably driving participation.</p>
<p>Neto said:</p>
<p><em>&ldquo;I think that this digitized, paid-in, integrated system, with inclusion, will help a lot in the development and inclusion of people in the financial world.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p>He also added:</p>
<p><em>&ldquo;Greater inclusion, lower cost, intermediation, competition with reduced barriers to entry, efficiency in risk control, monetization of data, complete tokenization of financial assets and contracts. This is what we see in this digital economy in Brazil.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p>It will be noted that today&rsquo;s development comes about eight months after Brazil announced plans to develop digital currency.</p>
<p>If successful, Brazil will join the likes of <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chinas-national-cryptocurrency-is-getting-more-ominous/">China</a>, Nigeria, India and other countries that have already launched their CBDC including plans to launch in the future. In general, there are many countries that are currently researching similar plans for launching CBDCs.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/brazil-central-bank-plans-to-launch-cbdc-in-2024/">Brazil Central Bank plans to launch CBDC in 2024</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/brazil-central-bank-plans-to-launch-cbdc-in-2024/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
