<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 09:15:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>THORChain (RUNE) up 65%: here&#8217;s why the token is rising</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/thorchain-rune-up-65-heres-why-the-token-is-rising/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/thorchain-rune-up-65-heres-why-the-token-is-rising/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 09:15:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bull run]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[THORChain News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/thorchain-rune-up-65-heres-why-the-token-is-rising/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THORChain (RUNE) token price has gained 65% over the past week and 53% over the past month. There has been a significant surge in social volume around THORChain. The social volume is driving notable attention toward the cross-chain liquidity protocol. Although the price of THORChain (RUNE) is still down 10% from its start of the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/thorchain-rune-up-65-heres-why-the-token-is-rising/">THORChain (RUNE) up 65%: here&#8217;s why the token is rising</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>THORChain (RUNE) token price has gained 65% over the past week and 53% over the past month.</li>
<li>There has been a significant surge in social volume around THORChain.</li>
<li>The social volume is driving notable attention toward the cross-chain liquidity protocol.</li>
</ul>
<p>Although the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/thorchain/">price of THORChain (RUNE)</a> is still down 10% from its start of the year price, the token has been on a strong bullish trend since the beginning of August. It has risen by 68% since August 1, pushing the price from around $0.92 to the current price of $1.55.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/07/15/1692090659788-d5334d29-4591-45da-ab37-d960e0370988.jpg" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="615" height="435"></p>
<p>While some are super excited with RUNE&rsquo;s upward trajectory, some are sceptical that the token could experience a pullback seeing that the rise has been so sharp. To fully understand how far the token could rise and the possibilities of a pullback, we shall delve into the factors pushing the price up.</p>
<h2>Why THORChian (RUNE) price is rising</h2>
<p>According to data on Santiment, the THORChain price surge is fueled by a surge in social volume. According to the data, RUNE&rsquo;s social volume increased by 4,300% between August 7 and August 13, driving significant attention toward the THORChian protocol and its native token.</p>
<p>In addition, THORChain&rsquo;s positive investor sentiment also grew 6,100% within the same timeline. This further caused RUNE&rsquo;s trading volume to spike as more investors jumped in.</p>
<p>THORCHian, which is a cross-chain liquidity protocol, in April, partnered with the web3 company Unizen to allow users to swap their <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/what-is-ethereum/">Ethereum (ETH)</a> and Avalanche (AVAX) for <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/what-is-bitcoin/">Bitcoin (BTC)</a> while also permitting users to store assets on different chains. This has been a great driver of the increased activity in the THORChain ecosystem.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/thorchain-rune-up-65-heres-why-the-token-is-rising/">THORChain (RUNE) up 65%: here&#8217;s why the token is rising</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/thorchain-rune-up-65-heres-why-the-token-is-rising/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance seeks court&#8217;s protection against US SEC&#8217;s probe</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-seeks-courts-protection-against-us-secs-probe/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-seeks-courts-protection-against-us-secs-probe/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 07:54:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-seeks-courts-protection-against-us-secs-probe/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The US SEC charged Binance for offering unregistered securities in the United States. The SEC then went ahead to seek for the freezing of Binance.US assets although the two later reached an agreement. Binance.US is now complaining that the SEC is overstepping its mandate according to the agreement. Binance.US, the US subsidiary of Binance, has [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-seeks-courts-protection-against-us-secs-probe/">Binance seeks court&#8217;s protection against US SEC&#8217;s probe</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>The US SEC charged Binance for offering unregistered securities in the United States.</li>
<li>The SEC then went ahead to seek for the freezing of Binance.US assets although the two later reached an agreement.</li>
<li>Binance.US is now complaining that the SEC is overstepping its mandate according to the agreement.</li>
</ul>
<p>Binance.US, the US subsidiary of <a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/binance/">Binance</a>, has filed to limit the extent of investigations by the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) in its case against the cryptocurrency exchange.</p>
<p>The <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-sec-is-seeking-court-order-to-freeze-binance-uss-assets/">SEC attempted to freeze all of Binance.US&rsquo;s assets</a> in June after expressing worries about the security of clients&rsquo; digital assets owned by the company. However, the US arm of Binance, doing business as BAM Trading Services and BAM Management US Holdings, entered into an agreement with the SEC as a result.</p>
<p>The agreement, which some commentators referred to as &ldquo;burdensome&rdquo; gave the SEC permission to conduct &ldquo;limited expedited discovery&rdquo; about the custody and accessibility of client funds.</p>
<h2>SEC&rsquo;s investigations into Binance.US</h2>
<p>Binance in a late <a href="https://www.courtlistener.com/docket/67474542/95/securities-and-exchange-commission-v-binance-holdings-limited/">Monday filing</a> claimed that the SEC&rsquo;s discovery demands have exceeded the parameters set forth in the consent agreement and constitute an improper &ldquo;fishing expedition.&rdquo;</p>
<p>In particular, Binance.US asserts that the SEC is requesting lengthy correspondence and deposition evidence from firm executives on &ldquo;dozens of topics&rdquo; irrelevant to client assets, including its CEO and CFO, who the filing argues have no understanding of the custody concerns at the heart of the matter.</p>
<p>Binance&rsquo;s request states that the company &ldquo;worked in good faith to respond to the SEC&rsquo;s requests&rdquo; by supplying hundreds of documents, providing depositions from staff members knowledgeable about asset security, and taking actions to guarantee assets are in US custody.</p>
<p>The crypto exchange, in its protective request to the court, argues that despite years of investigation by the SEC and all the provided information, &ldquo;the SEC still has not identified the slightest evidence that customer assets have been misused or mishandled in any way.&rdquo; It also opposes deposing top executives like the CEO and CFO stating that that would be unproductive, unduly burdensome, and disruptive to operations.</p>
<p>The crypto exchange suggests that the SEC should first investigate employees responsible for asset custody since they are the ones with &ldquo;far deeper knowledge&rdquo; about digital asset custody.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-seeks-courts-protection-against-us-secs-probe/">Binance seeks court&#8217;s protection against US SEC&#8217;s probe</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-seeks-courts-protection-against-us-secs-probe/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu, Bone prices outperform as Shiba Memu token sale thrives</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-bone-prices-outperform-as-shiba-memu-token-sale-thrives/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-bone-prices-outperform-as-shiba-memu-token-sale-thrives/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 20:09:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-bone-prices-outperform-as-shiba-memu-token-sale-thrives/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Shiba Inu and Bone Shibaswap have outperformed BTC and ETH. They have all jumped by over 68% and 115% from the lowest level in June. Shiba Memu has raised almost $2 million from investors. Meme coins are doing relatively well, with some outperforming popular cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin and Ethereum.&#160;Shiba Inu price has jumped by over [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-bone-prices-outperform-as-shiba-memu-token-sale-thrives/">Shiba Inu, Bone prices outperform as Shiba Memu token sale thrives</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Inu and Bone Shibaswap have outperformed BTC and ETH.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">They have all jumped by over 68% and 115% from the lowest level in June.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu has raised almost $2 million from investors.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Meme coins are doing relatively well, with some outperforming popular cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin and Ethereum.&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/shiba-inu"><u>Shiba Inu</u></a> price has jumped by over 68% from the lowest level in July while Bone Shibaswap has surged by over 115% in the same period. Large-cap coins like BTC and ETH, on the other hand, have remained in a tight range while drifting downwards.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Shibarium launch ahead&nbsp;</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Inu and Bone Shibaswap prices have done well in the past few weeks as investors wait for the upcoming&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/how-could-shibarium-laer-2-solution-unlock-shib-value/"><u>Shibarium launch</u></a>. Shibarium is an important technology that is designed to change how the Shibaswap ecosystem works.</p>
<p dir="ltr">For starters, ShibaSwap is a platform in Shiba Inu&rsquo;s ecosystem that makes it possible for people to swap tokens and make money by staking. It is now powered by Ethereum, the biggest chain in the world.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Ethereum has its own challenges, which explains why many layer-1 and layer-2 alternatives have come up. Some of the top L2 networks seeking to supercharge its ecosystem are Polygon, Optimism, and Arbitrum.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Shiabarium will be a layer-2 network whose goal will be to supecharge Shibaswap&rsquo;s ecosystem by reducing its transaction fees and boosting its speed. Its testnet has attracted thousands of users and there is hope that the mainnet will be better.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Shibarium&rsquo;s success will be a testament that a meme coin can create an ecosystem and thrive.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Shiba Memu token sale booms</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Bone Shibaswap and Shiba Inu are not the only meme coins that are thriving.&nbsp;<a href="https://shibamemu.com/"><u>Shiba Memu</u></a>, a new meme coin is taking shape as its token sale has raised almost $2 million from investors. This makes its token sale one of the most successful in the industry.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu is aiming to take advantage of some of the most important themes in the market this year. It is combining the ongoing meme coin craze and the one on artificicial intelligence.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Its AI angle will involve concepts like Natural Language Processing (NLP), sentiment analysis, and image and video recognition. In its&nbsp;<a href="https://shibamemu.com/whitepaper.pdf"><u>white paper</u></a>, Shiba Memu says this about the use of NLP:</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;AI-powered NLP algorithms can be used to analyze social media posts, forums and other online communities in order to identify discussions and topics relevant to Shiba Memu. This information can then be used to develop targeted marketing campaigns and engage with potential investors. Sentiment Analysis&rdquo;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Is Shiba Memu a good investment?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">It is too early to determine whether Shiba Memu will be a good long-term investment. As a result, you should do your own research about the ecosystem before investing. In my view, I believe that the token has the potential to become the next big thing in the crypto industry.</p>
<p>For one, its name has a close resemblance to Shiba Inu, the biggest meme coin in the world. Also, it has already gained traction even before its public debut as evidenced by the amount of money it has raised in a month. Most mportantly, it is targeting the biggest themes this year. You can buy the Shiba Memu token&nbsp;<a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news"><u>here</u></a>.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-bone-prices-outperform-as-shiba-memu-token-sale-thrives/">Shiba Inu, Bone prices outperform as Shiba Memu token sale thrives</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-bone-prices-outperform-as-shiba-memu-token-sale-thrives/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase enters the Canadian market with Coinbase One, free 30-day trial</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-enters-the-canadian-market-with-coinbase-one-free-30-day-trial/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-enters-the-canadian-market-with-coinbase-one-free-30-day-trial/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 17:50:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Canada]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto exchange]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-enters-the-canadian-market-with-coinbase-one-free-30-day-trial/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Coinbase is seeking to expand into Canada as it faces tough times at home. Coinbase launched an Ethereum layer-2 network last week. It is worth noting that a number of crypto exchanges have excited Canada in the recent past citing poor crypto environment. Coinbase cryptocurrency exchange is extending its already solid grasp on the North [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-enters-the-canadian-market-with-coinbase-one-free-30-day-trial/">Coinbase enters the Canadian market with Coinbase One, free 30-day trial</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Coinbase is seeking to expand into Canada as it faces tough times at home.</li>
<li>Coinbase launched an Ethereum layer-2 network last week.</li>
<li>It is worth noting that a number of crypto exchanges have excited Canada in the recent past citing poor crypto environment.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/coinbase/">Coinbase cryptocurrency exchange</a> is extending its already solid grasp on the North American market by expanding into Canada.</p>
<p>Coinbase will also provide Canadian citizens with a free 30-day trial of its recently established subscription service Coinbase One in an effort to attract new consumers. Coinbase One emphasizes staking and offers free trading and top-notch customer care.</p>
<h2>Canadian crypto market</h2>
<p>According to Coinbase&rsquo;s statement, the crypto exchange chose Canada as its new home because of the country&rsquo;s supposed high level of &ldquo;crypto-awareness&rdquo; and solid regulatory environment. This stands in stark contrast to the legal problems the company is currently facing domestically.</p>
<p>After the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-sec-strikes-again-first-binance-now-coinbase/">US Securities and Exchanges Commission (SEC) sued the exchange</a> for allegedly failing to register as a securities exchange while allegedly providing unregistered securities to its users, Coinbase has felt the heat from American regulators.</p>
<p>A group of thirty Canadian parliamentarians made international headlines in late June when they released a study backing cryptocurrencies and blockchain technology, along with 16 recommendations for the government of the nation to develop a national strategy on the subject.</p>
<p>However, despite the research, Canadian authorities have given conflicting signals on cryptocurrencies and many crypto businesses have stopped operating in the country or have withdrawn. Binance, the largest cryptocurrency exchange in the world by trading volume was the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-announces-exit-from-canada/">latest to exit Canada</a>.</p>
<p>Justin Trudeau, the prime minister of Canada, harshly criticizes opposition figures who support cryptocurrency.</p>
<h2>Coinbase feels the heat of the bear market</h2>
<p>The expansion into Canada comes at a time when Coinbase, the world&rsquo;s second-largest exchange by trading volume, is suffering from the effects of a long-lasting bear crypto market. The exchange reported a $96 million loss for the second quarter despite its financial results exceeding expectations.</p>
<p><a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbases-base-mainnet-featuring-100-dapps-opens-to-the-general-public/">Coinbase opened Base</a>, an <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/what-is-ethereum/">Ethereum </a>layer-2 network, to the general public late last week in an effort to promote the creation of fresh decentralized applications within its ecosystem. Immediately after its launch, Base took off and quickly rose to the top five layer-2 networks by the quantity of bridged traffic.</p>
<p>The exchange has also been investigating how to incorporate Lightning Network, a layer-2 scalability solution for <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/what-is-bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a>.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-enters-the-canadian-market-with-coinbase-one-free-30-day-trial/">Coinbase enters the Canadian market with Coinbase One, free 30-day trial</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-enters-the-canadian-market-with-coinbase-one-free-30-day-trial/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin address with 1,005 BTC suddenly wakes up after nearly 13 years</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-address-with-1005-btc-suddenly-wakes-up-after-nearly-13-years/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-address-with-1005-btc-suddenly-wakes-up-after-nearly-13-years/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 17:12:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin whales]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wallets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-address-with-1005-btc-suddenly-wakes-up-after-nearly-13-years/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Bitcoin address with 1,005 BTC activated 12+ years later, shifts more than $29 million. Wallet speculated to be from a miner who mined a lot in 2010. Bitcoin price remains largely flat above $29k. According to Whale Alert, the blockchain tracker and analytics system that provides regular updates of large coin transactions, another dormant [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-address-with-1005-btc-suddenly-wakes-up-after-nearly-13-years/">Bitcoin address with 1,005 BTC suddenly wakes up after nearly 13 years</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">A Bitcoin address with 1,005 BTC activated 12+ years later, shifts more than $29 million.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Wallet speculated to be from a miner who mined a lot in 2010.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Bitcoin price remains largely flat above $29k.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">According to Whale Alert, the blockchain tracker and analytics system that provides regular updates of large coin transactions, another dormant <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> address has just woken up.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin that has remained dormant for a significant period waking up suddenly when being transferred has often been subject to market speculation regarding the intention of the hodler. Whale transactions such as these often see jitters hit traders afraid of a major dump, and that is the case even as this particular <a href="https://coinjournal.net/wallets/">wallet</a> moved coins not touched for nearly 13 years.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Per the details shared today around 12 pm ET, the said dormant address holds 1,005 bitcoin (BTC), whose market value at current prices is about $29,750,772. The wallet &ldquo;has just been activated after 12.8 years.&rdquo; Whale Alert posted on X:</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">&#128164; &#128164; &#128164;  A dormant address containing 1,005 <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/BTC?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#BTC</a> (29,750,772 USD) has just been activated after 12.8 years!<a href="https://t.co/rLkpUZUvfH">https://t.co/rLkpUZUvfH</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Whale Alert (@whale_alert) <a href="https://twitter.com/whale_alert/status/1691116790066106369?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 14, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">According to one analyst who <a href="https://twitter.com/luckyking223/status/1691118342550282240" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">commented</a> on the Bitcoin whale&rsquo;s actions, the address appears to be of an early miner. Mempool analysis shows the individual had actively mined the flagship cryptocurrency in 2010.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitcoin price outlook</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin&rsquo;s price has over the past few weeks struggled to strengthen towards the $30,000 levels even as bulls defend the critical support base near $29,000. Pressure remains given a technical outlook that could see bears target the buffer area in the $28,000-$28,500 range.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/btc/">BTC</a>&rsquo;s chopping as seen over the last few weeks has resulted in a downtrend line on the weekly chart. Attempts to break higher have seen multiple upside wicks but no conviction from bulls. While bulls are capable of bouncing higher in the short term, any slight hammering could welcome the all-important $25k zone.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-address-with-1005-btc-suddenly-wakes-up-after-nearly-13-years/">Bitcoin address with 1,005 BTC suddenly wakes up after nearly 13 years</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-address-with-1005-btc-suddenly-wakes-up-after-nearly-13-years/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Recently listed Bitcoin Depot reports record revenue for its Q2</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-depot-reports-record-revenue-for-its-q2/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wajeeh Khan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 17:05:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ATMs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=149658</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin Depot reports an 18% annualised growth in its Q2 revenue. The Bitcoin ATM operator also updated its full-year guidance today. Bitcoin Depot stock is in the green only marginally on Monday. Bitcoin Depot Inc says its revenue jumped 18% to a record $197.5 million in the second quarter. The stock is still only marginally [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-depot-reports-record-revenue-for-its-q2/">Recently listed Bitcoin Depot reports record revenue for its Q2</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitcoin Depot reports an 18% annualised growth in its Q2 revenue.</li>
<li>The Bitcoin ATM operator also updated its full-year guidance today.</li>
<li>Bitcoin Depot stock is in the green only marginally on Monday.</li>
</ul>
<p>Bitcoin Depot Inc says its revenue jumped 18% to a record $197.5 million in the second quarter. The stock is still only marginally in the green at writing.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Depot reports a big increase in loss</h2>
<p>Shares of the <a href="https://www.bankrate.com/banking/what-are-bitcoin-atms/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin ATM</a> operator are having a hard time this morning primarily because the Georgia-based company lost $6.1 million in its recently concluded quarter, down an alarming 249% versus last year.</p>
<p>Its adjusted EBITDA, though, went up 54% to $19.8 million in Q2. Brandon Mintz &ndash; the Chief Executive of Bitcoin Depot said today in the <a href="https://ir.bitcoindepot.com/news-events/press-releases/detail/48/bitcoin-depot-reports-second-quarter-2023-financial-results" target="_blank" rel="noopener">press release</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>We&rsquo;re in position to further strengthen our balance sheet as we execute on our growth strategy &hellip; we&rsquo;re positioned to support mass crypto adoption as the leading Bitcoin ATM network.</p></blockquote>
<p>Note that the U.S. firm <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/largest-crypto-atm-operator-bitcoin-depot-debuts-on-nasdaq-after-spac-merger/">debuted on Nasdaq</a> only last month on July 3<sup>rd</sup>.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Depot&rsquo;s guidance for the full year</h2>
<p>Bitcoin Depot had $20.5 million worth of total operating expenses in its second quarter &ndash; up significantly from $12 million a year ago.</p>
<p>In Q2, the Nasdaq-listed firm partnered with a bunch of notable names including Stinker Stores, Jacksons Food Store, Gas Express, FastLane etc. According to CEO Mintz:</p>
<blockquote><p>We&rsquo;ve announced multiple partnerships and expanded our BDCheckout program. We look forward to increasing the number of our Bitcoin access points across North America.</p></blockquote>
<p>Just days ago, he said the Bitcoin ATM space was ready for <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/08/10/ceo-of-worlds-largest-bitcoin-atm-operator-sees-industry-ripe-for-consolidation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">consolidation</a>. Bitcoin Depot Inc now forecasts its revenue to grow by 8% to 13% this year on up to 44% increase in adjusted EBITDA.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-depot-reports-record-revenue-for-its-q2/">Recently listed Bitcoin Depot reports record revenue for its Q2</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>HBAR price soars as FedNow adds support for Hedera</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/hbar-price-soars-as-fednow-adds-support-for-hedera/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/hbar-price-soars-as-fednow-adds-support-for-hedera/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 16:09:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Federal Reserve]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/hbar-price-soars-as-fednow-adds-support-for-hedera/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Hedera (HBAR) price rose to above $0.065 on Monday morning. FedNow has added support for Dropp Inc, a Hedera-powered platform that now joins the Fed&#8217;s list of service providers. The Hedera (HBAR) price soared to above $0.065 on Monday morning (ET hours) as the cryptocurrency led the top 100 coins by market cap.&#160; According to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/hbar-price-soars-as-fednow-adds-support-for-hedera/">HBAR price soars as FedNow adds support for Hedera</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Hedera (HBAR) price rose to above $0.065 on Monday morning.</li>
<li dir="ltr">FedNow has added support for Dropp Inc, a Hedera-powered platform that now joins the Fed&rsquo;s list of service providers.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">The Hedera (HBAR) price soared to above $0.065 on Monday morning (ET hours) as the cryptocurrency led the top 100 coins by market cap.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to data from CoinGecko, Hedera&rsquo;s price spike was accompanied by a staggering 1,290% increase in its 24-hour trading volume as of 11 am ET, with buying pressure seeing over $224 million HBAR tokens traded.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The cryptocurrency, whose price had dipped below $0.060 last week, was up 17% and rising at the time of writing and 25% higher over the past 30 days.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Whys is HBAR price up today?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Hedera&rsquo;s native token was pumped on multiple occasions last month and early August following key partnerships and adoption efforts with major mainstream players. These included partnerships with South Korea multinational automakers Hyundai and Kia, which introduced an AI-enabled solution for tracking supply chain carbon emissions.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Also revealed recently is a partnership with global payments giant Mastercard.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The adoption of HBAR across these companies saw its price rise to its highest price since May. Profit taking took bulls back to lows of $0.56, but bulls are looking to reclaim the upper hand. The gains come amid new <a href="https://coinjournal.net/hedera/buy/">buy pressure for HBAR</a> following the Federal Reserve&rsquo;s FedNow <a href="https://explore.fednow.org/explore-the-city?id=10&amp;building=showcase-theater&amp;sortBy=newest&amp;postId=108&amp;vendor=dropp-inc" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">support</a> for &nbsp;Dropp Inc, a Hedera-powered platform. Dropp is now on the list of service providers for the Fed program.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As CoinJournal recently <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/federal-reserve-launches-fednow-instant-payment-system/">reported</a>, FedNow was launched to offer banks and credit unions access to instant payments. Hedera, on the other hand, is a decentralised public network based on the Hashgraph algorithm.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/hbar-price-soars-as-fednow-adds-support-for-hedera/">HBAR price soars as FedNow adds support for Hedera</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/hbar-price-soars-as-fednow-adds-support-for-hedera/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bad Idea crypto token has jumped: I think it’s a scam</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bad-idea-crypto-token-has-jumped-i-think-its-a-scam/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/bad-idea-crypto-token-has-jumped-i-think-its-a-scam/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 16:02:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bad-idea-crypto-token-has-jumped-i-think-its-a-scam/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bad Idea crypto token has jumped in the past few days. The token&#8217;s market cap has jumped to over $78 million. I think it is a scam that has no future in the industry. Bad Idea crypto has moved from obscurity to become a popular cryptocurrency worth over $78 million. The token surged to a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bad-idea-crypto-token-has-jumped-i-think-its-a-scam/">Bad Idea crypto token has jumped: I think it’s a scam</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Bad Idea crypto token has jumped in the past few days.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The token&rsquo;s market cap has jumped to over $78 million.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">I think it is a scam that has no future in the industry.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Bad Idea crypto has moved from obscurity to become a popular cryptocurrency worth over $78 million. The token surged to a high of $0.00000042 during the weekend and then pulled back to the current $0.00000015.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/cryptocurrencies/"><u>crypto</u></a> industry is made up of thousands of scams. This process has been made possible by crypto tokens, which can be created by anyone in a few minutes. Most of these tokens are built using Ethereum and BNB smart contracts.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bad Idea is one of the many project that I believe is not a valuable cryptocurrency. According to its&nbsp;<a href="https://static1.squarespace.com/static/64568e2523471d05956228f1/t/64570517d89163351580ef5c/1683424539459/BAD+IDEA+AI+WHITEPAPER+v1.0.pdf"><u>white paper</u></a>, it is a project that combines the concepts of artificial intelligence (AI), blockchain, and decentralized autonomous organization (DAO). It aims that these three parts will help to create a fully decentralized economy.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Unlike other projects, Bad Idea does not have a roadmap. Instead, the developers hope that it will be a system of interconnected AI agents working for humanity&rsquo;s benefit, instead of it. One way it will use AI is to produce weekly blog posts on AI and other topics (makes sense?)</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bad Idea&rsquo;s tokenomics seem to favor insiders, who I expect wil be cashing in soon. It has a supply limit of over 831 trillion tokens, with 58% going to the public. The rest will go to the team (we don&rsquo;t know who is the team), marketing, AI development, DAO development, and the Humanity Last Hope Fund. I believe that all these entities are the same team of insiders.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, in the short term, there is a likelihood that Bad Idea token will rise as insiders pump it. It will then crash, with most buyers left holding the bag. The white paper adds that:</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;The BAD IDEA Token and its associated project are intended for educational, entertainment, and experimental purposes only. By engaging with the BAD IDEA Token and project, you acknowledge that you are participating in a high-risk experiment and assume full responsibility for any decisions you make.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bad-idea-crypto-token-has-jumped-i-think-its-a-scam/">Bad Idea crypto token has jumped: I think it’s a scam</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/bad-idea-crypto-token-has-jumped-i-think-its-a-scam/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin miner Hut 8 revenue declined by $18.3 million in Q2</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-miner-hut-8-revenue-declined-by-18-3-million-in-q2/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-miner-hut-8-revenue-declined-by-18-3-million-in-q2/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 13:22:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-miner-hut-8-revenue-declined-by-18-3-million-in-q2/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Hut 8 posted revenue of $14.3 million (19.2 Canadian Dollars), which had fallen $18.3 million during the quarter compared to Q1, 2023. The company mined 399 Bitcoin (BTC) but sold a total of 396 BTC for $10.9 million (CAD 14.7 million) during the quarter. Hut 8 has announced its operating and financial results for Q2, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-miner-hut-8-revenue-declined-by-18-3-million-in-q2/">Bitcoin miner Hut 8 revenue declined by $18.3 million in Q2</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Hut 8 posted revenue of $14.3 million (19.2 Canadian Dollars), which had fallen $18.3 million during the quarter compared to Q1, 2023.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The company mined 399 Bitcoin (BTC) but sold a total of 396 BTC for $10.9 million (CAD 14.7 million) during the quarter.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Hut 8 has announced its operating and financial results for Q2, 2023. In details published on Monday August 14, the Bitcoin miner indicated its revenue fell $18.3 million (CAD 24.6 million) during the quarter ending June 30.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Hut 8 posted revenue of $14.3 million in Q2, 2023</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The Toronto-based cryptocurrency mining company highlighted revenue of $14.3 million (CAD 19.2 million) during the quarter, compared to $32.5 million (CAD 43.8 million) posted in Q2, 2022.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Meanwhile, the miner reported a loss of $12.4 million (CAD 16.7 million) for Q2, 2023 with per-share loss of 6 cents (8 Canadian cents).</p>
<p dir="ltr">Hut 8 also announced that it mined 399 Bitcoin (BTC) in the quarter, this being roughly 58% down on mined bitcoin for the same quarter in 2022. The company attributes the decrease to the increase in Bitcoin mining difficulty, impact of operations following issues at its North Bay Facility, as well as electrical issues encountered at the Drumheller facility.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>While we continued to face mining challenges during the second quarter at Drumheller, which are reflected in decreased revenue and fewer Bitcoin mined, we were successful in strategically managing our costs</em>,&rdquo; Shenif Visram, CFO at Hut 8, said in a <a href="https://hut8.io/2023/08/14/hut-8-reports-operating-and-financial-results-for-q2-2023/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">press release</a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Hut 8&rsquo;s financial results showed that the company&rsquo;s self-mined BTC balance as of June 30, 2023 &ndash; which it held in custody or had pledged as collateral &ndash; stood at 9,136 BTC. The holdings had a market value of $274 million (CAD 368.7 million). The miner sold a total of 396 BTC for $10.9 million (CAD 14.7 million) during the quarter.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/bitcoin-mining/">Bitcoin mining</a> giant, which secured a <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/hut-8-secures-50-million-credit-facility-from-coinbase/">$50 million credit facility</a> from Coinbase in June, also reported on the progress of its highly anticipated merger with US Bitcoin (USBTC). A shareholder vote on the merger is expected on September 12, the company said in a separate <a href="https://twitter.com/Hut8Mining/status/1691046291122393088" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">announcement</a>.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-miner-hut-8-revenue-declined-by-18-3-million-in-q2/">Bitcoin miner Hut 8 revenue declined by $18.3 million in Q2</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-miner-hut-8-revenue-declined-by-18-3-million-in-q2/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
