<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 16:21:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Goldman Sachs Selling Its Investment Advisory Business as It Suspends Attempts at Mass Market Businesses</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/goldman-sachs-sell-investment-advisory-business/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/goldman-sachs-sell-investment-advisory-business/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 16:19:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[goldman sachs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267535</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/goldman-sachs-sell-investment-advisory-business/">Goldman Sachs Selling Its Investment Advisory Business as It Suspends Attempts at Mass Market Businesses</a></p>
<p>Goldman Sachs has endured from losses from trying to cater to the broader market and is now looking to sell its investment advisor.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/goldman-sachs-sell-investment-advisory-business/">Goldman Sachs Selling Its Investment Advisory Business as It Suspends Attempts at Mass Market Businesses</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/goldman-sachs-sell-investment-advisory-business/">Goldman Sachs Selling Its Investment Advisory Business as It Suspends Attempts at Mass Market Businesses</a></p>
<p>Leading global investment banking and financial services company <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/goldman-sachs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Goldman Sachs</a> (NYSE: GS) is considering selling its investment advisory business. According to a Financial Times report, Goldman is “currently evaluating alternatives” for the company, which operates as a financial manager and investment adviser with assets worth about $29 billion.</p>
<p>Goldman Sachs says it hopes to find a solution that would be mutually beneficial for advisers and clients. The business expanded from United Capital, an investment firm Goldman purchased in 2019 for $750 million.</p>
<p>For the most part, Goldman typically catered to high-net-worth clients for its wealth management operations. Purchasing United Capital four years ago was Goldman’s attempt to reach a wide range of customers, especially those who are not high net-worth clients.</p>
<p>Unfortunately, Goldman has suffered losses as it pushed into broader investment advisory. This has put pressure on CEO David Solomon, who is now seeking to dispose of the investment arm. Notably, Goldman Sachs is looking to do away with its investment business at a time when the market is recording a lot of job switching among registered experts in the advisory field. Many of these persons are now moving to specialized outfits or launching their own businesses. These persons are also seemingly eager to take their clients along.</p>
<h2>Goldman Sachs to Sell GreenSky along with Investment Advisory Business</h2>
<p>Solomon is also trying to sell its specialty lender GreenSky. Founded in 2006, the company helps consumers get home improvement loans. GreenSky raised $874 million after going public in 2018 with Goldman Sachs as the lead underwriter. Goldman then acquired the company in 2022 to join its consumer banking business.</p>
<p>As part of its Q2 earnings <a href="https://www.goldmansachs.com/media-relations/press-releases/current/pdfs/2023-q2-results.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announcement</a>, Goldman said GreenSky suffered a $504 million write-down, plus $485 million in impairments connected to the company’s real estate investments.</p>
<p>People familiar with the matter have said that investment firm Sixth Street is leading a group of companies looking to take over GreenSky from Goldman. The group includes PIMCO, KKR, and CardWorks. The people also said Apollo Global Management is also trying to buy GreenSky in separate efforts. According to these people, Goldman might consider selling the platform and loan book to different parties. There’s also the possibility that Goldman could keep the loan book and only sell the platform. One of the parties said that the proposals are between $500 million and $1 billion. Other reports say the bids are about half of Goldman’s purchasing price at the time it acquired GreenSky.</p>
<p>The early GreenSky valuation in 2021 was $2.24 billion. However, the valuation eventually fell to $1.7 billion when the transaction was complete. After two rounds of bidding, the people familiar with the matter have said another round is unlikely.</p>
<p>Goldman had tried to buy GreenSky at a $7 per share price or $1.3 billion cash offer. However,  GreenSky canceled the process after Goldman refused to raise its bid.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/vitalik-buterin-deposited-eth-coinbase/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/goldman-sachs-sell-investment-advisory-business/">Goldman Sachs Selling Its Investment Advisory Business as It Suspends Attempts at Mass Market Businesses</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/goldman-sachs-sell-investment-advisory-business/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Creator Vitalik Buterin Has Deposited $1 Million Worth of ETH in a Coinbase Address</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/vitalik-buterin-deposited-eth-coinbase/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/vitalik-buterin-deposited-eth-coinbase/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 15:34:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vitalik Buterin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267500</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/vitalik-buterin-deposited-eth-coinbase/">Ethereum Creator Vitalik Buterin Has Deposited $1 Million Worth of ETH in a Coinbase Address</a></p>
<p>While there is still no word from Vitalik Buterin, the Ethereum co-founder's ETH move connects with a poor market and possible ETH ETF.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/vitalik-buterin-deposited-eth-coinbase/">Ethereum Creator Vitalik Buterin Has Deposited $1 Million Worth of ETH in a Coinbase Address</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/vitalik-buterin-deposited-eth-coinbase/">Ethereum Creator Vitalik Buterin Has Deposited $1 Million Worth of ETH in a Coinbase Address</a></p>
<p>Ethereum co-founder <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/vitalik-buterin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Vitalik Buterin</a> has moved 600 Ether (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ETH</a>), about $1 million, to a <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase</a> wallet, according to <a href="https://etherscan.io/address/0xd8da6bf26964af9d7eed9e03e53415d37aa96045" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">data</a> from Etherscan.</p>
<p>The move is interesting because, over the last few days, the value of ETH has fallen by nearly 10%. As of writing time, ETH is trading at $1,674, according to CoinMarketCap data. Also, trading volume over the last 24 hours is $4.5 billion, or 2.7 million ETH. At the moment, no one is sure why Buterin moved the ETH. There are also no details on the owner of the wallet. In addition, the Ethereum creator has not explained the move.</p>
<p>Buterin’s ETH transfer could likely spur some market action because of his person, and the mere fact that he moved the assets. While the crypto market is still struggling through uncertain times, a move like this, especially following a 10% plunge over the last seven days, may not augur well.</p>
<p>Already, crypto analyst Ali Martinez is bearish on ETH. Martinex believes that if ETH continues falling, a 37% to 45% plunge is possible if the price crashes below $1,550. This means that the world’s second-largest cryptocurrency by market cap could hit $1,000.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="474" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Ethereum?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Ethereum</a> | Slipping beneath the $1,600 &#8211; $1,550 bracket for <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24ETH&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$ETH</a> might set the stage for a significant 37% &#8211; 45% correction, targeting $1,000. <a href="https://t.co/Xmo7Mgfux5">pic.twitter.com/Xmo7Mgfux5</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Ali (@ali_charts) <a href="https://twitter.com/ali_charts/status/1693507725169193156?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 21, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The current ETH price might be a crucial one according to several analysts who believe the $1,600 zone is critical. Any move below that could push the asset to $1,550, and then it might continue to fall in agreement with predictions from Martinez.</p>
<h2>Vitalik Buterin Moving ETH Also Coincides with Possible ETF Approval</h2>
<p>ETH may also benefit from a <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-approve-ether-futures-us/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">possible approval of futures ETFs</a> (exchange-traded funds). According to recent reports, the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) could very likely approve ETFs that track ETH futures contracts. This brings the possibility of good tidings to the general ETH community, especially among people looking for this specific type of exposure to Ethereum.</p>
<p>While speculations suggest an approval may come by October, no one is sure which of the 16 active applications would receive regulatory greenlight. Volatility Shares had opened the floor with a <a href="https://www.sec.gov/Archives/edgar/data/1884021/000138713123009033/ethu-485apos_072823.htm" target="_blank" rel="noopener">filing</a> on July 28. Following the submission, several other applicants joined. Roundhill, ProShares, VanEck, Grayscale, and Bitwise all <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ethereum-etf-sec-bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">entered the mix within 24 hours</a>. So far, Valkyrie Investments, Direxion, and a few others have also joined the race.</p>
<p>According to Eric Balchunas, an analyst at Bloomberg, the likelihood of approval might be high. Balchunas says that in most cases, the SEC would have asked applicants to withdraw their filings within a few days. Although Balchunas noted the possibility of disapproval or a withdrawal request is still there, the analyst believes the fact that several approvals are still active after a few weeks is a good sign. In a <a href="https://twitter.com/EricBalchunas/status/1686752210036604928" target="_blank" rel="noopener">tweet</a> early this month, the analyst predicted that approvals would come sometime around August 16.</p>
<p>It is currently unclear whether or not the news means anything for Bitcoin ETFs. As the market waits on the SEC’s decision on BTC ETFs, the general expectation is that the Commission will start to respond in early September. The SEC may deny or approve applications, or decide to delay a decision for a while.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jio-financial-services-shares-drop/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/vitalik-buterin-deposited-eth-coinbase/">Ethereum Creator Vitalik Buterin Has Deposited $1 Million Worth of ETH in a Coinbase Address</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/vitalik-buterin-deposited-eth-coinbase/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Jio Financial Services (JFS) Drops 5% in Share Price Following Market Debut</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/jio-financial-services-shares-drop/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/jio-financial-services-shares-drop/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 13:03:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[india]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jfs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jio financial services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jio platforms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[reliance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267508</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jio-financial-services-shares-drop/">Jio Financial Services (JFS) Drops 5% in Share Price Following Market Debut</a></p>
<p>Despite recording a reduced valuation, JFS remains the third-largest non-banking financial company in India.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jio-financial-services-shares-drop/">Jio Financial Services (JFS) Drops 5% in Share Price Following Market Debut</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jio-financial-services-shares-drop/">Jio Financial Services (JFS) Drops 5% in Share Price Following Market Debut</a></p>
<p>Minutes after listing on stock exchanges on Monday, Jio Financial Services (JFS) has fallen limit-down. That is even as investors remain unsure about the expanse of the business cashed out of the stock.</p>
<p>JFS, which was recently spun off of billionaire Mukesh Ambani&#8217;s Reliance Industries, had its stock price set at 262 Indian rupees (approximately $3.15) per share. The discovery session of July held JFS&#8217; valuation to be 1.7 trillion Indian rupees ($20.5 billion).</p>
<p>The share price, however, soon fell 5% – the most a stock can fall in a session.  And that was despite that JFS started trading with over 73 million shares exchanging hands. The stocks are now valued at about 1.58 trillion Indian rupees ($19 billion).</p>
<h2>Investors Seek Clarity on JFS</h2>
<p>From all indications, it appears that investors are still unclear about the JFS share. Although <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/reliance-infibeam-digital-payment/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Reliance Industries</a> had earlier approved 6.35 billion JFS shares to be listed, there is yet an air of uncertainty around how much of a stake that represents in the company.</p>
<p>So, the investors will be expecting Ambani to throw more light on JFS during the Reliance annual general meeting that&#8217;s billed to take place on August 28.</p>
<p>So far, Reliance has only said so much about Jio Financial Services and what the company intends to offer as its products and services.  However, according to non-executive chairman KV Kamath, JFS might be aiming to become a &#8220;full-service financial services player&#8221;.</p>
<p>Besides, Reuters <a href="https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/indias-jio-financial-services-blackrock-launch-asset-management-venture-2023-07-26/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reported</a> in July that Jio Financial had partnered with BlackRock to launch an asset management platform for consumers in India. Although details of the full business plans have not been revealed, reports have it that both partners each committed $150 million to the joint venture. And as Reliance suggests in a filing, JFS&#8217; services may also include consumer and merchant lending, payments platform, insurance broking, AMC &amp; other NLFs.</p>
<p>Despite recording a reduced valuation, JFS remains the third-largest non-banking financial company in India. It comes in behind Bajaj Finance and Bajaj Finserv with 4.15 trillion rupees and 2.32 trillion rupees valuations respectively.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-web-version-threads-app/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jio-financial-services-shares-drop/">Jio Financial Services (JFS) Drops 5% in Share Price Following Market Debut</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/jio-financial-services-shares-drop/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Meta Platforms to Unveil Web Version of Its Threads App Soon</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-web-version-threads-app/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-web-version-threads-app/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 12:33:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Meta]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meta platforms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[threads]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267517</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-web-version-threads-app/">Meta Platforms to Unveil Web Version of Its Threads App Soon</a></p>
<p>The web version of Threads is scheduled for an early next week launch, citing sources familiar with the matter.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-web-version-threads-app/">Meta Platforms to Unveil Web Version of Its Threads App Soon</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-web-version-threads-app/">Meta Platforms to Unveil Web Version of Its Threads App Soon</a></p>
<p>American multinational technology conglomerate, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/meta/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Meta Platforms Inc</a> (NASDAQ: META) is on the brink of unveiling a web version of its new microblogging app, Threads. This development comes as part of Meta&#8217;s ongoing efforts to expand its reach and provide users with a seamless and interconnected experience across its various platforms.</p>
<h2>Meta Navigates Technical Hurdles</h2>
<p>However, the <a href="https://www.wsj.com/tech/metas-threads-app-to-launch-web-version-as-rivalry-with-x-enters-new-stage-706e8241" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">WSJ report</a> suggests that the company’s ambitious plans for Threads’ web version might be encountering technical complexities that necessitate a reevaluation of the launch timeline.</p>
<p>Developing a web version for an app as intricate as Threads poses a series of technical challenges. Ensuring consistent functionality across different devices, optimizing performance, and preserving the intuitive user interface are no small feats.</p>
<p>Consequently, addressing these technical hurdles requires meticulous attention to detail, rigorous testing, and perhaps even iteration of the feature’s design and functionality.</p>
<p>This cautious approach demonstrates Meta’s commitment to delivering a seamless and reliable user experience. The company’s history of adapting and iterating its products based on user feedback and technological advancements suggests that Meta is prioritizing quality over profitability in this case.</p>
<p>Threads, originally introduced as a companion app to Instagram, quickly garnered attention with <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/user-traffic-twitter-threads-100m/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">over</a> 100 million sign-ups in just five days of its launch. The app’s focus on succinct updates, coupled with its visual-rich content-sharing capabilities, resonated with users who sought a more streamlined way to share their experiences.</p>
<h2>Advantages for Users and Content Creators</h2>
<p>While mobile devices have become a vital part of our daily lives, many users still prefer the ease and vast canvas that desktop and laptop experiences provide. Threads’ web version strives to suit this choice by allowing users to access and interact with the app across their preferred devices.</p>
<p>The introduction of Threads to the web delivers an array of benefits to both casual users and content creators. Accessing Threads through web browsers ensures that users can engage with the app in a more versatile manner. Whether it&#8217;s a quick update, sharing multimedia content, or engaging in discussions, the web version will cater to a broader range of user preferences.</p>
<p>For content creators, the larger canvas provided by desktop and laptop screens will open up new possibilities for crafting captivating content. This enhancement may enable creators to explore more intricate images, resulting in higher-quality posts that fascinate people throughout the digital spectrum.</p>
<p>While the introduction of Threads on the web holds immense promise, it&#8217;s not without its challenges. Competing with <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/elon-musk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Elon Musk</a>’s <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/musk-twitter-logo-x/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">X platform</a> will require meticulous attention to detail, usability, and aesthetics.</p>
<p>Additionally, as with any online platform, issues related to privacy, security, and content moderation demand careful consideration to maintain a safe and enjoyable user environment.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-dollar-steady-china-5-year-interest-rates-unchanged/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-web-version-threads-app/">Meta Platforms to Unveil Web Version of Its Threads App Soon</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-web-version-threads-app/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>US Dollar Remains Steady as China Surprises by Keeping 5-Year Interest Rates Unchanged</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-dollar-steady-china-5-year-interest-rates-unchanged/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-dollar-steady-china-5-year-interest-rates-unchanged/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 12:11:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Currencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dollar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pboc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[us dollar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[usd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[yuan]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267488</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-dollar-steady-china-5-year-interest-rates-unchanged/">US Dollar Remains Steady as China Surprises by Keeping 5-Year Interest Rates Unchanged</a></p>
<p>China keeping the fiver-year loan rates unchanged has put breaks on the five weeks rally in the US Dollar. Investors now wait for the Federal Reserve's Jackson Hole symposium for any further guidance. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-dollar-steady-china-5-year-interest-rates-unchanged/">US Dollar Remains Steady as China Surprises by Keeping 5-Year Interest Rates Unchanged</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-dollar-steady-china-5-year-interest-rates-unchanged/">US Dollar Remains Steady as China Surprises by Keeping 5-Year Interest Rates Unchanged</a></p>
<p>On Monday, August 21, China <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/pboc-cuts-down-1-year-rates/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">announced</a> its decision to cut the one-year benchmark lending rates with authorities seeking to ramp up efforts in order to stimulate the credit demand. This comes as the recovery in the world&#8217;s second-largest economy has come to a major slowdown amid the worsening property slump.</p>
<p>Also, weak credit growth and the tumbling economy have negatively affected the country&#8217;s economy thereby forcing policymakers to release more stimulus. Despite this, China surprised by keeping the five-year rate unchanged despite a slowing economy.</p>
<p>But since the Yuan faces downward pressure, it also shows that China has limited room for further monetary easing. However, analysts say that if China&#8217;s yield differences with other major economies continue to increase, it could lead to a situation of Yuan sell-off and major capital outflows.</p>
<p>Thus, the country has decided to reduce the one-year loan prime rate (LPR) by 10 basis points to 3.45% from 3.55% previously. However, it kept the five-year LPR unchanged at 4.20%. But market analysts were expecting rate cuts for both tenures.</p>
<p>The majority of new and existing loans in China depend on the one-year LPR, and the pricing of mortgages is affected by the five-year rate. In June, China lowered both LPRs as a measure to stimulate the economy. Speaking to Reuters, Masayuki Kichikawa, chief macro strategist at Sumitomo Mitsui DS Asset Management <a href="https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-cuts-1-year-lending-benchmark-keeps-5-year-unchanged-2023-08-21/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Probably China limited the size and scope of rate cuts because they are concerned about downward pressure on the yuan. Chinese authorities care about currency market stability.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>China Puts Breaks to USD&#8217;s Gains</h2>
<p>After five straight weeks of gains, the US Dollar held firmly on Monday, with investors waiting for the Federal Reserve&#8217;s Jackson Hole symposium for any further guidance. This is when there will be more clarity on the rate hikes and the dust will finally settle.</p>
<p>Last week, the US Dollar strengthened against the euro by 0.7%, gained a slight advantage against the yen, and saw a more than 1% increase compared to currencies from Australia and New Zealand. This occurred as US Treasury yields rose due to expectations of interest rates remaining higher for an extended period.</p>
<p>Both the Australian dollar (valued at $0.6402) and the New Zealand dollar (valued at $0.5919) remained close to the lowest points they reached last week, which were the lowest in nine months. China&#8217;s rate cut influenced this drop, which disappointed markets concerned about an economic slowdown.</p>
<p>Despite the central bank fixing its trading range, the yuan declined past 7.3 per dollar, though it stayed above last week&#8217;s lows beyond 7.31. Even though the central bank intervened as buyers in London and New York trading hours, the yuan traded at 7.3077.</p>
<p>The currencies of Australia and New Zealand often act as a proxy for the yuan due to their substantial exports to China. As the outlook for interest rates pushes up the U.S. Dollar, these currencies become particularly vulnerable.</p>
<p>Similar to the yuan, the yen is being watched for possible intervention. It had fallen to levels at which authorities intervened the previous year. In early European trading, the yen was stable at 145.44 against the dollar.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/adyen-loses-20-billion-shares-plunge/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-dollar-steady-china-5-year-interest-rates-unchanged/">US Dollar Remains Steady as China Surprises by Keeping 5-Year Interest Rates Unchanged</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-dollar-steady-china-5-year-interest-rates-unchanged/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stripe Rival Adyen Loses $20 Billion in One Day as Shares Plunge Following Poor H1 Report</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/adyen-loses-20-billion-shares-plunge/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/adyen-loses-20-billion-shares-plunge/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 11:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[adyen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethan tandowsky]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Meta]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[netflix]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[spotify]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stripe]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267483</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/adyen-loses-20-billion-shares-plunge/">Stripe Rival Adyen Loses $20 Billion in One Day as Shares Plunge Following Poor H1 Report</a></p>
<p>Adyen published its slowest growth for a half-year since 2018 and lost $20 billion of its market valuation as shares also fell 39%.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/adyen-loses-20-billion-shares-plunge/">Stripe Rival Adyen Loses $20 Billion in One Day as Shares Plunge Following Poor H1 Report</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/adyen-loses-20-billion-shares-plunge/">Stripe Rival Adyen Loses $20 Billion in One Day as Shares Plunge Following Poor H1 Report</a></p>
<p>Shares of Dutch payment company <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/adyen/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Adyen</a> crashed 39% on Thursday causing the company’s market capitalization to plunge by 18 billion euros ($20 billion). Adyen had just published figures for the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/adyen-shares-fall-h1-performance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">first half of 2023</a>, which fell considerably below expectations.</p>
<p>Although Adyen reported a 21% year-over-year (YoY) growth in revenue of 739.1 million euros, about $804.3 million, it was the company’s slowest sales growth. Projections from Eikon Refinitiv analysts had put the expected revenue at 853.6 million euros, a 40% growth YoY.</p>
<p>The company’s growth was not enough to allay investor fears as they rushed to dump the stock. Adyen’s consistent revenue growth every half-year since it began trading in 2018 was also not enough to save the shares from plunging. Speaking to CNBC, Adyen chief financial officer Ethan Tandowsky <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/08/21/adyen-europes-fintech-darling-faces-big-challenges.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“With higher inflation, leading to higher interest rates, there has been a bit of a shift of focus &#8211; less focus on growth, more focus on bottom line.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Tandowsky says that Adyen is paying more attention to “functionality” than most of its competitors. This was in response to the competition offering cheaper services, especially in other markets like North America. The company’s competitors seem to give Adyen a run for its money as they can pull in more customers with cheaper services.</p>
<p>In a <a href="https://investors.adyen.com/financials/h1-2023" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">letter</a> sent to shareholders, Adyen revealed that its earnings before interest, tax, depreciation, and amortization (EBITDA) margin fell from 59% in H1 last year, to 43% in H1 2023. Nevertheless, Tandowsky believes the company’s focus on functionality will help Adyen remain successful:</p>
<blockquote><p>“The efficiency of which we can develop new functionality, functionality that out performs our peers will lead us to gaining the market share that we expect.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>Adyen Shares Plunge to Reflect Market Conditions</h2>
<p>The company’s H1 2023 report shows that Adyen’s conditions may have dampened since the beginning of the year. The report states that many customers in North America are already reducing costs to tackle general economic problems like inflation and the rise in interest rates.</p>
<p>In addition, profitability may have suffered because Adyen spent more on wages as it increased its staff count. After onboarding 551 new employees in H1, Adyen now has a total of 3,883 workers. Interestingly, rivals are taking the opposite route and have considerably reduced hiring. Stripe, for instance, cut 1,100 staff, or about 14% of its employee strength.</p>
<p>Adyen offers payment services to several major companies, including <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/meta/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Meta</a>, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/spotify/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Spotify</a>, and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/netflix/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Netflix</a>. It also helps process payments for brick-and-mortar stores using point-of-sale services and enables online payments. Adyen is one of the world’s top 200 fintech companies worldwide, according to CNBC and independent data and statistics company Statista.</p>
<p>Although the company has recorded growth since 2018, Adyen might be facing continued growth reduction. According to CEO Pieter van der Does, several merchants are already considering local alternatives with cost-effective options.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-settlement-approach-us-trustees-objections/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/adyen-loses-20-billion-shares-plunge/">Stripe Rival Adyen Loses $20 Billion in One Day as Shares Plunge Following Poor H1 Report</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/adyen-loses-20-billion-shares-plunge/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Exchange FTX Adapts New Settlement Approach after Objections from US Trustees </title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-settlement-approach-us-trustees-objections/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-settlement-approach-us-trustees-objections/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 11:29:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sam bankman-fried]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sbf]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267474</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-settlement-approach-us-trustees-objections/">Crypto Exchange FTX Adapts New Settlement Approach after Objections from US Trustees </a></p>
<p>The US Trustee had initially flagged concerns about disparities within the previous motion.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-settlement-approach-us-trustees-objections/">Crypto Exchange FTX Adapts New Settlement Approach after Objections from US Trustees </a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-settlement-approach-us-trustees-objections/">Crypto Exchange FTX Adapts New Settlement Approach after Objections from US Trustees </a></p>
<p>A new development has surfaced in the ongoing bankruptcy proceedings of the defunct cryptocurrency exchange <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a>. The troubled company has revised its proposed settlement plan after the US Trustees rejected its initial proposal. According to a <a href="https://restructuring.ra.kroll.com/ftx/Home-DocketInfo" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">court document</a> filed on August 20, FTX debtors have filed a motion to modify its proposed settlement plan to address the trustees&#8217; concerns and ensure the smooth continuation of the process.</p>
<h2>US Trustees Cite Concerns about Lack of Clarity</h2>
<p>The US Trustee had initially flagged concerns about disparities within the previous motion. Specifically, the Trustee questioned the designation of a $10 million threshold as appropriate for a minor claim. Additionally, there were concerns about the clarity surrounding the nature of the asserted claims.</p>
<p>Initially, the FTX debtors criticized the US Trustees as the sole objectors to the proposed &#8220;Motion&#8221;, claiming they attempted to &#8220;interfere in a routine settlement process that is already well-protected by two distinct creditor committees&#8221;.</p>
<p>However, the exchange has changed heart and filed to modify its settlement plan to include the trustees as a &#8220;noticed party&#8221; throughout the restructuring process.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the debtors also proposed reducing the maximum claim value, dropping the figure from the earlier $10 million to a more modest $7 million.</p>
<h2>An Attempt at Reconciliation</h2>
<p>FTX debtors have committed to regular updates on settled claims as part of their proactive approach. These updates will be provided monthly.</p>
<p>It is important to note that any concerns raised by notified parties must be addressed for a claim to advance. If an amicable resolution cannot be reached, the court&#8217;s intervention will be sought for a final decision.</p>
<p>The settlement process is being driven by two key creditor committees: The Official Committee of Unsecured Creditors and the ad hoc Committee representing international stakeholders. These committees are instrumental in ensuring fairness and equity throughout the settlement proceedings.</p>
<h2>Trouble in Paradise</h2>
<p>FTX, which held the title of the world&#8217;s second-largest exchange after Binance, started its bankruptcy proceedings earlier this year after its collapse in November 2022.</p>
<p>Recall that the company, which was then valued at around $32 billion, had suffered a brief liquidity crisis last year before ultimately <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-exchange-files-for-bankruptcy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">filing</a> for bankruptcy. The company&#8217;s founder Sam Bankman-Fried (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/sam-bankman-fried/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SBF</a>), was accused of mismanaging customers&#8217; funds, and he is currently facing many <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/judge-motions-dismiss-criminal-sbf/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">criminal </a>charges in the United States for his role in the collapse of the exchange.</p>
<p>Earlier this month, a judge issued a ruling that resulted in the placement of the disgraced FTX founder within the confines of the Brooklyn Metropolitan Detention Center (MDC) after he was deemed to have violated his bail conditions.</p>
<p>However, in a surprising turn of events, SBF is now seeking release under specific and unique circumstances. In an August 18 letter to US District Judge Lewis Kaplan, his lawyers have asked for SBF to be released during the weekdays to enable him adequately prepare for his defense. If approved, the former FTX CEO will only spend weekends in jail.</p>
<div id="gtx-trans" style="position: absolute; left: -24px; top: 177.333px;">
<div class="gtx-trans-icon"></div>
</div>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-social-credit-system-metaverse-regulation/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-settlement-approach-us-trustees-objections/">Crypto Exchange FTX Adapts New Settlement Approach after Objections from US Trustees </a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-settlement-approach-us-trustees-objections/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>China Proposes Its Social Credit System to Regulate the Metaverse</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-social-credit-system-metaverse-regulation/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-social-credit-system-metaverse-regulation/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Temitope Olatunji]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 11:12:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[metaverse]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267451</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-social-credit-system-metaverse-regulation/">China Proposes Its Social Credit System to Regulate the Metaverse</a></p>
<p>According to some experts, the idea of providing each person with a digital ID that also contains their social traits and other personal information is more akin to the Chinese social credit system.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-social-credit-system-metaverse-regulation/">China Proposes Its Social Credit System to Regulate the Metaverse</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-social-credit-system-metaverse-regulation/">China Proposes Its Social Credit System to Regulate the Metaverse</a></p>
<p>China is proposing a strategy to exert control over people’s activities in the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-metaverse/#:~:text=Metaverse%20is%20an%20interconnected%203D,from%20all%20over%20the%20world." target="_blank" rel="noopener">metaverse</a> by developing a scheme that looks like its social credit system. This became evident through China Mobile&#8217;s proposal for a &#8220;Digital Identity System&#8221; for virtual world users.</p>
<p>The proposal suggests creating IDs based on natural and social traits and getting data on individuals, like their occupations and distinctive characteristics. The collected information would also be securely stored and shared with law enforcement to ensure order.</p>
<p>According to some experts, the idea of providing each person with a digital ID that also contains their social traits and other personal information is more akin to the Chinese social credit system. The credit system has generated controversy since it was first introduced. The government employs it to evaluate and rank the moral character and trustworthiness of citizens and businesses. It requires collecting data like financial records, social interactions, online activities, and more to score various entities.</p>
<p>These scores can subsequently influence citizens&#8217; eligibility for diverse activities and privileges. They can also determine whether an entity should face penalties for undesirable behavior. Potential penalties include travel limitations, restricted job access, limited loan and business prospects, curtailed activities, public humiliation, and communication restrictions.</p>
<p>One of the primary concerns about a metaverse regulation system resembling China&#8217;s credit system is that it contradicts the fundamental principles of utilizing the metaverse. There&#8217;s a risk of compromising privacy and freedom.</p>
<h2>The Proposal Has Received Mixed Reactions from Experts</h2>
<p>China Mobile proposed the strategy at the second International Telecommunication Union (ITU) metaverse focus group meeting, and it could be voted upon in October.</p>
<p>Although China is making various plans in preparation for the future of the internet and setting standards that will guide the running of the virtual world even more than the United States and other European participants in the ITU, this move has been met with mixed reactions among experts.</p>
<p>Chris Kremidas-Courtney, Senior Fellow for Friends of Europe in Brussels, said that China seeks to lead in metaverse development and align it with its state-controlled digital system. Having these standards is the initial step in creating a future where China sets the norm for emerging technologies.</p>
<p>Another expert who also contributes to the ITU metaverse focus group and knows about the matter expresses mixed feelings about it. He <a href="https://www.politico.eu/article/china-beijing-designing-metaverse-proposal-social-credit-system-un-itu/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>:</p>
<blockquote>
<p style="text-align: left;">&#8220;Imagine a metaverse where your identity protocols are set and monitored by Chinese authorities. Every government must ask themselves &#8211; Is that the kind of immersive world we want to live in?&#8221;</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Matt Sheehan, a fellow at the Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, did not like the idea. He stated:</p>
<blockquote>
<p style="text-align: left;">&#8220;The ITU is the body that China has done the most damage to. Chinese actors flood it with bad proposals, often because they get government subsidies for filing them. But the result is that technology companies just don&#8217;t pay attention to ITU standards anymore.&#8221;</p>
</blockquote>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-mining-lebanon-cheaper-italy/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-social-credit-system-metaverse-regulation/">China Proposes Its Social Credit System to Regulate the Metaverse</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-social-credit-system-metaverse-regulation/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Mining in Lebanon Turns Ultra Cheaper in Comparison to Italy</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-mining-lebanon-cheaper-italy/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-mining-lebanon-cheaper-italy/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 10:50:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[changpeng zhao]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cz]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267448</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-mining-lebanon-cheaper-italy/">Bitcoin Mining in Lebanon Turns Ultra Cheaper in Comparison to Italy</a></p>
<p>Recent survey shows that Italy is the most expensive country for mining Bitcoin at $208,560 for each BTC produced.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-mining-lebanon-cheaper-italy/">Bitcoin Mining in Lebanon Turns Ultra Cheaper in Comparison to Italy</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-mining-lebanon-cheaper-italy/">Bitcoin Mining in Lebanon Turns Ultra Cheaper in Comparison to Italy</a></p>
<p>When it comes to the Bitcoin mining costs, there’s a strong contrast worldwide in the household electricity expenses for individual <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> miners. A recent survey shows that Bitcoin mining in Lebanon is 783 times cheaper than Bitcoin mining in Italy. Currently, the cost of mining 1 BTC in Italy is $208,560.</p>
<p>Last week on August 17, CoinGecko released a report, showing that only 65 countries are good for people who mine Bitcoin alone, considering just how much it costs to use electricity at home. Out of these countries, 34 are in Asia, but there are only five in Europe. But the problem is that people who mine Bitcoin on their own are having trouble because the average cost of electricity at homes worldwide is different.</p>
<p>“The average household electricity cost to mine 1 Bitcoin is $46,291.24, which is 35% higher than the average daily price of 1 BTC in July 2023 ($30,090.08),” the <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/research/publications/bitcoin-mining-cost" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a> notes.</p>
<p>The report names Italy as the most expensive country for mining Bitcoin at $208,560 for each Bitcoin. This means that mining one Bitcoin at home in Italy costs as much as about eight Bitcoins are worth.</p>
<p>Next in line were Austria at $184,352 and Belgium at $172,382. On the other hand, in Lebanon, the cost of electricity is low enough that individual miners can make one Bitcoin for just $266. Looking at these numbers, mining one Bitcoin in Lebanon is about 783 times cheaper than mining one in Italy.</p>
<h2>Iran among the Cheapest Countries to Mine Bitcoin</h2>
<p>Iran is among those countries where the cost to produce one Bitcoin was $532. Despite legalizing Bitcoin mining in 2019, the country has intermittently banned these operations, citing strains on energy grids, especially during winter.</p>
<p>Earlier this year, Iran’s Organization for Collection and Sale of State-Owned Property confiscated around 150,000 pieces of cryptocurrency mining equipment. In related news, new technology is claimed to increase the chances of successfully mining a winning hash by 260%.</p>
<p>On August 19, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a> CEO <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/changpeng-zhao/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Changpeng “CZ” Zhao</a> shared a screenshot of the report’s data on platform X (formerly known as <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/twitter/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Twitter</a>). He asked his 8.6 million followers why people in countries with cheap electricity wouldn’t consider mining Bitcoin.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="474" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Why wouldn&#39;t they? 🤷‍♂️😂 <a href="https://t.co/cD1TSgOZzx">pic.twitter.com/cD1TSgOZzx</a></p>
<p>&mdash; CZ 🔶 Binance (@cz_binance) <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1692807605599498358?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 19, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>However, CZ said that there could be other factors to consider. “The report probably didn’t consider feasibility and other logistics. But if the data is true, there definitely seems to be some potential opportunities,” noted CZ.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-btc-price-above-26k/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-mining-lebanon-cheaper-italy/">Bitcoin Mining in Lebanon Turns Ultra Cheaper in Comparison to Italy</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-mining-lebanon-cheaper-italy/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Is Hovering Above $26K amid Broad-based Selloff</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-btc-price-above-26k/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-btc-price-above-26k/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 09:57:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[grayscale]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267449</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-btc-price-above-26k/">Bitcoin Price Is Hovering Above $26K amid Broad-based Selloff</a></p>
<p>The latest data from CoinMarketCap has indicated an unsettling calm in BTC/USD trading over the weekend, with the market experiencing an 11% decline in a span of just seven days.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-btc-price-above-26k/">Bitcoin Price Is Hovering Above $26K amid Broad-based Selloff</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-btc-price-above-26k/">Bitcoin Price Is Hovering Above $26K amid Broad-based Selloff</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> (BTC) remains perched above the $26,000 mark, creating an air of uncertainty in the crypto market which has been recording a broad-based selloff in the past week. BTC’s price <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-26k-tests-investor-resilience/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">fell</a> below $26,000 on Friday afternoon, following a brief rise above $27,000 that served to mitigate some of the steep losses seen earlier in the past week.</p>
<h2>Analysts Remain Cautions on Bitcoin’s Price</h2>
<p>Market observers, still shaken by the recent price drop, remained cautious about the future trajectory of Bitcoin&#8217;s price. Keith Alan, the co-founder of Material Indicators, a monitoring resource outfit, maintained a relatively conservative outlook amidst the uncertainty.</p>
<p>Alan expressed his thoughts on the X platform, <a href="https://twitter.com/KAProductions/status/1692970230593577377" target="_blank" rel="noopener">predicting</a> that Bitcoin’s price will eventually fall below $25,000 and retest support near the 2017 Bull Market Top, which was just under $20,000. However, Alan did not foresee a linear path to this outcome, explaining:</p>
<blockquote><p>“I&#8217;m looking for a retest of $25,000 support to potentially create a double bottom and lay the groundwork for another upward rally. If this setup comes to fruition, a realistic range of $28,000 to $29,000 could be achieved.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Alan also mentioned that if and when the retest of the $25,000 level occurs, his focus would then shift to the possibility of a series of lower lows.</p>
<p>Many shared the sentiment that if Bitcoin fails to find support at $25,000, then the $20,000 range would once again become a focal point for market participants. A well-known pseudonymous trader Skew <a href="https://twitter.com/52kskew/status/1693188345164390754" target="_blank" rel="noopener">commented</a> on the potential scenario, noting:</p>
<blockquote><p>“A break below $25,300 might signal a move towards $24,000 &#8211; $23,000, which could initiate a stronger buyback response. Alternatively, continued downward momentum could lead to a further drop to $20,000. In the most extreme case, Bitcoin might even dip below $20,000, presenting an opportunity for swing trading.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Despite the prevalent pessimism, Skew predicted a short-term rally in intraday Bitcoin price movement around the weekly close, perhaps sending the price toward $28,500 if purchasing pressure becomes more pronounced.</p>
<h2>Grayscale vs SEC Case Tempers Bitcoin’s Optimistic Outlook</h2>
<p>The crypto market’s landscape remains uncertain and volatile, with traders and investors grappling with the ramifications of the recent price decline. Optimistic expectations have been tempered by the absence of positive developments stemming from the Grayscale vs the US Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) court battle, which had the potential to influence Bitcoin’s price trajectory.</p>
<p>The legal tussle revolves around Grayscale’s desire to convert its $12 billion <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-grayscale-bitcoin-trust/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">GBTC Bitcoin Trust</a> into a spot Bitcoin Exchange-Traded Fund (ETF), a move that could significantly enhance its attractiveness to investors. Despite the attention, the regulator had previously rejected Grayscale&#8217;s application, prompting the investment manager to take legal action in an attempt to overturn the decision.</p>
<p>As Bitcoin’s price continues to experience fluctuations and market participants wait for clarity on the Grayscale vs SEC case, the broader crypto community remains vigilant, well aware of the potential implications of such legal battles on the market&#8217;s future.</p>
<div id="gtx-trans" style="position: absolute; left: 219px; top: 80.7778px;">
<div class="gtx-trans-icon"></div>
</div>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-sbf-demands-weekly-release/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-btc-price-above-26k/">Bitcoin Price Is Hovering Above $26K amid Broad-based Selloff</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-btc-price-above-26k/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4034 metric#misses=48 metric#hit-ratio=98.8 metric#bytes=1034046 metric#prefetches=197 metric#store-reads=25 metric#store-writes=5 metric#store-hits=203 metric#store-misses=9 metric#sql-queries=38 metric#ms-total=111.27 metric#ms-cache=6.38 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.2199 metric#ms-cache-ratio=5.7 -->