<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 18:54:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Litecoin price drops below key technical area: What next for LTC?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/litecoin-ltc-price-decline-deepens-amid-key-technical-breakdown/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 18:54:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/litecoin-ltc-price-decline-deepens-amid-key-technical-breakdown/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Litecoin price has retreated 14% in the past 24 hours and 23% in the past week Price has also broken below an ascending channel trendline support. Can bulls stem post-halving dump? Litecoin price has declined 14% in the past 24 hours to add to the pain bulls have experienced over the past three weeks. The [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/litecoin-ltc-price-decline-deepens-amid-key-technical-breakdown/">Litecoin price drops below key technical area: What next for LTC?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Litecoin price has retreated 14% in the past 24 hours and 23% in the past week</li>
<li dir="ltr">Price has also broken below an ascending channel trendline support.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Can bulls stem post-halving dump?</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/litecoin/">Litecoin</a> price has declined 14% in the past 24 hours to add to the pain bulls have experienced over the past three weeks. The cryptocurrency, which successfully underwent its third block reward halving early this month, traded to lows of $60.75 and has plummeted 23% in the past week.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Why did Litecoin price go down today?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">LTC&rsquo;s latest price decline came as most top cryptocurrencies by market cap dumped heavily on the back of Bitcoin&rsquo;s sharp plunge to the $25k area. &nbsp;This was after investors spooked by rumours related to Elon Musk&rsquo;s SpaceX BTC holdings sold off, with the 24-hour <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-liquidations-hit-1b-as-bitcoin-dumps-to-near-25k/">crypto liquidations jumping to over $1 billion on Friday</a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The downward pressure cascaded to altcoins, which saw Ethereum nosedive to below $1,575 and XRP touch the technical support area of $0.50. Litecoin&rsquo;s reaction was for its post-halving rot to deepen and leave bulls poised at a key level that threatens further declines.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">LTC price technical outlook</h2>
<p dir="ltr">As seen on the daily chart below, the breakdown from highs of $114 in early July has all but wiped pre-halving gains. The psychologically important $100 is once again the primary horizontal resistance level while $60 is now crucial for bulls.</p>
<div class="fr-img-space-wrap"><span class="fr-img-caption fr-fic fr-dib fr-draggable" style="width: 700px"><span class="fr-img-wrap">
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/07/18/1692384356029-9aa12a65-ec57-495b-b30a-3ac181b32417.png" style="width: 700px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="700" height="267"><span class="fr-inner">Litecoin price on daily chart. Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/7a7c0B2x/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">TradingView</a></span></p>
<p></p></span></span>
<p class="fr-img-space-wrap2">The weekly chart also gives a bearish outlook, with the RSI indicator signaling negative momentum. The chart also shows that LTC has broken below the support line of an ascending parallel channel in place since mid-May 2022. The decisive breakdown suggests bears have the upper hand.</p>
</div>
<div class="fr-img-space-wrap"><span class="fr-img-caption fr-fic fr-dib fr-draggable" style="width: 700px"><span class="fr-img-wrap">
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/07/18/1692384235773-c36d36de-309b-4edb-b0a7-2636e75b14e9.png" style="width: 700px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="700" height="267"><span class="fr-inner">Litecoin price on weekly chart. Source:&nbsp;<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/AkBG7ay0/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">TradingView</a></span></p>
<p></p></span></span>
<p class="fr-img-space-wrap2">If the price breaks down from $60, Litecoin risks new declines of 30% or more to $40. While a rebound could materialize in the short term, bulls will remain under pressure unless price strengthens in the $80-$100 region.</p>
</div>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/litecoin-ltc-price-decline-deepens-amid-key-technical-breakdown/">Litecoin price drops below key technical area: What next for LTC?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Huobi Announces Strategic Partnership with TradingView</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/huobi-announces-strategic-partnership-with-tradingview/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/huobi-announces-strategic-partnership-with-tradingview/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire &#160;]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 17:31:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=150281</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Singapore, Singapore, August 18th, 2023, Chainwire Crypto Exchange Huobi announced a strategic partnership with TradingView on data and trading integration services. Users will now be able to directly view the real-time prices of cryptocurrencies on Huobi with TradingView. They can also create accounts and trade on Huobi without having to switch between platforms. With more [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/huobi-announces-strategic-partnership-with-tradingview/">Huobi Announces Strategic Partnership with TradingView</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Singapore, Singapore, August 18th, 2023, Chainwire</strong></p>
<p>Crypto Exchange Huobi announced a strategic partnership with TradingView on data and trading integration services. Users will now be able to directly view the real-time prices of cryptocurrencies on Huobi with TradingView. They can also create accounts and trade on Huobi without having to switch between platforms.</p>
<p>With more than 50 million traders and investors globally, TradingView is a premier financial chart analysis platform that covers various fields such as stocks, forex, bonds, and crypto. Users are able to customize financial charts and tools to gain comprehensive analyses on TradingView&rsquo;s own programming language called Pine Script. With this integration, users have more ways to learn and trade digital assets while enjoying more professional digital asset management services provided by Huobi.</p>
<p>TradingView is also one of the largest investor social platforms. In addition to regular financial updates and news, users can access chart analysis, investment papers, live broadcasts, and other related discussions among traders. Huobi users can now optimize their investment strategies and grow their profits with these features, which drives both platforms&rsquo; long-term development. Moreover, sharing investment-related content associated with Huobi improves user reputation and elevates brand exposure.</p>
<p>A Huobi spokesperson leading this initiative stated,</p>
<blockquote><p>&ldquo;It is a great honor to partner with TradingView and provide more investors with easy access to crypto assets. Huobi hopes that the launch of data and trading integration services will considerably optimize and upgrade user experience. It enables Huobi to expand to more regions, improve global brand awareness, build a Web3 gateway, and help more traders to trade crypto safely.&rdquo;</p></blockquote>
<p>A TradingView spokesperson also added,</p>
<blockquote><p>&ldquo;TradingView has established partnerships with multiple exchanges within the cryptocurrency industry. The addition of the well-established exchange Huobi brings more potential for future collaboration. As the partnership evolves, the platform&rsquo;s multi-dimensional customizable analysis tools and enriched social modules will undoubtedly spark unique synergies with Huobi. This will usher in new opportunities for the cryptocurrency industry.&rdquo;</p></blockquote>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>About TradingView</h3>
<p>TradingView is a world-leading financial charting platform that provides price feed from almost every financial market, such as stock, commodities, crypto, forex, etc. With its friendly UI, simple UX, and customizable chart analysis tools, TradingView has received thousands of favorable reviews from traders, investors, and even large organizations. TradingView is also one of the largest social platforms for investors. It is possible for traders and investors to discuss and share knowledge about the market using the TradingView platform.</p>
<h3>About Huobi</h3>
<p>Founded in 2013, Huobi has evolved from a crypto exchange into a comprehensive ecosystem of blockchain businesses that span digital asset trading, financial derivatives, wallets, research, investment, incubation and other areas. Huobi serves millions of users worldwide, with a business presence covering over 160 countries and regions across five continents. Its three development strategies &ndash; &ldquo;global development, technology drives development, and technology for good&rdquo; &ndash; underpin its commitment to providing comprehensive services and values to global cryptocurrency enthusiasts.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Contact</strong></p>
<p>Michael Wang<br>
glo-media@huobi.com</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/huobi-announces-strategic-partnership-with-tradingview/">Huobi Announces Strategic Partnership with TradingView</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/huobi-announces-strategic-partnership-with-tradingview/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Checkout.com terminates Binance support over AML concerns: report</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/checkout-com-terminates-binance-support-over-aml-concerns-report/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/checkout-com-terminates-binance-support-over-aml-concerns-report/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 15:39:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto payments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[UK]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/checkout-com-terminates-binance-support-over-aml-concerns-report/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Credit card processor Checkout.com cuts ties with Binance over AML concerns. Binance is reportedly considering legal action, Forbes said in a report published August 18. Binance recently announced it was shutting down its regulated buy-and-sell crypto arm Binance Connect. Checkout.com, the UK-based payments processor that has been one of the biggest payments partners for Binance, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/checkout-com-terminates-binance-support-over-aml-concerns-report/">Checkout.com terminates Binance support over AML concerns: report</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Credit card processor Checkout.com cuts ties with Binance over AML concerns.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Binance is reportedly considering legal action, Forbes said in a report published August 18.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Binance recently announced it was shutting down its regulated buy-and-sell crypto arm Binance Connect.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Checkout.com, the UK-based payments processor that has been one of the biggest payments partners for <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/binance/">Binance</a>, has reportedly ended its relationship with the crypto exchange giant.</p>
<p dir="ltr">A report&nbsp;<a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidjeans/2023/08/18/payment-processor-checkout-drops-binance-over-money-laundering-compliance-concerns/?sh=70ec64fd5623" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>published</u></a> by Forbes on August 18 indicated that the London-based firm informed Binance of the move this week, having sent letters to that effect on August 9 and 11. In the letters, Checkout.com cites the various regulatory actions against the crypto company and overall concerns over anti-money laundering (AML) compliance.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The termination, which took effect on August 17, was communicated to Binance by Checkout CEO Guillaume Pousaz, Forbes reported.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Binance is considering legal action following Checkout&rsquo;s decision, the exchange said via a statement attributed to spokesperson Dewi Mustajab. The crypto giant says the withdrawal by Checkout.com will not impact its services.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Binance recently shut Binance Connect</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The development comes shortly after Binance, as CoinJournal&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/regulated-buy-and-sell-arm-of-binance-binance-connect-shutting-down/"><u>reported</u></a> earlier this week, announced it was shutting down a Checkout-supported unit dubbed Binance Connect. The regulated buy-and-sell platform supported crypto payments for businesses.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Elsewhere, PaySafe, one of Europe&rsquo;s leading payments providers, also ended its partnership with Binance in June.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Notably, Binance <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/blog/ecosystem/binance-launches-payments-technology-company-bifinity-421499824684903541" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">launched</a> its fiat-to-crypto payments provider, Bifinity, in March 2022. The company was unveiled in partnership with both PaySafe and Checkout.com.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/checkout-com-terminates-binance-support-over-aml-concerns-report/">Checkout.com terminates Binance support over AML concerns: report</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/checkout-com-terminates-binance-support-over-aml-concerns-report/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu price outlook: SHIB army digs in despite Shibarium setback</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-price-outlook-shib-army-digs-in-despite-shibarium-setback/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-price-outlook-shib-army-digs-in-despite-shibarium-setback/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 13:39:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-price-outlook-shib-army-digs-in-despite-shibarium-setback/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Shiba Inu (SHIB) traded to lows of $0.0000072 before bouncing to $0.0000087. Declines for SHIB came amid wider crypto sell-off as Bitcoin fell to lows of $25,600. SHIB price could recover to the psychological $0.00001 or see fresh declines to major support levels. Shiba Inu&#8217;s native token SHIB has plunged to July lows, trading to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-price-outlook-shib-army-digs-in-despite-shibarium-setback/">Shiba Inu price outlook: SHIB army digs in despite Shibarium setback</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Shiba Inu (SHIB) traded to lows of $0.0000072 before bouncing to $0.0000087.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Declines for SHIB came amid wider crypto sell-off as Bitcoin fell to lows of $25,600.</li>
<li dir="ltr">SHIB price could recover to the psychological $0.00001 or see fresh declines to major support levels.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/shiba-inu/">Shiba Inu</a>&rsquo;s native token SHIB has plunged to July lows, trading to lows of $0.000000726 after a sharp 20% drop. SHIB price was down over 30% in the past week as of 8:30 am ET on Friday morning.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The token&rsquo;s sharp decline follows a broader market sell-off that also saw <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-on-knifes-edge-as-price-falls-below-28k/">Bitcoin flash crash</a> to $25,600 and Ethereum to $1,570. However, for Shiba Inu, the dump had another catalyst.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Sell-off came at a time the SHIB army &ndash; a passionate community of SHIB holders &ndash; was looking to navigate a major setback related to the cryptocurrency&rsquo;s layer-2 network Shibarium. Meanwhile, the data <a href="https://twitter.com/shibburn/status/1692521781804892312" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">shows</a> a total of over 97 million SHIB have been burnt in the past 24 hours.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Shibarium hit snag shortly after launch</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Shibarium, a fork of Polygon, launched to much hype on Wednesday, with the community celebrating a key milestone as the layer-2 network brought new functionality set to transform the Shiba Inu ecosystem.</p>
<p dir="ltr">But that enthusiasm hit the rocks shortly after, with the L2 going offline amid what the team says was an unprecedented traffic. The <a href="https://blog.shib.io/shibarium-update/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">latest update</a> from the team has nonetheless provided optimism for a swift reboot, more so after it was revealed Shibarium was getting help from major players within the ecosystem.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Developer Kaal Dhairya has also assured users that the $1.7 million in user funds locked in the ETH bridge as the blockchain went into &ldquo;fail safe&rdquo; mode were &ldquo;safu.&rdquo; Although its unclear when the Shiba Inu L2 platform reboots, the community&rsquo;s response to today&rsquo;s update has seen SHIB price turn just green as seen on the 24-hour time frame.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">SHIB price outlook after Shibarium setback</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The 4-hour chart below shows SHIB has bounced from lows of $0.00000726 to intraday highs of $0.0000087.&nbsp;</p>
<div class="fr-img-space-wrap"><span class="fr-img-caption fr-fic fr-dib fr-draggable" style="width: 700px"><span class="fr-img-wrap">
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/07/18/1692364594159-304af432-bb81-4519-b25e-c97e5a148dc2.png" style="width: 700px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="700" height="267"><span class="fr-inner">Shiba Inu price on 4-hour chart. Source:&nbsp;<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/z2fPES8u/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">TradingView</a></span></p>
<p></p></span></span>
<p class="fr-img-space-wrap2">This area however represents a previous resistance zone, which suggests the SHIB army might have to dig in push further to bounce to the psychologically important $0.00001 level.&nbsp;</p>
</div>
<p dir="ltr">Otherwise, more downside will follow as the 4-hour RSI remains below 50 to indicate strength still lies with the bears. In this case, the key areas to watch on the downside are $0.000008 and $0.0000075.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-price-outlook-shib-army-digs-in-despite-shibarium-setback/">Shiba Inu price outlook: SHIB army digs in despite Shibarium setback</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-price-outlook-shib-army-digs-in-despite-shibarium-setback/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto liquidations hit $1B in 24 hours as Bitcoin dumps to near $25k</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-liquidations-hit-1b-as-bitcoin-dumps-to-near-25k/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 12:04:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-liquidations-hit-1b-as-bitcoin-dumps-to-near-25k/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Over $1 billion in crypto liquidations occured as crypto prices dumped sharply. Bitcoin fell to near $25k amid a flash crash triggered by SpaceX rumour. The crypto market saw a sharp correction overnight Thursday/Friday morning, with Bitcoin price crashing within minutes from near $28k to lows of $25,600. Reverberations across the market resulted in over [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-liquidations-hit-1b-as-bitcoin-dumps-to-near-25k/">Crypto liquidations hit $1B in 24 hours as Bitcoin dumps to near $25k</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Over $1 billion in crypto liquidations occured as crypto prices dumped sharply.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Bitcoin fell to near $25k amid a flash crash triggered by SpaceX rumour.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">The crypto market saw a sharp correction overnight Thursday/Friday morning, with <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">Bitcoin price</a> crashing within minutes from near $28k to lows of $25,600. Reverberations across the market resulted in over $1 billion in liquidations and the crypto market cap shrunk by nearly 7%.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Traders rekt as amid massive $1 billion in liquidations</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Even though the benchmark cryptocurrency has pared some of the losses to trade around $26,440 at 7am ET, the negative flip left more than 176,000 traders rekt. According to data from <a href="https://www.coinglass.com/LiquidationData" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Coinglass</a>, the past 24 hours saw 176,700 traders liquidated &ndash; total liquidations in the time frame reaching $1.04 billion.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Most of the liquidated positions were longs at $832 million, while shorts accounted for about $206 million. Bitcoin saw over $499 million in liquidations &ndash; $373 million in longs and $125 million in shorts.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to Glassnode data, the largest single liquidation order was $55.92 million on Binance and involved ETH/BUSD. The ETH price fell to below $1,580, its lowest level since mid-June. Wu Blockchain posted <a href="https://twitter.com/WuBlockchain/status/1692496102216655289" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">this</a> on X.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">During today&rsquo;s sharp drop, an investor in Binance&rsquo;s ETHBUSD contract was liquidated at $1,434.37 for $55.9211 million, which was the largest liquidation order today. This could be a market maker, which may hedge on other exchanges. In the same minute, a Binance BTCUSDT contract&hellip;</p>
<p>&mdash; Wu Blockchain (@WuBlockchain) <a href="https://twitter.com/WuBlockchain/status/1692496102216655289?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 18, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Why did Bitcoin price fall so suddenly?</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-on-knifes-edge-as-price-falls-below-28k/">Bitcoin teetered on a knife&rsquo;s edge</a> on Thursday when crypto mirrored broader market&rsquo;s reaction to Fed minutes released on Wednesday. After breaking below $28k, largely on scant volume, the possibility of a flash crash increased.</p>
<p dir="ltr">That happened after rumours spread that Elon Musk&rsquo;s SpaceX had dumped its BTC holdings. By the time the rumour was debunked, BTC/USD was trading at levels last seen when the market reacted higher on news of BlackRock&rsquo;s spot <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/bitcoin-etf/">Bitcoin ETF</a> application.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Veteran trader and analyst Gareth Soloway highlighted the outlook via a post on X.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Bitcoin</a> flushed through 28k. With so little volume, stops triggering can cause an outsized move (flash crash).</p>
<p>Rumors that SpaceX dumped its holdings (unconfirmed) exacerbated the selling and increased the dump with so few buyers available. SpaceX did write down some of their&hellip; <a href="https://t.co/eN6QErapWc">pic.twitter.com/eN6QErapWc</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Gareth Soloway (@GarethSoloway) <a href="https://twitter.com/GarethSoloway/status/1692322798524317718?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 17, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">The recovery towards the critical $28k level is likely to hinge on regulatory news involving the Grayscale ETF application, which is expected today around 11 am ET. Still on ETF news, there&rsquo;s some optimism related to the approval of several Ether futures ETF applications. These and other market conditions could be key not just to Bitcoin and Ethereum, but the overall crypto market.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin below $25k would bring the $20k support level into view and likely threaten a retest of the 52-week cycle lows. On the flipside, rebound to $28k on a confluence of upside triggers could inject fresh momentum and strengthen bulls.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-liquidations-hit-1b-as-bitcoin-dumps-to-near-25k/">Crypto liquidations hit $1B in 24 hours as Bitcoin dumps to near $25k</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>SEI token takes a hit, plunges 26% after a splendid performance</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/sei-token-takes-a-hit-plunges-26-after-a-splendid-performance/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/sei-token-takes-a-hit-plunges-26-after-a-splendid-performance/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 09:59:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/sei-token-takes-a-hit-plunges-26-after-a-splendid-performance/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>At press time, SEI was trading at $0.1625 down 12.02% from where it was trading at yesterday the same time. The token&#8217;s trading volume has also dropped by 42% in the last 24 hours. SEI recently announced it was increasing the number of eligible wallets for $SEI Airdrop from 500K to 1.5M wallets. SEI token [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sei-token-takes-a-hit-plunges-26-after-a-splendid-performance/">SEI token takes a hit, plunges 26% after a splendid performance</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul class="decimal_type">
<li>At press time, SEI was trading at $0.1625 down 12.02% from where it was trading at yesterday the same time.</li>
<li>The token&rsquo;s trading volume has also dropped by 42% in the last 24 hours.</li>
<li>SEI recently announced it was increasing the number of eligible wallets for $SEI Airdrop from 500K to 1.5M wallets.</li>
</ul>
<p>SEI token price dropped to $0.1496 in the early hours of Friday morning, sending shockwaves among investors. The token has seen a very strong performance over the past seven days and it hit an all-time high of $0.2736 on August 16.</p>
<p>But why is the price of SEI dropping? Why is SEI going down after such a magnificent surge? Well, this article shall delve into the details of what caused SEI to take a dive.</p>
<h2>Here&rsquo;s why the SEI price is going down</h2>
<p>This price decline coincided with a decision by Sei Foundation to open airdrop claims to 1 million more wallets than previously anticipated.</p>
<p>Sei blockchain mainnet beta went live on August 15 promising to hold a token airdrop afterwards.</p>
<p>Sei today reported that the number of wallets eligible for the airdrop had surged from the initially planned number of 500,000 wallets to roughly 1.5 million in response to what the Sei Foundation termed &ldquo;fervent demand.&rdquo;</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Due to fervent demand, Sei Foundation has increased the number of eligible wallets for the cross-bridge airdrop from 500K to 1.5M on <a href="https://twitter.com/ethereum?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@ethereum</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/0xPolygonLabs?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@0xPolygonLabs</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/arbitrum?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@arbitrum</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/BNBCHAIN?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@BNBCHAIN</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/solana?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@solana</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/optimismFND?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@optimismFND</a>  and <a href="https://twitter.com/osmosiszone?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@osmosiszone</a>.</p>
<p>&mdash; Sei Foundation (@Sei_FND) <a href="https://twitter.com/Sei_FND/status/1692070808783368592?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 17, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The wallet surge is believed to have incorporated users from a variety of other blockchains pouring into the blockchain including but not limited to <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/what-is-ethereum/">Ethereum</a>, BNB Chain, and <a href="https://coinjournal.net/polygon/what-is-polygon/">Polygon</a>.</p>
<p>Sei Foundation had earmarked 3% (300 million) of SEI tokens for the airdrop, which constitute a significant chunk of the 1.8 billion Sei coins currently circulating out of the token&rsquo;s total supply of 10 billion coins.</p>
<p>Token airdrops often trigger a cascade of sell-offs as eligible users rush to convert their newfound coins into cash or other cryptocurrencies.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sei-token-takes-a-hit-plunges-26-after-a-splendid-performance/">SEI token takes a hit, plunges 26% after a splendid performance</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/sei-token-takes-a-hit-plunges-26-after-a-splendid-performance/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin dropped below $26k in sudden crash: Will traders suffer more losses</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-dropped-below-26k-in-sudden-crash-will-traders-suffer-more-losses/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-dropped-below-26k-in-sudden-crash-will-traders-suffer-more-losses/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 09:49:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-dropped-below-26k-in-sudden-crash-will-traders-suffer-more-losses/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways Bitcoin dropped below the $26k level on Thursday, with traders losing nearly $1 billion in the process. Chancer&#8217;s stage two presale is now closing in on the $1.5 million mark. The cryptocurrency market has been extremely bearish since the start of the week. The prices of most cryptocurrencies are down by more than [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-dropped-below-26k-in-sudden-crash-will-traders-suffer-more-losses/">Bitcoin dropped below $26k in sudden crash: Will traders suffer more losses</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin dropped below the $26k level on Thursday, with traders losing nearly $1 billion in the process.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Chancer&rsquo;s stage two presale is now closing in on the $1.5 million mark.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">The cryptocurrency market has been extremely bearish since the start of the week. The prices of most cryptocurrencies are down by more than 5% over the last seven days.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Despite the bearish sentiment, Chancer&rsquo;s presale is set to hit another benchmark as stage two is approaching the $1.5 million mark.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitcoin drops to the $25k zone</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin, the world&rsquo;s leading cryptocurrency by market cap, has been extremely bearish over the past 24 hours. BTC lost nearly 10% of its value and dropped to the $25,300 level late on Thursday.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The bearish trend saw long traders lose nearly $1 billion. However, the market is starting to recover, with Bitcoin and others setting new support levels. At press time, the&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>price of Bitcoin</u></a> stands at $26,543.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What does this mean for Chancer?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The bearish performance could see some investors take advantage of the discount price to invest in more cryptocurrency projects. Investors could be looking to purchase more bitcoins and other cryptocurrencies ahead of a likely bullish cycle.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As more investors look for projects to invest in, Chancer could be one of the projects they might consider.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Chancer</u></a> is one of the exciting and new projects currently in the cryptocurrency space. With stage two presale set to hit an important milestone, it is clear Chancer is gathering momentum amongst retail investors.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Chancer team is currently developing a unique Web3 peer-to-peer (P2P) custom betting platform that would make it possible for users to live-stream betting events.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer wants to decentralise the betting industry and is leveraging blockchain technology to achieve its objectives.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">With Chancer, there are no restrictions to betting opportunities for users. This implies that users can bet on a wide range of events, beyond traditional sports and casino bets.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Chancer presale is in its second stage and has raised nearly $1.5 million of the $2 million required. In the second presale, CHANCER is selling for $0.011 USDT but will be increased to $0.012 in the third stage.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Funds raised from the multiple presale events will be geared towards building Chancer&rsquo;s decentralised P2P betting platform.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The developers will use the funds raised from the various funding rounds to build a P2P betting platform.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to their whitepaper, Chancer users will have access to a wide range of features, including, betting markets in real-time and based on user interests, social media connections, and expertise.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Furthermore, with Chancer, users will no longer have to deal with the problems associated with using bookmakers when betting as they would be allowed to set up their custom P2P betting markets.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">An important feature of&nbsp;<a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Chancer</u></a> is that users can bet on various activities. Users can bet on important sporting or political events or trivial ones like the first to complete a task amongst friends.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">CHANCER to go for $0.012 in the third presale stage</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer&rsquo;s second presale stage will be completed soon and the team will move to the next phase. In this current stage, the CHANCER token is going for $0.011 USDT</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, the team will increase the token price to $0.012 in the third presale round. Funds generated from the presale will be used to develop Chancer&rsquo;s suite of products. There would be 12 presale events, with an accumulated target of $15 million.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The CHANCER token will power numerous activities within the ecosystem. Token holders can create and invest in markets within the Chancer ecosystem. Furthermore, token holders can also create, participate in, and profit from their very own predictive markets.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The CHANCER token can be purchased using numerous wallets, including, Trust Wallet, MetaMask, Coinbase Wallet, and Rainbow.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Visit the&nbsp;<a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Chancer website</u></a> to get more information about the presale.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Should you invest in Chancer now?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The recent bearish trend in the market could see more investors troop into the market as they look for buying opportunities.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Investors could be looking to invest in projects in their early stages and Chancer could be one of the projects to consider due to its unique native.&nbsp;</p>
<p>By decentralising the betting ecosystem,&nbsp;<a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Chancer</u></a> could gain massive adoption within the Web3 space and beyond. The adoption of the Chancer platform could result in a rally by its native CHANCER token.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-dropped-below-26k-in-sudden-crash-will-traders-suffer-more-losses/">Bitcoin dropped below $26k in sudden crash: Will traders suffer more losses</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-dropped-below-26k-in-sudden-crash-will-traders-suffer-more-losses/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance to convert all New Bitshares (NBS) token balances to USDT before year ends</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-to-convert-all-new-bitshares-nbs-token-balances-to-usdt-before-year-ends/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-to-convert-all-new-bitshares-nbs-token-balances-to-usdt-before-year-ends/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 08:54:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-to-convert-all-new-bitshares-nbs-token-balances-to-usdt-before-year-ends/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Binance periodically reviews its listed tokens to ensure they continue to meet the high level of standard we expect. The New Bitshares (NBS) token was delisted by Binance in October last year. At press time, the NBS token was trading at $0.0002246, down 6.05% in the last 24 hours. Binance, the biggest cryptocurrency exchange in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-to-convert-all-new-bitshares-nbs-token-balances-to-usdt-before-year-ends/">Binance to convert all New Bitshares (NBS) token balances to USDT before year ends</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul class="decimal_type">
<li>Binance periodically reviews its listed tokens to ensure they continue to meet the high level of standard we expect.</li>
<li>The New Bitshares (NBS) token was delisted by Binance in October last year.</li>
<li>At press time, the NBS token was trading at $0.0002246, down 6.05% in the last 24 hours.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/binance/">Binance</a>, the biggest cryptocurrency exchange in the world, has indicated that it will convert all New Bitshares (NBS) token balances in users&rsquo; wallets to USDT by December 8, 2023. The conversion will be carried out using the average NBS/USDT exchange rate between September 9 and December 8, 2023, and will be based on users&rsquo; NBS holdings in their Binance wallets at the snapshot time of September 9, 2023.</p>
<p>New NBS token deposits will not be credited to users&rsquo; accounts and withdrawals will not be possible until September 9, 2023.</p>
<h2>Binance delisted tokens</h2>
<p>The announcement of converting the NBS tokens to USDT comes almost a year after the exchange delisted District0x (DNT), New Bitshares (NBS), Bitcoin Gold (BTG), and Token Club (TCT) on October 24, 2022.</p>
<p>In the previous announcement, Binance had stated that deposits of these tokens will not be credited to users&rsquo; accounts after October 2022-10-25 00:00 (UTC). Users were supposed to commence withdrawing the delisted tokens and the withdrawals were to continue to be supported until January 25, 2023, at 00:00 (UTC).</p>
<h2>What users should expect</h2>
<p>According to the announcement made by Binance, users who hold New Bitshares (NBS) tokens in any of their Binance wallets will receive an email notification by August 25, 2023. 23:59 (UTC). &nbsp;</p>
<p>The users will be able to continue withdrawing their New Bitshares (NBS) tokens from Binance until September 9, 2023, 00:00 (UTC), subject to network conditions and availability. After this date, users will not be able to withdraw or transfer their NBS token to any external wallets. &nbsp;</p>
<p>The users should expect to receive the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/tether/what-is-tether/">Tether (USDT)</a> equivalent of their remaining NBS tokens by December 0, 2023, which is the scheduled date when the conversion will be completed. During the conversion period which will run between September and December, users will not be able to see their New Bitshares (NBS) token balances in their Binance wallets.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-to-convert-all-new-bitshares-nbs-token-balances-to-usdt-before-year-ends/">Binance to convert all New Bitshares (NBS) token balances to USDT before year ends</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-to-convert-all-new-bitshares-nbs-token-balances-to-usdt-before-year-ends/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Memu presale hits $2.1M as Shiba Inu’s Shibarium faces challenges</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memu-presale-hits-2-1m-as-shiba-inus-shibarium-faces-challenges/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memu-presale-hits-2-1m-as-shiba-inus-shibarium-faces-challenges/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 08:06:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto adoption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memu-presale-hits-2-1m-as-shiba-inus-shibarium-faces-challenges/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The highly-anticipated Shibarium layer-2 network is having problems with its bridge contract. Approximately $1.7 million worth of Ethereum is currently stuck on the bridge contract. Shibarium launch was expected to add some impetus to the price of SHIB but that has not happened. The much-hyped layer-2 network of Shiba Inu, Shibarium, is having significant problems [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memu-presale-hits-2-1m-as-shiba-inus-shibarium-faces-challenges/">Shiba Memu presale hits $2.1M as Shiba Inu’s Shibarium faces challenges</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul class="decimal_type">
<li>The highly-anticipated Shibarium layer-2 network is having problems with its bridge contract.</li>
<li>Approximately $1.7 million worth of Ethereum is currently stuck on the bridge contract.</li>
<li>Shibarium launch was expected to add some impetus to the price of SHIB but that has not happened.</li>
</ul>
<p>The much-hyped layer-2 network of <a href="https://coinjournal.net/shiba-inu/what-is-shiba-inu/">Shiba Inu</a>, Shibarium, is having significant problems a day after its launch. The network was expected to turn the tables of the SHIB token, which has been under bearish pressure for the last seven days; but that has not been the case. The token has dropped by over 10% since the Shibarium went live.</p>
<p>But as the future of Shiba Inu hangs on tenterhooks, another Shiba-themed meme coin called Shiba Memu (SHMU) is taking the crypto space by storm with its <a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news">token presale</a> which has hit $2.1 million in a little over a month. Shiba Memu is leveraging the power of artificial intelligence (AI) and the hype around meme coins.</p>
<h2>What is happening with Shibarium?</h2>
<p>According to an analysis of the Shibarium network&rsquo;s bridge contract, which transfers money from Ethereum to the layer-2 solution, there is currently $1.7 million worth of <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/what-is-ethereum/">Ethereum</a> stranded between the two networks.</p>
<p>The locked status of the funds has been confirmed by the blockchain security team Beosin, who has advised people to stop using Shibarium temporarily.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">&#128680;Transactions on <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Shibarium?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Shibarium</a> are stuck in a pending state. <br>$1.7M are currently locked on ETH. </p>
<p>Users are advised to temporarily stop using shibarium.<a href="https://t.co/io5puAibBc">https://t.co/io5puAibBc</a> <a href="https://t.co/q2SXqtthoO">https://t.co/q2SXqtthoO</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Beosin Alert (@BeosinAlert) <a href="https://twitter.com/BeosinAlert/status/1692003409602445743?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 17, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>In addition to the locked-up tokens, blockchain sleuth ZachXBT highlighted that $762,000 worth of BONE, a Shibarium governance token, was sent to the bridge contract.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="fr" dir="ltr">$762k BONE</p>
<p>0x885fcE983b6a01633f764325B8c3c5D31032C995 <a href="https://t.co/DCQ7wWDIwq">pic.twitter.com/DCQ7wWDIwq</a></p>
<p>&mdash; ZachXBT (@zachxbt) <a href="https://twitter.com/zachxbt/status/1691962308522582195?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 16, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>According to the <a href="https://www.shibariumscan.io/">information on BlockScout</a>, only 236 transactions had been validated on Shibarium Network almost two days after the network was launched.</p>
<p>Some users have pointed out issues with Shibarium&rsquo;s remote procedure call (RPC) system, which allows access to a network&rsquo;s server node to communicate with the blockchain.</p>
<h2>The response by Shiba Inu&rsquo;s developer</h2>
<p>Interestingly, the pseudonymous Shiba Inu developer Shytoshi Kusama repudiated reports that what Shibarium was facing was &ldquo;a bridge issue.&rdquo; In a <a href="https://blog.shib.io/shibarium-insane-influx/?ref=shiba-inu-ecosystem-newsletter">newsletter</a>, Kusama said:</p>
<p><em>&ldquo;Our technical difficulties are due to the massive amount of traffic we experienced within moments on Shibarium,&rdquo; they said. &ldquo;The team is working tirelessly to fix the issue and scale so that we can give the ShibArmy the experience they deserve. All funds are safe.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p>A moderator in Shibarium&rsquo;s Discord also stated that &ldquo;as a precautionary measure,&rdquo; admins &ldquo;have temporarily restricted access to certain channels due to the spread of misinformation and fake websites.&rdquo;</p>
<h2>What Shibarium&rsquo;s misfortunes mean for Shiba Memu</h2>
<p>Well, Shiba Inu stands out as a major rival to Shiba Memu and its mishaps could only be translated to mean an advantage to the new Shiba Memu project, which is already on course to become the most popular meme coin project.</p>
<p>Shiba Memu is a revolutionary token combining AI and the latest technology to create an entirely self-sufficient marketing powerhouse, deviating from the norm of most meme coins which purely depend on community involvement.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memu-presale-hits-2-1m-as-shiba-inus-shibarium-faces-challenges/">Shiba Memu presale hits $2.1M as Shiba Inu’s Shibarium faces challenges</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memu-presale-hits-2-1m-as-shiba-inus-shibarium-faces-challenges/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
