<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 18:48:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Just in: US court summons Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/just-in-us-court-summons-binance-ceo-changpeng-zhao/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 18:48:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Policy and Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/just-in-us-court-summons-binance-ceo-changpeng-zhao/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A US court has issued summons for Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao. He has 21 days to respond although he doesn&#8217;t have to appear in person. According to the court document, Zhao&#8217;s address has been given as Malta. The US District Court in Washington, D.C. has issued a summons for Changpeng Zhao, the CEO of Binance. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/just-in-us-court-summons-binance-ceo-changpeng-zhao/">Just in: US court summons Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">A US court has issued summons for Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao.</li>
<li dir="ltr">He has 21 days to respond although he doesn&rsquo;t have to appear in person.</li>
<li dir="ltr">According to the court document, Zhao&rsquo;s address has been given as Malta.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">The US District Court in Washington, D.C. has issued a summons for Changpeng Zhao, the CEO of <a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/binance/">Binance</a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Summons for CZ were issued on Wednesday, June 7, and came just two days after the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) sued the Binance CEO and his crypto exchange for alleged securities violations.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to <a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.dcd.256060/gov.uscourts.dcd.256060.1.5.pdf" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">court documents</a>, CZ&rsquo;s address is identified as Sliema, Malta. While the Binance boss isn&rsquo;t obligated to appear in person, he is required to respond to the summons within 21 days.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>If you fail to respond, judgment by default will be entered against you for the relief demanded in the complaint</em>,&rdquo; the summons reads in part.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Mr. Zhao has not commented on the news development as of writing. As this is a developing story, we will update it.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/just-in-us-court-summons-binance-ceo-changpeng-zhao/">Just in: US court summons Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>USDC issuer Circle receives a digital token licence in Singapore</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/usdc-issuer-circle-receives-a-digital-token-licence-in-singapore/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/usdc-issuer-circle-receives-a-digital-token-licence-in-singapore/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 18:42:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Policy and Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Singapore]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/usdc-issuer-circle-receives-a-digital-token-licence-in-singapore/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways Circle has received its Major Payment Institution (MPI) license for digital payment token services in Singapore. The company was first issued an in-principle approval in November 2022.&#160; Circle receives a digital token licence in Singapore Circle, the company that issues the USDC stablecoin,&#160;announced on Wednesday, June 7th, that it has received its Major [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/usdc-issuer-circle-receives-a-digital-token-licence-in-singapore/">USDC issuer Circle receives a digital token licence in Singapore</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Circle has received its Major Payment Institution (MPI) license for digital payment token services in Singapore.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The company was first issued an in-principle approval in November 2022.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr">Circle receives a digital token licence in Singapore</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Circle, the company that issues the USDC stablecoin,&nbsp;<a href="https://www.circle.com/en/pressroom/circle-singapore-obtained-major-payment-institution-license" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>announced</u></a> on Wednesday, June 7th, that it has received its Major Payment Institution (MPI) license for digital payment token services in Singapore.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>latest cryptocurrency news</u></a> comes after the company obtained in-principle approval last November.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to the company, the license issued by the Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS) allows it to offer digital payment token services, cross-border money transfer services and domestic money transfer services in Singapore.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">While commenting on this latest development, Jeremy Allaire, the CEO of Circle, said;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;Singapore is integral to Circle&rsquo;s global expansion and mission in raising global economic prosperity and through the frictionless exchange of value. We are honored to receive the MPI license from MAS, and we remain committed to being a part of Singapore&rsquo;s dynamic economy by advancing the future of financial technology innovations in the city-state, uplifting its emerging technology and fintech sector, and creating business and career opportunities for its technology and financial industry talent.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p dir="ltr">Circle Singapore is an affiliate of Circle Internet Financial, the company that issues the USDC stablecoin.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Circle falls behind Tether&rsquo;s USDT</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Circle has seen its USDC stablecoin take a hit this year due to the banking crisis in the United States. As the second-largest stablecoin by market cap, USDC has fallen behind Tether&rsquo;s USDT in recent months.</p>
<p dir="ltr">At the moment, Tether&rsquo;s USDT stablecoin has a market cap of $80.2 billion, more than twice that of USDC ($32.75 billion).&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Singapore&rsquo;s MAS proposed stablecoin regulation last year, which introduced capital and reserve requirements for issuers. The regulatory agency also seeks to ban users from some crypto-related activities like staking and lending.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/usdc-issuer-circle-receives-a-digital-token-licence-in-singapore/">USDC issuer Circle receives a digital token licence in Singapore</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/usdc-issuer-circle-receives-a-digital-token-licence-in-singapore/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>US SEC sues Binance and Coinbase, but Bitcoin remains above $26k</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/us-sec-sues-binance-and-coinbase-but-bitcoin-remains-above-26k/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/us-sec-sues-binance-and-coinbase-but-bitcoin-remains-above-26k/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 17:36:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/us-sec-sues-binance-and-coinbase-but-bitcoin-remains-above-26k/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways Bitcoin maintains its value above $26k despite the FUD surrounding Binance and Coinbase. The resilience of the market could prove beneficial to new projects like AltSignals.&#160; The cryptocurrency market looks promising at the moment despite the events of the last two days. In the first two days of the week, the US Securities [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/us-sec-sues-binance-and-coinbase-but-bitcoin-remains-above-26k/">US SEC sues Binance and Coinbase, but Bitcoin remains above $26k</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin maintains its value above $26k despite the FUD surrounding Binance and Coinbase.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The resilience of the market could prove beneficial to new projects like AltSignals.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">The cryptocurrency market looks promising at the moment despite the events of the last two days.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In the first two days of the week, the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) sued both Binance and Coinbase, two of the largest cryptocurrency exchanges in the world.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Despite the lawsuits, Bitcoin maintains its value above $26k, and this could indicate resilience amongst investors. Bitcoin maintaining its position above the $25k psychological level could serve as a boost for new projects coming into the industry, including AltSignals.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bulls provide strong support for Bitcoin</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Earlier this week, the US SEC filed lawsuits against Binance and Coinbase, the two leading cryptocurrency exchanges in the world.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The SEC&rsquo;s&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sec-sues-binance-and-cz-for-breaking-us-securities-rules/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>lawsuit against Binance</u></a> alleges that the cryptocurrency exchange and its CEO, Changpeng Zhao, violated US securities laws by offering services to high-valued US customers on its platform.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This was followed by&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-sec-strikes-again-first-binance-now-coinbase/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>another one against Coinbase</u></a>, with the SEC claiming that the crypto exchange is operating as an unregistered broker.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Despite the lawsuits against two of the biggest crypto exchanges in the world, Bitcoin&rsquo;s price remained above $25k. Bitcoin briefly rallied past the $27k on Tuesday and is now trading just above the $26K once again.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The resilience shown by investors could indicate confidence in the cryptocurrency market, and this could benefit new projects like AltSignals.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals is close to concluding its presale stage, and its token will be listed on numerous cryptocurrency exchanges afterward.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">AltSignals&rsquo; presale to conclude soon</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The presale stage of AltSignals is close to an end, and the development team has already started working on releasing their suite of products.</p>
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals is a unique project that leverages AI to make it easier for people to trade Bitcoin and a host of other cryptocurrencies.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The development team is working on a suite of AI products designed for cryptocurrency traders. The team has so far raised over $900,000 (86.9% of the required funds) and will conclude the presale of its token soon.</p>
<p dir="ltr">ASI, the native token of the&nbsp;<a href="https://token.altsignals.io/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=invezz&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>AltSignals</u></a> ecosystem, is trading at $0.015 per token, making it affordable for investors. Following the end of the presale and its launch on crypto exchanges, ASI could experience a price surge in the short to medium term.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Click here to read more about the&nbsp;<a href="https://token.altsignals.io/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=invezz&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>AltSignals presale</u></a>.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is AltSignals?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals is one of the projects designed to benefit cryptocurrency traders in the cryptocurrency space. In addition to crypto traders, forex, stock, commodities, and indices traders could also take advantage of this solution for their trading activities.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The platform allows cryptocurrency traders to gain access to trading signals. Forex, stocks, and commodities traders can also gain access to trading signals using this solution.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The funds raised from the presale will be used to develop ActualizeAI, an AI solution that could make it easier for people to trade cryptos and other financial assets.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">ActualizeAI will be an automated solution that works 24/7. The solution will make it easier to identify trading patterns and entry and exit points in the market. Hence, ensuring that traders could trade more accurately.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">By holding the ASI token, you will have access to AltSignals&rsquo; services. The solution is set to leverage natural language processing, machine learning, regression, and predictive modeling to boost its services.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The team is working on listing ASI on numerous exchanges, including Uniswap. They are also working to expand the team, secure OTC partnerships and launch the sentiment analysis engine.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">AltSignals (ASI) price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr">ASI is yet to list on any crypto exchange, which makes it harder to predict its price movement in the meantime. However, the token is going for $0.015 in the ongoing presale.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, listing on cryptocurrency exchanges usually influence the prices of cryptocurrencies positively, and ASI&rsquo;s value could increase once it lists on a few exchanges.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The crypto market has been able to hold its ground despite the FUD surrounding Binance and Coinbase at the moment.</p>
<p dir="ltr">If the fundamentals of the broader market improve in the near term, this could benefit tokens like ASI that could list on cryptocurrency exchanges soon.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Despite the negativity surrounding the industry, BTC and ETH have both added more than 40% to their values year-to-date.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals is set to enter a multi-billion dollar market, and its services could prove beneficial to traders. If AltSignals hit the right level of adoption, ASI could become a big winner n the cryptocurrency market.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Should I buy AltSignals in its presale?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Historically, investing in projects during their presale or ICO generates the best return on investment (ROI) for investors. Early investors in projects like Ethereum, Dogecoin, Solana, and Shiba Inu made thousands of percentages in ROI.&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://token.altsignals.io/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=invezz&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>AltSignals</u></a> is a project that holds a lot of promise for traders within the cryptocurrency space and beyond. With the right level of adoption, ASI could become a big winner in the cryptocurrency market.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/us-sec-sues-binance-and-coinbase-but-bitcoin-remains-above-26k/">US SEC sues Binance and Coinbase, but Bitcoin remains above $26k</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/us-sec-sues-binance-and-coinbase-but-bitcoin-remains-above-26k/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance.US to delist 40 trading pairs, pauses OTC trading</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-us-to-delist-40-trading-pairs-pauses-otc-trading/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-us-to-delist-40-trading-pairs-pauses-otc-trading/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 16:53:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto regulation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-us-to-delist-40-trading-pairs-pauses-otc-trading/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Binance.US is delisting advanced trading pairs for coins such as AAVE, BCH and MKR on June 8. The 40 coins being delisted are for advanced trading pairs of USDT, BTC and BUSD. Binance.US has also paused its OTC trading, but says withdrawals and deposits remain open. Binance.US, the US-based subsidiary of the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-us-to-delist-40-trading-pairs-pauses-otc-trading/">Binance.US to delist 40 trading pairs, pauses OTC trading</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Binance.US is delisting advanced trading pairs for coins such as AAVE, BCH and MKR on June 8.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The 40 coins being delisted are for advanced trading pairs of USDT, BTC and BUSD.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Binance.US has also paused its OTC trading, but says withdrawals and deposits remain open.</li>
</ul>
<p>Binance.US, the US-based subsidiary of the world&rsquo;s largest cryptocurrency exchange Binance, has announced it will delist 40 trading pairs.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The exchange also revealed it had paused OTC trading, with the news coming a day after the SEC sought to <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-sec-is-seeking-court-order-to-freeze-binance-uss-assets/">freeze</a> the company&rsquo;s assets following a lawsuit against Binance and its CEO Changpeng Zhao.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>After careful consideration, Binance.US will remove select Advanced Trading pairs on June 8, 2023 at 9 a.m. PDT / 12 p.m. EDT</em>,&rdquo; the exchange wrote in a notice to users.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>We have also decided to streamline our Buy, Sell &amp; Convert offering and have paused our OTC Trading Portal. Your assets remain safe and secure with Binance.US, and deposits and withdrawals continue to function as normal</em>.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to the notice <a href="https://support.binance.us/hc/en-us/articles/15133607064983-Binance-US-Will-Remove-Select-Trading-Pairs-Has-Paused-OTC-Trading" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">published</a> Wednesday June 7, 2023, the advanced trading pairs Binance.US plans to delist are for 40 altcoin pairs of USDT, BTC, and BUSD.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The majority of the pairs, 30, are for USDT and include 1INCH/USDT, AAVE/USDT, BCH/USDT, CHZ/USDT, COTI/USDT, MANA/USDT, MKR/USDT, and ZEC/USDT.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The platform will also delist eight BTC pairs and two BUSD pairs, with the former including ATOM/BTC, BCH/BTC, DOT/BTC, LRC/BTC, MANA/BTC, UNI/BTC, VET/BTC, and XTZ/BTC. The BUSD stablecoin pairs to be removed are HBAR/BUSD and ONE/BUSD.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-us-to-delist-40-trading-pairs-pauses-otc-trading/">Binance.US to delist 40 trading pairs, pauses OTC trading</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-us-to-delist-40-trading-pairs-pauses-otc-trading/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cathie Wood boosts stake in Coinbase stock despite SEC lawsuit</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/cathie-wood-buy-coinbase-stock-sec-lawsuit/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wajeeh Khan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 15:28:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=142263</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The U.S. SEC sued Coinbase Global for violating securities laws this week. Wood bought $21 million worth of Coinbase stock on consequent sell-off. Coinbase stock is currently up nearly 60% versus the start of the year. Cathie Wood remains bullish as ever on Coinbase Global Inc even though it has again come in the crosshairs [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/cathie-wood-buy-coinbase-stock-sec-lawsuit/">Cathie Wood boosts stake in Coinbase stock despite SEC lawsuit</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>The U.S. SEC sued Coinbase Global for violating securities laws this week.</li>
<li>Wood bought $21 million worth of Coinbase stock on consequent sell-off.</li>
<li>Coinbase stock is currently up nearly 60% versus the start of the year.</li>
</ul>
<p>Cathie Wood remains bullish as ever on <a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/coinbase/">Coinbase Global Inc</a> even though it has again come in the crosshairs of the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission.</p>
<h2>Wood spends $21 million on Coinbase stock</h2>
<p>On Tuesday, the SEC <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-sec-strikes-again-first-binance-now-coinbase/">sued</a> Coinbase for violating securities laws that resulted in an over 10% hit to its stock price &ndash; a sell-off that Wood saw as an opportunity to load up on 419,324 shares of the crypto exchange.</p>
<p>The Founder and CEO of Ark Invest spent about $21 million in total on the said purchase that was spit between three of her exchange-traded funds &ndash; Ark Innovation, Ark Next Generation Internet, and Ark Fintech Innovation.</p>
<p>It is noteworthy here that Wood expects Bitcoin to hit $1.3 million by the end of this decade. To that end, she&rsquo;s been adding to her position in Coinbase stock this year. It is now her sixth biggest holding.</p>
<h2>Coinbase Global&rsquo;s response to the SEC</h2>
<p>The lawsuit against Coinbase doesn&rsquo;t come as much of a surprise considering it was served a &ldquo;Wells Notice&rdquo; earlier this year. <a href="https://twitter.com/brian_armstrong/status/1666129111025324035?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Responding</a> to the SEC complaint, the crypto company said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Remember, SEC reviewed our business and allowed us to become a public company in 2021 and there&rsquo;s no path to come in and register &ndash; we tried, repeatedly, so we don&rsquo;t list securities.</p></blockquote>
<p>Who also remains bullish on Coinbase stock despite the SEC&rsquo;s aggressive move is HCW analyst Mike Colonnese.</p>
<p>He maintained his &ldquo;buy&rdquo; rating on the crypto exchange this morning and said its shares could climb all the way up to $77 &ndash; a rather lucrative 45% return from here.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/cathie-wood-buy-coinbase-stock-sec-lawsuit/">Cathie Wood boosts stake in Coinbase stock despite SEC lawsuit</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sweat Economy to decide the fate of 2B idle SWEAT tokens via Governance Vote</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/sweat-economy-to-decide-the-fate-of-2b-idle-sweat-tokens-via-governance-vote/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/sweat-economy-to-decide-the-fate-of-2b-idle-sweat-tokens-via-governance-vote/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 13:51:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/sweat-economy-to-decide-the-fate-of-2b-idle-sweat-tokens-via-governance-vote/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>There are 2 billion idle SWEAT tokens in inactive user accounts. These idle tokens constitute approximately 13% of the SWEAT token total supply. Sweat Economy has launched a new Governance Vote to decide the fate of these idle tokens. Pioneering move-to-earn project Sweat Economy is today launching a new governance vote in the Sweat Wallet [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sweat-economy-to-decide-the-fate-of-2b-idle-sweat-tokens-via-governance-vote/">Sweat Economy to decide the fate of 2B idle SWEAT tokens via Governance Vote</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>There are 2 billion idle SWEAT tokens in inactive user accounts.</li>
<li>These idle tokens constitute approximately 13% of the SWEAT token total supply.</li>
<li>Sweat Economy has launched a new Governance Vote to decide the fate of these idle tokens.</li>
</ul>
<p>Pioneering move-to-earn project Sweat Economy is today launching a new governance vote in the Sweat Wallet application, which is <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sweat-economys-sweat-token-and-web3-wallet-app-set-to-launch-in-the-us-this-year/">set to launch in the US this year</a>. The vote to allow the community to decide the fate of 2 billion idle SWEAT tokens in inactive user accounts.</p>
<p>The idle tokens were locked up in a 24-month contract in the inactive user accounts. However, it is not clear what should happen to the tokens once the lock-up time ends.</p>
<p>The tokens were left unclaimed after the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sweat-economy-launches-with-the-largest-ever-airdrop-to-active-opted-in-wallets/">Token Generation Event (TGE) that took place last September</a>. A number of Sweat Economy users did not activate their Sweat Wallet application to claim the tokens.</p>
<h2>The new Sweat Economy governance vote</h2>
<p>The new governance vote will give SWEAT token holders an opportunity of participating in answering the lingering question of what should be done with these idle tokens.</p>
<p>Users will be deciding on whether to have the 2 billion idle SWEAT tokens recovered and transferred back to the Sweat Treasury for potential future distribution or other uses as decided in future votes or to leave these tokens in the inactive user accounts.</p>
<p>75,000 votes will have to be cast for the proposal to be accepted or denied. The voting process which begins today will run for seven days to give everyone a fair opportunity to participate. There is also a possibility of the vote being extended if there will be an n influx of voters.</p>
<p>There were 153,783 participants in the most recent voting process which makes Sweat Economy believe it could see even higher engagement given the number of tokens at stake.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sweat-economy-to-decide-the-fate-of-2b-idle-sweat-tokens-via-governance-vote/">Sweat Economy to decide the fate of 2B idle SWEAT tokens via Governance Vote</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/sweat-economy-to-decide-the-fate-of-2b-idle-sweat-tokens-via-governance-vote/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>3 reasons why Bitcoin price remains resilient</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/3-reasons-why-bitcoin-price-remains-resilient/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/3-reasons-why-bitcoin-price-remains-resilient/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mircea Vasiu]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 12:12:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/3-reasons-why-bitcoin-price-remains-resilient/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Binance and Coinbase are sued by the SEC Bitcoin price remains resilient Scarcity, inflation rate halving, and an increase in the number of users help Bitcoin Once again, cryptocurrency investors are tested. In a span of 24h, several things challenged the market again. First, Binance, one of the largest crypto exchanges in the world, was [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/3-reasons-why-bitcoin-price-remains-resilient/">3 reasons why Bitcoin price remains resilient</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Binance and Coinbase are sued by the SEC</li>
<li>Bitcoin price remains resilient</li>
<li>Scarcity, inflation rate halving, and an increase in the number of users help Bitcoin</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p>Once again, cryptocurrency investors are tested. In a span of 24h, several things challenged the market again.</p>
<p>First, Binance, one of the largest crypto exchanges in the world, was sued by the Securities and Exchange Commission with thirteen charges. Second, Coinbase was sued by the same authority for operating as an unlicensed broker in the US.</p>
<p>Moreover, the SEC filed court documents to freeze Binance&rsquo;s US assets. Given how strategically important these two players are for the industry, how come Bitcoin price remains resilient? Here are three reasons that might explain such resilience:</p>
<ul>
<li>Scarcity</li>
<li>Increased number of holders</li>
<li>Halving inflation rate</li>
</ul>
<h2>Scarcity</h2>
<p>The upper limit of supply is mathematically fixed at 21 million. This scarcity makes Bitcoin attractive in the eyes of many investors, as it resembles a digital store of value.</p>
<h2>The number of users/holders increases</h2>
<p>More and more people use or hold Bitcoin. Throughout the years, the number of users and holders increased considerably despite the industry being challenged constantly by fraudsters or, in this case, lawsuits.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/05/07/1686139913980-fa71acf8-f58d-408b-bce4-6de605c1cc24.jpg" style="width: 1800px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="1800" height="489"></p>
<h2>Inflation rate halving</h2>
<p>By April 2024, Bitcoin&rsquo;s inflation rate halves again. It means that it will be lower than that of gold, which makes it an attractive asset to those looking for a hedge against inflation in times when inflation reached alarming levels, even in the developed world.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/3-reasons-why-bitcoin-price-remains-resilient/">3 reasons why Bitcoin price remains resilient</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/3-reasons-why-bitcoin-price-remains-resilient/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stacks price outlook: What next for STX after going vertical?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/stacks-price-outlook-what-next-for-stx-after-going-vertical/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/stacks-price-outlook-what-next-for-stx-after-going-vertical/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 12:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/stacks-price-outlook-what-next-for-stx-after-going-vertical/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Stacks crypto price jumped to the upper side of the descending channel. The coin jumped because of its close relationship with Bitcoin. This rebound could be part of a dead cat bounce. Stacks price has staged a strong comeback in the past two days even as concerns about regulations in the US continued. STX has [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/stacks-price-outlook-what-next-for-stx-after-going-vertical/">Stacks price outlook: What next for STX after going vertical?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Stacks crypto price jumped to the upper side of the descending channel.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The coin jumped because of its close relationship with Bitcoin.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">This rebound could be part of a dead cat bounce.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/stacks/"><u>Stacks</u></a> price has staged a strong comeback in the past two days even as concerns about regulations in the US continued. STX has jumped by more than 15% in the past 24 hours. In all, it has jumped by over 22% from the lowest level on Tuesday.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">A possible reason for the rally</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Stacks is a unique blockchain that creates a layer where developers can create applications for the&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/"><u>Bitcoin</u></a> ecosystem. According to its website, the network has over $901 million locked in its staking ecosystem. In the past few months, the network has distributed over 2000 BTCs to stakers.</p>
<p dir="ltr">It is unclear why Stacks price has jumped sharply in the past 24 hours. A likely reason is that this rally in sync with that of other coins. Bitcoin has risen by over 3% in the past 24 hours while other altcoins like Terra Classic and Pepe have jumped by double digits in the same period.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The other reason is that Bitcoin&rsquo;s ecosystem is growing, helped by Ordinals, the popular NFT platform. Data by TokenTerminal shows that Bitcoin fee revenue in the past 30 days came in at over $102.7 million, making it the second most profitable network in the industry.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Additional data by CryptoSlam shows that the total Ordinals sales jumped to a record high in May. Sales&nbsp;<a href="https://www.cryptoslam.io/blockchains/bitcoin"><u>soared</u></a> to over $195 million in May from the previous $33.2 million.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">While Stacks has no association with Ordinals, its success means that more developers could move to its ecosystem soon.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Further, STX price rose because Bitcoin seems safe in the ongoing war on exchanges like Coinbase and Binance. The agency highlighted some of the tokens that it sees as being securities. Bitcoin was not one of them.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Stacks price prediction</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/05/07/1686139176497-db4107d4-11cb-4abb-aba3-343383bc4d22.png" style="width: 662px;height: 322.33px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="662" height="322.33"></p>
<p dir="ltr">The other reason why STX price has jumped is that this could be a dead cat bounce, which happens after an asset dips sharply. On the daily chart, we see that the coin retested the upper side of the descending channel shown in orange. Most importantly, Stacks&rsquo; 50-day and 100-day moving averages have made a bearish crossover.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, I believe that the coin has more downside to go unless it moves above the two moving averages. If this happens, the next level to watch will be at $0.5200, the lower side of the channel.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy Stacks</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    Swapzone</h3>


<p>
    <a href="/visit/swapzone-crypto?guid=MTQyMjUw&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy STX with Swapzone today            </a>
    </p><h3>
    Bitvavo</h3>


<p>
    <a href="/visit/bitvavo-crypto?guid=MTQyMjUw&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy STX with Bitvavo today            </a>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/stacks-price-outlook-what-next-for-stx-after-going-vertical/">Stacks price outlook: What next for STX after going vertical?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/stacks-price-outlook-what-next-for-stx-after-going-vertical/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Blockchain Pioneer Acquires International Fashion House Blk DNM</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/blockchain-pioneer-acquires-international-fashion-house-blk-dnm/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/blockchain-pioneer-acquires-international-fashion-house-blk-dnm/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire &#160;]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 10:19:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=142243</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Stockholm, Sweden, June 7th, 2023, Chainwire ChromaWay to Integrate Blockchain Capabilities into BLK DNM, Pioneering Connected Fashion, and Inspiring Responsible Industry Behaviors Stockholm&#8217;s headquartered blockchain technology company ChromaWay today reveals its acquisition of the iconic Swedish-American fashion brand BLK DNM. The acquisition aligned with the recent relaunch of BLK DNM as a modern, community-driven fashion [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/blockchain-pioneer-acquires-international-fashion-house-blk-dnm/">Blockchain Pioneer Acquires International Fashion House Blk DNM</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Stockholm, Sweden, June 7th, 2023, Chainwire</strong></p>
<p>ChromaWay to Integrate Blockchain Capabilities into BLK DNM, Pioneering Connected Fashion, and Inspiring Responsible Industry Behaviors</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Stockholm&rsquo;s headquartered blockchain technology company <a href="https://chromaway.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">ChromaWay</a> today reveals its acquisition of the iconic Swedish-American fashion brand <a href="https://www.blkdnm.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">BLK DNM</a>.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">The acquisition aligned with the recent relaunch of BLK DNM as a modern, community-driven fashion house. It marks ChromaWay&rsquo;s first acquisition of an established company for the purpose of implementing real-world decentralization: i.e., creating positive behavioral change, fairer access, and more control by users within traditional industries.</p>
<ul>
<li>ChromaWay&rsquo;s blockchain capabilities will be integrated into BLK DNM&rsquo;s strategy and products, the first meaningful use of the tech in fashion.</li>
<li>In pioneering &lsquo;connected fashion,&rsquo; BLK DNM will seek to inspire more responsible behaviors in the industry.</li>
<li>First tech innovations will be announced ahead of BLK DNM&rsquo;s F/W 2023 collections reveal</li>
</ul>
<h2 class="ql-align-justify"><strong>First innovations to be revealed in BLK DNM&rsquo;s F/W 2023:</strong></h2>
<p class="ql-align-justify">ChromaWay&rsquo;s blockchain capabilities will be integrated in a revolutionary way into both BLK DNM&rsquo;s brand and products. BLK DNM will consequently become a pioneer of &lsquo;connected fashion&rsquo; &ndash; the use of technology to create community and responsibility within fashion &ndash; heralding the first significant use of blockchain tech in an industry yet to be meaningfully impacted by Web3 technologies.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">BLK DNM will reveal the first tranche of technological innovations built on ChromaWay&rsquo;s &lsquo;Chromia&rsquo; relational blockchain in the coming weeks. This will include software- and hardware-based innovations built into BLK DNM&rsquo;s F/W 2023 collections, underpinned by the ethical and communal concept of &lsquo;connected fashion.&rsquo;</p>
<p><img decoding="async" src="https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/photo_6053229922782131354_y_1686067167P1LHN4tXIL.jpg">Toni Collin, CEO of BLK DNM, and Henrik Hjelte, CEO and Co-founder of ChromaWay</p>
<blockquote><p>Henrik Hjelte, CEO and Co-founder of ChromaWay, comments: &ldquo;BLK DNM is a brand with an ethical mission and decentralization in its soul &ndash; it&rsquo;s something of a borderless community already. It was a natural fit for our aspirations to transform the fashion industry through innovation. BLK DNM&rsquo;s imminent tech rollout will illustrate the power of our blockchain capabilities to create true behavioral change in an industry that has hitherto struggled to control its problematic environmental impact and embrace progress.&rdquo;</p></blockquote>
<blockquote><p>Toni Collin, CEO of BLK DNM, comments: &ldquo;Our industry must start looking toward innovation: fast fashion&rsquo;s environmental impact is totally unacceptable, and at the same time, as the world becomes more digitized, the concept of community is changing. That&rsquo;s why BLK DNM joining ChromaWay is so exciting. The potential of this technology to create genuine change in fashion is evident, but no one else in the industry is using it in a meaningful way yet. Together, BLK DNM and ChromaWay are building something truly unique and groundbreaking. We will be able to reveal the first innovations very soon.&rdquo;</p></blockquote>
<h3><strong>About ChromaWay</strong></h3>
<p class="ql-align-justify">ChromaWay is an industry leader in blockchain technology and specializes in creating and deploying cutting-edge, scalable blockchain solutions for businesses and governments. The company, established in 2014 and headquartered in Stockholm, Sweden, has been at the forefront of driving the widespread adoption of blockchain technology. Its flagship product, relational blockchain Chromia, enables developers to build decentralized applications (dApps) with a relational database model that offers unprecedented scalability and flexibility.</p>
<h3><strong>About BLK DNM</strong></h3>
<p class="ql-align-justify">BLK DNM is a Swedish-American fashion brand that specialises in timeless tailoring, leather, and denim of extraordinary quality. Following its 2023 relaunch as an entry-luxury fashion house under the stewardship of new Creative Director Jessy Heuvelink, BLK DNM&rsquo;s focus on enduring craftsmanship and aesthetic timelessness encourages customers to love and treasure each item for decades and across generations.</p>
<h3>Contact</h3>
<p>Fati Hakim, Fati.Hakim@ChromaWay.com</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/blockchain-pioneer-acquires-international-fashion-house-blk-dnm/">Blockchain Pioneer Acquires International Fashion House Blk DNM</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/blockchain-pioneer-acquires-international-fashion-house-blk-dnm/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
