<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 12:44:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Apple Bans Use of ChatGPT by Staff, Fearing Data Leaks</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-bans-chatgpt-data-leaks/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-bans-chatgpt-data-leaks/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[staff writer]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 12:44:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ai]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chatgpt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ibm]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[microsoft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[samsung]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=255686</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-bans-chatgpt-data-leaks/">Apple Bans Use of ChatGPT by Staff, Fearing Data Leaks</a></p>
<p>With increasing concern over data leaks, AI tool makers are working to assure concerned users that their data is safe.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-bans-chatgpt-data-leaks/">Apple Bans Use of ChatGPT by Staff, Fearing Data Leaks</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-bans-chatgpt-data-leaks/">Apple Bans Use of ChatGPT by Staff, Fearing Data Leaks</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/apple-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Apple</a> has <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/apple-restricts-use-of-chatgpt-joining-other-companies-wary-of-leaks-d44d7d34" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">banned</a> the use of the AI tool ChatGPT among its employees in a bid to prevent data breaches and leaks. This was reported by the Wall Street Journal, which cited an internal memo from the company.</p>
<h2>Apple and Other Companies Are Concerned about Data Safety</h2>
<p>The restriction makes Apple one of several businesses that are limiting the use of the software by some of its workers. The release said that the reason for this is that the iPhone maker believes that workers may inadvertently upload confidential files to the AI platform. The report said that the restriction introduced by Apple is not limited to ChatGPT but to any other AI platform that could result in any form of data leakage. Some of these are from the coding platform GitHub, which owns a tool called Copilot, and another one from Microsoft.</p>
<p>Since the news broke, Apple has yet to make a public statement in response to inquiries. However, AI analysts are of the opinion that the move to restrict the use of AI platforms by workers stems from the fact that platforms such as ChatGPT warn against the upload of sensitive data by users. Such warnings make sense as all data sent to its database is used to condition their AI models to improve them.</p>
<h2>Samsung Placed Temporary Ban on ChatGPT</h2>
<p>Raising privacy concerns over data, several companies, such as <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/jpmorgan-chase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">JPMorgan</a>, Bank of America, and Amazon, moved against the use of ChatGPT in January. Another entity that may be considering banning the use of the AI tool is Samsung. Last month, its engineer uploaded sensitive data in a bid to rectify a faulty database. In the meantime, the management of Samsung has placed a temporary restriction on the use of ChatGPT. The tech giant has already begun the development of its own in-house AI platform.</p>
<p>Apart from businesses, governments are also concerned about the threat of data leaks. The Italian government briefly banned the use of ChatGPT, raising issues with the safety of personal data on the platform. It has since changed its position by allowing the company behind ChatGPT, OpenAI, to continue operating in the country after demands by the Italian government were met.</p>
<h2>Private Versions of AI Tools</h2>
<p>With increasing concern over data leaks, AI tool makers are working to assure concerned users that their data is safe. ChatGPT recently released a private version of its tool called incognito mode. This version, according to OpenAI, ensures that uploaded data is not kept permanently in their database. Neither would the prompts be saved longer than necessary for checks to prevent abuse.</p>
<p>Microsoft also announced its work on a private version of its software targeted at companies. The AI version will not use company data in training, the company has assured.</p>
<p>IBM is also working on its private AI tool, as the company announced this month. Watsonx&#8217;s privacy-centered AI would ensure that users have no worries about data leaks.</p>
<p>&#8220;Clients can quickly train and deploy custom AI capabilities across their entire business, all while retaining full control of their data,&#8221; <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ibm/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">IBM</a> CEO Arvind Krishna<a href="https://fortune.com/2023/05/09/ibm-watsonx-ai-productivity-data-privacy/" target="_blank"> said</a>.</p>
<p>However, these private versions are expected to be pricey.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hashkey-funds-1b-valuation/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-bans-chatgpt-data-leaks/">Apple Bans Use of ChatGPT by Staff, Fearing Data Leaks</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-bans-chatgpt-data-leaks/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>HashKey Group to Raise Funds at $1B Valuation</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/hashkey-funds-1b-valuation/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/hashkey-funds-1b-valuation/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 11:53:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investors News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[HashKey]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hashkey group]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=255667</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hashkey-funds-1b-valuation/">HashKey Group to Raise Funds at $1B Valuation</a></p>
<p>HashKey Capital emphasized that it plans to direct the investment into Web3 initiatives in order to broaden its crypto exposure.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hashkey-funds-1b-valuation/">HashKey Group to Raise Funds at $1B Valuation</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hashkey-funds-1b-valuation/">HashKey Group to Raise Funds at $1B Valuation</a></p>
<p>Crypto investment company HashKey Group is looking towards leveraging Hong Kong’s digital assets efforts to <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crypto-firm-seeks-funds-1-031450789.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">raise funds</a> at a valuation of over $1 billion to attract potential investors.</p>
<p>The Chinese Special Administrative Region is finalizing digital asset licensing legislation with the goal of becoming a worldwide crypto hub. Hong Kong has been making efforts to promote and regulate the digital asset industry, which could create a favorable environment for firms like HashKey Group.</p>
<p>HashKey is in early talks to raise between $100 million and $200 million, people familiar with the matter said. It is important to note that these details are based on insider information, and the terms of the deal, including the size and valuation, are subject to change as the negotiations progress and are not yet finalized.</p>
<p>Raising funds at a valuation above $1 billion suggests that HashKey Group has achieved significant growth and success in its operations. It also indicates investor confidence in the potential of the crypto industry despite the strains of the past year. It will be interesting to see how HashKey will use the raised funds to contribute to the development of Hong Kong&#8217;s digital asset ecosystem.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, HashKey Capital, the investment arm of HashKey Group, recently <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hashkey-capital-fund-500m-web3/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">announced</a> the closure of its third fund, HashKey FinTech Investment Fund III, which raised a total of $500 million. Notably, Fund III received significant support from institutional investors such as sovereign wealth funds, businesses, and family offices.</p>
<p>HashKey Capital emphasized that it plans to direct the investment into Web3 initiatives in order to broaden its crypto exposure. Additionally, the investment firm <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hashkey-wealth-management-platform/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">expanded</a> its business in April by adding wealth management services to its offering directory.</p>
<h2>HashKey Valuation and the Link with Hong Kong’s Crypto Push</h2>
<p>The push to support crypto is steadily gaining traction in Hong Kong. The Chinese government views Hong Kong as a testing ground for longer-term policy, even while banning most forms of crypto-activity on the mainland.</p>
<p>While regulators globally have been navigating the challenges of overseeing the crypto market following the market crash in the past year and notable incidents like the bankruptcy of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a>, Hong Kong appears to be taking a more open stance by introducing a licensing framework and expanding access for retail investors.</p>
<p>The news of Hong Kong <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hong-kong-consultation-paper-crypto/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">introducing</a> a new licensing regime for virtual-asset service providers and allowing retail investors to trade major tokens like Bitcoin and Ether showcases the city&#8217;s contrasting approach to regulating the crypto industry compared to regulators in other parts of the world.</p>
<p>By implementing a licensing regime, Hong Kong aims to establish a regulatory framework that promotes transparency, consumer protection, and the integrity of the virtual asset industry.</p>
<p>However, an Hong Kong official has <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hong-kong-crypto-businesses-regulation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">warned</a> that upcoming crypto regulation will not encourage a relaxed approach despite the city&#8217;s friendly stance on crypto and expanding access for retail investors.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microstrategy-michael-saylor-bitcoin-ordinals/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hashkey-funds-1b-valuation/">HashKey Group to Raise Funds at $1B Valuation</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/hashkey-funds-1b-valuation/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>MicroStrategy Executive Chairman Michael Saylor Says Firm Exploring Use Cases for Bitcoin Ordinals</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/microstrategy-michael-saylor-bitcoin-ordinals/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/microstrategy-michael-saylor-bitcoin-ordinals/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 11:15:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bictoin ordinals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[michael saylor]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[microstrategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nft]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=255663</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microstrategy-michael-saylor-bitcoin-ordinals/">MicroStrategy Executive Chairman Michael Saylor Says Firm Exploring Use Cases for Bitcoin Ordinals</a></p>
<p>MicroStrategy’s Michael Saylor recently suggested that Bitcoin Ordinals could immensely benefit the crypto ecosystem. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microstrategy-michael-saylor-bitcoin-ordinals/">MicroStrategy Executive Chairman Michael Saylor Says Firm Exploring Use Cases for Bitcoin Ordinals</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microstrategy-michael-saylor-bitcoin-ordinals/">MicroStrategy Executive Chairman Michael Saylor Says Firm Exploring Use Cases for Bitcoin Ordinals</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/microstrategy-incorporated/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">MicroStrategy Incorporated</a> (NASDAQ: MSTR) co-founder and Executive Chairman <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/michael-saylor/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Michael Saylor</a> has discussed his company’s work with <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/introduction-to-bitcoin-ordinals/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin Ordinals</a>. In a media session, Saylor revealed that his company was exploring how the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a>-backed non-fungible tokens (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NFTs</a>) could lead to software innovation. According to the innovative crypto executive, MicroStrategy was interested in assessing the application development potential of Bitcoin Ordinals.</p>
<p>Although Saylor did not expressly state the Ordinal use cases that MicroStrategy looked to tap into, he pointed out inherent Bitcoin blockchain diversity. Suggesting that the protocol of the world’s most prominent crypto is not solely for transactional purposes, the MicroStrategy co-founder explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>“The whole idea of burning a piece of data on the blockchain opens the door to the possibility that I might burn a digital signature, or I might burn a registration, or I might burn a hash of a document.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>MicroStrategy Executive Chairman Views Bitcoin Ordinals as Instrumental to Mining Success</h2>
<p>At the Bitcoin 2023 in Miami, Saylor stressed that discussions regarding Ordinals are vital to Bitcoin-mining success over the long term. Furthermore, he added that application development that builds on BTC’s functionality could strengthen the token’s widespread adoption.</p>
<p>Saylor explained that the security of most enterprises pales compared to Bitcoin. Furthermore, he added that innovations that deploy Bitcoin and its paraphernalia as an operational factor could tap into a new level of security.</p>
<p>Saylor’s latest comments on Bitcoin Ordinals come on the heels of similar glowing remarks on the <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=w1PRsS4SyUc&amp;t=1254s" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">PBD Podcast</a>. On last week’s wide-ranging business podcast, the MicroStrategy Chairman described Ordinals as a catalyst for BTC adoption. As Saylor put it at the time:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Every time someone builds an application that’s cool on Bitcoin, like all the Ordinals and inscriptions and whatever that are driving up transaction fees, it is a catalyst.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Although Saylor admitted that Ordinals might have also been deployed for more frivolous reasons, he went against censoring the digital assets. The one-time MicroStrategy CEO described potential censorship of Bitcoin against specific uses as wrong and inconsistent with community values. “I do believe in rules without rulers,” Saylor emphasized.</p>
<h2>Ordinals Explained</h2>
<p>Bitcoin Ordinals, also known as Bitcoin NFTs, is an innovative development quickly gaining popularity among blockchain enthusiasts. Founded by Casey Rodarmor and created on the Bitcoin blockchain, the Ordinals protocol allows users to attach digital content to the smallest divisible unit of 1 Bitcoin (satoshi).</p>
<p>Bitcoin Ordinals differ from traditional NFTs with one distinguishing feature. Ordinals are found on-chain with raw data directly written on the network. On the other hand, NFTs are minted separately as new tokens, with potential files on other protocols.</p>
<p>Earlier this month, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a> announced <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-bitcoin-ordinals-nft/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">plans to list</a> Bitcoin Ordinals on its NFT marketplace. The exchange has been aggressively expanding its NFT marketplace offerings and sees the Bitcoin NFTs as a worthy inclusion. In addition to onboarding Ordinals at the end of May, Binance would also provide loyalty support for Bitcoin NFT creators. Furthermore, the prominent exchange seeks to open up additional revenue-generating opportunities for said creators.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/filecoin-foundation-sec-fil-security/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microstrategy-michael-saylor-bitcoin-ordinals/">MicroStrategy Executive Chairman Michael Saylor Says Firm Exploring Use Cases for Bitcoin Ordinals</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/microstrategy-michael-saylor-bitcoin-ordinals/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Filecoin Foundation Lashes Out at SEC for Classifying FIL as Security</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/filecoin-foundation-sec-fil-security/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/filecoin-foundation-sec-fil-security/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 10:26:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fil]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[filecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[grayscale]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=255635</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/filecoin-foundation-sec-fil-security/">Filecoin Foundation Lashes Out at SEC for Classifying FIL as Security</a></p>
<p>Grayscale also noted that it doesn't believe that Filecoin is security and seeks to respond to the SEC staff with a legal basis for their position.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/filecoin-foundation-sec-fil-security/">Filecoin Foundation Lashes Out at SEC for Classifying FIL as Security</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/filecoin-foundation-sec-fil-security/">Filecoin Foundation Lashes Out at SEC for Classifying FIL as Security</a></p>
<p>Earlier this week, the US Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) classified the cryptocurrency <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/filecoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Filecoin</a> as a security and even asked asset manager Grayscale to pull up their application for the Grayscale Filecoin Trust. However, Filecoin has rejected the observation from the SEC adding that FIL was not a security. The Filecoin Foundation described the blockchain network as “a decentralized, peer-to-peer network for storing files”.</p>
<h2>Is FIL a Security?</h2>
<p>In an email statement to the crypto news publication CryptoSlate, Filecoin <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/filecoin-foundation-rejects-secs-classification-of-fil-as-security/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">noted</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Over the last decade, thousands of people around the world have contributed to this open-source project to create a decentralized, efficient, and robust foundation for humanity’s most important information. That includes hundreds of organizations and teams building on the network, thousands of storage providers, and 13,000 Github contributors, building a foundational layer for the next generation of the web.”</p></blockquote>
<p>The SEC action, however, hasn&#8217;t triggered much movement in the Filecoin (FIL) price. As of press time, FIL is trading 1.98% down at a price of $4.46 and a market cap of $1.8 billion.</p>
<h2>SEC and Cryptocurrencies</h2>
<p>The US securities regulator has been going hammer and tongs after crypto assets. SEC chair Gary Gensler also stated that almost every other cryptocurrency classifies as a security and thus shall be subject to federal securities laws.</p>
<p>Previously, Grayscale had filed for Form 10 to make the Grayscale Filecoin Trust a reporting company wherein they would quarterly reports as well as annual reports. However, the SEC asked Grayscale to withdraw this application. In its press release, Grayscale <a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/en/news-release/2023/05/17/2671509/0/en/Grayscale-Investments-Shares-Update-Regarding-Grayscale-Filecoin-Trust-Registration-Statement-on-Form-10.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">noted</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;On May 16, 2023, Grayscale received a comment letter from the SEC staff stating its view that the Trust’s underlying asset, FIL, meets the definition of a security under the federal securities laws, and that therefore the Trust appears to meet the definition of an investment company under the Investment Company Act of 1940. The SEC staff requested that Grayscale seek withdrawal of the registration statement promptly.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>However, Grayscale also noted that it doesn&#8217;t believe that Filecoin is security and seeks to respond to the SEC staff with a legal basis for their position. It will be interesting to see what actions the SEC initiates on the decentralized storage platform, Filecoin.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/musk-lawyer-microsoft-twitter/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/filecoin-foundation-sec-fil-security/">Filecoin Foundation Lashes Out at SEC for Classifying FIL as Security</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/filecoin-foundation-sec-fil-security/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Elon Musk’s Lawyer Sends Letter to Microsoft CEO due to Abusing Twitter’s Data Access</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/musk-lawyer-microsoft-twitter/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/musk-lawyer-microsoft-twitter/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 09:46:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[microsoft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[twitter]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=255622</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/musk-lawyer-microsoft-twitter/">Elon Musk’s Lawyer Sends Letter to Microsoft CEO due to Abusing Twitter’s Data Access</a></p>
<p>The letter did not mention a lawsuit, however, Musk threatened to seek legal redress if there is such a need when he first mentioned this violation back in April.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/musk-lawyer-microsoft-twitter/">Elon Musk’s Lawyer Sends Letter to Microsoft CEO due to Abusing Twitter’s Data Access</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/musk-lawyer-microsoft-twitter/">Elon Musk’s Lawyer Sends Letter to Microsoft CEO due to Abusing Twitter’s Data Access</a></p>
<p>There appears to be a subtle data war brewing between Twitter Inc and American tech giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/microsoft-corporation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Microsoft Corporation</a> (NASDAQ: MSFT). This claim stems from the <a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/5/18/23729216/twitter-microsoft-api-data-sharing-elon-musk-satya-nadella" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">letter</a> sent by <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/elon-musk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Elon Musk</a>’s personal lawyer Alex Spiro to Microsoft CEO Satya Nadella over the misuse of access to social media’s API.</p>
<h2>The Issue at Hand</h2>
<p>The news was first reported by the New York Times which claims that Microsoft has been violating “multiple provisions” of the social media company’s developer agreement for an extended length of time. Twitter is accusing Microsoft of using its data APIs in 8 of its applications including Bing, xBox One, Azure, and Power Platform to mention a few.</p>
<p>Despite this extended usage, the Elon Musk team said appropriate permissions were only sought for two of the products. With Twitter notably adjusting its terms of use such that developers can generally pay for some of its data content, Microsoft pulled away from using the APIs sometime in April this year.</p>
<p>The letter claimed specifically there were “unauthorized uses and purposes” and that Microsoft failed to inform it of “any use case for six of the eight Microsoft Apps that it continued to operate until last month”.</p>
<p>“The Agreement makes clear that Microsoft was obligated to disclose and obtain approval for its intended use case for each Microsoft App, and to notify Twitter of any substantive modification to those use cases,” the letter reads, “Yet Microsoft did not identify any use case for six of the eight Microsoft Apps that it continued to operate until last month.”</p>
<p>The letter, having stated some of the perceived ways in which Microsoft violated its generosity also gave a very specific demand. This demand included a full “compliance audit” on all of the Microsoft apps that utilized Twitter’s data up until the time the support was shut down by the bigger tech giant. Microsoft was given until June 7th to comply with the demands.</p>
<p>The letter did not mention a lawsuit, however, Musk threatened to seek legal redress if there is such a need when he first mentioned this violation back in April.</p>
<h2>Twitter’s Data Abuse: Microsoft Responds</h2>
<p>The claim of Twitter’s data abuse has elucidated a response from Microsoft spokesperson Frank Shaw. In his response, Shaw said;</p>
<p>“Today we heard from a law firm representing Twitter with some questions about our previous use of the free Twitter API. We will review these questions and respond appropriately. We look forward to continuing our long-term partnership with the company.”</p>
<p>Twitter has been pursuing a number of monetization options since the acquisition of the company by Elon Musk was finalized. In the age of ChatGPT’s Large Language Model (LLM) data training, Twitter&#8217;s current adjustment of its terms of use might turn out to be very profitable for it in the long term.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/chatgpt-app-ios-openai/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/musk-lawyer-microsoft-twitter/">Elon Musk’s Lawyer Sends Letter to Microsoft CEO due to Abusing Twitter’s Data Access</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/musk-lawyer-microsoft-twitter/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>ChatGPT App for iOS Is Live, OpenAI Planning to Launch Android Version</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/chatgpt-app-ios-openai/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/chatgpt-app-ios-openai/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Darya Rudz]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 09:07:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[artificial intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chatgpt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chatgpt app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chatgpt app ios]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[openai]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[openai artificial intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[openai chatgpt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[openai chatgpt app]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=255571</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/chatgpt-app-ios-openai/">ChatGPT App for iOS Is Live, OpenAI Planning to Launch Android Version</a></p>
<p>Previously, one of the simplest ways to access OpenAI’s software on a mobile device was to use Microsoft’s Bing app which offers access to ChatGPT. Now, with the app, using the chatbot will be easier and faster.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/chatgpt-app-ios-openai/">ChatGPT App for iOS Is Live, OpenAI Planning to Launch Android Version</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/chatgpt-app-ios-openai/">ChatGPT App for iOS Is Live, OpenAI Planning to Launch Android Version</a></p>
<p>OpenAI Inc, a research laboratory that focuses on <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/technology/artificial-intelligence-news/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">artificial intelligence</a> (AI), has <a href="https://openai.com/blog/introducing-the-chatgpt-app-for-ios" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announced</a> the launch of an iOS version of the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/everything-you-need-to-know-about-chatgpt-ai-chatbot/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ChatGPT</a> app. According to the company, later, the app will also be available on Android. It will first be rolled out for users in the US, with more countries added in the coming weeks.</p>
<p>As OpenAI has stated, the ChatGPT app is free to use. Its features include synchronizing a user&#8217;s history across devices as well as integration of Whisper – an open-source speech-recognition system that enables voice input. The app is also free from ads. In addition, those who have a subscription to ChatGPT Plus get exclusive access to GPT-4’s capabilities, early access to features and faster response times.</p>
<p>ChatGPT Plus is a special offering that was introduced in February 2023. For as much as $20 per month, it offers upgraded features, such as faster response times, early access to new features and improvements, and the ability to use ChatGPT even during peak times.</p>
<p>The launch of the ChatGPT application is an initiative that has been expected, considering the buzz around the chatbot introduced by OpenAI in November 2022. Initially, the chatbot was a kind of an experiment. However, its popularity surged, with ChatGPT&#8217;s user base rapidly expanding. Currently, ChatGPT has over 100 million users. The ChatGPT website generates 1.8 billion visitors per month. Notably, this number has been achieved within a three-month period from February to April 2023. Due to such growth, the need for the ChatGPT app has been obvious.</p>
<p>Previously, one of the simplest ways to access OpenAI’s software on a mobile device was to use Microsoft’s Bing app which offers access to ChatGPT. Now, with the app, using the chatbot will be easier and faster.</p>
<p>According to the ChatGPT team, the app will be upgraded based on user feedback, with more features coming later.</p>
<p>The first rumours about OpenAI launching the ChatGPT application appeared back in February. There were also reports about the company working on new software that would create videos with the help of artificial intelligence. Earlier this week, we also <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/chatgpt-openai-open-source-ai-model/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a> about ChatGPT preparing to release a new open-source language model.</p>
<h2>ChatGPT Leaving Rivals Behind</h2>
<p>The mobile ChatGPT app comes at a time when big tech players, including <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/google/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Google LLC</a> and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/meta/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Meta Platforms Inc</a> (NASDAQ: META), are experimenting with artificial intelligence. For example, Google is integrating AI capabilities into its search engine. Its Bard uses Google’s own LaMDA language model. Launched in 2021, Google LaMDA is considered to be one of the biggest competitors of ChatGPT. LaMDA has the ability to comprehend complex inquiries and discussions that span a wide range of subjects, it has been honed with the use of 1.56 trillion words and a whopping 137 billion parameters.</p>
<p>With more research into AI taking place, many bet on ChatGPT, saying that it wins over its competitors. The key advantages offered by ChatGPT are options for free and paid access, as well as collecting user feedback in order to improve the chatbot&#8217;s functionality. As a result, ChatGPT has secured a significant competitive advantage in the AI market, leaving competitors struggling to keep up.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/netflix-stock-jumps-ad-tier/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/chatgpt-app-ios-openai/">ChatGPT App for iOS Is Live, OpenAI Planning to Launch Android Version</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/chatgpt-app-ios-openai/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Netflix Stock Jumps 9% on Ad-Tier Growth, Currently Trading at $371</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/netflix-stock-jumps-ad-tier/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/netflix-stock-jumps-ad-tier/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 09:02:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wall Street]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[netfix]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[netflix stock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nflx stock]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=255597</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/netflix-stock-jumps-ad-tier/">Netflix Stock Jumps 9% on Ad-Tier Growth, Currently Trading at $371</a></p>
<p>Streaming giant Netflix experienced a rise in stock value Thursday after pitching advertisers at its first Upfronts session.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/netflix-stock-jumps-ad-tier/">Netflix Stock Jumps 9% on Ad-Tier Growth, Currently Trading at $371</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/netflix-stock-jumps-ad-tier/">Netflix Stock Jumps 9% on Ad-Tier Growth, Currently Trading at $371</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/netflix/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Netflix Inc</a> (NASDAQ: NFLX) recently saw its stock jump more than 9% on commendable ad-tier growth. On Wednesday, the entertainment and mass media company unveiled details about its new ad development to advertisers. Netflix said its new ad-supported tier is growing, as a quarter of its new subscribers chose the option. In addition, the streaming giant revealed that the cheaper ad-supported tier has a monthly active user base of 5 million.</p>
<p>Wednesday’s session marked the first time that Netflix would pitch to advertisers and was also the company’s inaugural participation in the industry’s <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/15/upfronts-media-writers-strike-soft-ad-market.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">‘Upfront presentations&#8217;</a>.</p>
<p>Media companies that once relied on boosting subscribership numbers for their struggling streaming services are now leaning toward advertising models. For instance, other media platforms participating in this year’s Upfront presentations include NBCUniversal and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/warner-bros-discovery/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Warner Bros. Discovery</a> (NASDAQ: WBD).</p>
<p>Netflix stock surged on Thursday and was up 9.22% as of press time at $371.29. The streaming and production company launched its ad-based option late last year following stagnated subscriber growth. Netflix’s quarterly subscriber growth struggles were underscored in <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nflx-stock-down-27-netflix-announces-loss-of-200k-paid-subscribers-in-q1-2022/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Q1 2022</a> when the company’s shares plummeted by over 25%. At the time, the popular streaming also lost subscribers for the first time in more than a decade.</p>
<h2>Netflix Stock Could Rise Further Following Userbase Growth &amp; Password-Sharing Crackdown</h2>
<p>Although Netflix’s <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/netflix-q1-2023-password-sharing/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">most recent quarterly outing</a> reflected mixed results, the company added 1.75 million subscribers. Meanwhile, Netflix’s bottom line for subsequent quarters could see even more revenue as the company prepares to <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/03/08/netflix-password-sharing-crackdown-college-students.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">crack down on password-sharing</a>. Also, its ad tier agenda marks a U-turn from management’s previous stance that it would not prioritize ads. Netflix’s ad tier costs $6.99 monthly and features commercials up to 30 seconds in duration before and during a video.</p>
<p>Last December, Netflix’s co-CEO Ted Sarandos said the company could offer multiple ad-based subscription plans in the future. At the time, Sarandos explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>“We have multiple tiers today, so it’s likely we’ll have multiple ad tiers over time, but nothing to talk about yet. And the product itself will evolve, I suspect, pretty dramatically, but slowly, gradually.”</p></blockquote>
<p>In the fourth quarter of 2022, the co-CEO also addressed the upcoming password-sharing crackdown vis-à-vis increasing prices. Although he admitted that the development irks customers, Sarandos also pointed out:</p>
<blockquote><p>“There are folks who are enjoying Netflix, literally for free today. So, they’re getting a lot of value out of it. I think they’ll be happy to have their own account.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Furthermore, the Netflix executive added that Netflix remains committed to making customers see the value in its offerings.</p>
<h2>Changing of The Guard at Netflix Helm</h2>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/netflix-subscribers-q4-2022-ceo-steps-down/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">In January</a>, Sarandos took over the helm alongside then-COO Greg Peters after Netflix co-founder Reed Hastings stepped down to become Executive Chairman. At the time, the departing Hastings expressed confidence in his successors’ abilities and said they helped Netflix through challenging times. Despite the company’s inauspicious start to 2022, it was able to round off well.</p>
<p>After re-evaluating its operational agenda ahead, Netflix remains braced to reaccelerate revenue growth while providing premium services for customers.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-one-subscription/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/netflix-stock-jumps-ad-tier/">Netflix Stock Jumps 9% on Ad-Tier Growth, Currently Trading at $371</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/netflix-stock-jumps-ad-tier/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase One: American Crypto Exchange to Roll Out Subscription Service in 35 Countries</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-one-subscription/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-one-subscription/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 08:44:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brian armstrong]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase one]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=255575</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-one-subscription/">Coinbase One: American Crypto Exchange to Roll Out Subscription Service in 35 Countries</a></p>
<p>By launching the subscription service, Coinbase is seeking to expand its global reach.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-one-subscription/">Coinbase One: American Crypto Exchange to Roll Out Subscription Service in 35 Countries</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-one-subscription/">Coinbase One: American Crypto Exchange to Roll Out Subscription Service in 35 Countries</a></p>
<p>American crypto exchange <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase</a> is bracing up to roll out its subscription service &#8211; Coinbase One. According to a Thursday <a href="https://www.coinbase.com/blog/new-updates-to-coinbase-one-zero-trading-fees-boosted-staking-rewards-and" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announcement</a>, the zero trading fee subscription service will start out in Germany, Ireland, and the United Kingdom. However, there are plans to extend the rollout to at least 32 other countries within the shortest time possible. A company statement reads:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Coinbase One is rolling out to full availability in the coming months, and we plan to expand to additional markets internationally.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Coinbase One, which has been in testing in the US since 2021, allows subscribers to pay a monthly fee of $29.99. With the subscription, users may trade for free throughout the month and also get amplified staking rewards.</p>
<p>Furthermore, subscribers will have exclusive access to industry insights and analytics from Messari and CoinTracker. And in addition to that, the subscription will also offer US members pre-filled tax return documents &#8211; Form 8949. That is, users do not have to go through the hassle of filing crypto taxes. Instead, they&#8217;ll enjoy the benefit of having their transactions organized automatically.</p>
<p>Coinbase also confirms that its new subscription service will give members round-the-clock access to its support team. That is, at any time of any day, members who need any form of assistance will get prompt help.</p>
<p>It might also be worth noting that Coinbase still has other plans to make the lives of subscribers much easier. Per its announcement, the exchange is also eyeing potential partnerships with the likes of Alto IRA (Individual Retirement Account) and Blockworks’ Permissionless and Lemonade.</p>
<h2>Coinbase One to Boost Exchange&#8217;s Global Reach</h2>
<p>For what it&#8217;s worth, the launch of the subscription service is part of Coinbase’s efforts to expand its global reach.  And with plans to offer the service in at least 35 countries, the exchange is looking to further deepen its roots across the globe.</p>
<p>It might be interesting to note that this launch comes after CEO <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/brian-armstrong/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Brian Armstrong</a> recently <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-uk-europe-market-us-regulatory/">suggested</a> that Coinbase might be moving out of the United States. At the time, Armstrong cited regulatory uncertainty in the country as the reason behind the company’s consideration. However, the CEO has since changed his earlier position, confirming that the exchange will no longer exit the US.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/quickswap-orb-dtwap-dex-orders/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-one-subscription/">Coinbase One: American Crypto Exchange to Roll Out Subscription Service in 35 Countries</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-one-subscription/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>QuickSwap Integrates Orb-Powered dTWAP for Cheaper Price Impact on DEX Orders</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/quickswap-orb-dtwap-dex-orders/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/quickswap-orb-dtwap-dex-orders/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 08:25:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dtwap]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[orbs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[quickswap]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=255555</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/quickswap-orb-dtwap-dex-orders/">QuickSwap Integrates Orb-Powered dTWAP for Cheaper Price Impact on DEX Orders</a></p>
<p>QuickSwap has become the latest DEX to integrate dTWAP for traders to cut down on the price impact of their orders. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/quickswap-orb-dtwap-dex-orders/">QuickSwap Integrates Orb-Powered dTWAP for Cheaper Price Impact on DEX Orders</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/quickswap-orb-dtwap-dex-orders/">QuickSwap Integrates Orb-Powered dTWAP for Cheaper Price Impact on DEX Orders</a></p>
<p>Leading Polygon decentralized exchange <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/quickswap/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">QuickSwap</a> recently integrated dTWAP for DEXs. Powered by <a href="https://www.orbs.com/dtwap/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Orbs</a>, dTWAP, the fully permissionless and composable DeFi protocol, will grant QuickSwap dragons access to its algorithmic trading strategy. This means that traders can lower the price impact of their orders without incurring additional costs. Meanwhile, besides dTWAP, QuickSwap dragons will also deploy Orbs &#8211; infrastructure for Limit Swap orders.</p>
<h2>Closer Look at QuickSwap &#8211; dTWAP Development</h2>
<p>The QuickSwap-dTWAP development follows similar integrations by the Orbs-powered protocol with SpookySwap, Spirit, and Pangolin. Furthermore, the latest dTWAP integration underpins the technical working relationship between QuickSwaps and the separate decentralized execution layer Orbs. Both projects leveraged dTWAP&#8217;s smart contract audits and comprehensive developer documentation to integrate the protocol with QuickSwap.</p>
<p>According to <a href="https://defillama.com/dexs/quickswap" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">DeFiLlama</a>, QuickSwap&#8217;s transaction volume for the past week exceeds $209 million. Furthermore, the decentralized layer-2 digital trading platform&#8217;s transaction volume in the last 24 hours exceeds $30 million. As a DEX automated market maker, QuickSwap&#8217;s offerings comprise multi-chain swaps, limit, order, and &#8216;best price trades&#8217;. However, the dTWAP integration will expand current offerings and increase transaction volumes from cost-conscious traders.</p>
<p>As an algorithmic trading strategy, TWAP also sees a lot of use cases in centralized finance (CeFi). The tool helps the protocol cut down the impact of large orders by reducing them into smaller portions.</p>
<p>Setting up a dTWAP order is relatively seamless and requires the specification of three parameters. These include the number of intervals, max duration, and the trade interval.</p>
<p>Users are also required to switch to the dTWAP UI to make the execution of trades easier and better manageable. The trade user interface features a customizable dashboard that updates changes in order in real time.</p>
<p>For instance, the &#8216;number of intervals&#8217; parameter lets the user choose the exact number of individual trades, after which the estimated trading interval is calculated. &#8216;Max duration&#8217; is the optimum time to execute the total amount of individual trades on the full dTWAP order. Lastly, &#8216;trade interval&#8217; establishes the time gap between each trade. However, users can edit this parameter to reflect the order sheet&#8217;s corresponding trade sizes and number changes.</p>
<h2>dTWAP</h2>
<p>The dTWAP protocol is the go-to tool in the decentralized finance space for algorithmic orders. Backed by the Orbs network L3 technology, the protocol is expected to experience substantial growth in usage as it adds support for additional DEXs. dTWAP is currently integrated with 4 DEXs across 3 different chains, accounting for its $200 million+ transaction volume in the past week.</p>
<h2>Orbs</h2>
<p>The Orbs Network is executed by secure permissionless validators that use the Proof-of-Stake (PoS) consensus. Founded in 2017, Orbs launched its mainnet and token in March 2019 and has a development team of more than 30 people. The backend staff of the open, decentralized, public blockchain infrastructure is based in offices in the Middle East (Tel Aviv), Europe (London), North America (New York), and Asia (Tokyo and Seoul).</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-details-ai-chips/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/quickswap-orb-dtwap-dex-orders/">QuickSwap Integrates Orb-Powered dTWAP for Cheaper Price Impact on DEX Orders</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/quickswap-orb-dtwap-dex-orders/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Meta Shares Details of Its AI Chips for First Time</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-details-ai-chips/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-details-ai-chips/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 08:13:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ai]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[facebook]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Meta]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=255570</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-details-ai-chips/">Meta Shares Details of Its AI Chips for First Time</a></p>
<p>The new Meta Training and Inference Accelerator (MTIA) chip shall specifically handle "inference", an already-trained AI model that makes a prediction or takes action. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-details-ai-chips/">Meta Shares Details of Its AI Chips for First Time</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-details-ai-chips/">Meta Shares Details of Its AI Chips for First Time</a></p>
<p>For the very first time, Facebook parent <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/meta/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Meta Platforms Inc</a> (NASDAQ: META) publicly announced that it is working on custom computer chips which will help the company with its artificial intelligence and video processing tasks.</p>
<p>Ahead of the virtual event on Thursday, May 18, Meta disclosed its internal silicon chip projects for the very first time while discussing the company&#8217;s AI technical infrastructure investments. Investors have been keen on knowing about Meta&#8217;s investments in AI along with the related data center hardware.</p>
<p>Over the last year, Meta has announced multiple layoffs as the company works on streamlining its operations while embarking on &#8220;a year of efficiency&#8221;. However, designing and building indigenous chips is always an expensive path for companies to undertake.</p>
<p>But Meta&#8217;s vice president of infrastructure Alexis Bjorlin believes that the improved performance will justify the investment. Recently, Meta has been overhauling its data center designs to focus on other energy-efficient techniques for reducing excess heat and liquid cooling.</p>
<p>For e.g. the company&#8217;s new computer chips, the Meta Scalable Video Processor, or MSVP, will process and transmit video to users while cutting down on energy requirements. Bjorlin said that there were no options available commercially to handle the task of processing and delivering 4 billion videos a day, as effectively as Meta wants.</p>
<p>Also, another processor Meta Training and Inference Accelerator, or MTIA, is the first in Meta&#8217;s family of chips that will help with various AI-specific tasks. The new MTIA chip shall specifically handle &#8220;inference&#8221;, an already-trained AI model that makes a prediction or takes action.</p>
<p>This AI-powered &#8220;inference&#8221; chip will power Meta&#8217;s recommendation algorithm used to show content and ads in people&#8217;s news feeds. However, Bjorlin didn&#8217;t speak about who the manufacturer is, but the blog post shows a “fabricated in TSMC 7nm process”.</p>
<h2>Meta&#8217;s Multi-Generational Roadmap</h2>
<p>Bjorlin said that Meta has a &#8220;multi-generational roadmap&#8221; for its family of AI chips which will include processors used for training AI models. As per the Reuters <a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/inside-metas-scramble-catch-up-ai-2023-04-25/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a> earlier, Meta canceled its AI inference chip project and started another one scheduled to roll out by 2025.</p>
<p>Bjorlin said that since Meta isn&#8217;t in the business of cloud computing, the company didn&#8217;t feel compelled to talk about the internal data center chip projects. She <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/18/meta-pulls-the-curtain-back-on-its-ai-chips-for-the-first-time.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">added</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“If you look at what we’re sharing &#8211; our first two chips that we developed &#8211; it’s definitely giving a little bit of a view into what are we doing internally. We haven’t had to advertise this, and we don’t need to advertise this, but you know, the world is interested.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Meta&#8217;s new hardware works effectively with the company&#8217;s PyTorch software. This has become one of the most popular tools used by third-party developers in creating AI apps. The new hardware will eventually power several metaverse-related tasks, including augmented reality and virtual reality.</p>
<p>Additionally, Meta has also created a generative AI-powered coding assistant which will help the company&#8217;s developers to easily create and develop software. Meta said that it will continue to contribute to open-source technologies and AI research driving technological innovation ahead.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-mixed-q4-full-year-2023/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-details-ai-chips/">Meta Shares Details of Its AI Chips for First Time</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-details-ai-chips/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4676 metric#misses=43 metric#hit-ratio=99.1 metric#bytes=1280734 metric#prefetches=201 metric#store-reads=21 metric#store-writes=17 metric#store-hits=207 metric#store-misses=4 metric#sql-queries=34 metric#ms-total=127.62 metric#ms-cache=8.09 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.2187 metric#ms-cache-ratio=6.3 -->