<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 14:31:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Does Litecoin&#8217;s halving provide clues ahead of Bitcoin&#8217;s next April?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/does-litecoins-halving-provide-clues-ahead-of-bitcoins-next-april/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/does-litecoins-halving-provide-clues-ahead-of-bitcoins-next-april/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dan Ashmore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 14:31:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/does-litecoins-halving-provide-clues-ahead-of-bitcoins-next-april/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key Takeaways The next Bitcoin halving is slated for April 2024, the fourth of Bitcoin&#8217;s existence Litecoin has just undergone its fourth halving, but the price effects of Litecoin halvings in the past have not been as strong Sample size is small meaning it is hard to conclude with confidence whether halvings have tangible price [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/does-litecoins-halving-provide-clues-ahead-of-bitcoins-next-april/">Does Litecoin&#8217;s halving provide clues ahead of Bitcoin&#8217;s next April?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2 dir="ltr">Key Takeaways</h2>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">The next Bitcoin halving is slated for April 2024, the fourth of Bitcoin&rsquo;s existence</li>
<li dir="ltr">Litecoin has just undergone its fourth halving, but the price effects of Litecoin halvings in the past have not been as strong</li>
<li dir="ltr">Sample size is small meaning it is hard to conclude with confidence whether halvings have tangible price effects in the short-term</li>
<li dir="ltr">Bitcoin is a very different proposition to Litecoin, but the price action going forward of the latter will be interesting to track as we approach Bitcoin&rsquo;s next halving in April 2024</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p dir="ltr">Whether Bitcoin halvings are priced in has become a fervent topic of debate among the community. We put together an <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/are-bitcoin-halvenings-priced-in-understanding-the-price-effects-of-bitcoins-supply-cut/"><u>analysis</u></a> of this question a few weeks ago, as we now fast approach the fourth halving of Bitcoin&rsquo;s young life.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Slated for April 2024, the halving&nbsp;will cut the Bitcoin block subsidy from 6.25 Bitcoins to 3.125 Bitcoins per block, halving the issuance rate of newly created supply.</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14533733">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">We will not rehash (pun intended!) our aforementioned analysis of the upcoming halving here. Instead, we will focus on another coin: Litecoin. One of the world&rsquo;s first altcoins, it is a derivative of Bitcoin and, intriguingly, just underwent the fourth halving of its life.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Can Litecoin therefore be seen as a guinea pig ahead of Bitcoin&rsquo;s own halving next year? Well, not really, but we may be able to gain certain insights.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">First, let us examine Litecoin&rsquo;s performance through past halvings. Price data is quite illiquid prior to 2015, so the below chart omits the first halving.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14728357">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">The log scale of the chart somewhat obscures it, but the second halving in 2015 preceded strong price performance for Litecoin. On the other hand, the third halving in 2019 saw falling prices, before the trend reversed after COVID struck in 2020, when the entire crypto sector surged into the mainstream.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">It is too soon to draw conclusions regarding the fourth halving, which occured just over a week ago on August 5th. Nevertheless, Litecoin&rsquo;s halvings don&rsquo;t offer compelling evidence of a strong relationship thus far at least. Furthermore, like most questions in crypto, the sample size is so small that even if they did precipitate aggressive price rises immediately, that would not necessarily mean there is causation. &nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin is not Litecoin, but again, we may be able to derive clues from the pattern in ascertaining the effect of halvings on the former, even if we can&rsquo;t be confident given the sample size issues. First, let us now look at Bitcoin&rsquo;s price action while marking the halving events:</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14728571">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">The pattern is clear. Typically, we have seen outsized volatility in the months leading up to a halving, before strong outperformance on the other side. The outperformance has also grown smaller with each halving, perhaps unsurprising given the market cap has grown so much in the four years between each event. &nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">So, why has the effect of halvings on Bitcoin been, at least optically, larger than the same events on Litecoin? The first theory takes us to the heart of the debate on whether halvings are really priced in: while previous events have preceded steep inclines for Bitcoin, they have also lined up well with global liquidity cycles.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The below chart from Fidelity shows this well. There is perhaps no greater influence on the valuations of risk assets than central bank balance sheets, and the halvings have lined up incredibly well with the expansion of those same balance sheets.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/07/15/1692092799057-7f270707-141a-457f-88a1-35379ccf079e.png" style="width: 600px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="600" height="319"></p>
<p dir="ltr">The thing is, the next halving could well line up with an expansion in liquidity again. The previous eighteen months have seen one of the fastest rate-hiking cycles in recent history, with the Fed funds rate now above 5%. Now, looking at probabilities implied by the futures market, the market is anticipating that the hikes are coming to a close (if they haven&rsquo;t done so already).&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Looking further forward towards the time period around the halving (April), futures imply that <em>rate cuts&nbsp;</em>could come into play. Not to mention, when we look at the yield curve, it is currently at the deepest level of inversion since the early 80s. The bottom line is this: the fourth halving, through sheer chance, could again line up miraculously well with global liquidity cycles.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14728625">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">Of course, the macro situation has been changing incessantly, and there is every chance that forecasts around the liquidity cycle could flip, and the halving won&rsquo;t line up as well as it has done in the past.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">This is where Litecoin may come in. With its halvings landing at different dates to Bitcoin in the past, yet not boosting prices as much as the orange coin saw, perhaps it is just a timing thing, whether macro-related or other? Looking at Litecoin&rsquo;s price action compared to Bitcoin, the duo are tightly correlated, like many altcoins in the space. If Litecoin&rsquo;s halving does not cause a slight outperformance this time compared to Bitcoin or other coins, what would be the explanation?&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14728658">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">Ultimately, like we keep saying, the sample size is small. Bitcoin has only experienced three halvings, and one could even argue that it was only the recent event in 2020 that occurred while the asset was trading with sufficient liquidity.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Litecoin&rsquo;s less explosive price action after its own halvings do perhaps throw further doubt on the theory that a 50% cut to the new supply issuance will inevitably kick up the price. And yet, Litecoin is not Bitcoin, so the debate will rage on.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Either way, revisiting Litecoin&rsquo;s price performance around the time of Bitcoin halving will be interesting, because by then it will have had around eight months post-halving and may present a more relevant reference point.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/does-litecoins-halving-provide-clues-ahead-of-bitcoins-next-april/">Does Litecoin&#8217;s halving provide clues ahead of Bitcoin&#8217;s next April?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/does-litecoins-halving-provide-clues-ahead-of-bitcoins-next-april/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Litecoin price pattern points to an 18% plunge to $64</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/litecoin-price-pattern-points-to-an-18-plunge-to-64/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 12:29:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/litecoin-price-pattern-points-to-an-18-plunge-to-64/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Litecoin has dropped by more than 30% from its highest level this year. Focus now shifts to the upcoming FOMC minutes. Litecoin price continued falling on Wednesday as focus shifted to the upcoming FOMC minutes. LTC plunged to a low of $78.78, the lowest level since June 20th. The coin has fallen by over 32% [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/litecoin-price-pattern-points-to-an-18-plunge-to-64/">Litecoin price pattern points to an 18% plunge to $64</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Litecoin has dropped by more than 30% from its highest level this year.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Focus now shifts to the upcoming FOMC minutes.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/litecoin/"><u>Litecoin</u></a> price continued falling on Wednesday as focus shifted to the upcoming FOMC minutes. LTC plunged to a low of $78.78, the lowest level since June 20th. The coin has fallen by over 32% from its highest level in July. Other coins like Bitcoin, Ethereum, and XRP have also retreated.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">FOMC minutes ahead</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Litecoin has lost momentum in the past few weeks as the hype of the recent&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/litecoin-completes-third-halving-block-reward-cut-to-6-25-ltc/"><u>halving</u></a> event faded. In most periods, cryptocurrencies tend to do well ahead of a major event and plunge shortly thereafter. This is known as buying the rumour, selling the news.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The next key catalyst that will move the LTC price will be the upcoming FOMC minutes. These minutes will show the deliberations that happened in the last meeting. In it, the bank decided to hike interest rates by 0.25%.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In the past, Fed minutes have moved key financial assets like cryptocurrencies and stocks. However, there is a likelihood that LTC and other cryptocurrencies will react mildly to the minutes.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Besides, they have failed to react positively to important events recently. For example, Litecoin and Bitcoin remained in a consolidation mode after last week&rsquo;s US inflation data. The numbers showed that US inflation, except housing, is falling at a quicker rate than expected.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, there is a likelihood that the Fed will pause hiking rates. Some analysts believe that the bank will even start cutting rates in the first quarter of 2024 since risks are rising.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin and Litecoin also ignored important news on China. The country has published weak economic numbers recently. For example, its imports and exports have slipped while retail sales and industrial production rose at a slower pace than expected.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Litecoin price forecast</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/07/16/1692188436220-f883b05e-c389-4aee-971d-47be21a47d8f.png" style="width: 548px;height: 266.693px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="548" height="266.693"></p>
<p dir="ltr">The daily chart shows that LTC price has been in a downward trend after peaking at $114 in July. It has already dropped below the 50-day moving average and the crucial support at $82.50, the lowest point on June 28th.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The two lines of the MACD indicator have moved to almost minus 3 while the Relative Strength Index (RSI) has moved to the oversold level. It also remains below the important resistance at $103.60, the highest point in February and March.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, Litecoin has more downside going forward, with the next level to watch being $64.77, the lowest swing on March 11th. This price is ~18% below the current level.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy Litecoin</h2>
<p dir="ltr">
        </p><div class="relative">

            <div class="mb-3  pb-6  px-6  bg-slate-50  rounded-xl  ps-shadow-inner">

    <h3 class="inline-block">
        eToro    </h3>

            <p class="text-sm">eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>
    
    <div class="w-full  flex  flex-wrap  items-start  flex-col  gap-2">

        
<a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=MTQ5OTgz&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="nofollow sponsored noopener" target="_self" class="inline-block  text-indigo-600  underline  hover:text-indigo-200  ease-in-out  duration-300  transition-all" title="Buy LTC with eToro today">Buy LTC with eToro today</a>

    </div>

</div><div class="  pb-6  px-6  bg-slate-50  rounded-xl  ps-shadow-inner">

    <h3 class="inline-block">
        Public    </h3>

            <p class="text-sm">Public is an investing platform that allows you to invest stocks, ETFs, crypto, and alternative assets like fine art and collectibles&mdash;all in one place.</p>
    
    <div class="w-full  flex  flex-wrap  items-start  flex-col  gap-2">

        
<a href="/visit/public-crypto?guid=MTQ5OTgz&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="nofollow sponsored noopener" target="_self" class="inline-block  text-indigo-600  underline  hover:text-indigo-200  ease-in-out  duration-300  transition-all" title="Buy LTC with Public today">Buy LTC with Public today</a>

    </div>

</div>
        </div>



<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/litecoin-price-pattern-points-to-an-18-plunge-to-64/">Litecoin price pattern points to an 18% plunge to $64</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Memu&#8217;s presale is nearly $2 million. Is the token set to explode?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memus-presale-is-nearly-2-million-is-the-token-set-to-explode/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memus-presale-is-nearly-2-million-is-the-token-set-to-explode/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Motiur Rahman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 12:24:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technical Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memus-presale-is-nearly-2-million-is-the-token-set-to-explode/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Shiba Memu has raised $2 million in a fast-happening presale Investors have been thrilled by Shiba Memu&#8217;s AI capabilities set to make it a marketing powerhouse Shiba Memu has a potential higher 1,000% price increase as the project gains popularity Shiba Memu (SHMU) buyers are shy of the $2 million mark regarding the value of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memus-presale-is-nearly-2-million-is-the-token-set-to-explode/">Shiba Memu&#8217;s presale is nearly $2 million. Is the token set to explode?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu has raised $2 million in a fast-happening presale</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Investors have been thrilled by Shiba Memu&rsquo;s AI capabilities set to make it a marketing powerhouse</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu has a potential higher 1,000% price increase as the project gains popularity</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu (SHMU) buyers are shy of the $2 million mark regarding the value of tokens bought. Since launching the presale a few weeks ago, token buying has been unstoppable. At this point, it is fair to say that buyers have huge bets for the new meme kid on the block. That positions the token to a potential price surge after listing. Investors can purchase the token via the project&rsquo;s&nbsp;<a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>website</u></a>.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Is Shiba Memu the best meme cryptocurrency of 2023?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">There are notable crypto names in the meme scene. Dogecoin and Shiba Inu have been the top dogs for quite a while. Still, new names like PEPE debuted in 2023 and became instant sensations. Undoubtedly, the meme space has been growing fast. The market hit a market cap of $20 billion in early 2022 from $0 in early 2020.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Nonetheless, there has been a notable challenge for most, if not all, meme cryptocurrencies. They have yet to replicate gains and remain sustainable to generate lasting returns. For Dogecoin and Shiba Inu, a prolonged bear market has caught up with the assets.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The search for a meme token likely to remain powerful and deliver lasting returns is on. Shiba Memu looks like that alpha edge investors have been looking into meme investments.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Against the backdrop of enjoying the privileges of being a meme, Shiba Memu aims to be sustainable. The project is built with an artificial intelligence angle. With AI, the focus is to make Shiba Memu powerful and intelligent, capable of doing more than humans. Shiba Memu will write its own PR, devise a marketing strategy, and generate FOMO for itself. After all, meme tokens are mostly driven by hype.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">But think of what AI can do in creative advertising. It can crawl the web and find the best ideas in marketing. The AI can then package the information in a fun, friendly, and understandable manner. As an AI-led project, Shiba Memu will feature these capabilities.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The added advantages of AI in Shiba Memu make the project one of the best in crypto right now. As such, Shiba Memu could be the unlikely hero of 2023 while the rest of the sector sleeps.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Is Shiba Memu a 10x investment?&nbsp;</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">It is highly speculative how much potential a newly launched token could rise. However, a 10x increase in value is an understatement, as meme tokens have risen up to 50x.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">So far, Shiba Memu has been a presale king, hinting at how much potential the token has. Thus, the future of the token is huge, which could start to get realised after listings in 2024.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The possible price drivers for the token are hype due to ingenious self-marketing and demand. As the world evolves through AI, we could see more demand being unlocked for Shiba Memu.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The project also allows users to interact with the software through an AI dashboard. They can ask questions, give suggestions, and be informed of the latest in creative advertising. This could unlock demand and make Shiba Memu a more than 10x investment.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>What are the benefits of buying Shiba Memu in the presale?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu&rsquo;s presale is quite unique. The price started at $0.011125 and is now at $0.020575. The price of the token will be $0.0244 when the presale ends. The increases have been due to SHMU tokenomics. The tokenomics will see SHMU value double by the end of the 8-week presale period.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Essentially, Shiba Memu&rsquo;s price increases daily at 6 pm GMT. This allows buyers to see investment increases for their tokens daily and have a meme vibe. At the end of the presale, investors will receive their tokens and be set for huge benefits as SHMU lists.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memus-presale-is-nearly-2-million-is-the-token-set-to-explode/">Shiba Memu&#8217;s presale is nearly $2 million. Is the token set to explode?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memus-presale-is-nearly-2-million-is-the-token-set-to-explode/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase gains approval to offer regulated crypto futures to US customers</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-gains-approval-to-offer-regulated-crypto-futures-to-us-customers/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-gains-approval-to-offer-regulated-crypto-futures-to-us-customers/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 11:30:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-gains-approval-to-offer-regulated-crypto-futures-to-us-customers/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways Coinbase has been cleared to offer regulated crypto futures to eligible US customers. Coinbase Advanced Trade users will have access to crypto futures in a few weeks. CFTC grants Coinbase permission to offer crypto futures The National Futures Association, a self-regulatory organization designated by the Commodity and Futures Trading Commission (CFTC), has granted [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-gains-approval-to-offer-regulated-crypto-futures-to-us-customers/">Coinbase gains approval to offer regulated crypto futures to US customers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Coinbase has been cleared to offer regulated crypto futures to eligible US customers.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Coinbase Advanced Trade users will have access to crypto futures in a few weeks.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr">CFTC grants Coinbase permission to offer crypto futures</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The National Futures Association, a self-regulatory organization designated by the Commodity and Futures Trading Commission (CFTC), has granted Coinbase the approval to offer eligible US customers access to crypto futures directly from its platforms.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>latest cryptocurrency news</u></a> comes despite Coinbase&rsquo;s ongoing legal battles with the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Coinbase Financial Markets CEO Andrew Sears stated that this latest development is key to unlocking growth and enabling broader participation in the crypto economy.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The cryptocurrency exchange filed an application with the NFA to register as an FCM nearly two years ago.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Following its application, Coinbase acquired CFTC-regulated futures exchange FairX and renamed it Coinbase Derivatives Exchange.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Coinbase Advanced Trade to gain access to crypto futures soon</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The cryptocurrency exchange revealed that users of Coinbase Advanced Trade will be the first to be granted access to the regulated crypto futures. The products will then become available to customers of the institutional-focused prime brokerage platform Coinbase Prime later afterwards.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Greg Tusar, Coinbase&rsquo;s head of institutional products, wrote in a company&nbsp;<a href="https://www.coinbase.com/blog/coinbase-financial-markets-inc-secures-fcm-approval-to-bring-regulated" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>blog post</u></a> that;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;Obtaining FCM approval was our next step in bringing these transparent and secure markets to our customers so they can access regulated futures contracts alongside our liquid spot market. In the coming months, we&rsquo;ll provide additional information on how our verified US customers can access our futures offering.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p dir="ltr">By offering regulated cryptocurrency futures, eligible users can be able to open long and short positions in the cryptocurrency market via Coinbase.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Coinbase Chief Policy Officer Faryar Shirzad believes that with the supervision of the CFTC and NFA, the cryptocurrency exchange can offer regulated futures that protect consumers and ensure that the United States remains the centre for digital innovation.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">This latest development came barely two days after Coinbase entered the Canadian market. The cryptocurrency exchange expanded its service into Canada with the&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-enters-the-canadian-market-with-coinbase-one-free-30-day-trial/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>launch of Coinbase One</u></a> in the North American country.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Coinbase also offered Canadians a free 30-day trial of Coinbase One as it looks to attract more customers to its platform.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-gains-approval-to-offer-regulated-crypto-futures-to-us-customers/">Coinbase gains approval to offer regulated crypto futures to US customers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-gains-approval-to-offer-regulated-crypto-futures-to-us-customers/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Volatility Shares aims to list its Ether Futures ETF on October 12</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/volatility-shares-aims-to-list-its-ether-futures-etf-on-october-12/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/volatility-shares-aims-to-list-its-ether-futures-etf-on-october-12/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 11:12:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/volatility-shares-aims-to-list-its-ether-futures-etf-on-october-12/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Volatility Shares plans to have its Ether Futures ETF (ETHU) open to investors on October 12.&#160; The company listed its 2x Bitcoin-linked ETF (BITX) in July. While all eyes remain on the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) with regard to the several spot Bitcoin ETF applications before it, market experts say the first Ethereum&#160;futures [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/volatility-shares-aims-to-list-its-ether-futures-etf-on-october-12/">Volatility Shares aims to list its Ether Futures ETF on October 12</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Volatility Shares plans to have its Ether Futures ETF (ETHU) open to investors on October 12.&nbsp;</li>
<li>The company listed its 2x Bitcoin-linked ETF (BITX) in July.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">While all eyes remain on the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) with regard to the several spot Bitcoin ETF applications before it, market experts say the first <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/">Ethereum</a>&nbsp;futures exchange-traded fund in the US is an equally massive development.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">First ETH Futures ETF for US market</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Volatility Shares, one of the leading ETF providers in the market, has indicated plans to list its Ether Strategy ETF on October 12, 2023. The product will trade under the ticker <a href="https://www.volatilityshares.com/ethu" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">ETHU</a>, offering the company&rsquo;s first Ether-linked ETF and come a few months after Volatility Shares&rsquo; 2x Bitcoin-linked ETF (BITX) that launched in July.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Eric Balchunas, a senior ETF analyst at Bloomberg, says Volatility Shares&rsquo;s positioning for the debut of the Ether ETF could see it beat rivals amid the race to be first to market with the highly anticipated product. &nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Even though the SEC hasn&rsquo;t pronounced itself on ETHU, Balchunas notes that the regulator &ldquo;looks to be ok&rdquo; with the proposal as there hasn&rsquo;t been any withdrawal. Also notable is the application date, which with the 75-day approval window, means the company is likely to be first to the market on October 12.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Nonetheless, the SEC may choose to group the filings and Volatility Shares are probably &ldquo;just pushing the envelope&rdquo; as they did with their BITX offering.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Well, there's been no withdrawals so SEC looks to be ok with them, but re the date, he did file first so he would normally go out first. but SEC may want to group them, he's prob just pushing the envolope like he did w BITX</p>
<p>&mdash; Eric Balchunas (@EricBalchunas) <a href="https://twitter.com/EricBalchunas/status/1691488090232172558?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 15, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">Stuart Barton, the CIO of Volatility Shares has indicated that the company is looking to have ETHU available to investors before they shift focus to the increasingly demanded-for spot ETF market.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The SEC has notably not approved any spot crypto ETF for the US, and the next big decision after a <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sec-delays-decision-on-ark-invest-spot-bitcoin-etf/">recent delay for the Ark spot Bitcoin ETF</a>, will be on Grayscale. With the 160-day window up on Tuesday, the <a href="https://twitter.com/EricBalchunas/status/1691467604630933504" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">expectation</a> is that this decision comes on Friday morning.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/volatility-shares-aims-to-list-its-ether-futures-etf-on-october-12/">Volatility Shares aims to list its Ether Futures ETF on October 12</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/volatility-shares-aims-to-list-its-ether-futures-etf-on-october-12/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>BNB Chain&#8217;s opBNB mainnet goes live for infrastructure providers</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bnb-chains-opbnb-mainnet-goes-live-for-infrastructure-providers/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/bnb-chains-opbnb-mainnet-goes-live-for-infrastructure-providers/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 10:10:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNB]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bnb-chains-opbnb-mainnet-goes-live-for-infrastructure-providers/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>opBNB mainnet has gone live for infrastructure providers a few days after Binance announced its deployment. The testnet for the layer-2 scaling solution built on the OP Stack took one and half months. BNB Chain has announced that its layer 2 scaling platform opBNB mainnet is now live for infrastructure providers, putting the EVM-compatible solution [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bnb-chains-opbnb-mainnet-goes-live-for-infrastructure-providers/">BNB Chain&#8217;s opBNB mainnet goes live for infrastructure providers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">opBNB mainnet has gone live for infrastructure providers a few days after Binance announced its deployment.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The testnet for the layer-2 scaling solution built on the OP Stack took one and half months.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">BNB Chain has <a href="https://twitter.com/BNBCHAIN/status/1691721686825980199" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">announced</a> that its layer 2 scaling platform opBNB mainnet is now live for infrastructure providers, putting the EVM-compatible solution on the path to the much anticipated public launch.</p>
<p dir="ltr">opBNB is built using the OP Stack and leverages Optimistic Rollups to allow for low gas fees, network stability and security. Its importance to the optimal performance of the BNB Chain ecosystem could be felt across gaming, decentralised exchanges (DEXs) and digital collectibles.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">opBNB mainnet launch</h2>
<p dir="ltr">opBNB&rsquo;s mainnet launch for infrastructure providers means the next step is a public launch, powering fresh adoption from developers and projects.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Today, opBNB mainnet opens up to Infrastructure providers &#128588;</p>
<p>Read our Path to Mainnet blog to find out more as we  get one step closer to the public opBNB mainnet launch.</p>
<p>Below, we've included several links for getting started!<a href="https://t.co/K2XHAU4NrH">https://t.co/K2XHAU4NrH</a></p>
<p>&mdash; BNB Chain (@BNBCHAIN) <a href="https://twitter.com/BNBCHAIN/status/1691721686825980199?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 16, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/binance/">Binance</a> released the opBNB testnet on June 19 and recently unveiled a promotion dubbed &ldquo;Odyssey&rdquo; as it revealed the imminent launch of the protocol&rsquo;s mainnet. That announcement came on August 10, with mainnet deployment scheduled for this month as BNB Chain prepared for a significant milestone that could revamp its position in the decentralised finance ecosystem.</p>
<p dir="ltr">On-chain transactions by the BNBChain community during the testnet surpassed 7 million, with a daily transaction range of 100-150K. &nbsp;A total of 435,972 unique wallet addresses connected to the network, Binance noted in a recent <a href="https://www.bnbchain.org/en/blog/opbnb-from-testnet-to-mainnet/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">post</a> highlighting opBNB&rsquo;s testnet performance.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The network also saw more than 6k daily active users and 40 dApps deployed on the testnet during the one-and-half months of testing.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">BNB price outlook</h2>
<p dir="ltr">BNB, the native cryptocurrency powering the BNB Chain ecosystem, was trading around $233 at the time of writing &ndash; down 2% in the past 24 hours and nearly 5% in the past week. Meanwhile, total value locked assets on the chain stood at $3.07 billion.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bnb-chains-opbnb-mainnet-goes-live-for-infrastructure-providers/">BNB Chain&#8217;s opBNB mainnet goes live for infrastructure providers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/bnb-chains-opbnb-mainnet-goes-live-for-infrastructure-providers/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Only 8% of people are familiar with Web3 &#8211; what has happened?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/only-8-of-people-are-familiar-with-web3-what-has-happened/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dan Ashmore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 09:31:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/only-8-of-people-are-familiar-with-web3-what-has-happened/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key Takeaways Google search interest in the metaverse is down 92% from its peak, highlighting the fall from grace for the concept 92% of respondents globally said that they have heard of crypto, but only 8% considered themselves to be very familiar with the concept of Web3 Web3 often has trouble defining exactly what it [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/only-8-of-people-are-familiar-with-web3-what-has-happened/">Only 8% of people are familiar with Web3 &#8211; what has happened?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2 dir="ltr">Key Takeaways</h2>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Google search interest in the metaverse is down 92% from its peak, highlighting the fall from grace for the concept</li>
<li dir="ltr">92% of respondents globally said that they have heard of crypto, but only 8% considered themselves to be very familiar with the concept of Web3</li>
<li dir="ltr">Web3 often has trouble defining exactly what it is, with abstract and shifting goals frequently changing with time</li>
<li dir="ltr">Collapse of token economy and pullback in wider crypto space has curtailed enthusiasm</li>
<li dir="ltr">Web3 is not the metaverse, but there are valuable lessons to be had for tokens with regard to lofty goals and abstract descriptions&nbsp;</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p dir="ltr">Lockdowns, stimulus packages, social distancing &ndash; the year 2021 could not seem more different when looking back on it today.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The same holds true within crypto. The year saw Bitcoin sail past $68,000, El Salvador declare the orange coin as legal tender, cartoon monkey pictures sold for millions of dollars, and a doggy token by the name of Dogecoin at a valuation of $88 billion.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Among the hysteria, a virtual world was touted more and more as the future. A future world where everybody could work, hang out and more, built on top of blockchain rails. They called it the &ldquo;metaverse&rdquo;. The only problem is, that clamour has become a whisper, as data for the search term &ldquo;metaverse&rdquo; on Google shows below, which is down 92% from its peak.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14727160">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<h2 dir="ltr">Web3 has also pulled back</h2>
<p dir="ltr">While the metaverse may be low hanging fruit to target, the more ubiquitous- and <em>somewhat</em> related &ndash; concept of Web3 has also struggled to maintain the excitement levels of the pandemic.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Despite lofty predictions that Web3 was on the verge of a parabolic rise, in a recent <a href="https://consensys.io/insight-report/web3-and-crypto-global-survey-2023"><u>survey</u></a> conducted by YouGov and Consensys, the results suggested this was nowhere near. While 92% of respondents globally said that they have heard of crypto, only 8% considered themselves to be very familiar with the concept of Web3.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">With so many aware of crypto yet so few familiar with what Web3 is, it may suggest two things. The first, quite simply, is that Web3 has had trouble catching on; the results not delivering on the lofty promises, the protocols struggling to deliver utility amid a declining crypto environment.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The second is a long-running criticism of Web3; namely, it has trouble defining exactly what it is, at least without venturing into an overly abstract realm.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Interestingly, the same survey indicated enthusiasm around solving problems which proponents of Web3 claim it aims to fix. For example:&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">79% want more control over their identity on the Internet</li>
<li dir="ltr">83% think data privacy is important</li>
<li dir="ltr">67% believe they should own the things they make&nbsp;</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p dir="ltr">For some enthusiasts, this may be optimistic, as it highlights interest in the problems which Web3 aims to solve and an inevitable target market. And yet, in another way, it sums up the exact problem. These issues are extremely broad and vague. In a survey, it is not surprising that the majority say that they believe they should own the things they make, or that data privacy is important.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Just because people are interested in these things does not necessarily mean that Web3 protocols built with the supposed goals of tackling these &ldquo;problems&rdquo; will succeed. As we have seen, once token prices fall, the climate shifts rapidly.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Facebook rebranding to Meta sums up struggles</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Perhaps there is no better way to sum up the popping of the bubble quite like Facebook&rsquo;s decision to rebrand as Meta. On last month&rsquo;s earnings call, CEO Mark Zuckerberg was forced to outline that the company&rsquo;s determination to focus on the metaverse remains intact.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;We remain fully committed to the Metaverse vision as well,&rdquo; Zuckerberg said. &ldquo;We&rsquo;ve been working on both of these two major priorities (AI and the metaverse) for many years in parallel now, and in many ways the two areas are overlapping and complementary.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Meta&rsquo;s metaverse ventures have hurt shareholders. Last year, its Reality Labs unit, in charge of the Metaverse project, lost $13.7 billion. The year before, a further $10.2 billion was lost.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;I can&rsquo;t guarantee you that I&rsquo;m going to be right about this bet. I do think that this is the direction that the world is going in,&rdquo; Zuckerberg added.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Thus far this year, Meta has performed strongly in conjunction with the bouceback in the tech sector. However, the rebound comes after the stock significantly underperformed the Nasdaq, with the underperformance widening after the company&rsquo;s Meta rebrand in October 2021 (not that it is necessarily indicative, but it is interesting all the same).&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14711094">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">Looking back, the timing of Meta&rsquo;s rebrand was unfortunate. Its public commitment to the metaverse and company name change came on October 28th 2021, only thirteen days before the Bitcoin price peak and the pinnacle of the COVID-driven crypto bonanza.</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14727474">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">Of course, the pertinent counterpoint of this is that Meta represents the exact antithesis of what many Web3 believers desire. A dominant big tech company with a questionable history and public image, to say the least. And besides, the metaverse is not Web3 &ndash; although this inability to define it in tangible and actionable terms is part of the issue.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Obviously, the entire crypto sector is hurting badly, not just metaverse and Web3 tokens. Bitcoin remains over 55% off its high. The macro environment has been problematic and risk assets have struggled across the board, with interest rates hiked north of 5% following so many years of treading water near zero.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In a more direct comparison, even interest in Bitcoin from the mainstream is down, with search volume for Bitcoin falling to <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/interest-in-bitcoin-down-to-two-year-low-google/"><u>two-year lows</u></a>. And yet the damage with regard to the metaverse has been worse. Looking at the coins classified as metaverse on CoinMarketCap, the top currencies are all down at least 84%, with an average 92% drop.</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14711173">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">It&rsquo;s been a rough ride for all of crypto. But for metaverse, it has nearly decimated the still-nascent concept. While the metaverse is not Web3, there are many tokens and projects leaning on the promises of the latter while creating nothing of genuine utility. For the projects still around in the space, examining the travails of metaverse coins could be a valuable lesson.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>If you use our data, then we would appreciate a link back to&nbsp;</em><a href="https://coinjournal.net"><em><u>https://coinjournal.net</u></em></a><em>. Crediting our work with a link helps us to keep providing you with data analysis research.</em></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Notes</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Consensys and YouGov survey <a href="https://consensys.io/insight-report/web3-and-crypto-global-survey-2023"><u>Link</u></a></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/only-8-of-people-are-familiar-with-web3-what-has-happened/">Only 8% of people are familiar with Web3 &#8211; what has happened?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>PayPal to halt crypto sales in U.K. from October 1st</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/paypal-to-halt-crypto-sales-uk-october-1st/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wajeeh Khan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 00:09:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FCA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[UK]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=149862</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>PayPal to pause crypto sales as it works to comply with new FCA rules. Crypto sales on its platform will likely be resumed in early 2024. PayPal is slated to launch its own stablecoin in the coming weeks. PayPal says its users in the United Kingdom will temporarily lose the ability to buy cryptocurrencies via [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/paypal-to-halt-crypto-sales-uk-october-1st/">PayPal to halt crypto sales in U.K. from October 1st</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>PayPal to pause crypto sales as it works to comply with new FCA rules.</li>
<li>Crypto sales on its platform will likely be resumed in early 2024.</li>
<li>PayPal is slated to launch its own stablecoin in the coming weeks.</li>
</ul>
<p>PayPal says its users in the United Kingdom will temporarily lose the ability to <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/buy/paypal/">buy cryptocurrencies</a> via its platform from October 1<sup>st</sup>.</p>
<h2>Why is PayPal pausing crypto sales?</h2>
<p>The Financial Conduct Authority has recently announced new rules that make it mandatory for crypto companies to institute &ldquo;<a href="https://www.fca.org.uk/news/press-releases/fca-introduces-tough-new-rules-marketing-cryptoassets" target="_blank" rel="noopener">clear risk warnings</a>&rdquo; as well as a 24-hour cooling-off period before they enable customers to put their money in crypto assets.</p>
<p>According to PayPal, it is &ldquo;deeply committed&rdquo; to complying with the said regulations and will, therefore, suspend crypto sales in U.K. for as long as it takes to make the required changes.</p>
<p>This announcement arrives only a day after the online payments company said Alex Chriss will replace Dan Schulman as its <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2023/08/14/paypal-announces-senior-intuit-exec-alex-chriss-as-new-ceo/?guccounter=1&amp;guce_referrer=aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuZ29vZ2xlLmNvbS8&amp;guce_referrer_sig=AQAAAL71G-j1S_KYOBzpQaWyFNTzFbwd9ZBt14tt5TN6LTgRaXAN64pl4nnSPc1FHVTgV0gULYav2AppCHvapn1vThmEhi0iIJZ3cg2SKR41q4hyb-6BYZXRyyLnhbGXjkmaaANxBJ1c7fEmUPFWQCA9i10cQ4C7No1m5stk7qR-LkjD" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Chief Executive</a> on September 27<sup>th</sup>. Its shares have lost about 20% month-to-date.</p>
<h2>When will PayPal resume crypto sales?</h2>
<p>PayPal was not specific in divulging when is it likely to resume crypto sales on its platform. What it told customers in a <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/15rpswj/paypal_is_stopping_crypto_until_2024/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">message</a> today was only that they will be re-enabled in early 2024.</p>
<p>So, it&rsquo;s fair to assume that the pause will remain in place for at least three months considering it starts on October 1<sup>st</sup>. During this time, though, users will be able to hold as well as sell their crypto assets on the platform, as per the digital payments giant.</p>
<p>Note that PayPal is slated to launch PYUSD in the coming weeks. PayPal USD &ndash; its own stablecoin will be issued by Paxos Trust Company and its value will be pegged to the U.S. dollar (<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/paypal-launches-a-us-dollar-stablecoin-on-the-ethereum-blockchain/">find out more).</a></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/paypal-to-halt-crypto-sales-uk-october-1st/">PayPal to halt crypto sales in U.K. from October 1st</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sports betting revenue is soaring as Chancer sale nears $1.4M</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/sports-betting-revenue-is-soaring-as-chancer-sale-nears-1-4m/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/sports-betting-revenue-is-soaring-as-chancer-sale-nears-1-4m/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 20:12:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/sports-betting-revenue-is-soaring-as-chancer-sale-nears-1-4m/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Sports betting and gambling companies published strong financial results. Chancer token has raised almost $1.4 million in the past few weeks. Sports betting and gambling revenue jumped in the first half of the year as demand for the services rose. Recently released financial results by companies like Penn National, Entain, and Flutter Entertainment. At the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sports-betting-revenue-is-soaring-as-chancer-sale-nears-1-4m/">Sports betting revenue is soaring as Chancer sale nears $1.4M</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Sports betting and gambling companies published strong financial results.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Chancer token has raised almost $1.4 million in the past few weeks.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Sports betting and gambling revenue jumped in the first half of the year as demand for the services rose. Recently released financial results by companies like Penn National, Entain, and Flutter Entertainment. At the same time,&nbsp;<a href="https://chancer.com/"><u>Chancer</u></a>, an upcoming betting platform that uses the&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/blockchain/"><u>blockchain</u></a> technology, has raised almost $1.4 million in the past few weeks.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Betting revenue is soaring</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Publicly-traded companies in the sports betting and gambling companies have published strong financial results in the past few weeks. Flutter Entertainment, the parent company of Fanduel, PokerStars, Paddy Power, Sisal, and Betfair, said that its revenue jumped by 42% in the first half of the year. It made over 4.8 billion in revenue as the number of users soared by 28%. In his statement, the head of Flutter&nbsp;<a href="https://www.flutter.com/media/an0n5qzm/flutter-2023-interim-financial-statement-final.pdf"><u>said</u></a>:</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;We acquired over two million new players in the period, cemented our leadership position in sports and grew our share in iGaming to 23%. The US business was profitable in the first half with FanDuel generating over $100m in EBITDA.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Similarly, Entain had a strong performance, offset by a huge fine in Turkey. Its revenue jumped by 19% in the first half of the year. Most of this growth came from the United States, where the company owns several brands. Its gaming revenue rose by 22%.</p>
<p dir="ltr">DraftKings, one of the leading players in the industry also recorded strong results as the company nears profitability. Its revenue jumped to over $874 million in Q2 and EBITDA coming in a positive territory. &nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Other companies in the sector like Penn National, 888 Holdings, and Churchill Downs have all reported strong financial results. As a result, most of these stocks have jumped by more than 20% this year. Entain has underperformed because of the company&rsquo;s legal issues.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Chancer is set to thrive</h2>
<p dir="ltr">All these numbers mean that Chancer is set to thrive when its product launches later this year. For starters, Chancer is a company that is building a unique beting platform where people from around the world can participate.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Its global nature is enabled by the company&rsquo;s use of blockchain technology. $CHANCER, its crypto token, will help to facilitate payments in its ecosystem. Also, holders will be able to create their market, live stream them, and then make money when people place bets on them.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Also, $CHANCER holders will take part in the network&rsquo;s governance, where they will be able to vote on key issues. As owners of the platform, they will receive a share of the profits that the network generates. All these features are different from traditional companies that are managed centrally. You can buy the Chancer token&nbsp;<a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news"><u>here</u></a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">While Chancer token has more room to grow, investors should always do their own research before investing.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sports-betting-revenue-is-soaring-as-chancer-sale-nears-1-4m/">Sports betting revenue is soaring as Chancer sale nears $1.4M</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/sports-betting-revenue-is-soaring-as-chancer-sale-nears-1-4m/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
