<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 14:37:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Home Depot’s Q2 2023 Earnings Surpass Expectations amid Sales Dip</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/home-depot-q2-2023-earnings/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/home-depot-q2-2023-earnings/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 14:37:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wall Street]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[home depot]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[home depot stock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[s&p 500]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267042</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/home-depot-q2-2023-earnings/">Home Depot&#8217;s Q2 2023 Earnings Surpass Expectations amid Sales Dip</a></p>
<p>Despite the favorable revenue surprise, Home Depot saw a moderated fiscal year earnings projection implying that the corporation remains cautious about the road ahead. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/home-depot-q2-2023-earnings/">Home Depot&#8217;s Q2 2023 Earnings Surpass Expectations amid Sales Dip</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/home-depot-q2-2023-earnings/">Home Depot&#8217;s Q2 2023 Earnings Surpass Expectations amid Sales Dip</a></p>
<p>American retail giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/home-depot/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Home Depot</a> (NYSE: HD) has once again demonstrated its financial resilience by surpassing Wall Street’s expectations for its Q2 2023 earnings. Despite a slight dip of 2% year-over-year sales, the company reported impressive results, reaffirming its position as a competitive player in the retail sector.</p>
<h2>Home Depot Beats Q2 2023 Earnings Expectation</h2>
<p>For the three-month period ending July 30, Home Depot <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/08/15/home-depot-hd-earnings-q2-2023.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reported</a> earnings per share of $4.65, outperforming the analysts’ consensus estimate of $4.45 per share. In addition, the company recorded revenue of $42.92 billion for the second quarter exceeding Wall Street&#8217;s projection of $42.23 billion.</p>
<p>Furthermore, Home Depot recorded a net income of $4.66 billion for the fiscal second quarter, translating to $4.65 per share. These figures represent a decline from last year’s results of $5.17 billion in net income and $5.05 per share.</p>
<p>While the decrease in net income and earnings per share might raise concerns, Home Depot’s recent financial report showcased a notable <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/home-depot-fiscal-q4-2022/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reversal</a> of fortune, as the company exceeded Wall Street&#8217;s revenue projections for the first time in three quarters.</p>
<p>The unexpected surge highlights Home Depot&#8217;s resilience in the face of economic challenges, reflecting its adaptability and responsiveness to evolving market dynamics.</p>
<h2>Navigating with Caution</h2>
<p>Despite the favorable revenue surprise, Home Depot saw a moderated fiscal year earnings projection implying that the corporation remains cautious about the road ahead. The retailer reiterated its forecast for sales and comparable sales to decline within a range of 2% to 5% when compared to the same period in the previous year.</p>
<p>Home Depot&#8217;s Chief Financial Officer, Richard McPhail, stated that consumer behavior remains cautious, particularly in terms of larger-ticket and discretionary purchasing. He mentioned that some homeowners made large purchases during the pandemic, while others are deferring such purchases because of rising interest rates.</p>
<p>McPhail also noted that some pandemic-induced dynamics are gradually reversing. Transportation expenses have decreased, and vendors are less likely to request price increases.</p>
<p>Home Depot’s challenges are compounded by a weakening housing market, which can impact home improvement spending. Additionally, the shift in consumer preferences towards spending more on services than goods is affecting the company’s performance.</p>
<p>The company is responding to these changing dynamics by adjusting its pricing strategies. McPhail explained that Home Depot is currently experiencing a period of “price settling,” characterized by adjustments to retail prices, including instances of lowering prices in various categories.</p>
<p>Addressing concerns about inflation, McPhail assured that the company does not anticipate significant inflation in the latter half of the year. He highlighted the typical Home Depot customer remains financially stable, partially due to substantial home equity gains during the pandemic.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the company’s shares have experienced a 4% increase year-to-date, which lags behind the broader <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-the-sp-500-index/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">S&amp;P 500</a>&#8216;s nearly 17% gain over the same period. As of Monday’s close, the company&#8217;s shares were trading at $329.95, a slight decline of less than 1%.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jacobi-europe-first-bitcoin-etf/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/home-depot-q2-2023-earnings/">Home Depot&#8217;s Q2 2023 Earnings Surpass Expectations amid Sales Dip</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/home-depot-q2-2023-earnings/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Jacobi Asset Management Makes History with Europe’s First Bitcoin ETF Listing</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/jacobi-europe-first-bitcoin-etf/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/jacobi-europe-first-bitcoin-etf/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 14:18:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funds & ETFs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blackrock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jacobi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267039</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jacobi-europe-first-bitcoin-etf/">Jacobi Asset Management Makes History with Europe&#8217;s First Bitcoin ETF Listing</a></p>
<p>The Jacobi FT Wilshere Bitcoin ETF listing marks a significant achievement for the firm and the broader European crypto investment landscape.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jacobi-europe-first-bitcoin-etf/">Jacobi Asset Management Makes History with Europe&#8217;s First Bitcoin ETF Listing</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jacobi-europe-first-bitcoin-etf/">Jacobi Asset Management Makes History with Europe&#8217;s First Bitcoin ETF Listing</a></p>
<p>Europe&#8217;s financial landscape is undergoing a significant change as Jacobi Asset Management company lists its first spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-an-exchange-traded-fund-etf/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ETF</a>) on Euronext, a stock exchange platform based in Amsterdam. The move comes two years after the investment vehicle was approved by the Guernsey Financial Services Commission (GFSC) in October 2021. The fund, named the Jacobi FT Wilshere Bitcoin ETF, was initially planned for release last year. But the company turned back on the plans due to the market conditions and other negative news in the industry, including the catastrophic collapse of the Terra (LUNA) blockchain and the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a> fiasco.</p>
<p>After months of postponement, Jacobi finally announced on August 15 that the Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a>) spot ETF is now available for trading on the stock exchange. The investment fund will be traded on Euronext under the ticker BCOIN. Investors are charged a 1.5% annual management fee.</p>
<h2>Europe Beats the US with the Launch of BCOIN</h2>
<p>According to the official <a href="https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20230815404630/en" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">press release</a>, Fidelity Digital Assets, a subsidiary of the famous financial services company Fidelity Investments, will become the custodian of BCOIN. Similarly, Flow Traders has been authorized to serve as the official market maker for the fund, while Jane Street and DRW will serve as participants.</p>
<p>Regarding the fund&#8217;s benchmark, the FT Wilshire Bitcoin Blended Price Index, Jacobi said that Wilshire Indexes would provide the services with the REC solution created in collaboration with the digital asset platform Zumo.</p>
<p>With the listing of this investment vehicle in Amsterdam, Europe, the continent has emerged as the first region to introduce BTC investing opportunities for traditional corporate investors, beating the US and Asia.</p>
<p>&#8220;It is exciting to see Europe moving ahead of the US in opening up Bitcoin investing for institutional investors who want safe, secure access to the benefits of digital assets using familiar and regulated structures like our ETF,&#8221; said Martin Bednall, CEO of Jacobi Asset Management.</p>
<p>Despite multiple applications <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-sec-spot-bitcoin-etf-applications/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">submitted</a> to the US Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) over the years, none have been approved. Nonetheless, the tide may be shifting, with industry heavyweights like <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/blackrock/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BlackRock</a> leading new applications designed to address concerns related to market manipulation.</p>
<h2>First Decarbonized Digital Asset Fund</h2>
<p>The Jacobi FT Wilshere Bitcoin ETF listing marks a significant achievement for the firm and the broader European crypto investment landscape. In a departure from exchange-traded notes (ETNs), this ETF introduces a fresh approach, offering investors direct ownership without the complexities associated with debt securities.</p>
<p>&#8220;Unlike other products in the European market, which are debt instruments, our fund owns the underlying asset directly. Jacobi is proud to be supported by Tier1 partners at the forefront of this digital asset market evolution while pioneering an innovative, environmentally sound solution for European investors,&#8221; Bednall continued.</p>
<p>The fund goes beyond technological innovation – it embraces sustainability. Aligned with Article 8 of the European Sustainable Finance Disclosure Regulation (SFDR), the ETF is hailed as the first decarbonized digital asset fund. The partnership with digital asset platform Zumo facilitates the integration of a Renewable Energy Certificate (REC) solution, ensuring institutional investors align with Environmental, Social, and Governance (ESG) objectives while participating in Bitcoin transactions.</p>
<p>As digital assets carve out a place within traditional finance, Jacobi&#8217;s debut as Europe&#8217;s first Bitcoin ETF showcases the region&#8217;s pioneering spirit in seizing transformative opportunities. By ushering in transparency, direct ownership, and sustainability considerations, the ETF marks a significant stride toward integrating digital assets into the heart of conventional financial systems.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tencent-music-q2-2023-revenue/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jacobi-europe-first-bitcoin-etf/">Jacobi Asset Management Makes History with Europe&#8217;s First Bitcoin ETF Listing</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/jacobi-europe-first-bitcoin-etf/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tencent Music Reports Surge in Q2 2023 Revenue as More Chinese Users Pay</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tencent-music-q2-2023-revenue/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tencent-music-q2-2023-revenue/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 12:01:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tencent music]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267009</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tencent-music-q2-2023-revenue/">Tencent Music Reports Surge in Q2 2023 Revenue as More Chinese Users Pay</a></p>
<p>Tencent Music entertainment noted that users are more willing to pay for the premium features. In Q2, the company registered 20% surge in the total paying users for its online music streaming service. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tencent-music-q2-2023-revenue/">Tencent Music Reports Surge in Q2 2023 Revenue as More Chinese Users Pay</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tencent-music-q2-2023-revenue/">Tencent Music Reports Surge in Q2 2023 Revenue as More Chinese Users Pay</a></p>
<p>On Monday, August 15, Tencent Music Entertainment Group, China&#8217;s leading online music and entertainment platform, reported a surge in revenue for Q2 2023. The company&#8217;s total revenue, which stood at RMB7.29 billion (US$1.01 billion), surged by 5.5% from a year ago.</p>
<h2>Tencent Music in Q2 2023</h2>
<p>This growth specifically comes from the growth in the paying users on its Spotify-like music-streaming platform as well as the recovery in the advertising market. Following a period of cautious expenditure, businesses are beginning to witness a recovery, driven by indications of decreasing inflation and an improving consumer outlook for the remainder of the year.</p>
<p>Revenues from the music subscription represented a 37.2% year-over-year growth. The count of active paying users rose to 99.4 million, marking a 20.2% increase compared to the previous year and a growth of 5.0 million users from the previous quarter. Mr. Cussion Pang, Executive Chairman of Tencent Music Entertainment <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/tencent-music-entertainment-group-announces-second-quarter-2023-unaudited-financial-results-301900506.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">noted</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We are pleased to report a solid second quarter, supported by the continued strong growth of our online music services. As we continue driving the healthy development of China&#8217;s online music industry, we have seen users become increasingly accustomed and willing to pay for copyrighted music, whether for songs they want to listen to or for premium listening features they enjoy. This trend is evidenced by the all-time high paying ratio and ARPPU recorded by our online music services in the reported quarter. Such achievements led to revenues from online music services exceeding that of social entertainment services for the first time in our Company&#8217;s history. This marks a significant step along TME&#8217;s growth trajectory.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>TME Plans Further Expansion</h2>
<p>The company has been increasing its original content offerings to draw in more users and counter competition from platforms like Cloud Music owned by NetEase and ByteDance&#8217;s Douyin, a short-video sharing platform.</p>
<p>Mr. Cussion Pang, the Executive Chairman of TME, has stated that the company has initiated several service enhancement and risk control measures since the latter part of the second quarter of 2023. These measures aim at fostering a more music-centric live-streaming atmosphere.</p>
<p>While these actions are expected to exert pressure on revenues from social entertainment services in the latter half of 2023, potentially impacting total revenues for the year, Mr. Pang believes that these measures will ultimately lead to an optimized user experience and contribute to the company&#8217;s long-term business development.</p>
<p>Read other <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/business/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">business news</a> on Coinspeaker.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ev-vinfast-nasdaq-spac/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tencent-music-q2-2023-revenue/">Tencent Music Reports Surge in Q2 2023 Revenue as More Chinese Users Pay</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tencent-music-q2-2023-revenue/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>EV Maker VinFast to Debut on Nasdaq Following SPAC Merger</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ev-vinfast-nasdaq-spac/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ev-vinfast-nasdaq-spac/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 11:56:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[IPO News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Transportation News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wall Street]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Black Spade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[spac]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vinfast]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267004</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ev-vinfast-nasdaq-spac/">EV Maker VinFast to Debut on Nasdaq Following SPAC Merger</a></p>
<p>In the heart of the rapidly evolving EV market in the United States, the Vietnamese automaker is confidently carving out its niche. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ev-vinfast-nasdaq-spac/">EV Maker VinFast to Debut on Nasdaq Following SPAC Merger</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ev-vinfast-nasdaq-spac/">EV Maker VinFast to Debut on Nasdaq Following SPAC Merger</a></p>
<p>Vietnamese Electric Vehicle (EV) manufacturer, VinFast is set to debut on the tech-focused <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-the-nasdaq-composite-index/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Nasdaq Composite</a> (INDEXNASDAQ: .IXIC) this morning in New York. This significant step follows the successful completion of its merger with the US-listed Special Purpose Acquisition Company (SPAC), Black Spade.</p>
<p>CEO Le Thi Thu Thuy articulated the magnitude of VinFast’s achievement in a recent <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/08/15/vinfast-completes-spac-merger-set-to-start-trading-on-nasdaq.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a>, stating:</p>
<blockquote><p>“It&#8217;s a big milestone for us to be listed in the US. The listing is going to open access to the capital markets for us in the future.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>VinFast’s Journey to Nasdaq</h2>
<p>VinFast&#8217;s journey to Nasdaq is a remarkable tale of ambition, innovation, and the convergence of global markets. Founded in 2017 as part of the Vingroup conglomerate, VinFast&#8217;s mission was to put Vietnam on the map as a serious contender in the automotive industry, focusing initially on traditional gasoline vehicles.</p>
<p>However, it did not take long for the company to pivot towards EVs, recognizing the critical role they play in addressing environmental concerns and the global shift toward sustainable transportation.</p>
<p>By 2021, VinFast had not only produced a line of electric automobiles but also electric buses and scooters, demonstrating its versatility and commitment to green mobility. This daring path caught the interest of investors, setting the road for its historic merger with Black Spade Acquisition.</p>
<p>The allure of SPACs lies in their ability to expedite <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-initial-public-offering-ipo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Initial Public Offering</a> (IPO) processes, offering companies like VinFast an efficient way to access capital markets. VinFast stated in a recent joint statement that its merger with Black Spade is valued at approximately $23 billion.</p>
<p>The merger not only elevated VinFast’s financial position but also integrated Black Spade as a wholly-owned subsidiary of the EV maker. Consequently, Black Spade is anticipated to delist from the New York Stock Exchange, streamlining VinFast’s presence on Nasdaq.</p>
<h2>VinFast Displays Competitive Edge in the US EV Market</h2>
<p>In the heart of the rapidly evolving EV market in the United States, the Vietnamese automaker is confidently carving out its niche.</p>
<p>Faced with giants such as <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/tesla/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tesla Inc</a> (NASDAQ: TSLA) and BYD VinFast’s CEO <a href="https://vinfastauto.us/newsroom/press-release/vinfast-and-black-spade-acquisition-co-complete-business-combination" target="_blank" rel="noopener">highlighted</a> the company’s strategy, which includes “offering premium quality products at affordable pricing with excellent after-sales service”. This strategy is the foundation of the company’s success, allowing it to present its goods as high-quality alternatives to other market competitors.</p>
<p>A notable example of VinFast’s pricing strategy is evident in its 5-seater VF 8 model, starting from $46,000, closely competing with the basic Tesla 5-seater Model Y priced from $47,740.</p>
<p>While Tesla benefits from federal tax credits for its vehicles, VinFast&#8217;s vehicles currently do not qualify for these incentives as they are not manufactured in the US. Notably, VinFast is constructing a manufacturing facility in North Carolina in order to <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/vinfast-us-ipo-expansion/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">enhance</a> its foothold in the US.</p>
<p>With a projected annual capacity of up to 150,000 vehicles, the factory is poised to become a crucial asset in VinFast’s expansion strategy.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/singapore-regulatory-framework-stablecoins/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ev-vinfast-nasdaq-spac/">EV Maker VinFast to Debut on Nasdaq Following SPAC Merger</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ev-vinfast-nasdaq-spac/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Singapore Unveils Comprehensive Regulatory Framework for Stablecoins</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/singapore-regulatory-framework-stablecoins/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/singapore-regulatory-framework-stablecoins/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 11:40:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mas]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267010</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/singapore-regulatory-framework-stablecoins/">Singapore Unveils Comprehensive Regulatory Framework for Stablecoins</a></p>
<p>MAS said that only stablecoin issuers meeting the requirements of the newly introduced guidelines would only be considered for regulation. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/singapore-regulatory-framework-stablecoins/">Singapore Unveils Comprehensive Regulatory Framework for Stablecoins</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/singapore-regulatory-framework-stablecoins/">Singapore Unveils Comprehensive Regulatory Framework for Stablecoins</a></p>
<p>Singapore, a global financial hub known for its innovative approach to technology and finance, has taken a decisive step in shaping the future of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/stablecoins-how-manage-operate/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">stablecoins</a> within its jurisdiction. The Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS) has introduced a detailed regulatory framework designed to ensure stability and security in issuing and operating single-currency stablecoins (SCS) around the city-state.</p>
<p>According to the <a href="https://www.mas.gov.sg/news/media-releases/2023/mas-finalises-stablecoin-regulatory-framework" target="_blank" rel="noopener">announcement</a> on August 15, the newly introduced regulatory framework comes after extensive consultations and assessments, reflecting the country&#8217;s commitment to responsible innovation in the ever-evolving world of cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>Under these guidelines, stablecoins pegged 1:1 to the value of the Singapore dollar or any other G10 currency, such as the United States dollar, the European euro, and the British pound, when issued within Singapore, fall under the regulatory purview of MAS. However, MAS explained that the regulation is subject to currencies with a total circulation of over 5 million Singapore dollars ($3.7 million).</p>
<h2>Monetary Authority of Singapore Outlines Three-Day Transfer Window for SCS Stablecoins</h2>
<p>According to MAS, non-bank issuers of stablecoins exceeding S$5 million in circulation will be subject to these regulations, with such stablecoins designated as MAS-regulated stablecoins. While the framework will require legislative amendments for full enforcement, its introduction showcases the authority&#8217;s proactive approach to fostering responsible financial innovation.</p>
<p>The central bank authorities emphasized the importance of maintaining value stability for stablecoins. Reserves backing SCS are subject to stringent requirements pertaining to composition, valuation, custody, and audit. This ensures a high level of assurance regarding the stability of these tokens. Furthermore, the financial authorities have outlined three business days as the transfer window for moving SCS tokens, despite suggestions for a more robust time frame.</p>
<p>The authorities said that companies creating stablecoins must maintain a minimum base of capital and liquid assets, reducing the risk of insolvency and enabling a controlled business wind-down if necessary.</p>
<p>MAS also said in the announcement that only stablecoin issuers meeting the requirements of the newly introduced guidelines would only be considered for regulation.</p>
<p>&#8220;Only stablecoin issuers that fulfill all requirements under the framework can apply to MAS for their stablecoins to be recognized and labeled as &#8216;MAS-regulated stablecoin&#8217; This label will enable users to readily distinguish MAS-regulated stablecoins from other digital payment tokens, including &#8216;stablecoins&#8217; which are not subject to MAS&#8217; stablecoin regulatory framework,&#8221; MAS said in the announcement.</p>
<h2>Stablecoin Issuers Are Mandated to Full Disclosure</h2>
<p>Another aspect of the stablecoin guidelines includes full transparency. MAS said the newly introduced framework also requires issuers to promptly return the par value of stablecoins to holders within five business days of a redemption request.</p>
<p>Additionally, the financial regulator said that stablecoin creators in Singapore are mandated to provide users with comprehensive disclosures, including information about the value stabilizing mechanism, rights of stablecoin holders, and the results of reserve asset audits.</p>
<p>Ms. Ho Hern Shin, the deputy director at MAS, believes that stablecoins are a credible digital medium of exchange and potentially serve as a bridge between the traditional finance ecosystem and the emerging economy. The MAS director also encouraged issuers to start making early preparations for compliance.</p>
<p>&#8220;We encourage SCS issuers who would like their stablecoins recognized as &#8216;MAS regulated stablecoins&#8217; to make early preparations for compliance,&#8221; Shin said.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/prime-trust-bankruptcy-protection/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/singapore-regulatory-framework-stablecoins/">Singapore Unveils Comprehensive Regulatory Framework for Stablecoins</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/singapore-regulatory-framework-stablecoins/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Prime Trust Files for Bankruptcy Protection amidst Financial Struggles</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/prime-trust-bankruptcy-protection/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/prime-trust-bankruptcy-protection/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 11:33:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banq]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitgo]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[celsius]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[celsius network]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[prime trust]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266966</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/prime-trust-bankruptcy-protection/">Prime Trust Files for Bankruptcy Protection amidst Financial Struggles</a></p>
<p>Prime Trust announced its intention to present a series of motions to the court.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/prime-trust-bankruptcy-protection/">Prime Trust Files for Bankruptcy Protection amidst Financial Struggles</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/prime-trust-bankruptcy-protection/">Prime Trust Files for Bankruptcy Protection amidst Financial Struggles</a></p>
<p>Prime Trust, a crypto custodian company based in the United States, has officially <a href="https://cases.stretto.com/public/X274/12452/PLEADINGS/1245208152380000000024.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">filed</a> for Chapter 11 bankruptcy protection due to its financial challenges. The filing was made in Delaware on August 15, with the company citing a significant shortfall in customer funds as the primary reason behind its drastic decision.</p>
<p>The latest filing comes a few weeks after the company&#8217;s subsidiary Banq filed for separate <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/banq-chapter-11-bankruptcy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">bankruptcy</a> protection at the United States Bankruptcy Court in Nevada in June. Its parent company Prime Trust has followed in its footsteps, seeking Chapter 11 protection.</p>
<p>The bankruptcy filing revealed the company&#8217;s complex financial situation, estimating its liabilities to fall within $100 million to $500 million. The figure far outweighed its estimated assets worth between $50 million and $100 million. The company&#8217;s dire circumstances have compelled it to take action to address these financial discrepancies.</p>
<h2>$105M to Be Paid to Unsecured Creditors</h2>
<p>In a <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/prime-trust-llc-files-voluntary-010000180.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">press release</a> accompanying the filing, Prime Trust announced its intention to present a series of motions to the court. These motions aim to facilitate a comprehensive evaluation of strategic alternatives available to the company. Among these options is the potential sale of its assets and operations, which could help stabilize its financial standing.</p>
<p>Part of the motion also includes plans to continue paying employees wages without restricting their full benefits.</p>
<p>&#8220;It is anticipated that these motions will include requests to continue to pay wages and provide benefits to ongoing employees as usual,&#8221; Prime Trust said.</p>
<p>According to the court document, Prime Trust has between 25,000 and 50,000 creditors. This massive number of creditors highlights the wide-ranging impact of the company&#8217;s financial instability, affecting a substantial network of stakeholders.</p>
<p>In terms of creditors, the company&#8217;s top five unsecured creditors have asserted claims totaling around $105 million, with the largest single claim amounting to $55 million. The entities filing for Chapter 11 relief include Prime Core Technologies Inc., Prime Trust, LLC, Prime IRA LLC, and Prime Digital LLC.</p>
<h2>Genesis of Prime Trust&#8217;s Financial Woes</h2>
<p>Prime Trust&#8217;s financial woes started with crypto lender Celsius during the 2022 crypto winter, prompting the firm to shut down operations and subsequently initiate bankruptcy protection in a US court. According to reports, Prime Trust held up to $119 million of Celsius assets which it returned to the company after its business contract ended in 2021.</p>
<p>However, Celsius claimed that the company still held $17 million in crypto, which Prime Trust has refused to pay back. In August 2022, the bankrupt lender brought legal action against the Prime Trust to claw back the funds. The company <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-provider-prime-17m-celsius/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">agreed</a> to return the crypto assets two months after the suit.</p>
<p>Aside from Celsius, Prime Trust faced other challenges. Most notably, Nevada&#8217;s Department of Business and Industry regulators issued a cease and desist order against the company on June 21, citing its inability to honor the customer&#8217;s withdrawal request.</p>
<p>According to the regulators, the company&#8217;s financial condition has significantly deteriorated, causing Prime Trust to default on withdrawal requests.</p>
<p>Shortly after the cease and desist order, the regulator took legal action against the company, successfully placing Prime Trust into receivership on July 18. This decision was based on the substantial disparity between the company&#8217;s assets and liabilities, revealing a significant financial gap.</p>
<h2>BitGo Backs Out Acquisition Deal with Prime Trust</h2>
<p>Aside from Prime Trust&#8217;s issues with Nevada regulators, the company also faced challenges when its rival BitGo, which wanted to buy out the firm, suddenly changed its heart and backed out of the deal in June. The <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitgo-cancels-acquisition-prime-trust/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">termination</a> of the supposed acquisition deal further heightened the company&#8217;s financial challenges.</p>
<p>The Prime Trust situation was exacerbated by regulatory findings that the firm had improperly utilized customer funds to fulfill withdrawals. The misuse of the funds allegedly began in December 2021, further adding to the company&#8217;s financial strain.</p>
<p>While the bankruptcy filing aims to provide a platform for evaluating strategic alternatives, the litany of problems faced by Prime Trust over the past year may complicate the search for a suitable buyer.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/grayscale-bitcoin-spot-etf-week/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/prime-trust-bankruptcy-protection/">Prime Trust Files for Bankruptcy Protection amidst Financial Struggles</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/prime-trust-bankruptcy-protection/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Court Verdict on Grayscale Bitcoin Spot ETF Expected by End of This Week</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/grayscale-bitcoin-spot-etf-week/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/grayscale-bitcoin-spot-etf-week/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Babafemi Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 10:54:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funds & ETFs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[grayscale]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266975</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/grayscale-bitcoin-spot-etf-week/">Court Verdict on Grayscale Bitcoin Spot ETF Expected by End of This Week</a></p>
<p>Aside from the Grayscale Bitcoin Spot ETF, the SEC is also reviewing other Bitcoin ETF proposals.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/grayscale-bitcoin-spot-etf-week/">Court Verdict on Grayscale Bitcoin Spot ETF Expected by End of This Week</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/grayscale-bitcoin-spot-etf-week/">Court Verdict on Grayscale Bitcoin Spot ETF Expected by End of This Week</a></p>
<p>The US Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) is expected to announce its decision on the Grayscale Bitcoin Spot ETF this week, according to pundits.</p>
<p>The Grayscale Bitcoin Spot ETF was filed by Grayscale Investments, the largest digital currency asset manager, in 2016. The fund is a proposed exchange-traded fund (ETF) that would track the price of Bitcoin directly. The Grayscale Bitcoin Spot ETF would also convert the existing Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC), which holds over 636,000 Bitcoins (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a>), into an ETF.</p>
<p>In June 2022, the SEC rejected Grayscale’s application. In return, Grayscale sued the regulator for inconsistency in its treatment of investment vehicles. Several industry commentators including ARK Invest’s Cathie Wood believe Grayscale will win the lawsuit.</p>
<h2>History-Backed August</h2>
<p>According to Finance Lawyer Scott Johnsson, law clerks in US District Courts generally cycle out in August. Consequently, judges push to clear their workload before the change happens.</p>
<p>Additionally, Mr. Johnson <a href="https://twitter.com/SGJohnsson/status/1691178323399905280" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">pointed out</a> that 30 out of 32 cases in March of 2021 and 2022 were heard by United States District Courts within 160 days of oral testimony. Interestingly,  it has also been 160 days since Grayscale delivered its oral arguments in its suit against the SEC.</p>
<p>Bloomberg analyst James Seyffart also noted the decision could come as early as Aug. 15 according to his analysis.</p>
<h2>Grayscale Bitcoin Spot ETF Approval Could Spur Bitcoin Adoption</h2>
<p>If approved, the asset class would be the first of its kind in the US and could potentially boost the demand and adoption of Bitcoin among institutional and retail investors. This would eliminate the premium or discount that GBTC often trades at compared to the spot price of Bitcoin.</p>
<p>However, the approval is not guaranteed, as the SEC has repeatedly delayed or rejected previous Bitcoin ETF applications. The SEC has been known to cite concerns over market manipulation, fraud, and investor protection. The regulator is also skeptical about the reliability and transparency of the ‘unregulated’ Bitcoin spot market.</p>
<p>Aside from the Grayscale Bitcoin Spot ETF, the SEC is also reviewing other Bitcoin ETF proposals. VanEck, BlackRock, WisdomTree, Fidelity, and Valkyrie have all submitted proposals for their spot ETFs. Thus, the approval could also pave the way for those of the other companies. This is especially true because Grayscale has opined that the SEC should approve all Bitcoin spot ETF applications simultaneously to reduce first-mover advantage between applicants.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/morgan-stanley-nvidia-ai/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/grayscale-bitcoin-spot-etf-week/">Court Verdict on Grayscale Bitcoin Spot ETF Expected by End of This Week</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/grayscale-bitcoin-spot-etf-week/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Morgan Stanley: Nvidia to Benefit from ‘Massive Shift’ in AI, NVDA Stock Jumps 7%</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/morgan-stanley-nvidia-ai/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/morgan-stanley-nvidia-ai/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 10:39:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wall Street]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[morgan stanley]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nvda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nvda stock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nvidia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nvidia stock]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266978</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/morgan-stanley-nvidia-ai/">Morgan Stanley: Nvidia to Benefit from &#8216;Massive Shift&#8217; in AI, NVDA Stock Jumps 7%</a></p>
<p>Morgan Stanley analysts find a strong visibility for Nvidia for the next 3-4 quarters amid the AI boom. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/morgan-stanley-nvidia-ai/">Morgan Stanley: Nvidia to Benefit from &#8216;Massive Shift&#8217; in AI, NVDA Stock Jumps 7%</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/morgan-stanley-nvidia-ai/">Morgan Stanley: Nvidia to Benefit from &#8216;Massive Shift&#8217; in AI, NVDA Stock Jumps 7%</a></p>
<p>On Monday, August 14, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/nvidia/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Nvidia</a> (NASDAQ: NVDA) stock price gained by a straight 7% after banking giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/morgan-stanley/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Morgan Stanley</a> reported that the chip manufacturer would immensely benefit from the &#8216;massive shift&#8217; in artificial intelligence.</p>
<p>The company stands to benefit from the rapid developments in the generative AI space. Monday&#8217;s NVDA stock price surge suggests investors believe that Nvidia&#8217;s GPUs will be the most popular computer chips powering large language models (LLMs).</p>
<p>In their report on Monday, Morgan Stanley said that Nvidia continues to be their &#8220;Top Pick&#8221;. This bullishness comes following Nvidia&#8217;s earnings report which offers a better-than-expected forecast. The Morgan Stanley analysts <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/08/14/nvidia-shares-up-7percent-on-morgan-stanley-upgrade.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">wrote</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“We think the recent selloff is a good entry point, as despite supply constraints, we still expect a meaningful beat and raise quarter &#8211; and, more importantly, strong visibility over the next 3-4 quarters. Nvidia remains our Top Pick, with a backdrop of the massive shift in spending towards AI, and a fairly exceptional supply demand imbalance that should persist for the next several quarters.”</p></blockquote>
<div>
<h2 id="JTPWx" role="tablist" data-hveid="CBIQAA">Nvidia (NVDA) Stock Rally</h2>
<p>Nvidia (NASDAQ: NVDA) has been one of the best-performing stocks on Wall Street this year in 2023. Since the beginning of the year, the NVDA stock price is already up by a staggering 205% and is currently trading at $437.</p>
<p>The company has registered a massive rebound following the tech slump of 2022. In fact, the NVDA stock price is trading much higher than the peak of the 2021 bull run. As a result, the company has managed to join the trillion-dollar club in terms of its valuations.</p>
<p>Despite a slight decrease of over 10% in Nvidia&#8217;s stock this month, which is in part due to <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-stock-plunges-china/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">supply limitations</a> and ongoing worries about the overall economy and its potential recovery, the analysts at Morgan Stanley anticipate that Nvidia will gain advantages in the long term. The analysts wrote:</p>
<blockquote><p>“The bottom line is that this is a very positive situation, October numbers are entirely gated by supply, and the upper end of the buy side consensus has been reined in. We see numbers are going up at least enough that this stock will trade at P/Es more similar to the upper end of semis, with material upside still ahead.”</p></blockquote>
<p>The company is already <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-ai-chip-llms/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">working on new chips</a> that are set to cut the costs of running LLMs. At present, Nvidia holds a commanding position in the AI chips sector, commanding a market share exceeding 80%. This dominance can be attributed to their expertise in producing graphics processing units (GPUs), which have emerged as the preferred chips for significant AI models like OpenAI&#8217;s ChatGPT and Google&#8217;s Bard, both pivotal in generative AI software.</p>
</div>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-sec-protective-order/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/morgan-stanley-nvidia-ai/">Morgan Stanley: Nvidia to Benefit from &#8216;Massive Shift&#8217; in AI, NVDA Stock Jumps 7%</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/morgan-stanley-nvidia-ai/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Counters SEC’s Discovery Requests by Seeking Protective Order</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-sec-protective-order/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-sec-protective-order/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 10:29:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Binance News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cz]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[securities and exchange commission]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266957</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-sec-protective-order/">Binance Counters SEC&#8217;s Discovery Requests by Seeking Protective Order</a></p>
<p>SEC's requests have not been limited to the discovery of Binance's custody, security and availability of customer assets alone.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-sec-protective-order/">Binance Counters SEC&#8217;s Discovery Requests by Seeking Protective Order</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-sec-protective-order/">Binance Counters SEC&#8217;s Discovery Requests by Seeking Protective Order</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a> has filed for the court to grant it a protective order against the United States Securities and Exchange Commission. This follows after the financial regulator has made several attempts to lay its hands on all of Binance&#8217;s documents that may have anything to do with customer assets.</p>
<h2>Binance Takes Issues with SEC&#8217;s Multiple Requests</h2>
<p>According to the August 14 <a href="https://www.courtlistener.com/docket/67474542/95/securities-and-exchange-commission-v-binance-holdings-limited/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">filing</a>, Binance suggested that the regulator&#8217;s requests are more like undertaking a “fishing expedition”.</p>
<p>Recall that in June, Binance agreed to a Consent Order with the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>. This was after the regulator initially <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-freezing-binance-funds/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">attempted to freeze all of its assets</a>, citing concerns over the safety of customer funds.</p>
<p>The exchange now believes that, while it has worked tirelessly in line with that same order, the SEC may have misunderstood the essence of it in the first place. Part of the filing reads:</p>
<blockquote><p>“BAM has worked in good faith, but the SEC has been steadfast in its belief that the Consent Order gives it carte blanche to investigate every aspect of BAM’s asset custody practices without any discernible limitation whatsoever.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Binance also claims that since the June order, it has handed over information about customer assets to the SEC. And while the SEC is yet to find any evidence of misuse, the request still feels ‘inappropriate’ in that it has no bearing on the ongoing suit.</p>
<p>But the requests have not been limited to the discovery of Binance&#8217;s custody, security, and availability of customer assets alone. Binance claims that the SEC is also requesting all communications dating as far back as November 2022 for topics that seemingly have no relevance to customer assets.</p>
<p>And, lastly, the regulator is also asking the exchange to produce six of its employees, including CEO Changpeng Zhao (CZ), for deposition. Interestingly, Binance claims that it has offered the depositions of senior employees in positions that are directly associated with customer funds. However, so far, the SEC has appeared unimpressed about the offer.</p>
<p>Defending its top executives and the decision to produce other employees for the deposition, Binance says:</p>
<blockquote><p>“They do not have unique firsthand knowledge about the facts surrounding the security, custody, and transfer of customer assets.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>Details About the Protective Order</h2>
<p>Overall, there are three major things that Binance seeks to achieve with the protective order, if it&#8217;s granted. It hopes to limit the SEC to deposing four employees that would not include CZ or the exchange&#8217;s chief financial officer. The order would bar the SEC from asking questions beyond matters outside of the order. And, lastly, it would also stop requests for communications about things not related to customer assets.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hut-8-mining-q2-2023-earnings/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-sec-protective-order/">Binance Counters SEC&#8217;s Discovery Requests by Seeking Protective Order</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-sec-protective-order/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hut 8 Mining Corp Announces Disappointing Q2 2023 Earnings Results, HUT Shares Drop Over 4%</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/hut-8-mining-q2-2023-earnings/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/hut-8-mining-q2-2023-earnings/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 09:58:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hut 8]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hut 8 mining]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266965</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hut-8-mining-q2-2023-earnings/">Hut 8 Mining Corp Announces Disappointing Q2 2023 Earnings Results, HUT Shares Drop Over 4%</a></p>
<p>Hut 8 Mining reported a revenue of about $19.2 million in Q2, a significant decline from $43.8 million recorded in the same period last year, mainly caused by increased mining difficulty.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hut-8-mining-q2-2023-earnings/">Hut 8 Mining Corp Announces Disappointing Q2 2023 Earnings Results, HUT Shares Drop Over 4%</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hut-8-mining-q2-2023-earnings/">Hut 8 Mining Corp Announces Disappointing Q2 2023 Earnings Results, HUT Shares Drop Over 4%</a></p>
<p>Toronto, Canada-based Bitcoin mining and blockchain infrastructure company, Hut 8 Mining Corporation (NASDAQ: HUT) released its Q2 2023 financial results on Monday, August, 14. According to the announcement, the company experienced significant Bitcoin mining challenges, which reflected a sharp decline in total revenue. As a result, HUT shares closed Monday trading at $2.78, down 6.4 percent from the day’s opening price. However, HUT shares regained about 2.52 percent during the after-hours session to trade around $2.85.</p>
<p>The heightened demand for <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> and other digital assets amid mainstream adoption has significantly increased the number of crypto miners around the world, hence causing a sharp uptick in mining difficulty. According to the latest on-chain data, the Bitcoin network had a total hash rate of about 415.17 EH/sd thus a mining difficulty of about 52.39 T, with the halving event about 255 days away.</p>
<h2>Hut 8 Mining Q2 2023 Financial Highlights</h2>
<p>During the second quarter that ended on June 30, Hut 8 announced that it mined about 399 Bitcoins, which represented a decline of approximately 58 percent during the same period last year. The company noted the suspension of operation at its North Bay Facility, and ongoing electrical issues at its Drumheller facility significantly contributed to the decline in Bitcoin mined. Notably, the company announced that it sold about 396 of the 399 Bitcoin mined during the second quarter and received proceeds of about  $14.7 million.</p>
<p>Nonetheless, the company announced that it continues to push beyond its boundaries to ensure its long-term growth prospects. Moreover, mainstream adoption of Bitcoin by institutional investors is expected to take place in the coming years.</p>
<p>“We continued to build momentum toward closing our transaction with USBTC by progressing toward receiving regulatory approvals to proceed and improving our projected post-merger self-mining capacity to 7.5 EH/s,&#8221; said Jaime Leverton, CEO of Hut 8.</p>
<p>Notably, the company&#8217;s high-performance computing operations generated $4.2 million of primarily monthly recurring revenue during the second quarter compared to about $4.7 million in Q2 2022. During the three months that ended on June 30, Hut 8 announced that it installed a total hash rate of about 2.6 EH/s, excluding the company&#8217;s North Bay facility.</p>
<p>“While we continued to face mining challenges during the second quarter at Drumheller, which are reflected in decreased revenue and fewer Bitcoin mined, we were successful in strategically managing our costs,” <a href="https://www.newswire.ca/news-releases/hut-8-reports-operating-and-financial-results-for-q2-2023-847470762.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a> Shenif Visram, CFO of Hut 8.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-btc-volatility-drops-atl/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hut-8-mining-q2-2023-earnings/">Hut 8 Mining Corp Announces Disappointing Q2 2023 Earnings Results, HUT Shares Drop Over 4%</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/hut-8-mining-q2-2023-earnings/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4138 metric#misses=41 metric#hit-ratio=99.0 metric#bytes=1032166 metric#prefetches=190 metric#store-reads=19 metric#store-writes=2 metric#store-hits=196 metric#store-misses=2 metric#sql-queries=34 metric#ms-total=96.86 metric#ms-cache=4.32 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.2159 metric#ms-cache-ratio=4.5 -->