<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 21:13:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Binance announces exit from Canada</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-announces-exit-from-canada/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-announces-exit-from-canada/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 21:13:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Canada]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto regulation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-announces-exit-from-canada/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Binance says new guidance on stablecoins has made it untenable to continue operating in the country. New rules required exchanges to seek approval before allowing their customers to buy or deposit stablecoins. The exchange says it will continue to engage regulators even if it doesn&#8217;t agree with new guidance. Binance, the world&#8217;s largest crypto exchange [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-announces-exit-from-canada/">Binance announces exit from Canada</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Binance says new guidance on stablecoins has made it untenable to continue operating in the country.</li>
<li dir="ltr">New rules required exchanges to seek approval before allowing their customers to buy or deposit stablecoins.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The exchange says it will continue to engage regulators even if it doesn&rsquo;t agree with new guidance.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/binance/">Binance</a>, the world&rsquo;s largest crypto exchange by trading volume, has announced its exit from <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/canada/">Canada</a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The crypto platform revealed its move on Friday, noting that the decision was down to new guidelines that make the Canadian market &ldquo;no longer tenable&rdquo; for its operations.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>We had high hopes for the rest of the Canadian blockchain industry. Unfortunately, new guidance related to stablecoins and investor limits provided to crypto exchanges makes the Canada market no longer tenable for Binance at this time</em>,&rdquo; the exchange said in a<a href="https://twitter.com/binance/status/1657099651210969088" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">&nbsp;<u>tweeted</u></a> statement.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The crypto exchange giant said it had &ldquo;put off this decision as long as [it] could to explore other reasonable avenues to protect [its] Canadian users.&rdquo; However, it&rsquo;s joining other platforms to withdraw from the market after the latest regulatory move.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>While we do not agree with the new guidance, we hope to continue to engage with Canadian regulators aimed at a thoughtful, comprehensive regulatory framework</em>,&rdquo; Binance wrote.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">The question of regulatory clarity</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/binance/">Binance</a> is a major crypto industry player that has sought regulatory approval in most of the jurisdictions that it offers its services. It has also been one of the main advocates of more regulatory clarity across the globe.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">But its decision to exit Canada comes a few months after the Canadian Securities Administrators (CSA) outlined new guidance regarding stablecoins.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The February communication had asked crypto trading platforms operating in the country to seek approval before allowing customers to use stablecoins on their platforms. This included buying or depositing stablecoins, a requirement that meant further due diligence checks for exchanges amid the tightening regulatory scrutiny.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-announces-exit-from-canada/">Binance announces exit from Canada</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-announces-exit-from-canada/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>DigiToads utility sets itself apart from Shiba Inu and Pepe as meme coins demand grows</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/digitoads-utility-sets-itself-apart-from-shiba-inu-and-pepe-as-meme-coins-demand-grows/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 17:10:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/digitoads-utility-sets-itself-apart-from-shiba-inu-and-pepe-as-demand-in-meme-coins-grows/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Digitoads is currently in the presale stage. PEPE has been the talk of the town over the last couple of after it got listed by Binance. 2023 has seen newly launched meme coins register staggering price movements. Many analysts are calling 2023 the year of meme coins. The market has seen new meme coins surpass [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/digitoads-utility-sets-itself-apart-from-shiba-inu-and-pepe-as-meme-coins-demand-grows/">DigiToads utility sets itself apart from Shiba Inu and Pepe as meme coins demand grows</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Digitoads is currently in the presale stage.</li>
<li>PEPE has been the talk of the town over the last couple of after it got listed by Binance.</li>
<li>2023 has seen newly launched meme coins register staggering price movements.</li>
</ul>
<p>Many analysts are calling 2023 the year of meme coins. The market has seen new meme coins surpass popular meme tokens like <a href="https://coinjournal.net/shiba-inu/what-is-shiba-inu/">Shiba Inu (SHIB)</a> and Pepe (PEPE) in popularity and soaring to meteoric heights. </p>
<p>One of the new trending meme coins is DigiToads (TOADS), an Ethereum-based meme token that was launched earlier this year. The meme coin has garnered a lot of praise for its unique economic design where users can access multiple options to bring home passive income. Its community-centric approach paves the way for community members to play a key role in the platform&rsquo;s growth and development.</p>
<h2>DigiToads: A trendsetter in the meme coin sector</h2>
<p><a href="https://digitoads.me/cjl">DigiToads</a> has been developed by using a hybrid model that leverages the strength of different cryptocurrencies. So, with one single platform, you can stake NFTs, play Web 3.0 games, enter giveaways, bag prizes, crypto tokens as rewards, trade cryptocurrencies and participate in trading competitions.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The platform has developed a native token called TOADS which would facilitate all transactions and financial purposes on the network. Built on the ERC-20 protocol, the DigiToads team would maintain a store of 585 million TOADS tokens. Of the supply, around 69.2% of it would be set aside for presale and giving out rewards.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Another reason why DigiToads has been in the news is because of its presale process. Comprising 10 stages, DigiToads&rsquo; presale process has been a stellar success till now and its fifth stage &lsquo;Lillypad 5&rsquo; is currently in progress.&nbsp;</p>
<p>DigiToads balances gameplay, rewards, and the storyline to create an exciting Web 3.0 game that will have players hooked to it in minutes.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In the game, players will be facing each other in a Metaverse swamp and will try to bag the highest scores in the season. To defeat the enemy, players can seek help from digital creatures called &lsquo;DigiToad&rsquo; who have special abilities. Players can also secure training equipment, food, and potions for DigiToads. They will have to pay for both the items as well as the DigiToad using the TOADS tokens. Those interested can participate in the <a href="https://digitoads.me/cjl">DigiToads presale here</a>.</p>
<h2>Here&rsquo;s why analysts are bullish on Shiba Inu</h2>
<p>Shiba Inu is among the top cryptocurrencies that have managed to maintain their hold over the market despite being launched years back. The meme coin has rolled out a native token called SHIB which is the main crypto token on the network. It is based on memes inspired by a Japanese breed of dog.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Apart from SHIB, the Shiba Inu team has also launched two other cryptocurrencies &ndash; BONE and LEASH. While <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bone/">BONE&nbsp;</a>is a governance token that helps Shiba Inu community members to participate in the decision-making process, LEASH is an exclusive token for dedicated community members who have been associated with the platform.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Given its popularity, analysts feel that the SHIB token might soar higher in 2023 and they expect it to stay in the bullish zone for now.</p>
<h2>PEPE is likely to make further gains</h2>
<p>PEPE is inspired by the popular internet cartoon &lsquo;Pepe, the Frog&rsquo; and its native token is PEPE. It is the medium of exchange on the network and has a deflationary model, which means its supply is intentionally kept low to curb fluctuating prices.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Another key advantage associated with Pepe is that token holders don&rsquo;t have to pay any transaction fee. The &lsquo;no tax&rsquo; policy has helped it ramp up its reach. As per market trends, the meme coin has witnessed a lot of ups and downs over the past few weeks.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Analysts expect the PEPE token to register another bullish rally as a sizable number of whales are still sitting in big positions.</p>
<h2>Conclusion&nbsp;</h2>
<p>Going by the fact that meme coins like Shiba Inu and PEPE have demonstrated their ability to drive gains in the market, analysts believe DigiToads will also perform well over the long term.&nbsp;</p>
<p>DigiToads&rsquo; dynamic economic framework and multiple utilities can help a community member diversify a portfolio while building a sustained source of passive income.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/digitoads-utility-sets-itself-apart-from-shiba-inu-and-pepe-as-meme-coins-demand-grows/">DigiToads utility sets itself apart from Shiba Inu and Pepe as meme coins demand grows</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Texas adds digital currency to the state&#8217;s Bill of Rights</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/texas-adds-digital-currency-to-the-states-bill-of-rights/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/texas-adds-digital-currency-to-the-states-bill-of-rights/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 15:08:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital currencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US regulation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/texas-adds-digital-currency-to-the-states-bill-of-rights/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Texas lawmakers vote to add digital currency to the state&#8217;s Bill of Rights. The move grants citizens the right to possess, retain and utilize digital currencies. The bill HJR 146 to amend the Bill of Rights was introduced by State Representative Giovani Capriglione. Texas legislators have voted to amend the state&#8217;s Bill of Rights to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/texas-adds-digital-currency-to-the-states-bill-of-rights/">Texas adds digital currency to the state&#8217;s Bill of Rights</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Texas lawmakers vote to add digital currency to the state&rsquo;s Bill of Rights.</li>
<li>The move grants citizens the right to possess, retain and utilize digital currencies.</li>
<li>The bill HJR 146 to amend the Bill of Rights was introduced by State Representative Giovani Capriglione.</li>
</ul>
<p>Texas legislators have voted to amend the state&rsquo;s Bill of Rights to add digital currency to allow individuals to possess, retain and utilize digital currencies like <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">Bitcoin (BTC)</a>.</p>
<p>The lawmakers voted in favour of the amendment by a large margin, possibly hinting at the general feeling among the lawmakers about digital currencies. 139 lawmakers voted in favour with only two voting against.</p>
<h2>Bill HJR 146</h2>
<p>The amendment was contained in a bill titled <a href="https://fastdemocracy.com/bill-search/tx/88/bills/TXB00063818/">Bill HJR 146</a>, which was introduced by State Representative Giovani Capriglione. According to the bill, individuals have the right to use a mutually agreed upon medium of exchange that includes digital currencies, coins, cash, scrip, or bullion, for contracting goods and services and trading.</p>
<p>The bill contains a stamen that reads:</p>
<p><em>&ldquo;No government shall prohibit or hinder the ownership or holding of any form or quantity of money or other currency.&rdquo;</em></p>
<h2>Texas Bill of Rights</h2>
<p>The Texas Bill of Rights protects essential rights like freedom of speech, religion and press similar to the US Bill of Rights.</p>
<p>However, the Texas Bill of Rights also includes specific clauses pertaining to Texas, such as the right to a prompt trial and the right to possess and carry weapons for self-defence.</p>
<p>Commenting on the development, the Texas Constitutional Enforcement group said that the inclusion of digital currencies in the Texas Bill of Rights is crucial in safeguarding Texans&rsquo; financial privacy.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/texas-adds-digital-currency-to-the-states-bill-of-rights/">Texas adds digital currency to the state&#8217;s Bill of Rights</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/texas-adds-digital-currency-to-the-states-bill-of-rights/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto price prediction: Kava, Cardano, Render Token</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-kava-cardano-render-token/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-kava-cardano-render-token/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 13:56:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-kava-cardano-render-token/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrency prices dived sharply this week partly because of Bitcoin&#8217;s congestion. KAVA, a DeFi-yielding protocol, was one of the best performing tokens. Cryptocurrency prices had a tough week as concerns about the industry continued. Bitcoin dropped below $27,000 while the total market cap of all digital currencies crashed to $1.10 trillion. Further, meme coins like [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-kava-cardano-render-token/">Crypto price prediction: Kava, Cardano, Render Token</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Cryptocurrency prices dived sharply this week partly because of Bitcoin&rsquo;s congestion.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">KAVA, a DeFi-yielding protocol, was one of the best performing tokens.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/cryptocurrencies/"><u>Cryptocurrency</u></a> prices had a tough week as concerns about the industry continued. Bitcoin dropped below $27,000 while the total market cap of all digital currencies crashed to $1.10 trillion. Further, meme coins like Pepe, Milady Meme Coin, Mrs Pepe, and Pepe AI have also plunged in the past few days. This crypto price prediction will look at Kava, Render Token, ad Cardano.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Kava price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/kava/"><u>Kava</u></a> price has been one of the best-performing cryptocurrencies this week. It jumped to a high of $0.9353, the highest point since April 19th. On the 4H chart, it has moved above the 38.2% retracement level.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Kava has also jumped above the 25-period and 50-period exponential moving averages (EMA) while the Relative Strength Index (RSI) and the MACD have risen sharply.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, the outlook for the Kava token is bullish, with the next key resistance level to watch will be at $1. This view will be confirmed if it moves above the key resistance point at $0.96, the highest point in April. The stop-loss for this trade will be at $0.84, the lowest point on Friday.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/04/12/1683899653198-895533fd-7fe3-4dd9-96d1-24a6de050ee7.png" style="width: 627px;height: 305.14px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="627" height="305.14"></p>
<h3 dir="ltr">How to buy Kava</h3>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    Binance.US</h3>

    <p>Binance.US provides secure and reliable access to the world&rsquo;s most popular cryptocurrencies, with some of the lowest fees in the industry.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/binance-us-crypto?guid=MTM5NDQ1&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy KAVA with Binance.US today            </a>
    </p><h3>
    Wazirx</h3>

    <p>WazirX is India's largest crypto exchange. Started in 2018, WazirX has grown to be the most trusted exchange in the Indian crypto market. It is a part of the binance group, serving users in 180 countries.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/wazirx-crypto?guid=MTM5NDQ1&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy KAVA with Wazirx today            </a>
    </p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Render Token price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/render-token/"><u>Render Token</u></a> price jumped sharply in April as investors cheered the vote to migrate it to Solana. This month, however, the token has pulled back and fallen by 34% from its highest point level. Render has moved to the 50% retracement level and dropped below the 25-day and 50-day exponential moving averages.</p>
<p dir="ltr">RNDR also retested the key support level at $1.6100, the lowest point on April 21st. Therefore, while the token has bounced back modestly in the past few days, I suspect that the bearish trend will resume as sellers target the key support at $1.400.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/04/12/1683899674782-6772f5e6-a127-4a32-b4af-aa0bb14e801f.png" style="width: 586px;height: 285.187px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="586" height="285.187"></p>
<h3 dir="ltr">How to buy RNDR</h3>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    Binance.US</h3>

    <p>Binance.US provides secure and reliable access to the world&rsquo;s most popular cryptocurrencies, with some of the lowest fees in the industry.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/binance-us-crypto?guid=MTM5NDQ1&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy RNDR with Binance.US today            </a>
    </p><h3>
    Swapzone</h3>

    <p>Swapzone is a crypto exchange aggregator that operates as a gateway between the cryptocurrency community and exchange services. Swapzone aims to provide a convenient interface, safe user flow, and crystal-clear data for users to find the best exchange rates among the whole cryptocurrency market.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/swapzone-crypto?guid=MTM5NDQ1&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy RNDR with Swapzone today            </a>
    </p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Cardano price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/cardano/"><u>Cardano</u></a>, like other major cryptocurrencies, has been in a steep bearish trend in the past few weeks. The sell-off intensified on April 20th after the coin moved below the lower side of the ascending channel shown in red. It has also moved below the 25-period and 50-period exponential moving averages and the support at $0.3786, the lowest point on April 25.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, I suspect that ADA price is about to rebound and retest the resistance at $0.3786 and then resume the bearish trend. More downside will be confirmed if the price moves below the support at $0.3500, the lowest point this week.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/04/12/1683899726788-76a5180e-6ecd-4203-8e7d-3b7131d6a03b.png" style="width: 577px;height: 280.807px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="577" height="280.807"></p>
<h3 dir="ltr">How to buy Cardano</h3>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>

    <p>eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=MTM5NDQ1&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy ADA with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    Public</h3>

    <p>Public is an investing platform that allows you to invest stocks, ETFs, crypto, and alternative assets like fine art and collectibles&mdash;all in one place.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/public-crypto?guid=MTM5NDQ1&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy ADA with Public today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptocurrency execution and custody services are provided by Apex Crypto LLC (NMLS ID 1828849) through a software licensing agreement between Apex Crypto LLC and Public Crypto LLC. Crypto trading on Public platforms is served by Public Crypto LLC and offered through APEX Crypto. Please ensure that you fully understand the risks involved before trading." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-kava-cardano-render-token/">Crypto price prediction: Kava, Cardano, Render Token</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-kava-cardano-render-token/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Super Six Tournament at 1xBit: A New Round with More Prizes is on the Horizon!</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/super-six-tournament-at-1xbit-a-new-round-with-more-prizes-is-on-the-horizon/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 13:39:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/super-six-tournament-at-1xbit-a-new-round-with-more-prizes-is-on-the-horizon/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If you are among the 90 lucky winners who have gained hefty prizes from the recently concluded second round in the Super Six tournament at 1xBit, congratulations to you! However, if you are yet to win anything, this is not the time to give up yet as there is a new prize draw on the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/super-six-tournament-at-1xbit-a-new-round-with-more-prizes-is-on-the-horizon/">Super Six Tournament at 1xBit: A New Round with More Prizes is on the Horizon!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">If you are among the 90 lucky winners who have gained hefty prizes from the recently concluded second round in the <a href="https://refpa9063395.top/L?tag=b_2242333m_3425c_S6_PR_2&amp;site=2242333&amp;ad=3425&amp;r=promotions/super-six-2023" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Super Six</u></a> tournament at 1xBit, congratulations to you! However, if you are yet to win anything, this is not the time to give up yet as there is a new prize draw on the way.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to Take Part?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Follow the steps below to get involved in this tournament:</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Visit the <a href="https://refpa9063395.top/L?tag=b_2242333m_3425c_S6_PR_2&amp;site=2242333&amp;ad=3425" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>1xBit</u></a> website and login to your account</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Fund your account using any of the altcoins available on the website</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Visit the tournament offer page and click on &ldquo;<a href="https://refpa9063395.top/L?tag=b_2242333m_3425c_S6_PR_2&amp;site=2242333&amp;ad=3425&amp;r=promotions/super-six-2023" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Take Part</u></a>&ldquo;</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Bet on EPL, Bundesliga, Serie A, La Liga, Ligue 1 and Primeira Liga and get promo tickets.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p>You get to unlock up to 50 mBTC in prizes at the end of each of the top six leagues. What more? There is a 100 mBTC prize draw as icing to the cake and most importantly, the final prize draw with rewards up to a whopping 300 mBTC! As you can see, the prizes keep getting bigger and better. You don&rsquo;t want to miss this. Get as many tickets as you can today, as the more you have, the higher your chances of winning any of the prizes mentioned above.</p>
<h2>Promotional Period</h2>
<p dir="ltr">As you may already know at this point, this tournament is already active. However, the tournament will be reaching its end on the 29th of May, 2023. Then all the results after the draw will be collated and winners will be made public in a matter of days. As such, it is in your best interest to get as many tickets as possible before the deadline. Hurry now!</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">1xBit Benefits</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Now, let&rsquo;s discuss some of the benefits of betting at 1xBit.</p>
<p><strong>Numerous Attractive Promotions</strong></p>
<p dir="ltr">The Super Six tournament is not the only tournament at 1xBit that will be available to you once you sign up. As a matter of fact, this betting platform has made it a point of duty to release frequent tournaments at least once every new month to give its users more reasons to play. If you think the prizes for the Super Six tournament are attractive, wait until you see what the other tournaments have in store.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>Over 40 Sports Available</strong></p>
<p dir="ltr">One area that many sports betting platforms struggle is their availability of betting markets. However, this is not the case with 1xBit. There are currently over 40 sports that you can bet on at 1xBit, with football being one of the most popular ones.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>Only Crypto Payment Methods Accepted</strong></p>
<p dir="ltr">1xBit stands out as one of the few betting sites out there that only accepts <a href="https://coinjournal.net/cryptocurrencies/">crypto</a> as the means of making payment. This innovation has changed the face of processing payments on betting platforms, as it has made it easier and faster to process transactions. Not only does 1xBit only accept crypto as a means of making payments, it makes sure that you have over 40 altcoins to choose from.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>Huge Welcome Bonus</strong></p>
<p dir="ltr">One of the major perks of joining the 1xBit community is the huge welcome bonus waiting for you. Once you are fully registered, you are eligible for a 300% welcome bonus on your 1-4th deposits. <em>Promo code&nbsp;</em><em><strong>SUPER1X&nbsp;</strong></em><em>will boost your first deposit bonus up!</em></p>
<p><strong>Fast Payouts</strong></p>
<p>A major challenge for most bettors that patronize traditional betting platforms is how long it can take to receive payouts. Because of the middlemen involved in processing the payments for those platforms, it could take as long as five days to get your winnings withdrawn. However, considering that 1xBit only uses crypto, you can be sure to get your payouts processed in a few hours.</p>
<h2>Conclusion</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><strong><br></strong>Get in on the action and win even more prizes in the upcoming draw of the Super Six tournament. For more information about promotions at 1xBit, follow the platform on the social media handles below: &nbsp; &nbsp;</p>
<p>Twitter &ndash;<a href="https://twitter.com/1x_bit" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">&nbsp;https://twitter.com/1x_bit<br>
</a></p>
<p>Instagram &ndash;<a href="https://www.instagram.com/1xbit/" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">&nbsp;https://www.instagram.com/1xbit/<br>
</a></p>
<p>Telegram &ndash;<a href="https://t.me/sportsbook_1xBit" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">&nbsp;https://t.me/sportsbook_1xBit<br>
</a></p>
<p>Telegram Contest Channel &ndash;<a href="https://t.me/Promo_1xBit" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"> <u>https://t.me/Promo_1xBit</u></a>&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/super-six-tournament-at-1xbit-a-new-round-with-more-prizes-is-on-the-horizon/">Super Six Tournament at 1xBit: A New Round with More Prizes is on the Horizon!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Metacade drops to $0.02225: Is this the right time to buy more MCADE tokens?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-drops-to-0-0222-is-this-the-right-time-to-buy-more-mcade-tokens/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 10:58:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-drops-to-0-0222-is-this-the-right-time-to-buy-more-mcade-tokens/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways Metacade reached an all-time high of $0.045 earlier this month but is now down by nearly 50% from that point. The broader crypto market is undergoing a correction, and this could present a good buying opportunity for investors. MCADE will be listing on more crypto exchanges before the end of the year.&#160; Metacade&#8217;s [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-drops-to-0-0222-is-this-the-right-time-to-buy-more-mcade-tokens/">Metacade drops to $0.02225: Is this the right time to buy more MCADE tokens?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Metacade reached an all-time high of $0.045 earlier this month but is now down by nearly 50% from that point.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The broader crypto market is undergoing a correction, and this could present a good buying opportunity for investors.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">MCADE will be listing on more crypto exchanges before the end of the year.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://metacade.co/en"><u>Metacade&rsquo;s</u></a> price has done well since going public last month. It surged to a high of $0.045 earlier this month after it was listed on the BitMart, Uniswap, and MEXC cryptocurrency exchanges.</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, it has lost nearly 40% of its value since then as the broader cryptocurrency market began its bearish move. With the MCADE price now low and the broader crypto market currently underperforming, is this a good opportunity for investors to invest in the project?&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Does Metacade offer a great investment opportunity?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">One of the best times to invest in financial assets is during a market correction. By investing during a bear market or a correction, investors set themselves up nicely to make excellent returns.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The broader cryptocurrency market has been underperforming since the start of the month. Bitcoin has lost more than 10% of its value over the past seven days and is struggling to maintain its price above $26k.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The poor performance of Bitcoin and other major cryptocurrencies has affected the prices of other cryptocurrencies, including Metacade.</p>
<p dir="ltr">MCADE rose to an all-time high of $0.045 earlier this month after it was listed on the MEXC cryptocurrency exchange. However, since then, MCADE has lost nearly 50% of its value as the market undergoes a correction.</p>
<p dir="ltr">At press time, the price of MCADE stands at $0.02225. The decline in the prices of cryptocurrencies, including Metacade, could serve as an excellent opportunity for investors to enter the market.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Those who didn&rsquo;t invest in Metacade during its pre-sale could take up this opportunity, as the token is now trading close to its presale price. Furthermore, existing investors could take advantage of the current market conditions to purchase more MCADE tokens.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Metacade?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">To determine if Metacade could be a good project to buy, investors need to know what Metacade is about.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://metacade.co/en" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade</u></a> is a web3 project that is powered by the Ethereum blockchain. The project seeks to improve the existing play-to-earn (P2E) ecosystem by making it possible for users to enjoy new web3 experiences.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Metacade development team is working to have a project that empowers users to play, connect, build, and earn seamlessly. The project also plans to transition into a decentralised autonomous organisation (DAO) by 2024, granting token holders control over the ecosystem.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">After raising $16 million in its presale stage, the Metacade development team is already working to launch some of its products.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Since it went public last month, MCADE, the native token of the ecosystem, has already been listed on the Uniswap, BitMart, and MEXC crypto exchanges. This means that the MCADE token is available to millions of investors globally.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The team also plans to list the token on several other leading cryptocurrency exchanges before the end of the year.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Will Metacade reach $0.1 by the end of 2023?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">MCADE reached its all-time high price of $0.045 earlier this month. However, it has dipped by roughly 50% since then as the broader crypto market is undergoing a correction.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The events of the past few weeks have shown that MCADE&rsquo;s performance is affected by the fundamentals of the broader cryptocurrency market.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">For MCADE to reach $0.1 by the end of the year, the development team will need to roll out some of their products.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In addition to that, the fundamentals of the broader cryptocurrency market will have to be bullish, as that could allow MCADE to rally to the $0.1 psychological level by the end of the year.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Finally, the Metacade team might also need to make MCADE available on other leading cryptocurrency exchanges. By listing MCADE on other top crypto exchanges, the token could be available to more people, and this could push its price higher in the medium term.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Is Metacade worth buying now?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">As an investor, one of the best times to invest in assets is when they are undergoing a correction. The broader crypto market is undergoing a correction at the moment, and this could be a good time to load on your investment.</p>
<p dir="ltr">After rallying to the $0.045 all-time high, MCADE is now trading close to the presale price of $0.02, and this could present an excellent buying opportunity for investors.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">MCADE will launch on more cryptocurrency exchanges before the end of the year, making it available to millions of investors globally.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the launch of&nbsp;<a href="https://metacade.co/en" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade</u></a> products over the next few months could increase the platform&rsquo;s utility and, ultimately, the value of the MCADE token.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-drops-to-0-0222-is-this-the-right-time-to-buy-more-mcade-tokens/">Metacade drops to $0.02225: Is this the right time to buy more MCADE tokens?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto liquidity falling as market makers pull back from hostile US market</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-liquidity-falling-as-market-makers-pull-back-from-hostile-us-market/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-liquidity-falling-as-market-makers-pull-back-from-hostile-us-market/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dan Ashmore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 10:20:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-liquidity-falling-as-market-makers-pull-back-from-hostile-us-market/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key Takeaways Jane Street and Jump Crypto, two prominent crypto market makers, are scaling back crypto operations The decision comes as US regulators continue an aggressive clampdown on the sector Liquidity is already thin in crypto, and these moves will only drop it further and increase volatility, writes our Head of Research, Dan Ashmore &#160; [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-liquidity-falling-as-market-makers-pull-back-from-hostile-us-market/">Crypto liquidity falling as market makers pull back from hostile US market</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2 dir="ltr">Key Takeaways</h2>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Jane Street and Jump Crypto, two prominent crypto market makers, are scaling back crypto operations</li>
<li dir="ltr">The decision comes as US regulators continue an aggressive clampdown on the sector</li>
<li dir="ltr">Liquidity is already thin in crypto, and these moves will only drop it further and increase volatility, writes our Head of Research, Dan Ashmore &nbsp;</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p dir="ltr">It was just earlier this week that I wrote a <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/has-institutional-money-left-crypto/"><u>piece</u></a> about institutions abandoning crypto. In the couple of days since, it has got worse.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bloomberg reported Tuesday that market makers Jane Street and Jump Trading are reducing their crypto focus. While not pulling out of the sector completely, the report stated the duo will be market making at a smaller scale than previously.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This is a big blow for crypto markets which were already showing thin liquidity since market making giant Alameda evaporated alongside FTX in November. I published a piece <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/22-billion-of-stablecoins-has-fled-exchanges-in-5-months-a-report-into-cryptos-capital-flight/"><u>last week</u></a> analysing the outflow of stablecoins from exchanges ($22 billion has headed for the exit doors in five months), while order book depth has been alarmingly shallow ever since Sam Baankman-Fried&rsquo;s party tricks were revealed.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/13547917">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">That liquidity is about to get even worse. With lower liquidity comes greater volatility, as less capital is required to move prices. Thus, moves to both the upside and downside are exacerbated, something I analysed <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-price-volatility-and-profits-are-all-the-highest-since-june-2022-but-why-and-will-it-continue/"><u>in April</u></a> when the Bitcoin price, volatility and profit levels all reached their highest marks since June 2022.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Investors need to be wary that, while price has been rising the last six months, there has not really been anything positive coming out of the sector. Quite the opposite, in fact &ndash; bankruptcies picked up in January amid the continued fallout from FTX, while regulators have put the squeeze on since.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">More than anything, prices have been rising as crypto markets are <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/no-bitcoin-is-still-as-correlated-as-ever-with-the-stock-market-a-deep-dive/"><u>so strongly correlated</u></a> with the stock market and other risk assets. As market expectations around the future path of interest rate rises have peeled back, risk assets have rebounded &ndash; and that means crypto, too.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">With this low liquidity only getting lower, the moves will only become more volatile. As of Friday morning, Bitcoin is trading at $26,200, down 7% in the last 36 hours.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Regulators squeezing the crypto sector</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Jane Street and Jump Crypto faced increasing scrutiny as US regulators continue to clamp down aggressively on the sector. Since FTX collapsed in November, the regauyltory environment has become far more hostile to the crypto industry.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Ironically, Sam Bankman-Fried worked at Jane Street before founding Alameda in 2017. Caroline Ellison, former CEO of Alameda who has reportedly turned on Bankman-Fried ahead of his trial, also worked at Jane Street before joining Alameda.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Jane Street was among three US trading firms cited by the Commodity Futures Trading Commission lawsuit against Binance as examples of how US firms could access the platform despite Binance claiming to prohibit them.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Jump Street was a large backer of Terra, the firm behind the TerraUSD stablecoin and sister coin LUNA, which spiralled to zero in May 2022. The firm was questioned by US prosecutors in an investigation after its demise.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The clampdown has been controversial, with crypto-native firms decrying that activity will need to move off offshore. Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong has been among the most high-profile voices to relay this sentiment, saying this week that Coinbase would consider the UAE as an international base, as the US continues to turn the screw.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The exchange was recently served with a Wells notice from the SEC, a warning of impending legal action, most likely in relation to a violation of securities laws.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;Crypto and Web3 serve as enormous opportunities for economic and technological diversification for the UAE, and the region has the potential to be a strategic hub for Coinbase, amplifying our efforts across the world&rdquo;, Coinbase said in a blog post.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">On the other hand, some are praising what they believe is a long overdue squeeze on a sector built upon nothing but greed, that has brought bone-crushing losses for many retail investors over the past year. Whatever your view, it is clear that the US is creating an increasingly hostile environment for any firm operating in the crypto space.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What next for crypto?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Right now, crypto seems primed to move beyond the US, through no choice of its own. While the industry can continue, this still constitutes a massive blow. So much of the steep trajectory of crypto during the pandemic was based upon the thought that institutions and traditional finance would inevitably pour into the sector. Today, it is going the opposite way.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The US is the economic and financial centre of the world. Crypto firms being forced out of this market won&rsquo;t entirely prevent everyday people from investing in the industry, but it certainly will make it more difficult and less convenient. It will also limit innovation in the sector. This is all bearish for the sector and will undoubtedly inhibit its growth going forward.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">As for the price effects, Jane Street and Jump Crypto&rsquo;s decision to pull back hurts the industry in a place it was already suffering &ndash; liquidity. The volatility in the sector certainly won&rsquo;t be going away anytime soon, therefore, but rather only increasing.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-liquidity-falling-as-market-makers-pull-back-from-hostile-us-market/">Crypto liquidity falling as market makers pull back from hostile US market</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-liquidity-falling-as-market-makers-pull-back-from-hostile-us-market/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>AltSignals AI project gathers steam as Google and Microsoft jump into the AI bandwagon</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-ai-project-gathers-steam-as-google-and-microsoft-jump-into-the-ai-bandwagon/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-ai-project-gathers-steam-as-google-and-microsoft-jump-into-the-ai-bandwagon/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 07:14:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-ai-project-gathers-steam-as-google-and-microsoft-jump-into-the-ai-bandwagon/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Microsoft incorporated GPT-4 into its Bing search engine earlier this year. Google has announced it is rolling out generative AI to its core search engine. AltSignals is developing an AI-based algorithm for generating trading signals. AltSignals AI-based trading signals algorithm seems to come at the right time as big tech companies flock to artificial intelligence [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-ai-project-gathers-steam-as-google-and-microsoft-jump-into-the-ai-bandwagon/">AltSignals AI project gathers steam as Google and Microsoft jump into the AI bandwagon</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Microsoft incorporated GPT-4 into its Bing search engine earlier this year.</li>
<li>Google has announced it is rolling out generative AI to its core search engine.</li>
<li>AltSignals is developing an AI-based algorithm for generating trading signals.</li>
</ul>
<p>AltSignals AI-based trading signals algorithm seems to come at the right time as big tech companies flock to artificial intelligence technology. Earlier this year, Microsoft incorporated OpenAI&rsquo;s GPT-4 into its Bing search engine shortly after investing heavily in the OpenAI Company.</p>
<p>The GPT-4 is a product of the same company that launched the now very popular ChatGPT. It is a large multimodal model that can imitate prose, audio, video, or art produced by a human and it can solve written problems or generate original text or images. It is basically the fourth generation of OpenAI&rsquo;s foundation model.</p>
<h2>Google to incorporate AI in its Search engine</h2>
<p>Following in the footsteps of its main competitor, Google yesterday announced that it is rolling out generative artificial intelligence (AI) to its core search engine.</p>
<p>Google search engine is one of the most popular search engines around the globe and the incorporation of AI is expected to revolutionize the search engine experience. Google&rsquo;s parent company Alphabet <a href="https://blog.google/technology/ai/google-io-2023-keynote-sundar-pichai/#helpful-ai">said</a>, &ldquo;Search Generative Experience &ndash; which will be part of Google &ndash; will craft responses to open-ended queries.&rdquo;</p>
<p>However, the system is currently in the experimental phase and will first only be available to a limited number of users.</p>
<h2>AltSignals&rsquo; AI project</h2>
<p>AltSignals has become popular for providing quality trading signals since its launch in 2017. The platform provides signals to over 50,000 Telegram members and its trading signal service has earned a 4.8 out of 5-star rating on Trustpilot.</p>
<p>The AI project is aimed at upgrading the platform&rsquo;s signal-generating service after its early success. The AltSignals team wants to integrate artificial intelligence, natural language processing, machine learning, and advanced sentiment analysis in signal generation.</p>
<p>The new AltSignals&rsquo; AI-powered trading platform, dubbed ActualizeAI, will be powered by a native cryptocurrency called ASI, which will be the unit of membership in ActualizeAI, with holders being able to vote on the governance of the platform.</p>
<p>At the moment, AltSignals is conducting a presale of the ASI token. The presale is in its second stage, which at press time was 67.67% sold out. Interested crypto investors can participate in the presale <a href="https://token.altsignals.io/">here</a>.</p>
<h2>What the AI hype means for the ASI Cryptocurrency</h2>
<p>Going by the success that ChatGPT has had since its launch towards the end of 2022, AltSignals&rsquo; ActualizeAI project is poised for a similar uptake and the quick <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-traders-gear-up-and-flock-to-altsignals-new-token-asi/">sell-out of the first AltSignals&rsquo; presale stage</a>, the BETA stage, is already a testament that investors have confidence in the ActualizeAI project.</p>
<p>Besides, AI technology is only in its initial stages seeing that big tech companies are currently working on workable solutions, with most of the AI products being in their testing stages including the recently announced incorporation of AI into the Google Search Engine.</p>
<p>This means that the end of the current ASI presale could well coincide with a matured AI market, which could spur its popularity higher notwithstanding that the AltSignals already have a sizeable number of customers that use its services even without the existence of native cryptocurrency.</p>
<p>Besides offering holders a membership opportunity to the new ActualizeAI, the ASI token will also offer AltSignals users an opportunity to make additional revenue from trading the token once it is listed on centralized cryptocurrency exchanges.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-ai-project-gathers-steam-as-google-and-microsoft-jump-into-the-ai-bandwagon/">AltSignals AI project gathers steam as Google and Microsoft jump into the AI bandwagon</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-ai-project-gathers-steam-as-google-and-microsoft-jump-into-the-ai-bandwagon/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>D-Central Launches Innovative &#8220;Hash No Cash&#8221; Promotion Across North America</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/d-central-launches-innovative-hash-no-cash-promotion-across-north-america/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/d-central-launches-innovative-hash-no-cash-promotion-across-north-america/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire &#160;]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 20:48:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=139398</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Laval, Canada, May 11th, 2023, Chainwire Groundbreaking Initiative Revolutionizes ASIC Repair Services, Encourages Sustainability and Decentralization in Cryptocurrency Mining. D-Central Technologies Inc., a pioneer in the cryptocurrency mining industry, is excited to announce the expansion of its revolutionary &#8220;Hash No Cash&#8221; program to all cryptocurrency miners in North America. This innovative initiative, previously accessible only [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/d-central-launches-innovative-hash-no-cash-promotion-across-north-america/">D-Central Launches Innovative &#8220;Hash No Cash&#8221; Promotion Across North America</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Laval, Canada, May 11th, 2023, Chainwire</strong></p>
<p>Groundbreaking Initiative Revolutionizes ASIC Repair Services, Encourages Sustainability and Decentralization in Cryptocurrency Mining.</p>
<p>D-Central Technologies Inc., a pioneer in the cryptocurrency mining industry, is excited to announce the expansion of its revolutionary &ldquo;Hash No Cash&rdquo; program to all cryptocurrency miners in North America. This innovative initiative, previously accessible only to select clients, is now available to miners of all scales, dramatically transforming the landscape of ASIC repair services.</p>
<p>The &ldquo;Hash No Cash&rdquo; program allows D-Central to provide high-quality repair services for mining hardware at no cash cost, instead accepting broken hardware as payment. This innovative approach is a testament to D-Central&rsquo;s commitment to fostering sustainable, accessible, and cost-effective solutions for miners.</p>
<p>&ldquo;In the rapidly evolving world of cryptocurrency mining, the need for efficient and affordable repair services is more important than ever,&rdquo; said Jonathan Bertrand, CEO of D-Central. &ldquo;With the &lsquo;Hash No Cash&rsquo; program, we&rsquo;re making it easier for miners to maintain and repair their hardware, allowing them to keep their capital for strategic investments such as new hardware purchases.&rdquo;</p>
<p>The &ldquo;Hash No Cash&rdquo; program also contributes to environmental sustainability by reducing electronic waste. By repairing and repurposing broken hardware, D-Central minimizes the demand for new equipment production, thereby reducing the environmental impact of cryptocurrency mining.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the program promotes decentralization in cryptocurrency mining. By making repaired hardware available to retail customers at affordable prices, D-Central is putting the power of ASICs into more hands, fostering the wider distribution of mining power.</p>
<p>&ldquo;D-Central is committed to driving change within the cryptocurrency mining industry,&rdquo; said Jonathan Bertrand. &ldquo;Our goal is not just to provide repair services, but to create solutions that are financially viable, environmentally friendly, and conducive to the decentralization of mining power.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Miners across North America are invited to take advantage of the &ldquo;Hash No Cash&rdquo; program. To learn more about the program or to get started, please visit: https://d-central.tech/</p>
<p><strong>About D-Central</strong></p>
<p>D-Central is a leading provider of cryptocurrency mining services, offering a wide range of solutions including ASIC repair services, mining support, and disinfection services. Since its establishment in 2016, D-Central has been committed to providing professional services tailored to the unique needs of the cryptocurrency mining industry. With a track record of delivering high-quality services and innovative solutions, D-Central continues to shape the future of cryptocurrency mining.</p>
<h5>Contact</h5>
<p><strong>CEO</strong><br>
<strong>Jonathan Bertrand</strong><br>
<strong>D-Central Technologies Inc.</strong><br>
<strong>support@d-central.tech</strong><br>
<strong>18557539997</strong></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/d-central-launches-innovative-hash-no-cash-promotion-across-north-america/">D-Central Launches Innovative &#8220;Hash No Cash&#8221; Promotion Across North America</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/d-central-launches-innovative-hash-no-cash-promotion-across-north-america/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
