<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 12:11:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Dogecoin price prediction: multi-time technical analysis</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/dogecoin-price-prediction-multi-time-technical-analysis/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/dogecoin-price-prediction-multi-time-technical-analysis/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 12:11:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOGE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/dogecoin-price-prediction-multi-time-technical-analysis/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Dogecoin price has joined other cryptocurrencies in a strong sell-off. Technical analysis shows that the coin will continue falling. Dogecoin price was not left behind in the recent cryptocurrency sell-off. The coin dropped to a low of $0.067, the lowest level since July 18th. It has dropped by more than 20% from the highest level [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/dogecoin-price-prediction-multi-time-technical-analysis/">Dogecoin price prediction: multi-time technical analysis</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Dogecoin price has joined other cryptocurrencies in a strong sell-off.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Technical analysis shows that the coin will continue falling.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/dogecoin/"><u>Dogecoin</u></a> price was not left behind in the recent cryptocurrency sell-off. The coin dropped to a low of $0.067, the lowest level since July 18th. It has dropped by more than 20% from the highest level in July and over 58% from the highest level in 2022. Other coins like Bitcoin, Litecoin, and Hedera Hashgraph have also dipped.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Dogecoin price forecast (daily chart)</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The daily chart shows that the DOGE price has been in a strong bearish trend after peaking at $0.1587 in October last year. It has underperformed the crypto market, partly because of the strong growth of alternative meme coins like Bone Shibaswap, Pepe, and Bad Idea.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The coin has remained below the descending trendline, which connects the highest levels since December last year. At the same time, the coin has moved below the 25-day and 50-day exponential moving averages (EMA).&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Dogecoin price is hovering slightly above the important support level at $0.065, the lowest point in March and December last year. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) has moved below the neutral point at 50 while the Stochastic Oscillator has moved below the oversold level.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, DOGE price will likely have a bearish breakout in the next few days. If this happens, the next level to watch will be at $0.055, the lowest level on June 10th 2023 and September last year. The stop-loss of this trade is at $0.080, the descending trendline.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/07/17/1692274251606-07ba49c3-2d3e-4cbb-939a-912d8194b2d5.png" style="width: 652px;height: 317.307px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="652" height="317.307"></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">DOGE price analysis (4H chart)</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Turning to the four-hour chart, DOGE price has been in a downtrend in the past few weeks. It has managed to move below the ascending channel shown in black. It dropped below that level on August 2nd and then retested it on August 5th. In technical analysis, a break and retest pattern is usually a sign of a bearish continuation.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Dogecoin has also retreated below the 25-period and 50-period moving averages while the Relative Strength Index has moved below the oversold level. Therefore, the outlook of the token is bearish, with the next level to watch will be at $0.063.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/07/17/1692274251559-bc22d108-bc9f-46fc-b2a5-c86fc82052cc.png" style="width: 693px;height: 337.26px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="693" height="337.26"></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy Dogecoin</h2>
<p dir="ltr">
        </p><div class="relative">

            <div class="mb-3  pb-6  px-6  bg-slate-50  rounded-xl  ps-shadow-inner">

    <h3 class="inline-block">
        eToro    </h3>

            <p class="text-sm">eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>
    
    <div class="w-full  flex  flex-wrap  items-start  flex-col  gap-2">

        
<a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=MTUwMDkz&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="nofollow sponsored noopener" target="_self" class="inline-block  text-indigo-600  underline  hover:text-indigo-200  ease-in-out  duration-300  transition-all" title="Buy DOGE with eToro today">Buy DOGE with eToro today</a>

    </div>

</div><div class="  pb-6  px-6  bg-slate-50  rounded-xl  ps-shadow-inner">

    <h3 class="inline-block">
        LiquidityX    </h3>

            <p class="text-sm">LiquidityX offers over 300 desirable financial assets to choose from. At LiquidityX, you can dive into global markets, and trade CFDs on Cryptocurrency assets ranging from the most popular coins like Bitcoin, Dogecoin and more.</p>
    
    <div class="w-full  flex  flex-wrap  items-start  flex-col  gap-2">

        
<a href="/visit/liquidityx-crypto?guid=MTUwMDkz&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="nofollow sponsored noopener" target="_self" class="inline-block  text-indigo-600  underline  hover:text-indigo-200  ease-in-out  duration-300  transition-all" title="Buy DOGE with LiquidityX today">Buy DOGE with LiquidityX today</a>

    </div>

</div>
        </div>



<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/dogecoin-price-prediction-multi-time-technical-analysis/">Dogecoin price prediction: multi-time technical analysis</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/dogecoin-price-prediction-multi-time-technical-analysis/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is Chancer a profitable bet in 2023 and 2024?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/is-chancer-a-profitable-bet-in-2023-and-2024/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/is-chancer-a-profitable-bet-in-2023-and-2024/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Motiur Rahman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 10:46:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technical Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/is-chancer-a-profitable-bet-in-2023-and-2024/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Chancer aims to take the mainstream betting market to the blockchain. The P2P betting has been in demand, as the presale raises $1.4 million Chancer has huge potential after listing and could rise more after the platform launches Blockchain is fast infiltrating traditional sectors. Betting is one of them, with Chancer taking steps to take [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/is-chancer-a-profitable-bet-in-2023-and-2024/">Is Chancer a profitable bet in 2023 and 2024?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Chancer aims to take the mainstream betting market to the blockchain.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The P2P betting has been in demand, as the presale raises $1.4 million</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Chancer has huge potential after listing and could rise more after the platform launches</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Blockchain is fast infiltrating traditional sectors. Betting is one of them, with Chancer taking steps to take the predictive market to the blockchain. Chancer lets users bet on a fully decentralised ecosystem powered by a crypto token. Since launching a presale, investors have bought over $1.43 worth of tokens. But is Chancer worth&nbsp;<a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>buying</u></a> at presale ahead of the listing?</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>How Chancer works</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer is coined under the phrase &ldquo;Your Game, Your Rules, Your Odds.&rdquo; That partly explains how the platform works.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer allows users to dictate the game of betting. Users can determine what they want to bet on, from mainstream events like football to social events. There is no limit on what users can bet on, making Chancer a game-changer in new betting experiences.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">To bet, users create a peer-to-peer Chancer market via the decentralised ecosystem. Users can invite others (peers) to their markets.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Once created, users develop rules that will govern their P2P betting market. They also determine the odds of claiming winnings.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The P2P model of Chancer is unique from the mainstream betting platforms. Users are not constrained to what bookmakers provide. This aspect is expected to bring limitless betting opportunities and attract new users. The revolutionary features explain the fast presale of the token.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>What is the value proposition of Chancer?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Betting is one of the fastest-growing and most popular sectors globally. By bringing it to the blockchain, Chancer has a huge potential to find unlimited uses. Users need not turn to their local or bookmaker currencies to bet and claim winnings. They will do so with the Chancer token. This means the potential for the token to skyrocket is high as demand increases, delivering returns.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Owning Chancer is also an opportunity to earn through market-making rewards. Users get rewarded for creating the P2P markets. The native token can also be staked for passive income-generating opportunities. Those who like to spread the word about Chancer are rewarded for their efforts through a Share2Earn feature.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Betting does not also need to be boring too. Chancer features real-time or live streaming powers via P2P markets. This is a good way to engage with wagers in one&rsquo;s betting cycles and have fun.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Chancer price potential and prediction in 2023 and 2024</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">The magic of creating one&rsquo;s betting market through Chancer gives the token a lot of potential. Analysts have lauded the token as a 10x investment, which is realistic and attainable.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Based on the project&rsquo;s roadmap, Chancer will be listed on Uniswap in Q3 2023. The company seeks a minimum of two CEX listings in the quarter. The listing will open up the token for more buys and unlock value. It means the value of Chancer could start to rise then.</p>
<p dir="ltr">But from a prudential perspective, Chancer&rsquo;s value could rise by 1,000% in 2024 or more in the future. This is after the main platform launches, and the value is unlocked from organic use rather than speculation. For 2023, investors should be comfortable with 100% or more increases. A 10x increase could be overambitious in the near term.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Is it the right time to buy the Chancer token?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">There is a clear expectation that Chancer will surprise the markets, looking at its successful presale. The price will be ready for takeoff when the token is listed in the third quarter. Investors that miss the presale may be forced to buy the token at a higher price on exchanges.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Buying the token at the presale is advantageous as the token&rsquo;s price is low. More so, the token is most attractively priced at the initial stages. For example, while Chancer started the presale at $0.01, it now goes for $0.011. That makes it worthwhile to buy it now rather than later.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/is-chancer-a-profitable-bet-in-2023-and-2024/">Is Chancer a profitable bet in 2023 and 2024?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/is-chancer-a-profitable-bet-in-2023-and-2024/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase stock: bouncing back but a disaster for investors to date</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-stock-bouncing-back-but-a-disaster-for-investors-to-date/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-stock-bouncing-back-but-a-disaster-for-investors-to-date/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dan Ashmore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 09:03:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-stock-bouncing-back-but-a-disaster-for-investors-to-date/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key Takeaways&#160; Coinbase went public in April 2021, close to the top of the crypto market and near a $100 billion valuation Despite a stout 141% rise thus far this year, it remains 77% off its IPO price It has underperformed Bitcoin significantly Regulatory issues cloud picture but hope remains that it can establish itself [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-stock-bouncing-back-but-a-disaster-for-investors-to-date/">Coinbase stock: bouncing back but a disaster for investors to date</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2 dir="ltr">Key Takeaways&nbsp;</h2>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Coinbase went public in April 2021, close to the top of the crypto market and near a $100 billion valuation</li>
<li dir="ltr">Despite a stout 141% rise thus far this year, it remains 77% off its IPO price</li>
<li dir="ltr">It has underperformed Bitcoin significantly</li>
<li dir="ltr">Regulatory issues cloud picture but hope remains that it can establish itself as largest fiat on-boarder</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p dir="ltr">Coinbase stock is having a bumper year. The cryptocurrency exchange is up 141% year-to-date, far exceeding both Bitcoin and the Nasdaq, which have risen 77% and 31% respectively. &nbsp;This year-to-date gain comes despite a 24% fall over the last month.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14724385">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">And yet, despite the boisterous performance thus far this year, for those who invested in Coinbase a couple of years ago, it has been nothing but pain. The stock remains 76% below its IPO price from April 2021. At one point flirting with a $100 billion valuation, today it has a market cap of $19 billion.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14724404">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">The travails of the stock sum up the struggles in the wider cryptocurrency industry over the last eighteen months. Booming during the pandemic as stimulus cheques flowed and interest rates were non-existent, the music stopped last year once inflation began to spiral. Central banks were forced to hike interest rates, with the US Federal Reserve particularly aggressive. Today, rates are north of 5%, with risk assets pulling back severely last year as a result.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14565862">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<h2 dir="ltr">Trouble within crypto</h2>
<p dir="ltr">In addition to the harsh macro climate, the crypto sector has done itself no favours. There have been several startling collapses which triggered mass contagion across the industry. The first was the death spiral of the UST stablecoin, taking down the entire Terra ecosystem and leading to a host of bankruptcies, including hedge fund Three Arrows Capital.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Crypto lender Celsius were among the other firms to follow, but it was the demise of FTX, the Bahamas-based exchange, that was the cherry on top. Bitcoin fell to $15,500 and the entire industry was in disarray. For Coinbase shareholders, despite the evaporation of a key competitor, the stock price suffered further, such was the damage to the ecosystem.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">In retrospect, Coinbase went public right at the top, walking into an oncoming storm. Marking their IPO on a Bitcoin price chart below shows how poignant the timing was.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14724413">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">Yet even with bad timing, it has underperformed Bitcoin. While the two assets have been highly correlated, since the start of 2022 (roughly coinciding with the start of the crypto bear market), Coinbase has headed lower than the world&rsquo;s biggest crypto.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14724433">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<h2 dir="ltr">Regulation</h2>
<p dir="ltr">A big part of the issue is regulation. US lawmakers are cracking down on the cryptocurrency industry, and Coinbase is squarely in the line of fire. The exchange was sued in June for securities violations.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;(The SEC) came back to us, and they said&thinsp;.&thinsp;.&thinsp;. we believe every asset other than bitcoin is a security,&rdquo; Brian Armstrong, CEO of Coinbase, said. &ldquo;And, we said, well how are you coming to that conclusion, because that&rsquo;s not our interpretation of the law. And they said, we&rsquo;re not going to explain it to you, you need to delist every asset other than Bitcoin.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;We really didn&rsquo;t have a choice at that point, delisting every asset other than bitcoin, which by the way is not what the law says, would have essentially meant the end of the crypto industry in the US,&rdquo; Armstrong continued. &ldquo;It kind of made it an easy choice&thinsp;.&thinsp;.&thinsp;.&thinsp;let&rsquo;s go to court and find out what the court says.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The court case will be pivotal not only for the future of Coinbase&rsquo;s business, but the entire crypto industry in the US. Yet despite the regulatory troubles, Coinbase is arguably the most reputable major exchange. Its legal trouble centres on securities violations, a far cry from the laundry list of accusations against the biggest exchange, Binance. Changpeng Zhao&rsquo;s company faces charges of trading against customers, manipulating volume, circumventing AML and KYC laws, and more.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Institutional on-boarder</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Additionally, many of the spot ETF applications which have been lodged with the SEC recently outline Coinbase as a proposed custodian. This, in addition to its cleaner reputation as mentioned above, highlights an angle that Coinbase could exploit if it does manage to fight its corner in court successfully: institutional money.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">If or when institutional capital is allowed to flow freely into crypto, Coinbase &ndash; at least right now &ndash; appears well placed to vacuum up all that volume and offer as a vital on-boarding into the on-chain world for all this trad-fi capital.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">It is difficult to forecast how the legal case will play out, and in any case, it will not be resolved quickly. On the positive side for COIN investors, last month&rsquo;s ruling in the landmark Ripple security case provided hope, even if it was only a partial win, with the result also pushed back against by the SEC.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Whatever happens with that case, COIN investors will hope that the future brings more positive results than the past, as the stock has been a disaster for most. Perhaps the best way to sum it up is this: had investors put their money in FTX, and if FTX creditors end up securing 24 cents on the dollar or greater, they would be better off than Coinbase investors. Obviously, that is a silly comparison and assumes Coinbase trades flat from here (not to mention the fact that bankruptcy proceedings will take years), but it does indicate quite how badly Coinbase stock has performed since those dizzying days of 2021.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-stock-bouncing-back-but-a-disaster-for-investors-to-date/">Coinbase stock: bouncing back but a disaster for investors to date</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-stock-bouncing-back-but-a-disaster-for-investors-to-date/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>TRON Joins Japan Cryptoasset Business Association (JCBA)</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/tron-joins-japan-cryptoasset-business-association-jcba/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/tron-joins-japan-cryptoasset-business-association-jcba/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire &#160;]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 20:26:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=150030</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Geneva, Switzerland, August 16th, 2023, Chainwire TRON DAO (&#8220;TRON&#8221;) is pleased to announce that it has joined the Japan Cryptoasset Business Association (&#8220;JCBA&#8221;) as an associate member starting from August 1st, 2023. As a leading global blockchain, TRON is committed to building cooperation and collaboration with other JCBA members to promote the growth of the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tron-joins-japan-cryptoasset-business-association-jcba/">TRON Joins Japan Cryptoasset Business Association (JCBA)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Geneva, Switzerland, August 16th, 2023, Chainwire</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://trondao.org/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><strong>TRON DAO</strong></a><strong> (&ldquo;TRON&rdquo;)</strong> is pleased to announce that it has joined the <a href="https://cryptocurrency-association.org" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><strong>Japan Cryptoasset Business Association</strong></a><strong> (&ldquo;JCBA&rdquo;)</strong> as an associate member starting from August 1st, 2023. As a leading global blockchain, TRON is committed to building cooperation and collaboration with other JCBA members to promote the growth of the crypto industry in Japan and all across Asia.</p>
<p>Established in 2016, JCBA is a Japanese based association for stakeholders within the Web3 ecosystem. It aims to foster a promising environment for the development of digital assets, including cryptocurrencies, NFTs, and stablecoins. Currently, JCBA has 134 members from both Web3 and traditional industries based in Japan and internationally.</p>
<p>By joining as an associate member of JCBA, TRON strives to closely collaborate with the Japanese market and contribute to JCBA&rsquo;s vision by leveraging TRON&rsquo;s efficient network and robust userbase.</p>
<p class="ql-align-center">-END-</p>
<h3>About TRON DAO</h3>
<p>TRON DAO is a community-governed DAO dedicated to accelerating the decentralization of the internet via blockchain technology and dApps.</p>
<p>Founded in September 2017 by H.E. Justin Sun, the TRON network has continued to deliver impressive achievements since MainNet launch in May 2018. July 2018 also marked the ecosystem integration of BitTorrent, a pioneer in decentralized Web3 services boasting over 100 million monthly active users. The TRON network has gained incredible traction in recent years. As of August 2023, it has over 179.07 million total user accounts on the blockchain, more than 6.26 billion total transactions, and over $13.01 billion in total value locked (TVL), as reported on TRONSCAN.</p>
<p>In addition, TRON hosts the largest circulating supply of USD Tether (USDT) stablecoin across the globe, overtaking USDT on Ethereum since April 2021. The TRON network completed full decentralization in December 2021 and is now a community-governed DAO. Most recently in October 2022, TRON was designated as the national blockchain for the Commonwealth of Dominica, which marks the first time a major public blockchain partnered with a sovereign nation to develop its national blockchain infrastructure. On top of the government&rsquo;s endorsement to issue Dominica Coin (&ldquo;DMC&rdquo;), a blockchain-based fan token to help promote Dominica&rsquo;s global fanfare, seven existing TRON-based tokens &ndash; TRX, BTT, NFT, JST, USDD, USDT, TUSD, have been granted statutory status as authorized digital currency and medium of exchange in the country.</p>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://tron.network/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">TRONNetwork</a></li>
<li><a href="https://trondao.org/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">TRONDAO</a></li>
<li><a href="https://twitter.com/TRONDAO" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Twitter</a></li>
<li><a href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC5OPOGRq02iK-0T9sKse_kA" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">YouTube</a></li>
<li><a href="https://t.me/tronnetworkEN" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Telegram</a></li>
<li><a href="https://discord.gg/trondao" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Discord</a></li>
<li><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/Tronix/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Reddit</a></li>
<li><a href="https://github.com/tronprotocol" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">GitHub</a></li>
<li><a href="https://trondao.medium.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Medium</a></li>
<li><a href="https://forum.trondao.org/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Forum</a></li>
</ul>
<h3>About JCBA</h3>
<p>The Japan Cryptoasset Business Association (JCBA) was established in 2016 as a membership organization for stakeholders in the public blockchain and Web3.0 ecosystems who conduct business related to crypto assets, NFTs, stablecoins, and other digital assets in Japan, with the goal of improving the environment.</p>
<p>Website of JCBA: <a href="https://cryptocurrency-association.org/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://cryptocurrency-association.org/</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h5><strong>Contact</strong></h5>
<p>Hayward Wong<br>
press@tron.network</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tron-joins-japan-cryptoasset-business-association-jcba/">TRON Joins Japan Cryptoasset Business Association (JCBA)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/tron-joins-japan-cryptoasset-business-association-jcba/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Valkyrie just filed for an ETH futures ETF with the U.S. SEC</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/valkyrie-just-filed-for-an-eth-futures-etf-with-the-u-s-sec/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/valkyrie-just-filed-for-an-eth-futures-etf-with-the-u-s-sec/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 17:21:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/valkyrie-just-filed-for-an-eth-futures-etf-with-the-u-s-sec/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Valkyrie already resubmitted its Bitcoin futures ETF with the SEC. Valkyrie is the first company to file for an ETH futures ETF in the U.S. Ethereum (ETH) price reacted minimally to the news and was trading at $1,819.73, down 0.96% in the last 24 hours. Asset management company Valkyrie has filed for an Ether (ETH) [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/valkyrie-just-filed-for-an-eth-futures-etf-with-the-u-s-sec/">Valkyrie just filed for an ETH futures ETF with the U.S. SEC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul class="decimal_type">
<li>Valkyrie already resubmitted its Bitcoin futures ETF with the SEC.</li>
<li>Valkyrie is the first company to file for an ETH futures ETF in the U.S.</li>
<li>Ethereum (ETH) price reacted minimally to the news and was trading at $1,819.73, down 0.96% in the last 24 hours.</li>
</ul>
<p>Asset management company Valkyrie has filed for an Ether (ETH) futures exchange-traded fund (ETF) with the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). In accordance with the filing made on August 16, the application represents an expansion of the business&rsquo;s prior decision to modify its <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/united-states-sec-officially-accepts-valkyrie-spot-bitcoin-etf-application/">Bitcoin futures ETF application</a> which the SEC accepted in July.</p>
<p>According to the application, the fund will seek to buy several Ether futures contracts rather than making a direct investment in the cryptocurrency. Ether, the native token of the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/what-is-ethereum/">Ethereum</a> blockchain, is utilized for decentralized network peer-to-peer transactions.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Valkyrie just filed for an Ether Futures ETF, which is in addition to their 497 filing to do name/strategy of <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24BTF&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$BTF</a> to Bitcoin + Ether Futures to get out early. Perhaps this is sign SEC not letting them do the 'ole <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24MJ&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$MJ</a> maneuver, not sure.. ht <a href="https://twitter.com/NateGeraci?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@NateGeraci</a> <a href="https://t.co/OeyGuyJP3y">pic.twitter.com/OeyGuyJP3y</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Eric Balchunas (@EricBalchunas) <a href="https://twitter.com/EricBalchunas/status/1691840487819292865?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 16, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>According to the application document, &ldquo;Ether may be regarded as a currency or digital commodity depending on its specific use in particular transactions. Ether may be used as a medium of exchange or unit of account, although a number of large and small retailers accept ether as a form of payment in the United States and foreign markets, there is relatively limited use of ether for commercial and retail payments. Similarly, ether may be used as a store of value [&hellip;], although it has experienced significant periods of price volatility.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/valkyrie-just-filed-for-an-eth-futures-etf-with-the-u-s-sec/">Valkyrie just filed for an ETH futures ETF with the U.S. SEC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/valkyrie-just-filed-for-an-eth-futures-etf-with-the-u-s-sec/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP boost as BitPay announces worldwide support – can bulls react?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/xrp-boost-as-bitpay-announces-worldwide-support-can-bulls-react/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/xrp-boost-as-bitpay-announces-worldwide-support-can-bulls-react/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 15:17:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitpay]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/xrp-boost-as-bitpay-announces-worldwide-support-can-bulls-react/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>XRP price is trading below $0.60, down 5% in the past 24 hours. BitPay recently announced worldwide support for XRP payments. Key price levels are at $0.55 and $0.70, respectively demand and reload zones. XRP price is down 5% in the past 24 hours to trade below $0.60, with bears threatening to wipe out all [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/xrp-boost-as-bitpay-announces-worldwide-support-can-bulls-react/">XRP boost as BitPay announces worldwide support – can bulls react?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">XRP price is trading below $0.60, down 5% in the past 24 hours.</li>
<li dir="ltr">BitPay recently announced worldwide support for XRP payments.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Key price levels are at $0.55 and $0.70, respectively demand and reload zones.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/ripple/">XRP price</a> is down 5% in the past 24 hours to trade below $0.60, with bears threatening to wipe out all gains from the past month or two.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The win over SEC that catapulted the Ripple cryptocurrency higher has all but faded too. For XRP bulls, it&rsquo;s all looking ominous with prices likely to retreat to a key support base. But could a reaction be in the offing even as the market ponders its next move amid widespread stagnation?</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">XRP got a BitPay boost</h2>
<p dir="ltr">On August 4, blockchain payments provider BitPay released a major <a href="https://bitpay.com/blog/bitpay-now-supports-xrp/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">update</a> &ndash; an impending worldwide support for XRP.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">BitPay released worldwide support for XRP, allowing <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/BitPay?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#BitPay</a> users across the world to buy, store, swap and spend <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24XRP&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$XRP</a> across all BitPay solutions. </p>
<p>Learn more about XRP:<a href="https://t.co/ndvp5M0Gdp">https://t.co/ndvp5M0Gdp</a> <a href="https://t.co/CBFztrBAVh">pic.twitter.com/CBFztrBAVh</a></p>
<p>&mdash; BitPay (@BitPay) <a href="https://twitter.com/BitPay/status/1691510139008827393?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 15, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">According to the company, adding the cryptocurrency to the list of supported coins (including Bitcoin, Ethereum, Litecoin and Dogecoin) would allow merchants to accept payments in XRP from across 100 wallets.</p>
<p dir="ltr">BitPay&rsquo;s move means its customers can now buy XRP, store it or spend it on goods and services from anywhere in the world where merchants accept the top 10 altcoin.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What&rsquo;s the XRP price reaction?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The XRP market hasn&rsquo;t seen significant upside reaction in the days following the news. Indeed, prices are down 10% in the past week. However, adoption news for XRP has been steady since Ripple&rsquo;s triumph over SEC, and could see more bullish reaction if the regulator loses again. [<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sec-appeal-would-not-be-a-setback-for-ripple-lawyer-says/">Read more</a>].</p>
<p dir="ltr">Looking at the charts, the daily RSI is heading deeper into the oversold territory and more room for sellers means prices could be poised for a retest of a previous support-turned-resistance zone at $0.55. A deeper rot to lows of $0.40 is possible.</p>
<div class="fr-img-space-wrap"><span class="fr-img-caption fr-fic fr-dib fr-draggable" style="width: 600px"><span class="fr-img-wrap">
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/07/16/1692198555955-900db125-ab74-46b7-a1cc-fc0ce89b9265.png" style="width: 600px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="600" height="260"><span class="fr-inner">XRP price chart. Source:&nbsp;<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/puGwJHOM/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">TradingView</a></span></p>
<p></p></span></span>
<p class="fr-img-space-wrap2">&nbsp;However, the 100-day SMA is located here and could provide a robust buffer. A rebound in the short term could bring bulls to the 50-day SMA level &ndash; with the hurdle at round $0.62 &ndash; and highlight a return to above $0.70.&nbsp;</p>
<p class="fr-img-space-wrap2">The psychological $1.00 remains the desired short-term play, before a retest of 2021 highs.</p>
</div>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/xrp-boost-as-bitpay-announces-worldwide-support-can-bulls-react/">XRP boost as BitPay announces worldwide support – can bulls react?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/xrp-boost-as-bitpay-announces-worldwide-support-can-bulls-react/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Does Litecoin&#8217;s halving provide clues ahead of Bitcoin&#8217;s next April?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/does-litecoins-halving-provide-clues-ahead-of-bitcoins-next-april/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/does-litecoins-halving-provide-clues-ahead-of-bitcoins-next-april/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dan Ashmore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 14:31:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/does-litecoins-halving-provide-clues-ahead-of-bitcoins-next-april/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key Takeaways The next Bitcoin halving is slated for April 2024, the fourth of Bitcoin&#8217;s existence Litecoin has just undergone its fourth halving, but the price effects of Litecoin halvings in the past have not been as strong Sample size is small meaning it is hard to conclude with confidence whether halvings have tangible price [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/does-litecoins-halving-provide-clues-ahead-of-bitcoins-next-april/">Does Litecoin&#8217;s halving provide clues ahead of Bitcoin&#8217;s next April?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2 dir="ltr">Key Takeaways</h2>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">The next Bitcoin halving is slated for April 2024, the fourth of Bitcoin&rsquo;s existence</li>
<li dir="ltr">Litecoin has just undergone its fourth halving, but the price effects of Litecoin halvings in the past have not been as strong</li>
<li dir="ltr">Sample size is small meaning it is hard to conclude with confidence whether halvings have tangible price effects in the short-term</li>
<li dir="ltr">Bitcoin is a very different proposition to Litecoin, but the price action going forward of the latter will be interesting to track as we approach Bitcoin&rsquo;s next halving in April 2024</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p dir="ltr">Whether Bitcoin halvings are priced in has become a fervent topic of debate among the community. We put together an <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/are-bitcoin-halvenings-priced-in-understanding-the-price-effects-of-bitcoins-supply-cut/"><u>analysis</u></a> of this question a few weeks ago, as we now fast approach the fourth halving of Bitcoin&rsquo;s young life.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Slated for April 2024, the halving&nbsp;will cut the Bitcoin block subsidy from 6.25 Bitcoins to 3.125 Bitcoins per block, halving the issuance rate of newly created supply.</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14533733">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">We will not rehash (pun intended!) our aforementioned analysis of the upcoming halving here. Instead, we will focus on another coin: Litecoin. One of the world&rsquo;s first altcoins, it is a derivative of Bitcoin and, intriguingly, just underwent the fourth halving of its life.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Can Litecoin therefore be seen as a guinea pig ahead of Bitcoin&rsquo;s own halving next year? Well, not really, but we may be able to gain certain insights.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">First, let us examine Litecoin&rsquo;s performance through past halvings. Price data is quite illiquid prior to 2015, so the below chart omits the first halving.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14728357">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">The log scale of the chart somewhat obscures it, but the second halving in 2015 preceded strong price performance for Litecoin. On the other hand, the third halving in 2019 saw falling prices, before the trend reversed after COVID struck in 2020, when the entire crypto sector surged into the mainstream.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">It is too soon to draw conclusions regarding the fourth halving, which occured just over a week ago on August 5th. Nevertheless, Litecoin&rsquo;s halvings don&rsquo;t offer compelling evidence of a strong relationship thus far at least. Furthermore, like most questions in crypto, the sample size is so small that even if they did precipitate aggressive price rises immediately, that would not necessarily mean there is causation. &nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin is not Litecoin, but again, we may be able to derive clues from the pattern in ascertaining the effect of halvings on the former, even if we can&rsquo;t be confident given the sample size issues. First, let us now look at Bitcoin&rsquo;s price action while marking the halving events:</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14728571">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">The pattern is clear. Typically, we have seen outsized volatility in the months leading up to a halving, before strong outperformance on the other side. The outperformance has also grown smaller with each halving, perhaps unsurprising given the market cap has grown so much in the four years between each event. &nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">So, why has the effect of halvings on Bitcoin been, at least optically, larger than the same events on Litecoin? The first theory takes us to the heart of the debate on whether halvings are really priced in: while previous events have preceded steep inclines for Bitcoin, they have also lined up well with global liquidity cycles.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The below chart from Fidelity shows this well. There is perhaps no greater influence on the valuations of risk assets than central bank balance sheets, and the halvings have lined up incredibly well with the expansion of those same balance sheets.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/07/15/1692092799057-7f270707-141a-457f-88a1-35379ccf079e.png" style="width: 600px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="600" height="319"></p>
<p dir="ltr">The thing is, the next halving could well line up with an expansion in liquidity again. The previous eighteen months have seen one of the fastest rate-hiking cycles in recent history, with the Fed funds rate now above 5%. Now, looking at probabilities implied by the futures market, the market is anticipating that the hikes are coming to a close (if they haven&rsquo;t done so already).&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Looking further forward towards the time period around the halving (April), futures imply that <em>rate cuts&nbsp;</em>could come into play. Not to mention, when we look at the yield curve, it is currently at the deepest level of inversion since the early 80s. The bottom line is this: the fourth halving, through sheer chance, could again line up miraculously well with global liquidity cycles.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14728625">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">Of course, the macro situation has been changing incessantly, and there is every chance that forecasts around the liquidity cycle could flip, and the halving won&rsquo;t line up as well as it has done in the past.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">This is where Litecoin may come in. With its halvings landing at different dates to Bitcoin in the past, yet not boosting prices as much as the orange coin saw, perhaps it is just a timing thing, whether macro-related or other? Looking at Litecoin&rsquo;s price action compared to Bitcoin, the duo are tightly correlated, like many altcoins in the space. If Litecoin&rsquo;s halving does not cause a slight outperformance this time compared to Bitcoin or other coins, what would be the explanation?&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14728658">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">Ultimately, like we keep saying, the sample size is small. Bitcoin has only experienced three halvings, and one could even argue that it was only the recent event in 2020 that occurred while the asset was trading with sufficient liquidity.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Litecoin&rsquo;s less explosive price action after its own halvings do perhaps throw further doubt on the theory that a 50% cut to the new supply issuance will inevitably kick up the price. And yet, Litecoin is not Bitcoin, so the debate will rage on.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Either way, revisiting Litecoin&rsquo;s price performance around the time of Bitcoin halving will be interesting, because by then it will have had around eight months post-halving and may present a more relevant reference point.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/does-litecoins-halving-provide-clues-ahead-of-bitcoins-next-april/">Does Litecoin&#8217;s halving provide clues ahead of Bitcoin&#8217;s next April?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/does-litecoins-halving-provide-clues-ahead-of-bitcoins-next-april/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Litecoin price pattern points to an 18% plunge to $64</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/litecoin-price-pattern-points-to-an-18-plunge-to-64/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 12:29:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/litecoin-price-pattern-points-to-an-18-plunge-to-64/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Litecoin has dropped by more than 30% from its highest level this year. Focus now shifts to the upcoming FOMC minutes. Litecoin price continued falling on Wednesday as focus shifted to the upcoming FOMC minutes. LTC plunged to a low of $78.78, the lowest level since June 20th. The coin has fallen by over 32% [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/litecoin-price-pattern-points-to-an-18-plunge-to-64/">Litecoin price pattern points to an 18% plunge to $64</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Litecoin has dropped by more than 30% from its highest level this year.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Focus now shifts to the upcoming FOMC minutes.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/litecoin/"><u>Litecoin</u></a> price continued falling on Wednesday as focus shifted to the upcoming FOMC minutes. LTC plunged to a low of $78.78, the lowest level since June 20th. The coin has fallen by over 32% from its highest level in July. Other coins like Bitcoin, Ethereum, and XRP have also retreated.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">FOMC minutes ahead</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Litecoin has lost momentum in the past few weeks as the hype of the recent&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/litecoin-completes-third-halving-block-reward-cut-to-6-25-ltc/"><u>halving</u></a> event faded. In most periods, cryptocurrencies tend to do well ahead of a major event and plunge shortly thereafter. This is known as buying the rumour, selling the news.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The next key catalyst that will move the LTC price will be the upcoming FOMC minutes. These minutes will show the deliberations that happened in the last meeting. In it, the bank decided to hike interest rates by 0.25%.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In the past, Fed minutes have moved key financial assets like cryptocurrencies and stocks. However, there is a likelihood that LTC and other cryptocurrencies will react mildly to the minutes.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Besides, they have failed to react positively to important events recently. For example, Litecoin and Bitcoin remained in a consolidation mode after last week&rsquo;s US inflation data. The numbers showed that US inflation, except housing, is falling at a quicker rate than expected.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, there is a likelihood that the Fed will pause hiking rates. Some analysts believe that the bank will even start cutting rates in the first quarter of 2024 since risks are rising.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin and Litecoin also ignored important news on China. The country has published weak economic numbers recently. For example, its imports and exports have slipped while retail sales and industrial production rose at a slower pace than expected.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Litecoin price forecast</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/07/16/1692188436220-f883b05e-c389-4aee-971d-47be21a47d8f.png" style="width: 548px;height: 266.693px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="548" height="266.693"></p>
<p dir="ltr">The daily chart shows that LTC price has been in a downward trend after peaking at $114 in July. It has already dropped below the 50-day moving average and the crucial support at $82.50, the lowest point on June 28th.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The two lines of the MACD indicator have moved to almost minus 3 while the Relative Strength Index (RSI) has moved to the oversold level. It also remains below the important resistance at $103.60, the highest point in February and March.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, Litecoin has more downside going forward, with the next level to watch being $64.77, the lowest swing on March 11th. This price is ~18% below the current level.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy Litecoin</h2>
<p dir="ltr">
        </p><div class="relative">

            <div class="mb-3  pb-6  px-6  bg-slate-50  rounded-xl  ps-shadow-inner">

    <h3 class="inline-block">
        eToro    </h3>

            <p class="text-sm">eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>
    
    <div class="w-full  flex  flex-wrap  items-start  flex-col  gap-2">

        
<a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=MTQ5OTgz&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="nofollow sponsored noopener" target="_self" class="inline-block  text-indigo-600  underline  hover:text-indigo-200  ease-in-out  duration-300  transition-all" title="Buy LTC with eToro today">Buy LTC with eToro today</a>

    </div>

</div><div class="  pb-6  px-6  bg-slate-50  rounded-xl  ps-shadow-inner">

    <h3 class="inline-block">
        Public    </h3>

            <p class="text-sm">Public is an investing platform that allows you to invest stocks, ETFs, crypto, and alternative assets like fine art and collectibles&mdash;all in one place.</p>
    
    <div class="w-full  flex  flex-wrap  items-start  flex-col  gap-2">

        
<a href="/visit/public-crypto?guid=MTQ5OTgz&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="nofollow sponsored noopener" target="_self" class="inline-block  text-indigo-600  underline  hover:text-indigo-200  ease-in-out  duration-300  transition-all" title="Buy LTC with Public today">Buy LTC with Public today</a>

    </div>

</div>
        </div>



<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/litecoin-price-pattern-points-to-an-18-plunge-to-64/">Litecoin price pattern points to an 18% plunge to $64</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Memu&#8217;s presale is nearly $2 million. Is the token set to explode?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memus-presale-is-nearly-2-million-is-the-token-set-to-explode/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memus-presale-is-nearly-2-million-is-the-token-set-to-explode/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Motiur Rahman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 12:24:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technical Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memus-presale-is-nearly-2-million-is-the-token-set-to-explode/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Shiba Memu has raised $2 million in a fast-happening presale Investors have been thrilled by Shiba Memu&#8217;s AI capabilities set to make it a marketing powerhouse Shiba Memu has a potential higher 1,000% price increase as the project gains popularity Shiba Memu (SHMU) buyers are shy of the $2 million mark regarding the value of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memus-presale-is-nearly-2-million-is-the-token-set-to-explode/">Shiba Memu&#8217;s presale is nearly $2 million. Is the token set to explode?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu has raised $2 million in a fast-happening presale</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Investors have been thrilled by Shiba Memu&rsquo;s AI capabilities set to make it a marketing powerhouse</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu has a potential higher 1,000% price increase as the project gains popularity</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu (SHMU) buyers are shy of the $2 million mark regarding the value of tokens bought. Since launching the presale a few weeks ago, token buying has been unstoppable. At this point, it is fair to say that buyers have huge bets for the new meme kid on the block. That positions the token to a potential price surge after listing. Investors can purchase the token via the project&rsquo;s&nbsp;<a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>website</u></a>.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Is Shiba Memu the best meme cryptocurrency of 2023?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">There are notable crypto names in the meme scene. Dogecoin and Shiba Inu have been the top dogs for quite a while. Still, new names like PEPE debuted in 2023 and became instant sensations. Undoubtedly, the meme space has been growing fast. The market hit a market cap of $20 billion in early 2022 from $0 in early 2020.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Nonetheless, there has been a notable challenge for most, if not all, meme cryptocurrencies. They have yet to replicate gains and remain sustainable to generate lasting returns. For Dogecoin and Shiba Inu, a prolonged bear market has caught up with the assets.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The search for a meme token likely to remain powerful and deliver lasting returns is on. Shiba Memu looks like that alpha edge investors have been looking into meme investments.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Against the backdrop of enjoying the privileges of being a meme, Shiba Memu aims to be sustainable. The project is built with an artificial intelligence angle. With AI, the focus is to make Shiba Memu powerful and intelligent, capable of doing more than humans. Shiba Memu will write its own PR, devise a marketing strategy, and generate FOMO for itself. After all, meme tokens are mostly driven by hype.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">But think of what AI can do in creative advertising. It can crawl the web and find the best ideas in marketing. The AI can then package the information in a fun, friendly, and understandable manner. As an AI-led project, Shiba Memu will feature these capabilities.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The added advantages of AI in Shiba Memu make the project one of the best in crypto right now. As such, Shiba Memu could be the unlikely hero of 2023 while the rest of the sector sleeps.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Is Shiba Memu a 10x investment?&nbsp;</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">It is highly speculative how much potential a newly launched token could rise. However, a 10x increase in value is an understatement, as meme tokens have risen up to 50x.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">So far, Shiba Memu has been a presale king, hinting at how much potential the token has. Thus, the future of the token is huge, which could start to get realised after listings in 2024.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The possible price drivers for the token are hype due to ingenious self-marketing and demand. As the world evolves through AI, we could see more demand being unlocked for Shiba Memu.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The project also allows users to interact with the software through an AI dashboard. They can ask questions, give suggestions, and be informed of the latest in creative advertising. This could unlock demand and make Shiba Memu a more than 10x investment.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>What are the benefits of buying Shiba Memu in the presale?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu&rsquo;s presale is quite unique. The price started at $0.011125 and is now at $0.020575. The price of the token will be $0.0244 when the presale ends. The increases have been due to SHMU tokenomics. The tokenomics will see SHMU value double by the end of the 8-week presale period.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Essentially, Shiba Memu&rsquo;s price increases daily at 6 pm GMT. This allows buyers to see investment increases for their tokens daily and have a meme vibe. At the end of the presale, investors will receive their tokens and be set for huge benefits as SHMU lists.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memus-presale-is-nearly-2-million-is-the-token-set-to-explode/">Shiba Memu&#8217;s presale is nearly $2 million. Is the token set to explode?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memus-presale-is-nearly-2-million-is-the-token-set-to-explode/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
