<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 14:52:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Morgan Stanley Posts Q4 2022 Report, Receives Huge Boost from Wealth Management Revenue</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/morgan-stanley-q4-2022-report/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/morgan-stanley-q4-2022-report/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 14:52:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wall Street]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[morgan stanley]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[morgan stanley shares]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[morgan stanley stock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ms]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=232886</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/morgan-stanley-q4-2022-report/">Morgan Stanley Posts Q4 2022 Report, Receives Huge Boost from Wealth Management Revenue</a></p>
<p>New York banking powerhouse Morgan Stanley has posted its Q4 2022 financial report, which reveals mixed results.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/morgan-stanley-q4-2022-report/">Morgan Stanley Posts Q4 2022 Report, Receives Huge Boost from Wealth Management Revenue</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/morgan-stanley-q4-2022-report/">Morgan Stanley Posts Q4 2022 Report, Receives Huge Boost from Wealth Management Revenue</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/morgan-stanley/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Morgan Stanley</a> (NYSE: MS) recently posted its <a href="https://www.morganstanley.com/content/dam/msdotcom/en/about-us-ir/shareholder/4q2022.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Q4 2022 earnings report</a>, surpassing consensus estimates. The New York-based banking giant received a significant boost in its latest quarterly bottom line from record wealth management revenue.</p>
<p>For Q4 2022, Morgan Stanley reported a revenue haul of $12.75 billion compared to the $12.64 billion Wall Street analysts expected. In addition, the leading bank’s earnings per share (EPS) for the period ended December 31st came in at $1.31 after adjustments. Furthermore, the company saw a record net revenue of $6.63 billion in the latest quarter from wealth management. This respected figure represented a 6% increase from the year-ago period and benefited from higher interest rate-induced net interest income. In addition, Morgan Stanley’s latest record wealth management earnings also came about as a result of organic bank lending growth.</p>
<p>Morgan Stanley shares rose more than 1% during premarket trading after its earnings report. The company’s stock is up approximately 8% since the start of the year, following a 13% drawdown last year.</p>
<h2>Morgan Stanley Q4 2022 Headwinds</h2>
<p>Morgan Stanley Chairman and chief executive James Gorman commented on the company’s latest financial report in a statement. According to Gorman, the investment management and financial services behemoth “reported solid fourth-quarter results amidst a difficult market environment.”</p>
<p>Indeed, it was not all rosy for Morgan Stanley during the fourth quarter of last year. Despite beating earnings estimates, the banking giant’s net income declined from $3.59 billion, or $2.01, to $2.11 billion, or $1.26 per share year-over-year (YoY). Furthermore, the Manhattan-situated financial powerhouse also suffered a significant downturn in investment banking activities. This contraction came amid a plunge in initial public offerings (IPOs) and debt and equity issuance.</p>
<p>According to Morgan Stanley’s investment management unit, there was a 15% YoY decline in fourth-quarter revenue. The bank says that investment management realized a gain of $1.46 billion amid the Federal Reserve’s aggressive rate hike policy. Meanwhile, Morgan Stanley’s assets under management (AUM) also contracted to $1.30 trillion from $1.57 trillion in 2022.</p>
<p>Morgan Stanley’s Q4 revenue from investment banking is $1.25 billion, representing a lofty 49% drawdown from the year-ago period. The bank also explained that the decline was due to the substantial downswing in global equity underwriting volumes. In addition, Morgan Stanley ascribed investment banking underperformance to lower merger and acquisition (M&amp;A) performances.</p>
<p>In the latest period, Morgan Stanley set aside $85 million for credit losses. This sum compares unfavorably to the relatively minimal $5 million the bank earmarked for the exact cause in the year-ago period.</p>
<h2>Headcount Trimming</h2>
<p>Last December, Morgan Stanley cut roughly 2% of its workforce, impacting around 1,600 people in an 81,567 headcount. The bank deemed this exercise necessary to cull underperformers. Commenting on the staff cuts at the time, Gorman explained that “some people are going to be let go.” According to the company CEO, “In most businesses, that’s what you do after many years of growth.”</p>
<p>Morgan Stanley claimed that the annual culling of the weakest workers had been put on hold during the pandemic.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/n26-crypto-trading-expansion/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/morgan-stanley-q4-2022-report/">Morgan Stanley Posts Q4 2022 Report, Receives Huge Boost from Wealth Management Revenue</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/morgan-stanley-q4-2022-report/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>German Online Bank N26 Announces Crypto Trading Expansion to 5 More European Nations</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/n26-crypto-trading-expansion/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/n26-crypto-trading-expansion/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 13:18:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FinTech News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[n26]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=232872</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/n26-crypto-trading-expansion/">German Online Bank N26 Announces Crypto Trading Expansion to 5 More European Nations</a></p>
<p>N26 recently launched N26 Crypto, a new digital currency trading initiative it hopes would gain traction across the West.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/n26-crypto-trading-expansion/">German Online Bank N26 Announces Crypto Trading Expansion to 5 More European Nations</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/n26-crypto-trading-expansion/">German Online Bank N26 Announces Crypto Trading Expansion to 5 More European Nations</a></p>
<p>German neobank <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/n26/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">N26</a> has announced an expansion of its <a href="https://n26.com/en-at/crypto" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">N26 Crypto trading</a> product to Germany, Switzerland, Belgium, Ireland, and Portugal. This development lets customers in these countries gain access to and trade a suite of more than 200 digital currencies. The company said it would roll out the expanded trading gradually over subsequent weeks.</p>
<p>N26 pitches its N26 Crypto scheme as a perk for premium customers. Account holders in its N26 Metal program will be privy to Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a>) transaction fees as low as 1%. Reports also state that standard N26 customers will also have access.</p>
<h2>N26 Executives Weigh in on Crypto Trading Expansion</h2>
<p>N26 co-founder and co-CEO Valentin Stalf weighed in on the growing popularity of crypto trading, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Market fluctuations aside, cryptocurrencies continue to remain a requested and interesting asset class for investors and a growing part of the financial system. Cryptocurrency trading is often the entry point to investing for a new generation of investors who are looking to explore ways to grow their wealth.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The decision by N26 to extend crypto trading to five further European Union (EU) territories follows its <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/n26-crypto-trading-services-austria/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Austrian debut</a> in late 2022. As it stands, the German online bank already has €6 billion in assets under management (AUM) and has an existing partnership with Bitpanda. This partnership sees N26 rendering services to the asset management division of the Austrian crypto trading platform.</p>
<p>According to company executives, N26&#8217;s banking experience is always centered around customer needs. The virtual banking platform has always provided features that facilitate seamless money management. As N26&#8217;s chief product officer, Giles BianRosa, put it:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;With N26 Crypto, we have created a simple, intuitive product that integrates seamlessly into N26&#8217;s fully-regulated banking experience where one&#8217;s bank balance, savings, and investment portfolio sit side by side &#8211; with cryptocurrencies being the first asset class we intend to offer.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>N26 Crypto&#8217;s interface is designed to be accessible, providing real-time trading logs and lucid visual graphs. This way, company officials explain that customers can accurately handle portfolio performance.</p>
<h2>How the Feature Works</h2>
<p>Customers who fulfill all KYC background checks can access crypto trading from the N26 app&#8217;s new &#8216;Finance&#8217; tab. Opening a position simply requires selecting the desired token and preferred trading amount. Following this step, the app deducts the cash equivalent of the trade from the user&#8217;s bank balance. The corresponding coins will appear almost instantly in the trader&#8217;s crypto portfolio.</p>
<p>The same also applies when customers close an open trading position in their N26 Crypto. Funds are made available immediately in their primary bank account at the closure of any trading position. N26 also has drag-and-drop functionality for both transaction types to further aid the process.</p>
<p>N26&#8217;s expansion comes at a time when the industry is still feeling the ill effects of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a>&#8216;s collapse last November.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/chinas-e-cny-purchase-securities/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/n26-crypto-trading-expansion/">German Online Bank N26 Announces Crypto Trading Expansion to 5 More European Nations</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/n26-crypto-trading-expansion/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>China’s CBDC, e-CNY Used to Purchase Securities for First Time</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/chinas-e-cny-purchase-securities/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/chinas-e-cny-purchase-securities/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 13:13:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital yuan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[e-cny]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pboc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Soochow Securities]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=232873</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/chinas-e-cny-purchase-securities/">China’s CBDC, e-CNY Used to Purchase Securities for First Time</a></p>
<p>Previously, the Chinese CBDC has been subjected to a series of retail trials in some of its most technologically advanced regions including but not limited to Shanghai and Suzhou.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/chinas-e-cny-purchase-securities/">China’s CBDC, e-CNY Used to Purchase Securities for First Time</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/chinas-e-cny-purchase-securities/">China’s CBDC, e-CNY Used to Purchase Securities for First Time</a></p>
<p>As the most advanced economy with an active Central Bank Digital Currency (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-central-bank-digital-currency-cbdc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CBDC</a>) in circulation, China’s Digital Yuan (e-CNY) is now gaining a more customized utility in the country. As <a href="https://www.cs.com.cn/qs/202301/t20230116_6319196.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reported</a> by the China Securities Journal, the e-CNY can now be used to purchase securities, as it was used for this purpose for the first time on Monday.</p>
<p>The purchase of securities and wealth management service products was facilitated with the help of the Bank of China digital wallet. Following this inaugural move, the expansion of the use of the Digital Yuan for the purchase of securities can be accessed through the Soochow Securities mobile application.</p>
<p>The People’s Bank of China (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/peoples-bank-of-china/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">PBoC</a>) has remained very deliberate with respect to its research and development efforts bordering on the Digital Yuan. With many use cases in the pipeline to be implemented, the purchase of securities products was resorted to as one of the first important mega shifts to integrate the CBDC into the broader digital and financial economy.</p>
<p>The purchase of securities with China’s CBDC, e-CNY through Soochow was an initiated that was designed in alliance with the “Bank of China, China Unicom, and other digital renminbi research institutions to carry out in-depth research, and formed multiple digital currency innovative application solutions in the securities field in terms of digital currency payment, smart contracts, and interconnection.”</p>
<p>Designed to cater to the complex financial needs of stakeholders in the Chinese financial ecosystem, Soochow Securities has detailed plans to continue to develop products and services that can easily be powered by the Digital Yuan ahead of its mega nationwide launch.</p>
<p>Amongst its core aims is to enable securities investors to “experience the safety, convenience, and efficiency of digital RMB services, and drive the high-quality development of the securities industry and Suzhou&#8217;s local digital economy.”</p>
<h2>China’s e-CNY and the Growing CBDC Adoption</h2>
<p>As <a href="https://www.yicaiglobal.com/news/e-yuan-app-adds-payment-function-for-when-mobiles-are-offline-out-of-power" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reported</a> by the local media outlet, Yicai Global, China’s e-CNY was made available for transactions in offline environments pushing further the boundaries of the CBDC. Per the report, the Digital Yuan was made available in cash circulation for the first time.</p>
<p>The Chinese CBDC has been subjected to a series of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-cbdc-tap-payments/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">retail trials</a> in some of its most technologically advanced regions including but not limited to Shanghai and Suzhou.</p>
<p>The Digital Yuan was a prominent part of the Beijing Olympics Games in early 2022, and though the government has not shared official data on when the new legal tender will be made officially available to every member of the public nationwide, it has continued to increase accessibility to the new money in the most creative ways.</p>
<p>Amongst the most ambitious use case of the e-CNY at this time include the use of the new money for <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-e-cny-public-transport/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">payment</a> of public transport fares and its <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/digital-yuan-cbdc-didi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">acceptance</a> by ride-hailing giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/didi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Didi Global Inc</a> (OTCMKTS: DIDIY)</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-crypto-mining-stocks-highs/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/chinas-e-cny-purchase-securities/">China’s CBDC, e-CNY Used to Purchase Securities for First Time</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/chinas-e-cny-purchase-securities/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>With Bitcoin Bounce Back, Crypto Mining Stocks Surge to Yearly Highs</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-crypto-mining-stocks-highs/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-crypto-mining-stocks-highs/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 11:37:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitfarms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[core scientific]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hive blockchain technologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vaneck]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=232842</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-crypto-mining-stocks-highs/">With Bitcoin Bounce Back, Crypto Mining Stocks Surge to Yearly Highs</a></p>
<p>A strong 28% jump in the BTC over the last two weeks has given crypto miners some relief after they faced acute financial stress last year. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-crypto-mining-stocks-highs/">With Bitcoin Bounce Back, Crypto Mining Stocks Surge to Yearly Highs</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-crypto-mining-stocks-highs/">With Bitcoin Bounce Back, Crypto Mining Stocks Surge to Yearly Highs</a></p>
<p>The strong rebound in the Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a>) price earlier this week has had a very positive <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-01-17/crypto-mining-stocks-eye-best-month-in-a-year-atop-bitcoin-jump" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">impact</a> on the crypto mining stocks. Stocks of the crypto mining firms have recorded their best monthly performance in over a year.</p>
<p>This has relieved the troubled miners a bit who had to sell a significant portion of their mined Bitcoins to boost liquidity last year in 2022. Just within the first two weeks of 2023, the top BTC mining firm Bitfarms saw a 140% surge in its stock price. Similarly, the stock of Marathon Digital Holdings clocked a 120% surge. During the same period, Hive Blockchain Technologies saw its stock value jump by 100%.</p>
<p>With the Bitcoin price advancing by more than 28% since the beginning of 2023, the 20-member MVIS Global Digital Assets Mining Index has gained more than 64% so far. This has been the best month for the index since its inception at the end of 2021.</p>
<p>At the same time, the Luxor Hashprice Index which measures how much a miner can expect to earn from the computing power dedicated to the Bitcoin network is up by 21% this year. It shows that a higher Bitcoin price leads to bigger rewards.</p>
<h2>Will Crypto Mining Stocks Continue to Surge Further if Bitcoin Price Grows?</h2>
<p>Despite the recent pump in the BTC price, it is still trading at a 70% discount from its all-time high of $69,000. After last year&#8217;s digital asset rout, cash-strapped miners have been reducing loans after facing acute financial stress.</p>
<p>Just last month in December, Core Scientific, the largest Bitcoin miner by computing power <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/core-scientific-bankruptcy-mining/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">declared</a> bankruptcy. Matthew Sigel, head of digital-asset research at fund manager VanEck warned about the substantial debt levels of many crypto miner, along with the sharp slide in the price of Bitcoin mining rigs. Sigel added:</p>
<blockquote><p>“It appears more attractive to start a new Bitcoin mining venture than to try to pick the bottom in many of these listed stocks right now&#8221;.</p></blockquote>
<p>As inflation cools, the broader markets have turned optimistic that further interest rate hikes won&#8217;t be aggressive. As a result, riskier investments like crypto have rallied since the beginning of 2023. But if this market narrative shifts, the quick gains in crypto could reverse very fast.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/activision-blizzard-netease-rejected-proposal/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-crypto-mining-stocks-highs/">With Bitcoin Bounce Back, Crypto Mining Stocks Surge to Yearly Highs</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-crypto-mining-stocks-highs/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Activision Blizzard Announced NetEase Rejected Proposal to Extend Partnership</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/activision-blizzard-netease-rejected-proposal/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/activision-blizzard-netease-rejected-proposal/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 11:34:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Deals News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gaming News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[activision blizzard]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[microsoft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[netease]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=232853</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/activision-blizzard-netease-rejected-proposal/">Activision Blizzard Announced NetEase Rejected Proposal to Extend Partnership</a></p>
<p>US gaming developer Activision Blizzard is looking for a new Chinese partnership after NetEase turned down its latest proposal.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/activision-blizzard-netease-rejected-proposal/">Activision Blizzard Announced NetEase Rejected Proposal to Extend Partnership</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/activision-blizzard-netease-rejected-proposal/">Activision Blizzard Announced NetEase Rejected Proposal to Extend Partnership</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/blizzard/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Activision Blizzard</a> (NASDAQ: ATVI) recently disclosed that Chinese publisher NetEase <a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/blizzard-says-chinas-netease-rejects-proposal-extend-partnership-six-months-2023-01-17/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">rejected</a> a proposal to extend their long-running partnership. According to the US video game holding company, NetEase rejected the opportunity to extend their collaboration by six months.</p>
<p>In a statement on the microblogging site Weibo, Activision Chinese subsidiary Blizzard China wrote:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;It is a pity that NetEase is not willing to extend services of our game for another six months on the basis of existing terms as we look for a new partner.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Blizzard China further stated that it would discontinue its game services in a few days due to the NetEase impasse. However, Activision Blizzard revealed last December that it was in talks with potential partners. The Santa Monica-based video game developer looks to continue offering its hit World of Warcraft game to Chinese end users.</p>
<p>In the meantime, Blizzard China will allow gamers to save their game progress and some user data offline before January 23rd. Gamers should be able to restore their progress in the game once Activision secures a new Chinese publisher.</p>
<h2>Activision Blizzard-NetEase Development Follows November Impasse</h2>
<p>The Activision Blizzard-NetEase development comes after the video game developer&#8217;s November announcement that it would end its 14-year partnership with the Chinese publisher. Activision&#8217;s announcement sent shockwaves throughout the video game industry because of how lucrative the deal is perceived to be.</p>
<p>On its part, NetEase, the second-largest gaming firm in China, also touched on the pending cessation of its partnership with Activision&#8217;s Chinese subsidiary. In a November earnings brief, the Hangzhou-based company stated that despite valiant efforts to negotiate with Activision, there was no headway. In addition, NetEase said that it found the US company&#8217;s proposed terms unacceptable. Furthermore, the Chinese internet tech service provider said that it would discontinue Activision&#8217;s game service in China on January 23rd.</p>
<p>NetEase rose through the ranks to emerge as a gaming behemoth partly by publishing Activision&#8217;s games in China. However, the online content, community, communications, and commerce service provider has since grown its own game development capability and capacity. As it stands, NetEase&#8217;s in-house games now account for more than 60% of its entire revenue.</p>
<h2>Microsoft Acquisition Development</h2>
<p>In other Activision-related news, the Federal Trade Commission (FTC) stands <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftc-microsoft-activision-blizzard/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">firm</a> in its resolve to block a <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/microsoft-corporation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Microsoft</a> (NASDAQ: MSFT) acquisition. This development comes after the software giant announced plans to <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-activision-blizzard-68-7b-deal/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">acquire</a> the gaming developer for $69 billion a year ago. However, the FTC reckons acquiring Activision would imbue Microsoft with an unfair advantage within the gaming space. Should the tech giant take over the gaming company, it would control wildly-popular gaming franchises like &#8216;Call of Duty&#8217; and &#8216;War of Warcraft.&#8217; This possibility could also see Microsoft&#8217;s Xbox have the edge over rivals Sony PlayStation in the war of video game consoles.</p>
<p>However, Microsoft maintains that it is willing to share access with Sony to Activision&#8217;s fabled intellectual property for a sustained period of time.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bank-of-england-digital-pound-digital-euro/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/activision-blizzard-netease-rejected-proposal/">Activision Blizzard Announced NetEase Rejected Proposal to Extend Partnership</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/activision-blizzard-netease-rejected-proposal/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bank of England to Backtrack on Digital Pound as Digital Euro Receives Major Boost</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bank-of-england-digital-pound-digital-euro/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bank-of-england-digital-pound-digital-euro/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 11:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[andrew bailey]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bank of england]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital pound]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digitalpound]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Euro Zone]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[european union]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fiat]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=232821</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bank-of-england-digital-pound-digital-euro/">Bank of England to Backtrack on Digital Pound as Digital Euro Receives Major Boost</a></p>
<p>Several nations trying to adopt CBDCs have maintained that digital currencies should only complement cash rather than outrightly replace them.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bank-of-england-digital-pound-digital-euro/">Bank of England to Backtrack on Digital Pound as Digital Euro Receives Major Boost</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bank-of-england-digital-pound-digital-euro/">Bank of England to Backtrack on Digital Pound as Digital Euro Receives Major Boost</a></p>
<p>Andrew Bailey, the Bank of England (BoE) governor, has shared his thoughts on the idea of the country&#8217;s central bank digital currency (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-central-bank-digital-currency-cbdc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CBDC</a>) &#8211; the digital pound. Bailey <a href="https://www.scmp.com/tech/policy/article/3207081/bank-england-sceptical-digital-pound-euro-zone-backs-work-digital-euro" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">believes</a> that there might be no need for a wholesale CBDC. According to him, his reason borders on the fact that the country already enjoys a “wholesale central bank money settlement system with a major upgrade.”</p>
<h2>Digital Pound Is Not a Priority, Says BoE Governor</h2>
<p>The BoE governor stated that England is not in any way trying to abolish the retail use of cash. At least, not for the time being. So, he believes that changing retail payments now will only amount to a misplacement of priorities. For him, there is no conviction that retail payments need any such upgrades at the moment. He wrote:</p>
<blockquote><p>“We have to be very clear what problem we are trying to solve here before we get carried away by the technology and the idea.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Additionally, Bailey&#8217;s reservation may also be due to recent comments from a former BoE adviser on the costs and potential problems of launching a CBDC.</p>
<h2>Eurozone Countries Intensify Efforts on Digital Euro</h2>
<p>Meanwhile, it might be noteworthy that BoE&#8217;s intention to stop pushing for a digital pound is coming at an impeccable time. Bailey’s statement came a few moments after CBDC development in the eurozone received a major boost. Finance ministers from member countries of the eurozone just recently <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tether-comes-under-threat-but-snowfall-protocol-stands-strong-while-eu-approves-digital-euro/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">approved</a> work to continue with the upcoming digital euro. The ministers shared the approval via a <a href="https://www.ecb.europa.eu/paym/digital_euro/investigation/governance/shared/files/ecb.degov230116_eurogroupstocktake.en.pdf?55d13366cc74303c85f996ec9f60ab47" target="_blank" rel="noopener">public statement</a> on Monday, January 16.</p>
<p>It is expected that the European Union EU will publish a draft law this year, that will integrate the digital euro into its laws. But that is after it must have found out from the European Central Bank, the results of its study of the potential digital euro.</p>
<p>For what it&#8217;s worth, however, several nations trying to adopt CBDCs have maintained that digital currencies should only complement cash. This means that they are not intended to outrightly replace fiat. Rather, they&#8217;ll offer a wider range of payment forms and improve financial inclusion.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/animoca-cryptoslam-forcast-news/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bank-of-england-digital-pound-digital-euro/">Bank of England to Backtrack on Digital Pound as Digital Euro Receives Major Boost</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bank-of-england-digital-pound-digital-euro/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Animoca Founder Yat Siu Orchestrates Merger of CryptoSlam and Forcast.News</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/animoca-cryptoslam-forcast-news/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/animoca-cryptoslam-forcast-news/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 11:06:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[animoca brands]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CryptoSlam]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Forkast.News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[yat siu]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=232834</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/animoca-cryptoslam-forcast-news/">Animoca Founder Yat Siu Orchestrates Merger of CryptoSlam and Forcast.News</a></p>
<p>The combined CryptoSlam and Forkast.news entity will devise creative means to attain profitability.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/animoca-cryptoslam-forcast-news/">Animoca Founder Yat Siu Orchestrates Merger of CryptoSlam and Forcast.News</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/animoca-cryptoslam-forcast-news/">Animoca Founder Yat Siu Orchestrates Merger of CryptoSlam and Forcast.News</a></p>
<p>In a bid to further cushion the growing strain in the digital currency ecosystem, Animoca Brands Founder and Chairman, Yat Siu has engineered the merger of CryptoSlam and Forkast.News, two of the companies in its portfolio. As <a href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/animoca-portfolio-firms-merge-to-form-crypto-news-site-1.1870995">reported</a> by Bloomberg, Yat Siu introduced the founder of CryptoSlam, Randy Wasinger, and Forkast.News founder Angie Lau, and got the discussions for the merger off of the ground.</p>
<p>CryptoSlam is a platform that curates data about the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/">Non-Fungible Token</a> (NFT) world while Forkast.News offers video journalism that is tailored to the cryptocurrency ecosystem. The combined entity has now been renamed Forkast Labs and will offer the two services in a more coordinated way.</p>
<p>The combined entity will have about 60 staff and both Lau and Wasinger will co-lead the firm as Chief Executive Officers. There are no details shared about the size of the deal and whether one of the two founders will have a bigger stake at Forkast Labs.</p>
<p>The merger was seen as a very necessary one to jointly combat the bearish sentiments amongst investors who became cautious of injecting money into the crypto ecosystem following the bouts of bankruptcies the industry experienced in 2022. The latest of these <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-exchange-files-for-bankruptcy/">bankruptcies</a> was that of FTX Derivatives Exchange. FTX was faced with a liquidity run on its platform back in early November last year and filed the bankruptcy on the 11 of the same month.</p>
<p>While there’s been no news of a direct contagion of the firm’s collapse with either of CryptoSlam or Forkast.News, Yat Siu believes a merger will help to cushion the effects of any likely impact in both the near and long term.</p>
<p>“This industry is very unstable and rocky,” Siu said. “People have to be able to weather these storms together.”</p>
<p>Both firms have made their marks in the crypto ecosystem, and have dedicated followership and user base, two major factors the combined entity requires to succeed.</p>
<h2>CryptoSlam and Forkast.News to Jointly Pursue Productivity</h2>
<p>The strain the crypto ecosystem has experienced over the past year has pushed the few firms that have not gone bankrupt to start searching for new cash injections in a bid to stay profitable. The combined CryptoSlam and Forkast.news entity will also devise creative means to attain profitability according to Angie Lau.</p>
<p>Animoca Brands participated in the $9 million seed round that was raised by CryptoSlam about a year ago and the Yat Siu lead venture capital firm also injected capital into Forkast.News when the news site raised $1.9 million.</p>
<p>Out of the two firms, the Bloomberg report detailed that Forkast.News has been running on a deficit for some time, making it a very big beneficiary of the current transition to Forkast Labs. The new entity will compete with other known news and data providers Cointelegraph, Coindesk, and Coinspeaker amongst others.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/japan-tougher-crypto-regulations/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/animoca-cryptoslam-forcast-news/">Animoca Founder Yat Siu Orchestrates Merger of CryptoSlam and Forcast.News</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/animoca-cryptoslam-forcast-news/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Japan Pushes for Tougher Crypto Regulations</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/japan-tougher-crypto-regulations/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/japan-tougher-crypto-regulations/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Babafemi Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 10:58:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx japan]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=232764</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/japan-tougher-crypto-regulations/">Japan Pushes for Tougher Crypto Regulations</a></p>
<p>Japan is also using its position on the International Financial Stability Board to push for global regulations of the cryptocurrency industry.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/japan-tougher-crypto-regulations/">Japan Pushes for Tougher Crypto Regulations</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/japan-tougher-crypto-regulations/">Japan Pushes for Tougher Crypto Regulations</a></p>

<p>Japanese financial regulators have urged their counterparts globally to toughen crypto regulations, according to a Bloomberg <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-01-16/japan-pushes-global-counterparts-to-regulate-crypto-like-banks" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a>. The call was made by the Deputy Director-General of the Financial Services Agency’s Strategy Development and Management Bureau, Mamoru Yanase while speaking about FTX Japan.</p>
<p>Recall that last week, the Delaware Bankruptcy court handling the FTX Bankruptcy case agreed to the sale of FTX Japan and three other assets. Following this, 41 companies showed interest in the sale, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/monex-interest-ftx-japan/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">including Monex</a>. Monex CEO, Oki Matsumoto, believes buying FTX Japan will reduce the competition in the local market.</p>
<p>Yanase noted that the FTX subsidiary’s assets have been separated from the rest of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a>. He stated that the Japanese regulator is communicating closely with FTX Japan and the firm will resume withdrawals in February.</p>
<h2>What Tougher Crypto Regulations Will Look Like</h2>
<p>Yanase noted that the problem wasn’t with cryptocurrencies themselves, but with how they have been regulated thus far. This position is in stark contrast with that taken by some of his US counterparts who believe crypto is the problem. Instead, Yanase stressed the need to regulate and supervise crypto entities like traditional financial institutions.</p>
<p>Yanase urged U.S. and European regulators to enforce similar regulations for crypto institutions as for banks and brokerages. He asserted that countries need to implement consumer protection measures for crypto exchanges. Contrarily, he noted that measures relating to auditing, disclosure, governance, internal controls, and preventing money laundering should be implemented for crypto brokerages.</p>
<p>The Deputy DG also believes talks on global regulations should focus on unifying national regulations. Germany’s securities watchdog has issued a similar call. Yanase argues that a multinational resolution mechanism may be necessary to coordinate efforts when large crypto companies fail. </p>
<h2>Tough or Playing Tough?</h2>
<p>Meanwhile, Japan is also using its position on the International Financial Stability Board to push for global regulations of the cryptocurrency industry.</p>
<p>Despite the calls for stricter regulations, Japan is generally perceived as a crypto-friendly clime. It has few measures restricting cryptocurrency. Recently, Japan also announced plans to remove its ban on foreign stablecoins. Whatever the case, tougher crypto regulations will only strengthen the crypto sector. It may also raise investor confidence in the otherwise volatile market.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/settlement-binance-mirror/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/japan-tougher-crypto-regulations/">Japan Pushes for Tougher Crypto Regulations</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/japan-tougher-crypto-regulations/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Launches Off-exchange Settlement Solution Binance Mirror for Institutional Investors</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/settlement-binance-mirror/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/settlement-binance-mirror/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 10:51:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Alameda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance mirror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[changpeng zhao]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cz]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sol]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[solana]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=232797</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/settlement-binance-mirror/">Binance Launches Off-exchange Settlement Solution Binance Mirror for Institutional Investors</a></p>
<p>Binance announced it recorded a huge influx of institutional investors interested in digital assets during the fourth quarter of 2022.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/settlement-binance-mirror/">Binance Launches Off-exchange Settlement Solution Binance Mirror for Institutional Investors</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/settlement-binance-mirror/">Binance Launches Off-exchange Settlement Solution Binance Mirror for Institutional Investors</a></p>
<p>The <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a> cryptocurrency exchange, the world leading digital asset exchange on daily traded volume and global regulations, has <a href="https://www.binanceinstitutional.com/support/announcements/article/204448334901952512" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announced</a> the launch of its off-exchange settlement solution for institutional investors dubbed Binance Mirror. According to the announcement, digital assets in the Binance Mirror account for more than 60 percent of all assets secured on Binance Custody. As such, the company saw it prudent to provide institutional investors with a secure alternative to trade digital assets.</p>
<h2>Binance Mirror</h2>
<p>Reportedly, Binance Mirror accounts will feature a 1:1 balance on the exchange and the cold storage. The tokenization of institutional assets will help reduce theft of underlying digital assets, which mostly prove cumbersome to recover. Notably, the Binance crypto exchange will allow Mirror customers to redeem their positions at any time.</p>
<p>“Security is a top priority for institutions, who also desire the deep liquidity that the Binance Exchange offers. Binance Mirror brings the best of both worlds,” shares Athena Yu, VP of Binance Custody. “We spent much of last year refining its operations to help our clients unlock the liquidity of their assets held in our cold storage. We’re very excited about where we are today and can’t wait to introduce our upcoming new features that will elevate Binance Mirror’s functionality even further.”</p>
<p>The company announced it recorded a huge influx of institutional investors interested in digital assets during the fourth quarter of 2022. Moreover, qualified institutional investors can access VIP loans through the Binance Mirror.</p>
<p>Notably, Binance takes pride in regulatory approvals in various jurisdictions which enhance its cryptocurrency&#8217;s deep liquidity. Furthermore, more traders under the right leadership reciprocate to deeper trading liquidity.</p>
<h2>Binance and the Crypto Market Outlook</h2>
<p>Despite the heat of a year-long bear market, Binance has recorded higher monthly visits than any other exchange. According to aggregate data provided by Coingecko, Binance recorded 66.6 million monthly visits while Coinbase Global and  ByBit posted 35.4 million and 15.6 million respectively. The exchange also commands daily traded volume, which makes it desirable for institutional investors.</p>
<p>The crypto exchange has significantly helped stabilize the industry in the past few months following the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a> and Alameda implosion. According to Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/changpeng-zhao/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CZ</a>), developing the right trading tools will help crypto adoption to the mainstream market.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="474" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">There seems to be plenty of weird surprises in crypto. But build never fails. Keep building.</p>
<p>&mdash; CZ 🔶 Binance (@cz_binance) <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1615062571098247170?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 16, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The crypto market led by Bitcoin price has significantly rebounded from the FTX fallout. According to our latest crypto price oracles, the total market capitalization has regained $1 trillion with Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a>) price trading steadily above $21k. The Solana ecosystem tops in recent gains with <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/solana/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SOL</a> price up over 44 percent in the last seven days.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bradesco-tokenized-bank-credit-note/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/settlement-binance-mirror/">Binance Launches Off-exchange Settlement Solution Binance Mirror for Institutional Investors</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/settlement-binance-mirror/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bradesco Unveils Its First Tokenized Bank Credit Note, BBD Shares Drop 3%</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bradesco-tokenized-bank-credit-note/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bradesco-tokenized-bank-credit-note/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 10:16:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bbd shares]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bbd stock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bradesco]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[credit note]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=232803</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bradesco-tokenized-bank-credit-note/">Bradesco Unveils Its First Tokenized Bank Credit Note, BBD Shares Drop 3%</a></p>
<p>Bradesco joins other banks in Brazil already offering tokenized assets including Itaú Unibanco and Santander.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bradesco-tokenized-bank-credit-note/">Bradesco Unveils Its First Tokenized Bank Credit Note, BBD Shares Drop 3%</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bradesco-tokenized-bank-credit-note/">Bradesco Unveils Its First Tokenized Bank Credit Note, BBD Shares Drop 3%</a></p>
<p>Banco Bradesco SA (NYSE: BBD), a Brazilian financial services company headquartered in Osasco, launched its first tokenized bank credit note on Friday. According to a <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/01/16/brazils-second-largest-private-bank-launches-first-tokenized-credit-note/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a> by Coindesk, Bradesco completed the transaction for a total of 10 million Brazilian reals &#8211; equivalent to $1.95 million &#8211; under a regulatory sandbox run by the Central Bank of Brazil. The bank added that it was the first financial market tokenization operation regulated by that monetary authority.</p>
<h2>Bradesco&#8217;s First Tokenized Bank</h2>
<p>Brazil, one of the largest South American economies, announced last year through the central bank chief that it is moving its economy to a digital and tokenized system</p>
<p>During an event organized last year, Roberto Campos Neto &#8211; the governor of the central bank of Brazil &#8211; said the world’s economy is fast transitioning towards a tokenized market. Moreover, tokenization offers customers a cheap, fast, and secure means of transaction.</p>
<p>“We are leaving a world based on accounts to a world based on tokens. We are talking about digital assets and the financial system of the future,” Neto noted.</p>
<p>The idea is that financial institutions will offer stablecoins and other tokens to customers in a representative of the Central Bank Digital Currency (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-central-bank-digital-currency-cbdc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CBDC</a>) seamlessly. Moreover, the tokenization of traditional assets makes transiting more interoperable and ends up opening the locked-up economy to global investors.</p>
<p>As the country struggles with an election crisis, the incoming president is much more likely to focus on the digital economy to deal with the high rate of reported unemployment.  Notably, Bradesco joins other banks in Brazil already offering tokenized assets including Itaú Unibanco and Santander.</p>
<h2>Bradesco and the Market Outlook</h2>
<p>The Bradesco bank has been working on diversifying its revenue collection amid a struggling share market. According to market data provided by MarketWatch, BBD shares are trading 14.80 percent down in the past year and a 22 percent decline in the last three months.</p>
<p>With a market capitalization of approximately $29. 42 billion, Bradesco is well poised to morph with the Brazilian economy. Moreover, three ratings have BBD shares an average rating of Over and an average recommendation of Overweight.</p>
<p>According to the company’s third-quarter earnings results, the net income fell to 5.21 billion Brazilian reais from approximately 6.65 billion a year ago. The company attributed the poor performance to weaker-than-expected net interest income and bigger provisions. As loans.</p>
<p>Nonetheless, the bank is optimistic that the digital economy, which is significantly adopted in the country, will open up Brazilian markets to the world seamlessly. Furthermore, the crypto market is borderless and offers cheap and secure cross-border transactions as observed with <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ripple-labs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ripple</a>’s ODL and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/xrp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">XRP</a>.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/3ac-coinflex-founders-gtx-exchange/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bradesco-tokenized-bank-credit-note/">Bradesco Unveils Its First Tokenized Bank Credit Note, BBD Shares Drop 3%</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bradesco-tokenized-bank-credit-note/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>