<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 09:09:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>US Prosecutors to Weigh on SBF’s Alleged Campaign Financing Scheme in Next Trial</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-sbf-financing-trial/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-sbf-financing-trial/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 09:09:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[doj]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sam bankman-fried]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sbf]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266211</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-sbf-financing-trial/">US Prosecutors to Weigh on SBF&#8217;s Alleged Campaign Financing Scheme in Next Trial</a></p>
<p>Amid the arrangement with the Bahamian government, the DoJ couldn't add further charges on SBF. However, it still plans to look at the alleged campaign finance scheme. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-sbf-financing-trial/">US Prosecutors to Weigh on SBF&#8217;s Alleged Campaign Financing Scheme in Next Trial</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-sbf-financing-trial/">US Prosecutors to Weigh on SBF&#8217;s Alleged Campaign Financing Scheme in Next Trial</a></p>
<p>In a letter to a Manhattan federal judge Tuesday, August 8, US prosecutors said that the campaign financing charges against disgraced <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a> founder Sam-Bankman Fried (SBF) are still on the table. They added that these charges shall appear in the indictment next week against <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/sam-bankman-fried/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SBF</a>.</p>
<p>The development comes after the US government had to remove extra claims of campaign finance fraud, last month in July. This happened because of the US extradition treaty with the Bahamas, where Bankman-Fried and his company were located.</p>
<p>US Attorney Damian Williams also stated that the Department of Justice (DoJ) is planning to pursue seven charges against SBF in a trial that will begin in October 2022. The DoJ said it couldn&#8217;t add another charge to SBF&#8217;s case due to its agreement with the Bahamas. However, they will still look at the evidence related to the alleged campaign finance scheme while considering an existing wire fraud charge.</p>
<p>If found guilty of the initial seven charges, Bankman-Fried could face several years of sentence in prison. These charges are related to a supposed fraud against FTX investors worth billions of dollars. Attorney Williams <a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.nysd.590939/gov.uscourts.nysd.590939.195.0.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“The superseding indictment will make clear that Mr. Bankman-Fried remains charged with conducting an illegal campaign finance scheme as part of the fraud and money laundering schemes originally charged. The defendant’s use of customer deposits to conduct a political influence campaign was part of the wire fraud scheme charged in the original indictment. And as part of the originally charged money laundering scheme, the defendant also concealed the source of his fraudulent proceeds through political straw donations.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>SBF and His Political Donations</h2>
<p>Even during the glory year of FTX, and before its collapse, Sam Bankman Fried was well known in the crypto circle for donations to political parties. currently, SBF has been facing a trial in the US after his extradition from the Bahamas in December 2022.</p>
<p>Back then, the DoJ officials had officially announced eight charges against SBF. Later, they added another five charges in superseding indictments earlier this year in February and March 23. However, the treaty with the Bahamas prevents prosecutors from adding further charges without prior consultation with the Bahamian government. The charge about illegal campaign donations was removed in July because it wasn&#8217;t part of the extradition agreement with the Bahamas.</p>
<p>Since his arrest, Bankman-Fried has mostly stayed at his parents&#8217; house in California with a $250 million bond. However, prosecutors want to cancel his bail because he talked to reporters and shared information from his ex-girlfriend&#8217;s private journals in a way that might have scared her. She will be a witness at his trial in October.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/rivian-q2-2023-revenue/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-sbf-financing-trial/">US Prosecutors to Weigh on SBF&#8217;s Alleged Campaign Financing Scheme in Next Trial</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-sbf-financing-trial/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rivian Delivers Better-Than-Expected Q2 2023 Revenue, Raises Production Targets</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/rivian-q2-2023-revenue/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/rivian-q2-2023-revenue/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Darya Rudz]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 08:26:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Transportation News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wall Street]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[rivian]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[rivian amazon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[rivian automotive]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[rivian electric vehicles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[rivian ev]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[rivian q2 2023]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[rivian revenue]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266213</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/rivian-q2-2023-revenue/">Rivian Delivers Better-Than-Expected Q2 2023 Revenue, Raises Production Targets</a></p>
<p>Following to the progress achieved in Q2, Rivian is expecting to raise its previous full-year production guidance from 50,000 units to 52,000 units.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/rivian-q2-2023-revenue/">Rivian Delivers Better-Than-Expected Q2 2023 Revenue, Raises Production Targets</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/rivian-q2-2023-revenue/">Rivian Delivers Better-Than-Expected Q2 2023 Revenue, Raises Production Targets</a></p>
<p>Electric vehicle maker <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/rivian/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Rivian Automotive Inc</a> (NASDAQ: RIVN) has <a href="https://downloads.rivian.com/2md5qhoeajym/12yGznaOrSfdDtFni3WqJn/6667f965bc0542dfd50b0bf12d665d07/RIVN_2Q23_Shareholder_Letter_08.08.23.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">released</a> its Q2 2023 earnings, delivering great results and beating experts&#8217; expectations. Besides, Rivian reduced its losses and increased gross profit per vehicle. With good sales for the second quarter, Rivian is planning to raise its production target for the next three months.</p>
<h2>Rivian Q2 Earnings: Highlights</h2>
<p>For the quarter that ended on June 30, 2023, Rivian generated a $1.12 billion revenue, higher than the $1 billion expected. Further, the company reported an adjusted loss of $1.08 per share, beating an estimate of a loss of $1.41 per share. The net loss was $1.19 billion, down from $1.7 billion in the same quarter last year.</p>
<p>The revenue has been driven by strong production. Within the first half of 2023, Rivian produced 23,387 vehicles, which is in line with the production volumes the company achieved for the full 2022. In the second quarter of 2023, Rivian manufactured 13,992 and delivered 12,640 vehicles. The numbers mark a nearly 50% increase in production compared to the prior quarter.</p>
<p>Rivian CEO RJ Scaringe commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Our second quarter results reflect our continued focus on cost efficiency as we accelerate the drive towards profitability. On a quarter-over-quarter basis, delivered vehicles grew around 60% while gross profit per vehicle improved by about $35,000.  We have achieved meaningful reductions in both R1 and EDV vehicle unit cost across the key components, including material costs, overhead and logistics. It was a strong quarter, and we remain focused on ramping production, driving cost efficiencies, developing future technologies, and enhancing the customer experience.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The performance shows that the company has managed to settle its issues with suppliers, as well as cut the costs such as &#8216;material cost, manufacturing labour, overhead and logistics&#8217;.</p>
<p>According to Rivian, it also maintains its focus on improving customer experience. Its more than 280 mobile service vehicles on the road are handling over 50% of Rivian vehicle repairs. Currently, the company has 43 physical service centers opened, with 17 more centers scheduled to open by the end of the year.</p>
<h2>Raised Production Guidance</h2>
<p>Following the progress achieved in Q2 2023, Rivian is expecting to raise its previous full-year production guidance from 50,000 units to 52,000 units.</p>
<p>Rivian stated:</p>
<div title="Page 3">
<div>
<div>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Due to the progress we have seen to date on our production lines, the ramp of our in-house motor line, and the supply chain outlook, we are increasing our 2023 production guidance to 52,000 total units.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<p>Besides, following effective cost-cutting measures taken during the first half of the year, Rivian lowered its 2023 capital expenditures guidance to $1,700 million.</p>
<div title="Page 3">
<div>
<div>
<p>&#8220;For the remainder of 2023, we intend to maintain the momentum of the first half of the year by continuing to deliver against our value drivers: production ramp, cost efficiency, future platforms and technologies, and customer experience,&#8221; said the company.</p>
<p>Currently, Rivian is looking for new partnerships that will allow it to improve its technology and ramp up production.</p>
<p>Recently, Rivian has acquired Iternio, developer of the ‘A Better Routeplanner’ (ABRP) app that allows EV drivers to plan their routes and check the nearest and most convenient charging stations.</p>
<p>In addition, Rivian has partnered with <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/amazon/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Amazon.com Inc</a> (NASDAQ: AMZN) to bring 100,000 electric delivery vehicles on the road by 2030.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/marathon-digital-q2-2023-earnings/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/rivian-q2-2023-revenue/">Rivian Delivers Better-Than-Expected Q2 2023 Revenue, Raises Production Targets</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/rivian-q2-2023-revenue/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Marathon Digital Misses Q2 2023 Earnings and Revenue Estimates, MARA Shares Drop 2%</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/marathon-digital-q2-2023-earnings/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/marathon-digital-q2-2023-earnings/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 08:22:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mara stock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marathon digital]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marathon digital stock]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266233</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/marathon-digital-q2-2023-earnings/">Marathon Digital Misses Q2 2023 Earnings and Revenue Estimates, MARA Shares Drop 2%</a></p>
<p>Marathon Digital announced that the gains on the sale of Bitcoin were $23.4 million in Q2 2023.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/marathon-digital-q2-2023-earnings/">Marathon Digital Misses Q2 2023 Earnings and Revenue Estimates, MARA Shares Drop 2%</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/marathon-digital-q2-2023-earnings/">Marathon Digital Misses Q2 2023 Earnings and Revenue Estimates, MARA Shares Drop 2%</a></p>
<p>One of the leading <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> miners in total hash rate, Marathon Digital Holdings Inc (NASDAQ: MARA) released its Q2 2023 earnings on August 8. According to the announcement, Marathon Digital reported an adjusted loss per share of $0.13 on revenues of $81.8 million whereas analysts surveyed by FactSet had issued an estimate for a loss per share of about $0.06 on revenues of $83.4 million. As a result, MARA shares closed Tuesday trading at $15.72, up 4.31 percent from the day’s opening price. However, MARA shares dropped approximately 2.29 percent during the after-hours market session to trade around $15.36. Nonetheless, the company has performed exemplary well YTD with an uptick of about 359 percent.</p>
<p>The mainstream adoption of Bitcoin among other digital assets has helped BTC value gain more than 77 percent YTD. However, due to a lack of safe Bitcoin investment products like ETFs in the United States, institutional investors are pushed to expose themselves to crypto assets through companies like Marathon Digital.</p>
<h2>Marathon Digital Q2 2023 Financial Statement</h2>
<p>For Q2 2023 which ended on June 30, the company recorded a net loss of $21.3 million, or $0.13 per share, compared to a net loss of $212.6 million, or $1.94 per share, in the same period last year. The company highlighted that revenues from Bitcoin mining during the second quarter came in at $81.8 million, a significant bump from $24.9 million reported during the same time last year. During the second quarter, the company announced that its Bitcoin production increased by 314 percent, which significantly helped offset the 14 percent lower BTC price compared to the same time last year.</p>
<p>Notably, Marathon Digital sold about 63 percent of the 2,926 Bitcoins produced during the second quarter amounting to $23.4 million. The company highlighted that its adjusted EBITDA was $25.6 million during the second quarter compared with a loss of $167.1 million in the prior year period.</p>
<p>In a bid to ensure future growth prospects, Marathon Digital grew its energized hash rate by approximately 54 percent from 11.5 to 17.7 exahashes. Consequently, the company accounted for a total of 3.3 percent of the total Bitcoins mined during the second quarter.</p>
<p>“In addition to our operational progress, we also improved our financial position during the quarter. We exited the quarter with $113.7 million in unrestricted cash and cash equivalents and approximately 12,538 bitcoin, the market value of which was approximately $380 million on June 30. Although our cash position decreased by $11.2 million from Q1, we increased our unrestricted bitcoin holdings by 1,072 bitcoin, the market value of which was approximately $32.7 million on June 30,” the company <a href="https://ir.mara.com/news-events/press-releases/detail/1323/marathon-digital-holdings-reports-second-quarter-2023" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">noted</a> in the announcement.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-price-30k-moodys/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/marathon-digital-q2-2023-earnings/">Marathon Digital Misses Q2 2023 Earnings and Revenue Estimates, MARA Shares Drop 2%</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/marathon-digital-q2-2023-earnings/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Briefly Revisits $30K after Ratings Agency Moody’s Downgraded US Banking Sector</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-price-30k-moodys/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-price-30k-moodys/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 08:17:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcsud]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[moody's]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266231</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-price-30k-moodys/">Bitcoin Price Briefly Revisits $30K after Ratings Agency Moody’s Downgraded US Banking Sector</a></p>
<p>Increased Bitcoin demand from institutional investors led by the ETF frenzy and new stablecoins launch has widened crypto liquidity and trading volume.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-price-30k-moodys/">Bitcoin Price Briefly Revisits $30K after Ratings Agency Moody’s Downgraded US Banking Sector</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-price-30k-moodys/">Bitcoin Price Briefly Revisits $30K after Ratings Agency Moody’s Downgraded US Banking Sector</a></p>
<p>The United States market has in the past few months doubled down its interest in digital assets as the Federal Reserve pushes its limit to lower the inflation to the desired 2 percent. With Bitcoin&#8217;s current inflation below 1 percent, and expected to halve in less than a year, institutional investors in the United States led by <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/blackrock/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BlackRock Inc</a> (NYSE: BLK) have shown increased interest in Bitcoin and other digital assets. As a result, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> price has continued to gain more momentum in favor of banking stocks that have struggled YTD. Furthermore, the banking sector experienced a contraction period earlier this year when several regional banks in the United States and around collapsed due to low deposits and customer retention.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Price</h2>
<p>According to the latest crypto price oracles, Bitcoin suddenly rebounded from a bearish outlook to briefly trade above $30k on Tuesday. Undeniably, several reasons contributed to the sudden rise of Bitcoin on Tuesday. Among the top reasons include the increased demand by institutional investors, which led rating agency Moody&#8217;s to put the U.S. banking sector on a downgrade watch.</p>
<p>Notably, the firm changed its outlook to negative for 11 banks, including Capital One, Citizens Financial, and Fifth Third Bancorp. The downgrade follows the recent revelation of banks struggling to make profits and generate internal capital according to Q2 results.</p>
<p>“US banks continue to contend with interest rate and asset-liability management (ALM) risks with implications for liquidity and capital, as the wind-down of unconventional monetary policy drains systemwide deposits and higher interest rates depress the value of fixed-rate assets,” Moody’s analysts Jill Cetina and Ana Arsov <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/08/08/moodys-cuts-ratings-of-10-us-banks-and-puts-some-big-names-on-downgrade-watch.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a> in a research note.</p>
<p>Notably, experts believe Bitcoin price is well positioned to rally beyond $100k in the next few years, with some predicting $1 million per coin by 2030. The ambitious rally is expected to be fueled by global hyperinflation and mainstream adoption of digital assets. As a result, the traditional banking sector has continued to bleed its customers into the new banking industry using modern technology like Artificial Intelligence (AI) and blockchain.</p>
<p>“Bitcoin is holding strong. The correlation between the stock market and bitcoin is decoupling as bitcoin has proven to be a beneficiary of banking turmoil,” Greg Magadini, director of derivatives at Amberdata.</p>
<h2>Bigger Picture</h2>
<p>Most crypto analysts believe Bitcoin price will not revisit its ATH and beyond until after next year’s halving as it has performed historically. The Bitcoin halving is expected to take place during the first half of 2024 when the BTC miners will receive half the reward per block. Meanwhile, an accumulation phase could lead to a Bitcoin correction towards $25k as the top coin establishes a solid support base.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-ai-chip-llms/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-price-30k-moodys/">Bitcoin Price Briefly Revisits $30K after Ratings Agency Moody’s Downgraded US Banking Sector</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-price-30k-moodys/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nvidia Unveils New AI Chip Set to Cut Cost of Running LLMs</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-ai-chip-llms/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-ai-chip-llms/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 08:14:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ai chip]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[amd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[artificial intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[artificial intelligence nvidia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gh200]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gpu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[h100]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nvidia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nvidia ceo]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266205</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-ai-chip-llms/">Nvidia Unveils New AI Chip Set to Cut Cost of Running LLMs</a></p>
<p>GPUs have recently become the first-choice chips for large AI models that support generative AI software.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-ai-chip-llms/">Nvidia Unveils New AI Chip Set to Cut Cost of Running LLMs</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-ai-chip-llms/">Nvidia Unveils New AI Chip Set to Cut Cost of Running LLMs</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/nvidia/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Nvidia</a> appears to have turned up the heat on its competitors within the artificial intelligence (AI) hardware space. This follows after the firm unveiled its latest AI chip on Tuesday, in a move that may just have set it apart from its rivals, which include <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/amd-ai-chip-nvidia/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">AMD</a>, Amazon, and Google.</p>
<p>According to a BBC <a href="https://www.bbc.com/news/business-65675027" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a>, Nvidia currently dominates the AI chips market with a market share that tops 80%. And that may be linked to its special forte in making graphics processing units (GPUs), which have recently become the first-choice chips for large AI models that support generative AI software. Examples of such models are OpenAI’s ChatGPT and Google&#8217;s Bard.</p>
<p>With the huge demands from tech giants, cloud providers, and startups alike, Nvidia chips have inadvertently come up short in supply. Therefore, it is only understandable that Nvidia is coming out with its new chip – the GH200 – at this time.</p>
<h2>Nvidia Shares Details About the New AI GH200 Chip</h2>
<p>According to the company, the new chip has a similar GPU to its current most expensive AI chip, the H100. But there is an improvement in the area of memory and processor. The GH200 will come with 141 gigabytes of memory as opposed to the H100&#8217;s 80GB of memory. It also has a 72-core ARM central processor, says Nvidia.</p>
<p>Speaking about the new chip during a Tuesday conference, Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang noted that “the processor is designed for the scale-out of the world’s data centres.” So, the company set out to give the processor a boost right from the onset.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, AI models often work in two parts; the training and inference parts. An AI model must first be trained extensively for months, even at the expense of thousands of GPUs. It is then used in software to generate content in the inference stage.</p>
<p>However, inference is usually expensive and requires a lot of processing power. This cost of running the software is what Nvidia has targeted to reduce with the new GH200, Huang disclosed. And, considering that it has more memory capacity, it is only safe to conclude that the new chip has been designed for inference. Huang notes:</p>
<blockquote><p>“You can take pretty much any large language model (LLM) you want and put it in this and it will inference like crazy.”</p></blockquote>
<p>The CEO expects to see the inference cost of LLMs drop significantly, adding that the GH200 will be available from Nvidia’s distributors in the second quarter of 2024. However, Huang also projects that the new chip may already be available for sampling by the end of this year.</p>
<p>As of publication, Nvidia is yet to give an official price for the new chip.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/eli-lilly-q2-2023-profit/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-ai-chip-llms/">Nvidia Unveils New AI Chip Set to Cut Cost of Running LLMs</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-ai-chip-llms/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Eli Lilly Raises Full Year Outlook amid Q2 2023 Profit Surge of 85%</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/eli-lilly-q2-2023-profit/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/eli-lilly-q2-2023-profit/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 15:03:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wall Street]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eli lilly]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eli lilly stock]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266179</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/eli-lilly-q2-2023-profit/">Eli Lilly Raises Full Year Outlook amid Q2 2023 Profit Surge of 85%</a></p>
<p>Eli Lilly’s success can be ascribed in part to its promising medical pipeline and strategic acquisitions.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/eli-lilly-q2-2023-profit/">Eli Lilly Raises Full Year Outlook amid Q2 2023 Profit Surge of 85%</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/eli-lilly-q2-2023-profit/">Eli Lilly Raises Full Year Outlook amid Q2 2023 Profit Surge of 85%</a></p>
<p>American pharmaceutical company <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/eli-lilly-and-company/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Eli Lilly and Co</a> (NYSE: LLY) has reported an impressive surge in profits during the second quarter of 2023, leading to a significant increase in its full-year outlook.</p>
<p>The company’s quarterly financial report, <a href="https://investor.lilly.com/news-releases/news-release-details/lilly-reports-second-quarter-2023-financial-results-highlights" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">released</a> earlier today, reveals an 85% jump in net income, surpassing expectations and demonstrating the company’s resilience and growth in the face of global challenges.</p>
<h2>Eli Lilly’s Q2 Profit and Performance</h2>
<p>During Q2 2023, the company reported adjusted earnings of $2.11 per share, beating analysts&#8217; expectations of $1.98 per share. Also, its revenue for the quarter reached an impressive $8.31 billion, outperforming the estimated $7.58 billion.</p>
<p>Additionally, Eli Lilly booked a net income of $1.76 billion, or $1.95 per share. This notable increase in net income is a substantial improvement from the same period the previous year when the company reported net income of $952.5 million, or $1.05 per share.</p>
<p>To provide a clearer picture of its core operational performance, Eli Lilly reported adjusted income, accounting for charges associated with some intangible assets and losses on securities. The company recorded an adjusted income of $1.9 billion, or $2.11 per share.</p>
<p>This adjusted figure indicates Eli Lilly’s underlying financial strength after adjusting for any one-time or non-operational factors that may have influenced the results.</p>
<p>One of the key drivers behind Eli Lilly’s strong financial performance during Q2 2023 was its outstanding sales figures. The company reported $8.31 billion in sales for the quarter, representing a remarkable 28% increase from the same period the previous year.</p>
<p>Sales of Verzenio, a breast cancer pill, recorded a remarkable 57% increase, reaching $926.8 million in the second quarter. Similarly, Jardiance, a tablet used to lower blood sugar in Type 2 diabetes patients, recorded a substantial 45% sales increase, reaching $668.3 million during the quarter.</p>
<p>Eli Lilly’s newer drug, Mounjaro, an injection for Type 2 diabetes, posted impressive sales of $979.7 million in the quarter. The drug’s approval in the US in May 2022 and subsequent demand surge have fueled its rapid revenue growth. However, intermittent delays in fulfilling orders due to overwhelming demand have been reported.</p>
<h2>Promising Developments</h2>
<p>Eli Lilly’s success can be ascribed in part to its promising medical pipeline and strategic acquisitions. The company’s investment in research and development has yielded positive results, as evidenced by the favorable trial outcomes of donanemab, a drug targeted at Alzheimer&#8217;s disease.</p>
<p>Furthermore, Eli Lilly’s progress in its obesity drug pipeline has also garnered attention from investors and the industry alike. As obesity continues to be a major global health concern, the development of effective drugs to combat this condition presents a substantial market opportunity for the company.</p>
<p>One significant move that has bolstered Eli Lilly&#8217;s position is its recent <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/eli-lilly-2-4b-dice-therapeutics/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">acquisition</a> of biopharma company Dice Therapeutics. Eli Lilly expects that the $2.4 billion deal will help the business develop more medications to treat immunological illnesses.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-xrp-price-rally-1-clarity/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/eli-lilly-q2-2023-profit/">Eli Lilly Raises Full Year Outlook amid Q2 2023 Profit Surge of 85%</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/eli-lilly-q2-2023-profit/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple-backed XRP Price Struggles to Rally towards $1 despite Regulatory Clarity</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-xrp-price-rally-1-clarity/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-xrp-price-rally-1-clarity/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 14:53:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gary gensler]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpprice]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266170</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-xrp-price-rally-1-clarity/">Ripple-backed XRP Price Struggles to Rally towards $1 despite Regulatory Clarity</a></p>
<p>The XRP market is heavily bolstered by the adoption of Ripple payment products including On-Demand Liquidity (ODL) and RipppeNet.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-xrp-price-rally-1-clarity/">Ripple-backed XRP Price Struggles to Rally towards $1 despite Regulatory Clarity</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-xrp-price-rally-1-clarity/">Ripple-backed XRP Price Struggles to Rally towards $1 despite Regulatory Clarity</a></p>
<p>On July 13, the United States judicial system through a ruling by District Judge Analisa Torres declared <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/xrp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">XRP</a> exchanges’ sales as non-security. However, the ruling also tied the XRP institutional sales to investment contracts, thus security under the Howey test. Nonetheless, almost all centralized exchanges led by <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase Global Inc</a> (NASDAQ: COIN) re-listed the digital assets for trading. As a result, XRP’s daily traded volume experienced a sharp uptick in the subsequent days towards $14 billion. Additionally, Ripple-backed XRP price doubled following the ruling from trading around 46 cents to as much as 95 cents.</p>
<p>The recent XRP correction has since eaten away significant gains made after the Ripple case ruling. According to the latest market data, XRP price exchanged around 62 cents, down more than 25 percent from this year’s high. Additionally, XRP’s average daily traded volume was about $1.2 billion, a huge drop from the recent highs of about $14 billion.</p>
<p>According to John E Deaton, founder of Crypto-law.us, the ultimate <a href="https://decrypt.co/151712/xrp-price-falls-week-bullish-sec-hype-fades" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">trigger</a> for a parabolic rally of XRP or any other altcoin lies with Bitcoin. Historically, every major crypto bull rally has been triggered by the Bitcoin halving, which is less than a year away.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="474" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">If I had told you <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/XRP?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#XRP</a> would get regulatory clarity but not hit $1, many wouldn’t have believed it. Likewise, if I had told you PayPal would issue a stable coin on Ethereum but <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/ETH?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#ETH</a> wouldn’t increase at all, many wouldn’t have believed it. Like it or not, <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Bitcoin</a> drives this…</p>
<p>&mdash; John E Deaton (@JohnEDeaton1) <a href="https://twitter.com/JohnEDeaton1/status/1688873607605170176?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 8, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2>Ripple-backed XRP Price and Market Analysis</h2>
<p>The XRP price is heavily bolstered by the adoption of Ripple payment products including On-Demand Liquidity (ODL) and RipppeNet. Additionally, the mainstream adoption of XRPL has helped widen the utility of XRP including NFT minting and DeFi operations. As a result, most experts believe XRP price is on the pathway to trading above $1 in the near term perspective.</p>
<p>However, the ongoing XRP price correction could push the digital asset towards a notable support zone between 53 and 58 cents, which acted as significant resistance levels before last month’s ruling.</p>
<p>The mainstream adoption of digital assets is expected to significantly accelerate the use of XRP in cross-border payments. As the fifth largest digital asset with a market capitalization of about $32 billion and deep trading liquidity in different pairs, XRP is well poised for further growth, more so fueled by institutional adoption.</p>
<p>Worth noting that Ripple is already working with several global central banks in developing interoperable <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-central-bank-digital-currency-cbdc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CBDCs</a>.</p>
<p>Additionally, the XRPL has a private chain that helps in the seamless issuance and burning of stablecoins by institutional investors.</p>
<h2>Bigger Picture</h2>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ripple-labs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ripple</a> is yet to fully settle the case with the SEC despite the recent ruling. Notably, the SEC through Chair Gary Gensler has severally stated that the agency does not agree with Judge Torres ruling and thus is preparing to appeal in the next circuit. As a result, the XRP price could continue to lose upward momentum until the case is completely settled.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/moodys-ratings-us-banks/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-xrp-price-rally-1-clarity/">Ripple-backed XRP Price Struggles to Rally towards $1 despite Regulatory Clarity</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-xrp-price-rally-1-clarity/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Moody’s Reduces Ratings of Several US Banks and Puts More Under Review for Potential Downgrades</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/moodys-ratings-us-banks/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/moodys-ratings-us-banks/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 14:44:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[first republic bank]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[moody's]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pacwest bancorp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[wells fargo]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[western alliance bankcorp]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266147</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/moodys-ratings-us-banks/">Moody’s Reduces Ratings of Several US Banks and Puts More Under Review for Potential Downgrades</a></p>
<p>Moody's is watching the banking sector and has already cut its ratings on several institutions because of ongoing economic headwinds.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/moodys-ratings-us-banks/">Moody’s Reduces Ratings of Several US Banks and Puts More Under Review for Potential Downgrades</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/moodys-ratings-us-banks/">Moody’s Reduces Ratings of Several US Banks and Puts More Under Review for Potential Downgrades</a></p>
<p>Bond credit rating platform Moody’s Investors Service has reduced its ratings of several banks in the US. In addition to the cut in these ratings, Moody’s also put several banks under review for possible rating cuts.</p>
<p>The announced reduction affected multiple small and mid-size banks, including Pinnacle Financial, BOK Financial, Webster Financial, and M&amp;T Bank. Others affected are Citizens Financial, Fifth Third Bancorp, and Capital One.</p>
<p>Explaining the decision, Moody’s analysts Ana Arsov and Jill Cetina <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/08/08/moodys-cuts-ratings-of-10-us-banks-and-puts-some-big-names-on-downgrade-watch.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">wrote</a> in a research note that banks are struggling with several problems, largely caused by official monetary policy:</p>
<blockquote><p>“US banks continue to contend with interest rate and asset-liability management (ALM) risks with implications for liquidity and capital, as the wind-down of unconventional monetary policy drains systemwide deposits and higher interest rates depress the value of fixed-rate assets.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Moody’s also put a few major lenders under review for a possible downgrade but has yet to cut their ratings. The potential downgrades include State Street, Bank of New York Mellon, Northern Trust, US Bancorp, Cullen/Frost Bankers, and Truist Financial.</p>
<p>As part of its explanation, Moody’s adds that many banks are facing “profitability pressures” that will affect how much internal capital they can generate.</p>
<h2>Moody’s Forecast for 2024 amid Rating Cut</h2>
<p>Moody’s expects a mild recession in early 2024. The note also states that banks might face risks in their commercial real estate (CRE) portfolios. In addition, analysts have warned about the public loss of confidence in regional banks. This follows the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nydfs-signature-bank-svb-fails/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">collapse of Signature Bank</a> and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/silvergate-shut-down-liquidate-operations/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Silicon Valley Bank</a> earlier this year. While US authorities like the New York Department of Financial Services (NYDFS) stepped in to allay fears, the sector may still suffer distrust. According to Moody’s, banks with heavy unrealized losses face the highest risks for loss of consumer confidence.</p>
<p>In addition to these problems, Moody’s expects banks to face heightened ALM risks because of the Federal Reserve’s continuous increases in interest rates. Like many analysts, Moody’s believes the Fed will keep interest rates high until inflation is reasonably controlled. Unfortunately, this will negatively affect fixed-rate assets. Other causative factors as described by Moody’s include lower deposits and reduced reserves.</p>
<p>Last month, the Federal Reserve increased interest rates by <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fed-25-basis-point-hike-rates/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">25 basis points to 5.25 &#8211; 5.5%</a>, with a midpoint height not seen since 2001. The 22-year high will likely put pressure on banks, assets, and consumers. Regardless, Fed Chairman Jerome Powell has hinted that another increase is possible in September. According to Powell, economic data at the time of the meeting would inform the apex bank’s decision on whether or not another hike is necessary.</p>
<h2>Bullish on Bank Stocks</h2>
<p>Despite the banking problem in Q1, not everyone is bearish. Investor and hedge fund manager Michael Burry has <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/investor-burry-regional-banks/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">made big purchases in regional banks</a>. In a now-deleted tweet, the ‘Big Short’ investor said he believes the crisis would quickly resolve.</p>
<p>According to securities filings in May, Burry’s Scion Asset Management bought 150,000 First Republic Bank shares and 850,000 shares in New York Community Bancorp (NYSE: NYCB). Scion also bought 250,000 shares in PacWest Bancorp (NASDAQ: PACW), and 125,000 Western Alliance Bancorp (NYSE: WAL) shares. Reportedly, Scion spent $23.4 million on these purchases. There is also a reported $4.6 million purchase of Wells Fargo (NYSE: WFC).</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/brazil-name-cbdc-drex/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/moodys-ratings-us-banks/">Moody’s Reduces Ratings of Several US Banks and Puts More Under Review for Potential Downgrades</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/moodys-ratings-us-banks/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Brazil Gives Name and Logo to Its Central Bank Digital Currency (CBDC) – DREX</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/brazil-name-cbdc-drex/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/brazil-name-cbdc-drex/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 14:14:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[drex]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266158</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/brazil-name-cbdc-drex/">Brazil Gives Name and Logo to Its Central Bank Digital Currency (CBDC) &#8211; DREX</a></p>
<p>The DREX CBDC will utilize distributed ledger technology (DLT) for settling wholesale interbank transactions, and retail access will rely on tokenized bank deposits.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/brazil-name-cbdc-drex/">Brazil Gives Name and Logo to Its Central Bank Digital Currency (CBDC) &#8211; DREX</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/brazil-name-cbdc-drex/">Brazil Gives Name and Logo to Its Central Bank Digital Currency (CBDC) &#8211; DREX</a></p>
<p>The Central bank of Brazil continues to push further with its progress o the central bank digital currency (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-central-bank-digital-currency-cbdc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CBDC</a>). Previously popular as Digital Real, the CBDC gets a new official brand name aka the DREX.</p>
<p>On Monday, August 7, Brazil&#8217;s central bank unveiled the new brand and logo for its CBDC through a press release. As per the central bank, the brand &#8220;DREX&#8221; is an acronym. The press release notes:</p>
<blockquote><p>“‘D’ and ‘r’ allude to Real Digital; the ‘e’ stands for electronic and the ‘x’ conveys the idea of ​​modernity and connection, the use of distributed ledger technology (DLT).”</p></blockquote>
<p>In addition to unveiling the brand name, the central bank also introduced Drex&#8217;s visual identity. The CBDC logo features two arrows within the capital letter &#8220;D,&#8221; symbolizing the progression from the national fiat currency, the real, to its digital counterpart. The color shift from blue to light green represents the completion of transactions.</p>
<p>The Drex CBDC by Brazil is all set to hit the market next year in 2024. Central bank officials had previously forecasted that the Brazilian digital currency&#8217;s adoption would begin by the close of 2024, once the testing phase had been concluded.</p>
<p>However, Fabio Araujo, who leads the initiative at the bank, mentioned that employee strikes seeking improved career opportunities might potentially influence the project.</p>
<h2>The DREX CBDC to Bolster Lending and Investments</h2>
<p>The DREX CBDC will utilize distributed ledger technology (DLT) for settling wholesale interbank transactions, and retail access will rely on tokenized bank deposits.</p>
<p>In a live discussion hosted by the central bank, Araujo emphasized that the main focus of developing DREX is to enhance access to financial services within the country. &#8220;By enabling simple and reliable access to registered values through DLT technology, we reduce costs and democratize access to financial services,&#8221; Araujo stated.</p>
<p>He also pointed out that Brazilians are already actively participating in extensive digital payments using the instant payment platform Pix, which was introduced in late 2021 and has been widely adopted. The anticipation now is that DREX will strengthen lending, investment, and insurance services.</p>
<p>&#8220;We aim to make these financial products accessible to the public and increase financial inclusion in Brazil,&#8221; Araujo <a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/brazil-central-bank-names-its-digital-currency-drex-scheduled-2024-launch-2023-08-07/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">added</a>.</p>
<p>Last month, some developers <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/developer-loopholes-brazil-cbdc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">pointed out</a> the loopholes in the code for the DREX. Thus, the central bank might have to conduct some more tests before introducing DREX into the market.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-usdc-btc-eth-silvergate/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/brazil-name-cbdc-drex/">Brazil Gives Name and Logo to Its Central Bank Digital Currency (CBDC) &#8211; DREX</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/brazil-name-cbdc-drex/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Traded USDC In for BTC and ETH Following Silvergate Collapse</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-usdc-btc-eth-silvergate/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-usdc-btc-eth-silvergate/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mercy Tukiya Mutanya]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 13:51:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Binance News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brian armstrong]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[usd coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[usdc]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266160</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-usdc-btc-eth-silvergate/">Binance Traded USDC In for BTC and ETH Following Silvergate Collapse</a></p>
<p>The exchange’s USDC balance was reduced from $3.4 billion on March 1 to $23.9 million by May 1.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-usdc-btc-eth-silvergate/">Binance Traded USDC In for BTC and ETH Following Silvergate Collapse</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-usdc-btc-eth-silvergate/">Binance Traded USDC In for BTC and ETH Following Silvergate Collapse</a></p>
<p>Cryptocurrency exchange <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a> provided a closer look into its reserves with the August 1 release of its proof-of-reserves (PoR). The move of Binance to dump its USD Coin (USDC) reserves after the collapse of Sivergate Bank has become a major topic of discussion in crypto circles online, particularly on social media platform X.</p>
<p>Overall, the <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/proof-of-reserves" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">PoR report</a> paints a picture of good financial health for the exchange. It shows that Binance has enough crypto and cash reserves to cover user funds. The report includes a snapshot of the ratios of Binance’s net balances to its customers’ net balances for cryptocurrencies Bitcoin, Ethereum, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/binance-coin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BNB</a>, USDT, BUSD, USDC, Litecoin and XRP. The ratio of the exchange’s net balances to user net balances on all crypto assets shown is more than 100%.</p>
<p>A main point of discussion online is the movements of Binance’s USDC reserves following the collapse of crypto-friendly Silvegate Bank in March. The exchange’s USDC balance was reduced from $3.4 billion on March 1 to $23.9 million by May 1. Onchain data suggests that Binance started converting its USDC into Ether following Silvergate’s collapse. Onchain analyst Aleksandar Djakovic pointed out that between March 12 and May 1, Binance bought about 100,000 BTC and 550,000 ETH averaging about $3.5 billion, close to the amount of USDC the exchanged had in surplus on March 1.</p>
<p>The discourse surrounding Binance&#8217;s handling of its USDC holdings was furthered when Coinbase CEO <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/brian-armstrong/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Brian Armstrong</a> stated in jest during the company’s Q2 earnings call that Binance had moved a chunk of their funds from USDC to another stablecoin.</p>
<p>“Binance actually moved some of their funds from USDC into another stablecoin. I think the data we have in the last six or seven weeks, I believe, that the USDC market cap is up net of that. And so that’s an important data point,” said he.</p>
<p>PoR has been an industry standard following the seemingly abrupt collapse of the crypto exchange FTX in November last year. Major exchanges began to share reserve audits with the public in an attempt to quell investors’ worries.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/singapore-blockchain-com-license/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-usdc-btc-eth-silvergate/">Binance Traded USDC In for BTC and ETH Following Silvergate Collapse</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-usdc-btc-eth-silvergate/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4279 metric#misses=43 metric#hit-ratio=99.0 metric#bytes=1083057 metric#prefetches=213 metric#store-reads=22 metric#store-writes=3 metric#store-hits=220 metric#store-misses=4 metric#sql-queries=35 metric#ms-total=106.35 metric#ms-cache=5.66 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.2360 metric#ms-cache-ratio=5.3 -->