<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 09:06:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Shares of Overstock.com (OSTK) Jump 20% after Announcing Rebrand for Bed Bath and Beyond</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/shares-overstock-ostk-bed-bath-and-beyond/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/shares-overstock-ostk-bed-bath-and-beyond/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 09:06:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Deals News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bed bath beoynd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[overstock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[overstock.com]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261124</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shares-overstock-ostk-bed-bath-and-beyond/">Shares of Overstock.com (OSTK) Jump 20% after Announcing Rebrand for Bed Bath and Beyond</a></p>
<p>Overstock said that it will start operating under the domain of Bedbathandbeyond.com, which offer greater brand awareness and recognition.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shares-overstock-ostk-bed-bath-and-beyond/">Shares of Overstock.com (OSTK) Jump 20% after Announcing Rebrand for Bed Bath and Beyond</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shares-overstock-ostk-bed-bath-and-beyond/">Shares of Overstock.com (OSTK) Jump 20% after Announcing Rebrand for Bed Bath and Beyond</a></p>
<p>On Thursday, June 29, the price of Overstock.com (NASDAQ: OSTK) shares skyrocketed by 20% and closed the day at $30.57. This happened the day after Overstock announced that it plans to change its website name to Bed, Bath and Beyond.</p>
<p>Overstock.com had paid a sum total of $21.5 million for using the brand Bed, Bath and Beyond, after it filed for bankruptcy in April. The E-commerce retailer announced that it shall stop using its official website and rather operate under the domain of Bedbathandbeyond.com.</p>
<p>This news comes after the federal bankruptcy court approved Overstock&#8217;s demand of taking over the intellectual property assets of Bed Bath &amp; Beyond. Note that this deal doesn&#8217;t include the physical stores of BB&amp;B, which would be closing pretty soon.</p>
<p>Jonathan Johnson, the CEO of Overstock, expressed that the company&#8217;s current product offerings are no longer aligned with its previous liquidation-focused model, and as a result, the name &#8220;Overstock&#8221; no longer accurately represents the nature of the business. Speaking to CNBC&#8217;s The Exchange, he <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/06/29/overstock-shares-spike-after-company-announces-website-rebrand-.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">added</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We started out 20-plus years ago as a liquidator and became a general merchandiser. Now we’re a home furnishings and furniture company and there [were] a lot of headwinds with the name Overstock, headwinds with customers who were confused who we were and what we were selling, headwinds with suppliers that didn’t want to necessarily sell if it was associated with liquidation.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>BB&amp;B Has Strong Brand Awareness and Recall</h2>
<p>Johnson believes that despite the collapse this year and eventual bankruptcy, Bed Bath &amp; Beyond offers a strong brand awareness in the market. He added that both Overstock and BB&amp;B has overlapping customers which will help make the transition smoother.</p>
<p>Johnson added:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We’ll do this transition slowly where the Overstock customer will come to the new website and will recognize it, but so will the Bed Bath &amp; Beyond customer. And then over time, we’ll sunset out the Overstock feel.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>During a recent call with analysts, Johnson assured shoppers that Bed Bath &amp; Beyond&#8217;s renowned coupons will continue to be available, at least for a transitional period. However, he also mentioned that the company intends to reduce the frequency and depth of discounts in the long run.</p>
<p>“One thing that Bed Bath &amp; Beyond customers will realize is that our non-coupon price is really good. And I think people will be very surprised with the deals that Overstock and now Bed Bath &amp; Beyond is able to offer and has been offered,” he said.</p>
<p>The relaunch of the Bed, Bath &amp; Beyond website shall happen in Canada by the next week. Later in the coming weeks, there will be a subsequent rollout of a website, mobile app, and loyalty program in the US.</p>
<p>Read other <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/business/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">business news</a> on Coinspeaker.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cme-ether-bitcoin-ratio-futures/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shares-overstock-ostk-bed-bath-and-beyond/">Shares of Overstock.com (OSTK) Jump 20% after Announcing Rebrand for Bed Bath and Beyond</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/shares-overstock-ostk-bed-bath-and-beyond/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>CME Group Unveils Plans of Launching Ether/Bitcoin Ratio Futures</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/cme-ether-bitcoin-ratio-futures/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/cme-ether-bitcoin-ratio-futures/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 09:02:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funds & ETFs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cme]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cme group]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261106</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cme-ether-bitcoin-ratio-futures/">CME Group Unveils Plans of Launching Ether/Bitcoin Ratio Futures</a></p>
<p>The settlement of the ETH/BTC ratio futures will be linked to the value of CME Group Ether futures final settlement price, divided by the corresponding CME Group Bitcoin futures final settlement price.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cme-ether-bitcoin-ratio-futures/">CME Group Unveils Plans of Launching Ether/Bitcoin Ratio Futures</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cme-ether-bitcoin-ratio-futures/">CME Group Unveils Plans of Launching Ether/Bitcoin Ratio Futures</a></p>
<p>On Thursday, June 29, the world&#8217;s leading derivatives platform CME Group announced plans to launch the ether/bitcoin (ETH/BTC) ratio futures subject to approval from the regulators.</p>
<p>These futures will be cash-settled meaning that the settlement will happen in cash instead of the underlying instrument. Also, the settlement will happen to the value of the CME Group Ether futures final settlement price, divided by the corresponding CME Group <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> futures final settlement price.</p>
<p>The ETH/BTC ratio futures will follow the same settlement cycle as that of the CME Group Bitcoin futures and Ether futures contracts. Speaking of the development, Giovanni Vicioso, CME Group Global Head of Cryptocurrency Products <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/cme-group-to-launch-etherbitcoin-ratio-futures-on-july-31-301867241.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Historically, ether and bitcoin have been highly correlated; however, as the two assets have grown over time, market dynamics may affect the performance of one more than the other, creating relative value trading opportunities. With the addition of Ether/Bitcoin Ratio futures, investors will be able to capture ether and bitcoin exposure in a single trade, without needing to take a directional view. This new contract will help create opportunities for a broad array of clients looking to hedge positions or execute other trading strategies, all in an efficient, cost-effective manner.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Major Advantage of Ether/Bitcoin Ratio Futures</h2>
<p>The introduction of Ether/Bitcoin Ratio futures (EBR) enables traders to efficiently engage in relative value trading between Ether futures (ETH) and Bitcoin futures (BTC) contracts within a single trade. This innovative contract provides investors with an opportunity to gain exposure to cryptocurrencies without requiring a specific directional bias.</p>
<p>Ether/Bitcoin Ratio futures offer traders a convenient means to express their perspective on the relative value of the two cryptocurrencies, regardless of their overall cryptocurrency market outlook. The ratio futures are denoted by the ticker EBR on CME Globex, with the ratio being defined as the price of Ether futures divided by the price of Bitcoin futures.</p>
<p>The EBR Final Settlement price is determined by dividing the Final Settlement Price of Ether futures by the Final Settlement Price of Bitcoin futures. The ratio is calculated using the same expiration month for both the underlying Ether and Bitcoin futures contracts. The ratio is always positive and is available for all listed contract months. The contract&#8217;s notional value is derived by multiplying the ratio by $1,000,000.</p>
<p>Crypto industry players have lauded this move from the CME Group stating that it will bring more liquidity into the markets.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/3iq-coinbase-streamline-eth-staking/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cme-ether-bitcoin-ratio-futures/">CME Group Unveils Plans of Launching Ether/Bitcoin Ratio Futures</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/cme-ether-bitcoin-ratio-futures/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Canadian Investment Fund Manager 3iQ to Work with Coinbase to Streamline ETH Staking</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/3iq-coinbase-streamline-eth-staking/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/3iq-coinbase-streamline-eth-staking/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 08:39:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funds & ETFs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3iq]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261118</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/3iq-coinbase-streamline-eth-staking/">Canadian Investment Fund Manager 3iQ to Work with Coinbase to Streamline ETH Staking</a></p>
<p>3iQ intends to offer staking for its Ether Fund and 3iQ Ether ETF with the help of Coinbase Custody Trust Company in a regulated manner.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/3iq-coinbase-streamline-eth-staking/">Canadian Investment Fund Manager 3iQ to Work with Coinbase to Streamline ETH Staking</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/3iq-coinbase-streamline-eth-staking/">Canadian Investment Fund Manager 3iQ to Work with Coinbase to Streamline ETH Staking</a></p>
<p>Canadian digital asset investment fund manager with more than $881 million in AUM &#8211; 3iQ Corp &#8211; <a href="https://3iq.io/ca/3iq-announces-ether-staking-in-the-ether-fund-and-the-3iq-ether-etf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">has announced</a> a strategic collaboration with <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase Global Inc</a> (NASDAQ: COIN) to offer <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ether</a> staking through its products, including The Ether Fund (TSX: QETH.UN, QETH.U) and The 3iQ Ether ETF (TSX: ETHQ, ETHQ.U). The Ether staking program by 3iQ is set to begin on August 28, 2023, to ensure the products are regulated for safe adoption by retail and institutional investors.</p>
<p>The announcement was bullish for all involved entities with COIN shares closing Thursday trading around $72.43, up approximately 2.3 percent from the day’s opening price. On the other hand, 3iQ Ether ETF jumped about 1.45 percent on Thursday to close the day trading around $9.79.</p>
<h2>3iQ Ether Staking via Coinbase</h2>
<p>According to the announcement the implementation of the latest enhancement will market the first Ether staking for ETP and ETF in the Northern American market. Once implemented, the Fund holders will have an opportunity for a yield-earning program that is secure and regulated. Moreover, the Funds will earn rewards in the form of ETH and be reflected in the holders’ net asset value (NAV).</p>
<p>“While staying true to the investment objectives of the Funds, we believe that commencing ETH staking offers the best of both worlds to our investors – providing additional yield while eliminating the complexities of directly handling digital assets,&#8221; said Fred Pye, Chairman and CEO of 3iQ.</p>
<p>Over the years since being established in 2012, the company has proved to be a leader in digital assets products. As a result, 3iQ intends to keep the momentum to launch attractive products for institutional investors in North America and worldwide. Furthermore, the digital economy has significantly grown to a trillion-dollar industry with experts forecasting more exponential gains.</p>
<p>Reportedly, Coinbase Custody Trust Company will serve as a custodian of the Funds, while Coinbase Custody&#8217;s institutional staking infrastructure will support ETH staking in these products.</p>
<p>“We are proud to strengthen our strategic relationship with 3iQ and continue to demonstrate that Coinbase is consistently chosen by reputable players for our unwavering commitment to safety, trust, and security in the digital asset ecosystem,” Brett Tejpaul, Head of Coinbase Institutional, <a href="https://www.newswire.ca/news-releases/3iq-announces-ether-staking-in-the-ether-fund-and-the-3iq-ether-etf-841159211.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">noted</a>.</p>
<p>Notably, Coinbase Custody will be entitled to a fee charged in accordance with the rewards. Additionally, 3iQ will enter into a revenue-sharing agreement with the fund holders, for which the company will issue a notice before the commencement of Ether staking.</p>
<p>The announcement is a huge welcome to the crypto market in North America, where most institutional investors have received hostile treatment from the US Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>).</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nike-fiscal-2023-q4-results/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/3iq-coinbase-streamline-eth-staking/">Canadian Investment Fund Manager 3iQ to Work with Coinbase to Streamline ETH Staking</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/3iq-coinbase-streamline-eth-staking/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nike Announces Fiscal 2023 Q4 Results, Misses Profits Expectations</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nike-fiscal-2023-q4-results/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nike-fiscal-2023-q4-results/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 08:32:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nike]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261107</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nike-fiscal-2023-q4-results/">Nike Announces Fiscal 2023 Q4 Results, Misses Profits Expectations</a></p>
<p>Despite an earnings miss during the fiscal 2023 Q4, Nike beat revenue estimates for the seventh straight quarter.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nike-fiscal-2023-q4-results/">Nike Announces Fiscal 2023 Q4 Results, Misses Profits Expectations</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nike-fiscal-2023-q4-results/">Nike Announces Fiscal 2023 Q4 Results, Misses Profits Expectations</a></p>
<p>While <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/nike/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Nike</a> (NYSE: NKE) surpassed estimates in its fiscal 2023 Q4 revenue, the company’s profit for the same quarter was short of expectations. For the first time in three years, the footwear manufacturing company missed on earnings due to lower margins in the fourth quarter. Nike announced its fiscal 2023 Q4 and full-year results on the 29th of June, revealing that lower margins impacted its profits during the three months.</p>
<h2>Nike Releases Fiscal 2023 Q4 Performance Results</h2>
<p>According to the <a href="https://s1.q4cdn.com/806093406/files/doc_financials/2023/q4/FY23-Q4-Combined-NIKE-Press-Release-Schedules-FINAL.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">fiscal Q4 report</a>, Nike saw its revenue increase 5% YoY to $12.8 billion, while expectations were $12.59 billion. The quarterly revenue was also up 8% on a currency-neutral basis. The company noted that Nike Direct reported revenue for the same period was $5.5 billion, representing a 15% increase compared to the previous year. This was led by a 24% growth from Nike-owned stores and another 14% surge from Nike Brand Digital.</p>
<p>On the other hand, Nike posted earnings per share of 66 cents, falling short of the expected 67 cents. The manufacturing company’s President and CEO, John Donahoe, commenced on how Nike performed during the fiscal 2023 Q4.</p>
<p>“NIKE’s strong results make clear that our strategy is working. FY2023 was a milestone for NIKE as our unique advantages continue to drive competitive separation. Our investment in innovation and our digital leadership are fueling broad-based growth across our portfolio of brands, as we create value by serving the future of sport,” told the CEO.</p>
<p>However, the retailer also experienced a rare miss as net income was $1.03 billion compared with $1,44 billion in the year before. It also noted that its gross margin fell 140 basis points to 43.6%, majorly because of the higher cost of product input and freight and logistics costs. The unfavorable changes in net foreign currency exchange rates also contributed to the lower gross margin. Furthermore, Nike stated that selling and administrative expenses went up 8% to $4.4 billion.</p>
<h2>Higher Sales in China</h2>
<p>The company revealed that sales rose by about 5% from $12.23 billion the year before to $12.83 billion. Despite an earnings miss during the fiscal 2023 Q4, Nike beat revenue estimates for the seventh straight quarter. This can be traced to the sales boom in China as the company resumes its pre-covid operations. It has rolled back its zero-Covid policy, which severely hurt its economy. The quarter after the poly was lifted, China’s economy jumped 4.5%, and US companies in the country confirmed higher sales.</p>
<p>For the coming quarter, Nike expects revenue to be flat to up low single digits. Meanwhile, according to Refinitiv, analysts&#8217; expectations were for sales to grow by 5.8%. In addition, the manufacturer is looking forward to its gross margin dropping between 0.5 to 0.75 percentage points.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/melania-trump-us-nfts/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nike-fiscal-2023-q4-results/">Nike Announces Fiscal 2023 Q4 Results, Misses Profits Expectations</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nike-fiscal-2023-q4-results/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Melania Trump Releases US Independence Day-Inspired NFTs</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/melania-trump-us-nfts/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/melania-trump-us-nfts/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 08:18:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[donald trump]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[melania trump]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261102</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/melania-trump-us-nfts/">Melania Trump Releases US Independence Day-Inspired NFTs</a></p>
<p>The new release is named “The 1776 Collection”, and it includes Six Limited Edition Collectables.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/melania-trump-us-nfts/">Melania Trump Releases US Independence Day-Inspired NFTs</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/melania-trump-us-nfts/">Melania Trump Releases US Independence Day-Inspired NFTs</a></p>
<p>Melania Trump, the former first lady of the United States and ex-president Donald Trump’s wife, recently released a set of NFTs inspired by the July 4th Independence Day holiday. It appears the Trump family is ready for rounds of back-to-back <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NFTs</a>, as Donald Trump just unveiled the second batch of his NFT trading cards about two months ago.</p>
<p>The politician dropped a <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/donald-trump-nft-collection/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">second collection</a> of digital trading cards in April for $99 a piece, with tens of thousands of new collectibles available for minting. Some of the cards have his signature, and the collectibles were the talk of the town at the time of release. However, the new set caused the first&#8217;s price to plummet.</p>
<h2>Melania Trump Begins Independence Day Celebration Early with NFTs Launch</h2>
<p>The new NFTs by Melania Trump are available for sale through “USAmemorabilia&#8221; for $50 each. Interested persons will be able to purchase them from the 29th of June, before the independent day celebration. The former first lady retweeted a tweet by the company about the sale. The new release is named “The 1776 Collection”, and it is Six Limited Edition Collectables. The Melania Trump NFTs consist of historical images across the US, including the Statue of Liberty. Others are Mount Rushmore, the Liberty Bell, etc.</p>
<p>According to Melania, each of the digital collectibles represents an aspect of Americana. She added that the collection was designed to revere America’s history. The former first lady <a href="https://www.foxnews.com/politics/melania-trump-launches-1776-nft-collection-july-4th-foster-kids?intcmp=tw_pols" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">told</a> Fox News Digital:</p>
<blockquote><p>“The 1776 Collection of artwork draws inspiration from several iconic landmarks of our nation, which I had the privilege of visiting during the time I served as first lady. Each piece provides a view into our nation’s history, culture and patriotism. I am proud to celebrate our great nation and remain inspired by the words contained within the Declaration of Independence.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Fox News revealed that Melania plans to channel a percentage of the proceeds from the Solana-based NFTs sale to Be Best initiative- Fostering the Future. This program focuses on helping children in foster care communities secure education opportunities and scholarships. The initiative grants computer science scholarships to children aging out of the foster care systems. This helps them gain knowledge that may help them get technology-based jobs and further help them to be financially independent.</p>
<p>Before releasing the latest NFTs, Melania Trump noted in a last month&#8217;s interview that her commitment to the foster community has increased since she left Washington D.C. Also, she plans to continue supporting children if she gets to serve as the US first lady again.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fidelity-spot-bitcoin-etf-blackrock/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/melania-trump-us-nfts/">Melania Trump Releases US Independence Day-Inspired NFTs</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/melania-trump-us-nfts/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fidelity Investments Rejoins Race for Spot Bitcoin ETF after BlackRock, Others</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fidelity-spot-bitcoin-etf-blackrock/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fidelity-spot-bitcoin-etf-blackrock/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 08:11:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funds & ETFs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blackrock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cboe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fidelity investments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261100</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fidelity-spot-bitcoin-etf-blackrock/">Fidelity Investments Rejoins Race for Spot Bitcoin ETF after BlackRock, Others</a></p>
<p>Following BlackRock's growing chance of an approval, Fidelity Investments has submitted another application for a spot Bitcoin ETF.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fidelity-spot-bitcoin-etf-blackrock/">Fidelity Investments Rejoins Race for Spot Bitcoin ETF after BlackRock, Others</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fidelity-spot-bitcoin-etf-blackrock/">Fidelity Investments Rejoins Race for Spot Bitcoin ETF after BlackRock, Others</a></p>
<p>Asset management firm <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/fidelity-investments/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Fidelity Investments</a> has submitted another filing for a spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-bitcoin-exchange-traded-fund-etf/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ETF</a>). Fidelity is making another play at a spot ETF after a previous rejection from the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>).</p>
<p>Last year, the SEC <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-disapproves-fidelity-spot-bitcoin-etf/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">rejected</a> Fidelity’s proposal for the Wise Origin spot Bitcoin ETF. The SEC said the proposal did not contain enough measures to detect and prevent market manipulation and fraud. According to the Commission, the ETF must be designed to prevent fraudulent activity.</p>
<p>On Wednesday, CoinSpeaker <a href="https://www.theblock.co/post/236588/fidelity-preparing-to-submit-spot-bitcoin-etf-filing-source" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a> that the company was close to refiling a spot Bitcoin ETF proposal, according to people familiar with Fidelity’s plans. The assumption was a possible Tuesday filing for Fidelity’s second attempt at a spot Bitcoin ETF. Fidelity had already <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fidelity-bitcoin-etf-canada/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">launched</a> a spot Bitcoin ETF in Canada in 2021, called the Fidelity Advantage Bitcoin.</p>
<h2>Fidelity’s Second Attempt Comes Shortly After BlackRock’s</h2>
<p>Interestingly, giant asset manager BlackRock <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/blackrock-spot-bitcoin-etf-sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">filed an application</a> for a spot Bitcoin ETF barely two weeks ago. BlackRock’s iShares Bitcoin Trust ETF application includes crypto exchange <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase</a> (NASDAQ: COIN) as the Bitcoin custodian, and Bank of New York Mellon (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/bny-mellon/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BNY Mellon</a>) as the cash custodian.</p>
<p>Initially, BlackRock’s chance of approval seemed bleak because the SEC has rejected all spot Bitcoin ETF proposals ever submitted. However, some Bloomberg analysts believe that the asset manager now has a <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/blackrock-chance-spot-bitcoin-etf-approval/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">50% chance of receiving approval</a>. Senior ETF analyst Eric Balchunas says this is because of Grayscale’s SEC case. Bloomberg Senior legal analyst gave Grayscale a 70% chance of triumph against the SEC after recent oral arguments in court. Consequently, the analysts believe that the SEC could soon approve BlackRock’s application, allowing a traditional finance company to run a Bitcoin ETF, while ignoring Grayscale.</p>
<h2>Grayscale May Indirectly Help Secure the First Spot Bitcoin ETF in the US</h2>
<p>Last June, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/grayscale/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Grayscale Investments</a> filed a <a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2022/06/30/2471737/0/en/Grayscale-Investments-Initiates-Lawsuit-Against-the-SEC.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">lawsuit</a> against the SEC after the Commission rejected its spot Bitcoin ETF proposal. The SEC also said Grayscale’s proposal did not adequately include measures to prevent market fraud and manipulation. Grayscale CEO Michael Sonnehshein said he was disappointed, and “vehemently disagrees” with the regulator’s position.</p>
<p>Another reason BlackRock could snag approval is the amendment of its filing that includes a Spot BTC SSA. The SSA is a bilateral agreement that ensures surveillance sharing to prevent market fraud. Recently, the Cboe BZX Exchange also <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cboe-ark-bitcoin-etf/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">amended</a> an ETF filing to include an SSA. The proposers likely hope the market surveillance agreement addresses the SEC’s concerns about market manipulation.</p>
<p>Fidelity Investment’s decision to make another play for a spot Bitcoin ETF may be connected to BlackRock’s possible approval. The likelihood that the SEC would approve more proposals may be high if it allows BlackRock.</p>
<p>The SEC rejected the first-ever spot Bitcoin ETF application proposed in 2013 by the Winklevoss Bitcoin Trust. Since then, the Commission has rejected applications from Vaneck, Fidelity, Grayscale, the New York Digital Investment Group (NYDIG), Wilshire Phoenix, and Bitwise.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-german-license-denied-bafin/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fidelity-spot-bitcoin-etf-blackrock/">Fidelity Investments Rejoins Race for Spot Bitcoin ETF after BlackRock, Others</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fidelity-spot-bitcoin-etf-blackrock/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Application for German Operational License Denied by BaFin</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-german-license-denied-bafin/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-german-license-denied-bafin/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 14:22:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Binance News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bafin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261080</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-german-license-denied-bafin/">Binance Application for German Operational License Denied by BaFin</a></p>
<p>The denial of a custody license in Germany poses significant challenges for Binance, as Germany represents one of Europe's largest and most influential markets.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-german-license-denied-bafin/">Binance Application for German Operational License Denied by BaFin</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-german-license-denied-bafin/">Binance Application for German Operational License Denied by BaFin</a></p>
<p>Germany&#8217;s Federal Financial Supervisory Authority (BaFin) has reportedly denied the Binance exchange&#8217;s application for a crypto custody license. Finance Forward, a news publication, has <a href="https://financefwd.com/de/binance-lizenz-deutschland/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reported</a> that BaFin has communicated this decision directly to the exchange.</p>
<p>The decision signifies a regulatory setback for the crypto trading platform. A custody license would have allowed <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a> to legally offer crypto custody services to its German customers, ensuring compliance with the country&#8217;s stringent financial regulations.</p>
<p>People familiar with the matter suggest that BaFin&#8217;s decision was influenced by concerns over the lack of transparency and regulatory compliance within Binance&#8217;s operations. However, The nature of BaFin&#8217;s decision regarding Binance&#8217;s custody license remains uncertain.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s unclear if the denial constitutes a formal cancellation or an expression of intent amid ongoing negotiations. However, the message conveyed by these discussions is undeniably clear, BaFin has doubts about Binance&#8217;s compliance with regulatory standards.</p>
<p>Notably, a Binance spokesperson has acknowledged the ongoing discussions with regulators and emphasized the company&#8217;s commitment to complying with BaFin&#8217;s requirements. On the other hand, BaFin declined to comment on the matter due to professional secrecy requirements in Germany.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Binance has already established a significant presence in the German crypto market. As one of the largest crypto apps in Germany, Binance has managed to attract a substantial user base, with an estimated two million customers.</p>
<p>Despite the absence of a license, individuals can still access the Binance website and app, as there are no explicit restrictions on visiting or using the platform. However, limitations arise in terms of the Binance exchange&#8217;s ability to legally provide custodial services and certain other regulated activities in Germany.</p>
<h2>BaFin Rejection: Implications for Binance</h2>
<p>The denial of a custody license in Germany poses significant challenges for Binance, as Germany represents one of Europe&#8217;s largest and most influential markets. With the license, Binance would have gained a competitive advantage by offering compliant custodial services to German customers.</p>
<p>However, without the necessary license, Binance is not permitted to promote its services within the country. This can potentially impede the company&#8217;s growth and outreach to potential customers in the German market.</p>
<p>Furthermore, this action may affect Binance&#8217;s credibility in the broader crypto market. Given the increased emphasis on regulatory compliance, exchanges that fail to meet regulatory criteria risk losing credibility and may find it difficult to retain the trust of both investors and institutional partners.</p>
<p>It is worth mentioning that Binance is not the only Fintech startup that has been scrutinized by German regulators. Other fintech startups targeted by German regulators include Crypto.com, Cakedefi, and Uniswap.</p>
<p>Recent reports also suggested that Binance has encountered challenges with regulatory approvals and operations in various jurisdictions. A recent report revealed that Binance <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-withdraws-application-austria/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">withdrew</a> its application for regulatory approval in Austria.</p>
<p>Additionally, the company has reportedly abandoned its registration with Cyprus&#8217; securities regulator and decided to <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-bids-farewell-to-the-netherlands-a-new-crypto-gem-with-the-growth-potential-of-btc-goes-global/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">exit</a> the Netherlands after an unsuccessful attempt to register.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ecb-cbdc-trials-2024/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-german-license-denied-bafin/">Binance Application for German Operational License Denied by BaFin</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-german-license-denied-bafin/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>ECB Set to Launch CBDC Market Settlement Trials by 2024</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ecb-cbdc-trials-2024/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ecb-cbdc-trials-2024/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 14:16:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ecb]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261073</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ecb-cbdc-trials-2024/">ECB Set to Launch CBDC Market Settlement Trials by 2024</a></p>
<p>As research continues into a possible digital euro, the ECB plans to begin trials that settle transactions using a CBDC.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ecb-cbdc-trials-2024/">ECB Set to Launch CBDC Market Settlement Trials by 2024</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ecb-cbdc-trials-2024/">ECB Set to Launch CBDC Market Settlement Trials by 2024</a></p>
<p>The European Central Bank will begin trials on market transaction settlements using distributed ledger technology (DLT) via a central bank digital currency (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-central-bank-digital-currency-cbdc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CBDC</a>). The ECB’s readiness to begin the CBDC trials and experimentation follows the first <a href="https://www.ecb.europa.eu/paym/groups/ntwcg/pdf/ecb.ntwdocs230621_outcome_1st_ntwcg_meeting.en.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener">meeting</a> of the New Technologies for Wholesale Settlement Contact Group (NTW-CG).</p>
<p>The minutes of the meeting explored transaction settlements between financial institutions in addition to the development of a CBDC. The ECB’s trials will begin in 2024 and likely cover basic transactions and settlements as they will be “limited in capacity and time”.</p>
<h2>The ECB and the Digital Euro CBDC</h2>
<p>Last month, the ECB <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ecb-digital-euro-prototype-cbdc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">finalized</a> a digital euro prototype and published a report on its findings. Although this prototype is a result of deep research, the apex bank has yet to decide on CBDC issuance.</p>
<p>The ECB’s report indicated that it researched the use of DLT and smart contracts as a framework for the CBDC. While they proved essential, the ECB has concerns about decentralized smart contracts. Nonetheless, executive board member Fabio Panetta notes that the digital euro would integrate with the existing financial ecosystem. This would help financial institutions to expand innovation and related solutions. The report came after the ECB conducted the prototype exercise from July 2022 to February 2023.</p>
<p>The European Commission also published proposals that support the use of a digital euro that complements coins and banknotes. The Commission said it recognizes that while most people like the cash option, many others want digital options for payment, especially since the COVID-19 pandemic.</p>
<h2>More Research into a European CBDC</h2>
<p>Proposals submitted by the European Commission contain a legislative proposal to safeguard the role of cash and another to create a legal framework for the digital euro. The Commission’s proposal states that the euro would support direct transactions between devices, would not require an internet connection, and would ensure a higher level of privacy. However, the Commission notes that its proposal still depends on the ECB to determine CBDC issuance.</p>
<p>The European Parliament is in favor of continued research into a CBDC. However, its position on issuance may be less favorable. According to a <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-parliament-research-digital-euro/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">report</a> by the Parliament’s Committee on Economic and Monetary Affairs, a CBDC could adversely affect the ECB. Economist Ignazio Angeloni, who authored the report, believes that a CBDC would force the ECB to compete with commercial banks for deposits.</p>
<p>Furthermore, Angeloni states that the CBDC should not be too successful or too unsuccessful. If too successful, there would be adverse consequences for the monetary policy if bank intermediation is not optimum. This could lead to financial instability if the process &#8211; which channels funds between institutions with surplus and those that do not have enough &#8211; is destabilized.</p>
<p>On the other hand, an unsuccessful CBDC would mean the ECB wasted a lot of resources. According to the economist, the ECB would also suffer reputational damage.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-future-growth-aspects/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ecb-cbdc-trials-2024/">ECB Set to Launch CBDC Market Settlement Trials by 2024</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ecb-cbdc-trials-2024/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Continues to Focus on Future Growth Aspects despite Regulatory Hurdles</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-future-growth-aspects/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-future-growth-aspects/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 12:49:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bicasso]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261058</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-future-growth-aspects/">Binance Continues to Focus on Future Growth Aspects despite Regulatory Hurdles</a></p>
<p>Binance is using top technologies like machine learning and AI to enhance customer safety and security on the platform. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-future-growth-aspects/">Binance Continues to Focus on Future Growth Aspects despite Regulatory Hurdles</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-future-growth-aspects/">Binance Continues to Focus on Future Growth Aspects despite Regulatory Hurdles</a></p>
<p>This month, crypto exchange <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a> has gone through a lot of regulatory turbulence after facing major lawsuits from the US Securities and Exchange Commission. The <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a> action has also led to Binance losing some market share in June.</p>
<p>However, these regulatory hurdles haven&#8217;t deterred Binance from making further progress with future goals in mind. As per the latest press release shared with Coinspeaker, Binance is implementing machine learning and AI to make the platform safer and more secure.</p>
<div>
<div>
<div>
<div>
<div>
<div>
<p>In Binance&#8217;s peer-to-peer (P2P) platform, ML technology is employed to identify suspicious language in communications. By utilizing ML in P2P chat, feedback, and advertisements, potential payment scams, customer service impersonation, and malicious messaging can be detected. This technology has proven effective in preventing thousands of scams.</p>
<p>For the know-your-customer (KYC) process, Binance utilizes a combination of computer vision (CV) and AI. These technologies aid in verifying documents and videos submitted by users during the registration process. The implementation of CV and AI has significantly strengthened the verification process, enabling the detection of forged KYC documents and facial attacks.</p>
<p>In addition to enhancing security, Binance explores the creative use of AI. An example is Bicasso, a feature that leverages advanced AI technology to generate user avatars, which can then be transformed into non-fungible tokens (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NFTs</a>). This demonstrates Binance&#8217;s commitment to leveraging AI for innovative product development.</p>
<h2>Binance Is Improving Infrastructure</h2>
<p>Over the last year, Binance&#8217;s engineering team has been working hard to improve the platform&#8217;s infrastructure thereby making it more faster and efficient for users. Binance has also upgraded its futures matching engine and thus increasing the capacity by 50%.</p>
<p>With some improvements to its Ledger, Binance claims that it has made transactions anywhere between 5-50 times faster.</p>
<p>Binance has implemented significant improvements to enhance user security, including the integration of passkey technology into Binance ID. This advanced technology provides users with increased protection against SMS scams and malicious attacks by making it more difficult for scammers to gain unauthorized access to accounts.</p>
<p>Continuing their focus on user-centric developments, Binance has introduced an updated <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-decentralized-finance-defi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">DeFi</a> wallet, offering users greater flexibility in choosing the crypto wallet that suits their needs. Leveraging Binance ID and passkey technology, the new DeFi wallet ensures that users never have to worry about losing their passkey or seed phrase.</p>
<p>Another example of Binance&#8217;s responsiveness to user needs is the introduction of the Binance Tax tool. This tool was developed after users expressed the need for a simplified and clearer method to access information for their tax returns.</p>
<p>Binance also understands the value of continuous improvements to the core trading experience. Throughout the year, they have introduced nearly 200 updates to enhance trading accessibility and provide users with essential information. These updates include features like the ability to reverse positions, access yearly profit and loss analysis, view multiple currencies simultaneously on charts, and additional shortcut buttons for easier navigation, such as Adjust Leverage, Stop PnL, Close Position, Market Close, and Reverse.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hm-shares-soar-16-month-high/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-future-growth-aspects/">Binance Continues to Focus on Future Growth Aspects despite Regulatory Hurdles</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-future-growth-aspects/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>H&amp;M Shares Soar 17%, Hits 16-Month High</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/hm-shares-soar-16-month-high/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/hm-shares-soar-16-month-high/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 12:39:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[h&m]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hm stock]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261057</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hm-shares-soar-16-month-high/">H&#038;M Shares Soar 17%, Hits 16-Month High</a></p>
<p>The company's CEO Helena Helmersson said H&#038;M upped sales in multiple markets even as customers reduced their spending behavior.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hm-shares-soar-16-month-high/">H&#038;M Shares Soar 17%, Hits 16-Month High</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hm-shares-soar-16-month-high/">H&#038;M Shares Soar 17%, Hits 16-Month High</a></p>
<p>On Thursday, popular fashion retailer H&amp;M saw its shares reach a 16-month high as its Q2 profits exceeded expectations. The multinational clothing company gained 16.74% to reach its highest level since February 2022. At a time when people are spending more on food to survive the increasing cost of living, the retailer managed to surge as it targets shoppers less vulnerable to the high standard of living. H&amp;M also began to record a significant share increase as it began its <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hm-exits-russia/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">cost-cutting measures</a>.</p>
<p>Like many other companies, H&amp;M laid off employees to reduce high costs and amass profit. The company became the first European retailer to dismiss staff in response to the cost of living crisis. It cut 1,500 off its workers to save 2 billion Swedish crowns ($190 million) a year in November 2022.</p>
<p>&#8220;The external factors that affect our purchasing costs continue to improve, work on the cost and efficiency program is proceeding at full speed, and much of the work that we have done in recent years is starting to bear fruit,&#8221; H&amp;M CEO Helena Helmersson <a href="https://hmgroup.com/news/h-m-hennes-mauritz-ab-six-month-report-14/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>.</p>
<h2>H&amp;M Shares Pop as Sales Spike</h2>
<p>The company&#8217;s CEO Helena Helmersson said H&amp;M upped sales in multiple markets even as customers reduced their spending behavior. The number of people who splurge on clothing has diminished amid the unstable economy. Also, She mentioned that H&amp;M gathered profits in the second quarter, which caused its shares to soar despite the &#8220;unfavorable weather&#8221;. The CEO added that the sale of the company&#8217;s summer collection also began on a good level as summer kicks in across northern Europe.</p>
<p>Following impressive performance during the second quarter, H&amp;M continued at a good pace. Sales between June 1 and June 27 grew 10% YoY, with the most contribution from the womenswear collection. Cedric Rossi, the next-gen consumer analyst at Bryan Garnier in Paris, also had something to say about the factors pushing H&amp;M shares to a high level:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;I was really surprised to see that, without any higher promotional activity &#8211; because markdowns were in line with last year &#8211; H&amp;M decreased its inventory position.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The sharp drop in inventory sales was another surprising cause, as the company&#8217;s inventory was at 16.7% of rolling 12-month sales on May 31, down from 19.2% a year earlier. Considering the better-than-expected profit and the inventory margin, investors could digest a weaker margin of 8.2% for the second quarter. Meanwhile, the company recorded 9.2% in the previous year.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/worldcoin-okta-world-id/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hm-shares-soar-16-month-high/">H&#038;M Shares Soar 17%, Hits 16-Month High</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/hm-shares-soar-16-month-high/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4086 metric#misses=41 metric#hit-ratio=99.0 metric#bytes=992854 metric#prefetches=186 metric#store-reads=19 metric#store-writes=2 metric#store-hits=192 metric#store-misses=2 metric#sql-queries=34 metric#ms-total=111.87 metric#ms-cache=5.31 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.2656 metric#ms-cache-ratio=4.8 -->