<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 14:45:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Arthur Hayes: ETH Will Be Main Winner of AI Economy Next Decade</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/eth-ai-economy/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/eth-ai-economy/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 13:53:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[arthur hayes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitmex]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=264949</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/eth-ai-economy/">Arthur Hayes: ETH Will Be Main Winner of AI Economy Next Decade</a></p>
<p>Hayes says ETH will skyrocket sometime in the next few years as the AI revolution strengthens and DAOs begin to form. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/eth-ai-economy/">Arthur Hayes: ETH Will Be Main Winner of AI Economy Next Decade</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/eth-ai-economy/">Arthur Hayes: ETH Will Be Main Winner of AI Economy Next Decade</a></p>
<p>Co-founder and former CEO of the BitMEX crypto exchange <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/arthur-hayes/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Arthur Hayes</a> believes that Ethereum (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/">ETH</a>) will be the main winner and beneficiary of the AI revolution over the next decade. In a long-form <a href="https://entrepreneurshandbook.co/moai-da798c72a83b" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">blog post</a> titled Moai, Hayes argues that the price of ETH would likely skyrocket.</p>
<p>Hayes states that the world relies on the limited liability company (LLC) to produce and exchange goods and services that keep the global economy running. He explains that there are several rules guiding the operations of these companies that will not apply to artificial intelligence. According to Hayes, the regular organizational structure companies use will not work with AI “who ‘thinks’ in lines of computer code and has no physical body”.</p>
<p>The BitMEX co-founder believes the only organizational structure that agrees with AI is a Decentralised Autonomous Organisation (DAO). According to him, the DAO structure is the best way for humans and AI to interact and collaborate because it relies on blockchain technology. Hayes also argues that it’s the only organizational structure AI will willingly follow. This is because, save for eradicating all computers in the world and destroying the internet, AI cannot be killed and will therefore have no reason to comply with human laws.</p>
<h2>Hayes Predicts ETH Will Soar via AI DAOs</h2>
<p>The Hayes argument for ETH is that the Ethereum Virtual Machine is the world’s “most robust decentralized computer.” He believes that ETH is the best fit for the AI revolution, and the price will spike with the growth of AI DAOs:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Ethereum transactions will grow exponentially as DAOs proliferate. As a result, the price of ETH should skyrocket in anticipation if this AI DAO hypothesis is widely believed.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Hayes also creates a bullish case for decentralized exchanges (DEXs) with EVM-compatible governance tokens. According to him, the DEXs will achieve “natural monopolies” and provide significant profits to people who can identify them early and purchase their governance tokens. However, he is most bullish on ETH for AI and other endeavors as he believes the original Ethereum will never lose its position for a duplicate.</p>
<blockquote><p>“I’m a bit of an ETH maxi when it comes to needing actual utility on a Layer-1. While investors might make money trading the latest hyped Ethereum clone, none of them will ever eclipse Ethereum in terms of adoption and usefulness.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>Bullish Case for Bitcoin</h2>
<p>In an earlier <a href="https://cryptohayes.substack.com/p/massa" target="_blank" rel="noopener">post</a> published on July 7, Hayes argues in favor of Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a>) as the AI currency. His argument for Bitcoin specifies the need for a blockchain-based digital payments system but also compares the world’s largest cryptocurrency by market capitalization to other assets like gold and fiat.</p>
<p>As part of his comparison, Hayes highlights inherent problems with gold. He argues that gold is not digitally efficient because people have to use gold certificates. The problem here is they must trust that they can redeem the gold from the issuer at any time. Because of these issuers, gold is not censorship resistant. The argument against fiat is similar as the government controls the issuance, ensuring it is not censorship resistant.</p>
<p>Finally, Hayes says Bitcoin is best because it is censorship resistant, has a public network, and cannot be shut down by any one entity.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-com-dutch-central-bank/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/eth-ai-economy/">Arthur Hayes: ETH Will Be Main Winner of AI Economy Next Decade</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/eth-ai-economy/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto.com Receives Green Light from Dutch Central Bank to Offer Crypto Services</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-com-dutch-central-bank/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-com-dutch-central-bank/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 13:32:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto.com]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=264990</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-com-dutch-central-bank/">Crypto.com Receives Green Light from Dutch Central Bank to Offer Crypto Services</a></p>
<p>Crypto.com's entrance to the Dutch market comes a few weeks after Binance exited the country due to regulatory hurdles.  </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-com-dutch-central-bank/">Crypto.com Receives Green Light from Dutch Central Bank to Offer Crypto Services</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-com-dutch-central-bank/">Crypto.com Receives Green Light from Dutch Central Bank to Offer Crypto Services</a></p>
<p>Leading digital asset service provider Crypto.com has successfully registered its business offerings with the Dutch central bank to offer crypto services in the Netherlands.</p>
<p>In an <a href="https://crypto.com/company-news/crypto-com-secures-registration-approval-in-the-netherlands" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announcement</a> on June 28, the company said it obtained approval from the De Nederlandsche Bank (DNB) after a comprehensive review of its business and compliance with the country&#8217;s Anti-Money Laundering and Terrorist Financing (Prevention) Act.</p>
<p>By successfully meeting the regulatory requirements set by DNB, the exchange can now offer its crypto services to users in the Netherlands in compliance with local regulations.</p>
<p>&#8220;This registration approval from De Nederlandsche Bank is a significant milestone for our business and the latest testament to our commitment to compliance. We look forward to continuing to work with DNB and other regulators around the world,&#8221; said Kris Marszalek, CEO of Crypto.com.</p>
<p>Crypto.com has joined other digital asset service providers already registered in the Netherlands to explore the market. The country has granted 36 companies, including Coinbase Europe, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/etoro/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">eToro</a>, and Bitstamp, licenses to legally offer custodial and exchange services to customers in the region.</p>
<h2>Crypto.com Registered in Singapore and Other Jurisdictions</h2>
<p>The new registration with the DNB marks a significant milestone for Crypto.com as it continues its global expansion strategy. Before its latest achievement in the Netherlands, the company had previously obtained approvals and licenses in different countries, including Singapore, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/france-crypto-com-approval/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">France</a>, the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-com-registers-with-uk-financial-conduct-authority/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">United Kingdom</a>, Australia, and Spain.</p>
<p>Each of these registrations enables the exchange to offer specific services compliant with local regulations. In Singapore, for example, Crypto.com <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-com-license-singapore/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">obtained</a> a Major Payment Institution (MPI) license for Digital Payment Token (DPT) and an MPI for e-money issuance and cross-border money transfer services.</p>
<p>With its commitment to responsible compliance and collaboration with regulators, the exchange aims to foster a sustainable and thriving crypto ecosystem while gaining greater acceptance and recognition from users and regulators.</p>
<h2>Binance Backs Out of Dutch Market while Crypto. Com Is Entering It</h2>
<p>Crypto.com&#8217;s entrance to the Dutch market comes a few weeks after Binance, the world&#8217;s largest digital asset trading platform, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-exit-netherlands-vasp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">exited</a> the country due to regulatory hurdles.</p>
<p>Despite Binance&#8217;s efforts to collaborate with the country&#8217;s financial watchdog and explore various alternatives and strategies, the exchange could not find a viable alternative to register as a digital asset service provider (VASP) in the region.</p>
<p>In light of the hurdles encountered, the company maintains its commitment to adhering to regulations and plans to continue working with the authorities to seek better avenues to establish itself as a VASP in the future.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bank-of-spain-etoro-registration/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-com-dutch-central-bank/">Crypto.com Receives Green Light from Dutch Central Bank to Offer Crypto Services</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-com-dutch-central-bank/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bank of Spain Approves eToro Registration as Virtual Asset Exchange</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bank-of-spain-etoro-registration/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bank-of-spain-etoro-registration/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 12:54:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[algo]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[algorand]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[decentraland]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[etoro]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[matic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[polygon]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=264967</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bank-of-spain-etoro-registration/">Bank of Spain Approves eToro Registration as Virtual Asset Exchange</a></p>
<p>eToro said that it will continue to empower our Spanish users by providing them with access to a diverse range of asset classes. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bank-of-spain-etoro-registration/">Bank of Spain Approves eToro Registration as Virtual Asset Exchange</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bank-of-spain-etoro-registration/">Bank of Spain Approves eToro Registration as Virtual Asset Exchange</a></p>
<p>Multi-asset investment platform <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/etoro/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">eToro</a> announced on Friday, July 28, that the Bank of Spain has approved its registration as a service provider for offering virtual assets, fiat assets, and other custodial wallet services.</p>
<p>The eToro platform is an investment platform that helps people invest and learn about various assets. It&#8217;s like a community where users can share and gain knowledge to grow their wealth. On eToro, users can invest in traditional and new assets, and there are different ways to invest, like direct trading, portfolio investing, or copying other investors.</p>
<p>They also offer educational resources for beginners and experienced investors where users can practice investing without real money using a virtual portfolio. Speaking on the development, Tali Salomon, eToro’s Regional Manager for Iberia and LatAm, <a href="https://www.etoro.com/news-and-analysis/press-releases/etoro-receives-virtual-asset-registration-from-bank-of-spain/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>:</p>
<div>
<div id="ctl00_ctl00_body_mainContent_NewsActicle_pnlBody">
<blockquote><p>“This registration is a testament to our commitment to operating a growing business which prioritises consumer protection while also nurturing innovation and ensuring access for individual investors. As a multi-asset platform which has been a long standing supporter of crypto and blockchain technology, we are proud to have received this registration from the Bank of Spain. We will continue to empower our Spanish users by providing them with access to a diverse range of asset classes, investment tools and educational resources to enable them to grow their knowledge and wealth.”</p></blockquote>
</div>
</div>
<h2>eToro Plans Expansion with More Offerings</h2>
<p>Over the last year, crypto trading platform eToro decided to expand in the US market by <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/etoro-trading-app-gatsby/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">acquiring</a> the options trading platform Gatsby for a deal worth $50 million.  Moreover, acquiring Gatsby allows the firm to expand its product offerings for customers, going beyond crypto and stocks. Gatsby&#8217;s app offers commission-free options and stock trading, opening up endless investment possibilities.</p>
<p>As part of the acquisition, some of Gatsby&#8217;s top executives have also joined eToro. To support its expansion plans, eToro had already applied for regulatory approval with the SEC.</p>
<p>Earlier this month, eToro stopped offering four crypto assets &#8211; Algorand (ALGO), Decentraland (MANA), Polygon (MATIC), and Dash (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/dash/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">DASH</a>) &#8211; to its US customers. “We are constantly monitoring the changing regulatory environment in the US and how it affects the crypto assets that we offer on our platform,” it <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/etoro-delists-algo-mana-matic-dash/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">noted</a>.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/doordash-ai-chatbot/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bank-of-spain-etoro-registration/">Bank of Spain Approves eToro Registration as Virtual Asset Exchange</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bank-of-spain-etoro-registration/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>DoorDash Joins AI Frenzy with Creation of AI-driven Chatbot</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/doordash-ai-chatbot/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/doordash-ai-chatbot/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 11:57:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ai]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Amazon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chatgpt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[doordash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[microsoft]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=264961</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/doordash-ai-chatbot/">DoorDash Joins AI Frenzy with Creation of AI-driven Chatbot</a></p>
<p>DoorDash's deployment of an AI-based chatbot is just one of the recent additions and service offerings the company has introduced to enhance its food delivery platform.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/doordash-ai-chatbot/">DoorDash Joins AI Frenzy with Creation of AI-driven Chatbot</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/doordash-ai-chatbot/">DoorDash Joins AI Frenzy with Creation of AI-driven Chatbot</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/doordash/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">DoorDash Inc</a> (NYSE: DASH), a prominent food-delivery service in the United States has reportedly joined the recent Artificial Intelligence (AI) frenzy with the development of a cutting-edge system called DashAI.</p>
<p>A <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-07-27/doordash-is-working-on-an-ai-chatbot-to-speed-up-food-ordering?srnd=technology-vp#xj4y7vzkg" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a> from Bloomberg highlighted that the AI-powered chatbot is currently being tested in a restricted number of markets. Evidence of this technology was initially discovered in DoorDash’s iPhone app by developer Steve Moser, who shared the findings with Bloomberg News.</p>
<p>The introduction of DashAI aims to bring DoorDash into the AI era, offering customers personalized restaurant recommendations through simple text prompts. The core idea behind DashAI is to leverage the power of AI to enhance the customer experience and simplify the process of finding and ordering food.</p>
<p>Through AI, the chatbot can engage in natural language interactions with customers, making the experience more intuitive and user-friendly. The DashAI system includes a disclaimer stating that the technology is still in its early stages and that accuracy may vary. Its code also includes samples of how users could interact with the AI system.</p>
<p>For instance, users might be encouraged to provide specific information about their preferences, such as cuisine types, restaurants with high ratings, or desired price ranges. These details can help the chatbot understand user preferences better and offer more precise recommendations.</p>
<p>DoorDash’s entry into the AI frenzy with the creation of DashAI demonstrates the revolutionary power of AI technology in the food-delivery industry. Following the success of ChatGPT, major tech giants such as <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/apple-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Apple Inc</a> (NASDAQ: AAPL), <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/microsoft-corporation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Microsoft Corp</a> (NASDAQ: MSFT), and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/amazon/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Amazon.com Inc</a> (NASDAQ: AMZN) have intensified their efforts in advancing AI technologies.</p>
<h2>DoorDash AI: Staying Ahead in a Competitive Landscape</h2>
<p>As the food-delivery sector becomes more competitive, DoorDash acknowledges the importance of staying at the forefront of technological innovation. Competing with industry giants like <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/uber/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Uber Technologies Inc</a> (NYSE: UBER) and GrubHub requires DoorDash to continually enhance its services and provide the best possible experience for its users.</p>
<p>As the chatbot undergoes testing and refinement, its potential to reshape the way people order food and interact with delivery platforms is promising, further fueling the AI-driven transformation of the food-delivery sector.</p>
<p>This strategic move demonstrates the company’s commitment to using cutting-edge technology to maintain a competitive edge and solidify its position as a leading food-delivery service in the US.</p>
<p>Other companies in the industry, such as <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/instacart/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Instacart</a>, are also recognizing the value of AI and have begun incorporating it into their platforms.</p>
<p>DoorDash&#8217;s deployment of an AI-based chatbot is just one of the recent additions and service offerings the company has introduced to enhance its food delivery platform. One significant addition to DoorDash’s services is the ability to pay via the Supplemental Nutrition Assistance Program (SNAP) Electronic Benefits Transfer (EBT).</p>
<p>Furthermore, DoorDash’s collaboration with Edible has broadened its product offerings. This partnership enables DoorDash to provide on-demand delivery from roughly 1,000 Edible locations.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/british-museum-metaverse-sandbox/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/doordash-ai-chatbot/">DoorDash Joins AI Frenzy with Creation of AI-driven Chatbot</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/doordash-ai-chatbot/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>British Museum Enters Metaverse through Partnership with The Sandbox </title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/british-museum-metaverse-sandbox/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/british-museum-metaverse-sandbox/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 11:46:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[british museum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nft]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=264942</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/british-museum-metaverse-sandbox/">British Museum Enters Metaverse through Partnership with The Sandbox </a></p>
<p>Meanwhile, the British Museum is not the only cultural institution engaging with the crypto ecosystem.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/british-museum-metaverse-sandbox/">British Museum Enters Metaverse through Partnership with The Sandbox </a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/british-museum-metaverse-sandbox/">British Museum Enters Metaverse through Partnership with The Sandbox </a></p>
<p>The British Museum, a renowned institution steeped in culture and history, is venturing into the world of the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-metaverse/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">metaverse</a> through a partnership with The Sandbox, an Ethereum-based metaverse game. With this collaboration, the museum plans to create a collection of non-fungible tokens (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NFTs</a>) to showcase its vast diversity of artifacts housed within its walls. The digital artworks will be built in association with the museum&#8217;s licensing partner, French startup LaCollection.</p>
<p>In a  <a href="https://sandboxgame.medium.com/the-british-museum-is-bringing-history-to-the-sandbox-54003eae9fc7" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">blog post</a> dated 28 July, this range of NFT collections will offer immersive experiences, allowing players around the globe to explore the rich tapestry of the museum&#8217;s collections. Furthermore, The British cultural institute will establish its own space within The Sandbox&#8217;s online game world, placing it alongside other renowned cultural icons such as Snoop Dogg, McDonald&#8217;s, Adidas, and Gucci.</p>
<h2>Great Opportunity for The Sandbox Players</h2>
<p>Sebastien Borget, COO and co-founder of The Sandbox, expressed enthusiasm for the partnership, acknowledging the incredible opportunity it presents for players to delve into the fascinating history, art, and culture available at the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/antwerp-kmska-tokenizes-fine-arts/">museum</a>.</p>
<p>&#8220;We are very excited to collaborate with the British Museum to share its incredible collections with new audiences in the metaverse. This is a great opportunity for The Sandbox players, regardless of where they are, to learn about and enjoy the amazing collections of human history, art, and culture in the British Museum,&#8221; he said.</p>
<p>According to reports, the museum&#8217;s spokesperson said the cultural institution is keen on exploring fresh and innovative ventures to share its collections and connect with a broader audience.</p>
<p>While this marks The British Museum&#8217;s debut in the metaverse realm, the institution has proven to be no stranger to digital innovation. Before collaborating with The Sandbox, the London-based art gallery had successfully partnered with LaCollection on three NFT collections featuring works by renowned artists like Katsushika Hokusai and Joseph Mallord William Turner.</p>
<h2>British Museum and NFT Sales</h2>
<p>In 2021, the British Museum conducted its first NFT sales with 200 digital postcards showcasing the masterpieces of Katsushika Hokusai, including the iconic &#8220;Under the Wave, Off Kanagawa,&#8221; famously known as &#8220;The Great Wave.&#8221;</p>
<p>Continuing this creative endeavor, in spring 2022, the museum also presented 20 tokenized versions of captivating works by British artist Joseph Mallord William Turner, including the mesmerizing watercolor painting &#8220;A Storm (Shipwreck)&#8221; from 1823.</p>
<p>The most recent sale at the museum highlighted NFT artwork, presenting 20 pen and chalk drawings by the renowned Venetian-born draftsman, Giambattista Piranesi, sourced from The British Museum&#8217;s collection.</p>
<h2>Not the First Museum to Engage with NFTs</h2>
<p>Meanwhile, the British Museum is not the only cultural institution engaging with the crypto ecosystem. In Paris, the Pompidou Center embraced the Web3 movement with its immersive year-long exhibition titled &#8220;Policies of the Immaterial: From Certificate to Blockchain.&#8221;</p>
<p>The exhibition explores the dynamic relationship between blockchain technology and art, featuring the iconic CryptoPunk #110, generously gifted to the museum by CryptoPunks parent company Yuga Labs. Alongside this, the exhibition proudly showcases a diverse range of crypto, generative, and pixel art examples.</p>
<p>Coinspeaker <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/museum-new-york-nfts/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a> last year that the Museum of the City of New York filed a patent application for NFTs.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sequoia-crypto-ecosystem-funds/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/british-museum-metaverse-sandbox/">British Museum Enters Metaverse through Partnership with The Sandbox </a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/british-museum-metaverse-sandbox/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sequoia Capital Navigates Market Challenges with Reduction of Cryptocurrency and Ecosystem Funds</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sequoia-crypto-ecosystem-funds/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sequoia-crypto-ecosystem-funds/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Temitope Olatunji]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 11:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investors News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Startups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sequoia capital]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=264887</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sequoia-crypto-ecosystem-funds/">Sequoia Capital Navigates Market Challenges with Reduction of Cryptocurrency and Ecosystem Funds</a></p>
<p>A noteworthy aspect of Sequoia Capital's approach is the strategic shift towards supporting younger startups, diverting attention from larger companies.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sequoia-crypto-ecosystem-funds/">Sequoia Capital Navigates Market Challenges with Reduction of Cryptocurrency and Ecosystem Funds</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sequoia-crypto-ecosystem-funds/">Sequoia Capital Navigates Market Challenges with Reduction of Cryptocurrency and Ecosystem Funds</a></p>
<p>Sequoia Capital, a venture capital giant based in Silicon Valley, has recently made significant adjustments to its cryptocurrency and ecosystem funds, as detailed in a report by <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/sequoia-capital-slashes-crypto-fund-as-it-downsizes-amid-startup-crunch-f396bb0b" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">The Wall Street Journal</a>.</p>
<p>The strategic moves are a response to the prevailing challenges posed by the current market downturns, which make it more difficult for the company to raise money, and the current state of the crypto market, which causes Sequoia Capital to find it more demanding to invest in larger companies. These strategies showcase the firm&#8217;s adaptability in the ever-evolving landscape of technology investments.</p>
<p>The cryptocurrency fund under Sequoia Capital&#8217;s purview has undergone a substantial reduction, shrinking by more than 65% from its initial size of $585 million to $200 million. Similarly, the ecosystem fund has been halved in size, diminishing from $900 million to $450 million.</p>
<p>In a report by Financial Times, Sequoia expressed its rationale behind the changes, <a href="https://www.ft.com/content/4cfd2711-315e-40bd-8ea6-1b818f65e5d8" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">stating</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p><span style="text-align: center;">“We made these changes to sharpen our focus on seed-stage opportunities and to provide liquidity to our limited partners.”</span></p></blockquote>
<p>The company&#8217;s previous investment of $150 million in <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a>, a cryptocurrency exchange that experienced a collapse in November 2022,  and the subsequent technology market crash likely contributed to paper losses on its holdings of public stocks. Consequently, Sequoia Capital finds itself compelled to reassess its investment strategy and implement the necessary changes to its funds.</p>
<p>According to Wall Street Journal, Alfred Lin, a Sequoia Capital Partner, mentioned:</p>
<blockquote>
<p style="text-align: left;">“When the money got a little easier, did the marginal investments sneak in? Yes. And that’s why we’re all sort of taking pause and getting back to basics.”</p>
</blockquote>
<h2>Sequoia Capital Plans to Support More Early-Stage Startups</h2>
<p>A noteworthy aspect of Sequoia Capital&#8217;s approach is the strategic shift towards supporting younger startups, diverting attention from larger companies. This shift aligns with the current slowdown in deal-making within the startup industry, with venture firms encountering challenges in raising capital.</p>
<p>The resizing of the fund proportions will also reduce the amount of committed capital required from investors, granting the firm increased flexibility to navigate the ever-changing investment landscape.</p>
<p>While the full implications of these strategic changes are yet to unfold, they reflect a prudent and adaptive move by Sequoia Capital to restructure its investment approach and mitigate potential risks. As the startup and cryptocurrency markets continue to evolve, the company&#8217;s emphasis on supporting younger companies positions it well to leverage emerging opportunities in the future.</p>
<p>As of now, Sequoia Capital has not issued an official statement regarding the reported downsizing of its funds. Nevertheless, the alleged approach showcases a cautious and thoughtful stance as it navigates the dynamic landscapes of the tech and cryptocurrency industries.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/phoenix-technology-ipo-abu-dhabi/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sequoia-crypto-ecosystem-funds/">Sequoia Capital Navigates Market Challenges with Reduction of Cryptocurrency and Ecosystem Funds</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sequoia-crypto-ecosystem-funds/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>UAE’s Crypto Mining Giant Phoenix Technology Considers Floating IPO in Abu Dhabi</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/phoenix-technology-ipo-abu-dhabi/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/phoenix-technology-ipo-abu-dhabi/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 11:36:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[IPO News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brian armstrong]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[phoenix technology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=264879</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/phoenix-technology-ipo-abu-dhabi/">UAE’s Crypto Mining Giant Phoenix Technology Considers Floating IPO in Abu Dhabi</a></p>
<p>The prospective Phoenix Technology IPO is expected sometime this year in Abu Dhabi. However, there are no further details on size and price.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/phoenix-technology-ipo-abu-dhabi/">UAE’s Crypto Mining Giant Phoenix Technology Considers Floating IPO in Abu Dhabi</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/phoenix-technology-ipo-abu-dhabi/">UAE’s Crypto Mining Giant Phoenix Technology Considers Floating IPO in Abu Dhabi</a></p>
<p>Crypto mining equipment retailer Phoenix Technology is considering an initial public offering (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-initial-public-offering-ipo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">IPO</a>) according to reports. On Friday, Bloomberg <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-07-28/crypto-hardware-retailer-phoenix-said-in-early-talks-for-uae-ipo#xj4y7vzkg" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reported</a> that the company is already in preliminary discussions, citing people familiar with the matter.</p>
<p>The report states that the United Arab Emirates-based firm is considering an IPO in Abu Dhabi. While conversations are ongoing, the suggested timeline for the Phoenix Technology IPO is sometime this year. However, all details, including the proposed timeline, are tentative.</p>
<p>Phoenix Technology was established in 2015 and is a part of the Phoenix Group. The company is considered one of the largest in the crypto and blockchain sector, with mining facilities capable of more than 700 megawatts (MW) across the Middle East, Canada, Europe, and the USA. Currently, Phoenix Technology is building one of the Middle East’s largest mining facilities.</p>
<h2>Phoenix Technology IPO to Boost UAE’s Position as Leading Mining Hub</h2>
<p>The United Arab Emirates has a crypto and Web3-friendly environment, which is attractive to stakeholders in the industry. The country is now focusing more on renewable energy than traditional fossil fuels, a move that would likely benefit its mining ecosystem. This transition could create excess energy that crypto miners like Phoenix Technology can use to ensure their activities, while energy-intensive, are green.</p>
<p>Earlier this month, Luxor business development associate and crypto mining expert Jaran Mellerud <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uae-leading-bitcoin-mining-hub/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">highlighted</a> the country’s mining industry in a Twitter <a href="https://twitter.com/JMellerud/status/1676652814401937447?t=fD6gI66UYksw9XEuT_TPdA&amp;s=19" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">thread</a>. Mellerud discussed a partnership between blockchain infrastructure company and Abu Dhabi sovereign wealth fund subsidiary Zero Two, and US-based crypto mining giant Marathon Digital. The partnership between both companies will see the launch of two mining facilities in Abu Dhabi with 250MW in combined capacity. Interestingly, Zero Two partnered with Phoenix Technology back in 2021.</p>
<p>Mellerud also talked about a nuclear power plant the UAE recently launched, the largest in the Arab world. The plant has a capacity of 4 gigawatts (GW) with three commissioned reactors, generating about 19% of the UAE’s electricity. The plant’s capacity is expected to hit 5.4 GW when a fourth reactor goes live sometime this year. Crypto mining in the country is likely to benefit from the surplus energy that the country generates via renewable sources.</p>
<h2>UAE Mining Regulation</h2>
<p>Authorities in the UAE have been more open to mining activities than governments in other countries like China. The UAE allows miners to use its zero tax policy, as these companies can register in of the many free trade zones in the country. This way, they get to sidestep obligations such as import duties, value-added tax (VAT), and corporate tax.</p>
<p>Some of the biggest names in crypto are also paying close attention to the UAE and engaging its ecosystem. For instance, Chanpeng Zhao and He Yi, both Binance co-founders, now live in Dubai. In addition, Coinbase CEO <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/brian-armstrong/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Brian Armstrong</a> has also set eyes on the city and met with authorities.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-users-retention-threads/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/phoenix-technology-ipo-abu-dhabi/">UAE’s Crypto Mining Giant Phoenix Technology Considers Floating IPO in Abu Dhabi</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/phoenix-technology-ipo-abu-dhabi/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Meta Platforms Seeks Users Retention on Threads</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-users-retention-threads/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-users-retention-threads/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 11:05:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mark zuckerberg]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Meta]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[threads]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[twitter]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[x]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=264912</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-users-retention-threads/">Meta Platforms Seeks Users Retention on Threads</a></p>
<p>To continue serving its sign-ups and entice users to return to Threads, Meta wants to add more “retention-driving hooks”.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-users-retention-threads/">Meta Platforms Seeks Users Retention on Threads</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-users-retention-threads/">Meta Platforms Seeks Users Retention on Threads</a></p>
<p>Following its buzzy launch and recording over 100 million users within a week of rolling out Threads, the executives of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/meta/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Meta Platforms</a> (NASDAQ: META) are now working on boosting retention on the new app. The management of the multinational technology company is heavily focusing on keeping Threads user base after it lost over 50% of its users. The matter was revealed by CEO <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/mark-zuckerberg/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Mark Zuckerberg</a>, who on Thursday said at an internal company town hall that the retention of users on the new Twitter rival was better than executives&#8217; expectations. However, the Meta Platforms’ CEO noted that user retention on Threads is “not perfect”.</p>
<h2>Meta Plans Retention Hooks for Threads Users</h2>
<p>In his speech, he explained that it is still “awesome” if all 100 million sign-ups or even half remain on the app. “We’re not there yet,” he added. Zuckerberg sees departing users as a “normal” occurrence, with the hope to accommodate and house more users as time goes on. The CEO expects user retention on Threads to improve as Meta adds more exciting features to the app. Some of the expected additions include a desktop version and search functionality.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, these features are available on Twitter, which Threads appears to be in competition with. Since Twitter, now X, was launched in 2006, the social media networking service has onboarded hundreds of millions of users. The social media app still boasts millions of monthly active users despite the recent changes that caused the departure of many. As much as social media users seek alternatives to Twitter amid <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/elon-musk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Elon Musk</a>’s restructuring, Threads still has quite some upgrades to do to meet up with the X app.</p>
<p>To continue serving its sign-ups and entice users to return to Threads, Meta wants to add more “retention-driving hooks”. According to chief product officer Chris Cox, the technology firm wants to ensure that users of the Instagram apps can also see important Threads. The efforts of Meta on sustaining Threads users came shortly after Meta posted a bullish revenue growth forecast. The company sees strong engagement across its app, adding that costs will rise in 2023 and 2024.</p>
<h2>Meta&#8217;s Metaverse Push</h2>
<p>Speaking further at the internal company town hall, Zuckerberg also talked to employees about the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-q2-2023-reality-labs-loses/">metaverse push</a>. He said Meta&#8217;s efforts on augmented and virtual reality technology that would power the metaverse were not “massively ahead of schedule, but on track”.</p>
<p>Eric Wittman of VSCO, a social media app that gained brief momentum in 2019, has issued some advice to Meta on its Threads app. Wittman said Meta could make the new app the “purest form” of social media by running the business as a loss leader. Directing his suggestion to Zuckerberg, he asked that the Twitter-like could simply be generating “goodwill” instead of revenue.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/eco-wallet-beam-backed-a16z/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-users-retention-threads/">Meta Platforms Seeks Users Retention on Threads</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-users-retention-threads/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Eco Launches Cash-Like Crypto Wallet Beam Backed by a16z and Coinbase</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/eco-wallet-beam-backed-a16z/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/eco-wallet-beam-backed-a16z/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 10:51:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[a16z]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[beam]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eco]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=264882</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/eco-wallet-beam-backed-a16z/">Eco Launches Cash-Like Crypto Wallet Beam Backed by a16z and Coinbase</a></p>
<p>The Beam wallet has been designed atop Ethereum Layer-2 blockchains such as Coinbase's Base and Optimism for facilitating faster crypto transactions at low cost. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/eco-wallet-beam-backed-a16z/">Eco Launches Cash-Like Crypto Wallet Beam Backed by a16z and Coinbase</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/eco-wallet-beam-backed-a16z/">Eco Launches Cash-Like Crypto Wallet Beam Backed by a16z and Coinbase</a></p>
<p>Money and payments platform Eco announced the launch of its cash-like crypto wallet Beam backed by some of the biggest players and notable digital asset investors. This includes names such as venture capital giant Andreessen Horowitz (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/a16z/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">a16z</a>) and the investment arm of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase</a> (COIN).</p>
<p>Fintech firm Eco developed the Beam wallet, powered by account abstraction and built atop Optimism and Base. The Beam crypto wallet has a simple UX thereby making crypto payments easier than ever before. It also brings the promises of Web3 such that its permissionless, offers self-custody, and is censorship resistant. It is one of the first self-custody wallets available for use by anyone and everyone.</p>
<p>Beam is different from other crypto wallets available in the market as of date. Many crypto wallets are difficult to use and confusing for regular people. They are designed for professionals and enthusiasts, not for everyday users. But Beam wants to change that. They want to create a crypto payment product that is easy and enjoyable for everyone to use, while still keeping the important features of cryptocurrencies like being secure, private, and not controlled by a central authority.</p>
<p>Users of Beam can quickly pay family and friends by sending them the Beam link or sending money directly to their username. Beam is a crypto wallet that offers low fees and simple pricing on low-fee blockchains. It ensures security and ease of use, so you don&#8217;t have to worry about scams or losing access to your account. You can recover your wallet easily with a login and password. Beam is designed specifically for payments and is the first of its kind for mainstream users.</p>
<h2>Beam &#8211; Built on Ethereum Layer-2 Blockchains</h2>
<p>The Beam wallet is built on two blockchains called Optimism and Coinbase&#8217;s Base. These blockchains make it easier and faster to send and receive crypto with lower fees. The wallet is also designed to help users recover their crypto if they lose their private keys.</p>
<p>This simplification of the process could lead to more people using crypto in their everyday lives. Other developers are also working on ways to make crypto more accessible, like enabling payments on messaging apps.</p>
<p>Beam has <a href="https://echo.mirror.xyz/FbaqedtGg7SZuwOXesLnO8-Gk-Nzpna5ZvLZiw2TIFs" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">partnered</a> with Stackup to facilitate paymaster transactions. Paymaster transactions enable users to pay gas fees denominated in the currencies they are already sending. Beam also makes those transaction fees fixed, providing an intuitive and predictable pattern for users coming from traditional fintech products.</p>
<p>The Beam design facilitates a limited and specific set of actions users can do with their smart contract wallet. For this limitation, Beam has a whitelist of sponsored smart contract interactions provided by Stackup, the paymaster.</p>
<p>Whitelisting transactions sets boundaries on the types of smart contracts users can interact with, making it much harder for potential theft to occur. It also allows to submit transactions without bytecode approvals, making the interactions similar to that offered by Web2 products.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-crypto-companies-job-market/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/eco-wallet-beam-backed-a16z/">Eco Launches Cash-Like Crypto Wallet Beam Backed by a16z and Coinbase</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/eco-wallet-beam-backed-a16z/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>UK Crypto Companies Recruiting despite Sharp Decline in Job Market</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-crypto-companies-job-market/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-crypto-companies-job-market/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Darya Rudz]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 10:41:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gemini uk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ripple uk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[robinhood uk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[uk crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[uk crypto jobs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[uk employment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[uk jobs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=264841</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-crypto-companies-job-market/">UK Crypto Companies Recruiting despite Sharp Decline in Job Market</a></p>
<p>As per the UK Office for National Statistics, the UK unemployment rate was estimated at 4.0% for the second quarter of this year, which is 0.2% higher than the previous quarter.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-crypto-companies-job-market/">UK Crypto Companies Recruiting despite Sharp Decline in Job Market</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-crypto-companies-job-market/">UK Crypto Companies Recruiting despite Sharp Decline in Job Market</a></p>
<p>The job market in the UK is suffering a sharp decline. The experts believe the crisis has been caused not only by the general economic recession but also by a shortage of talent on the market. According to the report by the Broadbean Technology firm, a fall in the number of open positions is accompanied by a 30% decline in the number of applicants. The shortage of staff is extremely sharp in engineering, science, architecture, hospitality and catering, as well as health services.</p>
<p>Alex Fourlis, Managing Director at Broadbean Technology, <a href="https://www.thelondoneconomic.com/jobs/uk-talent-crisis-worsens-as-job-applications-fall-in-skill-short-industries-353211/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">explained</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Although the market is slowing down, the skills crisis is far from over. The UK simply doesn’t have enough of the highly trained and highly skilled professionals it needs to fill the demand. It’s imperative that employers stay focused on the skills agenda and continue to invest in talent attraction and development if they are to grow their competitive standing.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>He further added:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The lack of candidates isn’t going to be solved overnight and is already a big issue for firms. Those that can get in front of the right people quickly, and via the right channels, will be the ones in a prime position to win the war for talent.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>As per the UK Office for National Statistics, the UK unemployment rate was estimated at 4.0% for the second quarter of this year, which is 0.2% higher than the previous quarter. Reed Recruitment has <a href="https://www.reed.co.uk/recruiter-advice/job-market-review-may-2023/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reported</a> a 24.40% fall in the number of advertised positions over the past three months in comparison to the previous year. Notably, the number of available jobs is below the pre-pandemic era.</p>
<h2>UK Crypto Companies Posting New Job Offers</h2>
<p>Meanwhile, crypto companies located in the UK are publishing new job offers and actively <a href="https://beincrypto.com/uk-jobs-drop-crypto-companies-hiring/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">looking for employees</a>.</p>
<p>For example, the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/gemini/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Gemini</a> exchange is looking for a Compliance Associate at its UK office. <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase Inc</a> (NASDAQ: COIN) is hiring the Head of Mobile Business Development and International Policy Manager.</p>
<p>Further, Ripple is seeking Employment and Litigation Counsel to provide strategic legal advice and counseling globally on a broad range of employment law matters. The company is also in need of an Executive Assistant based in London. Recently, it won a court ruling in the US against the Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>).</p>
<p>Following the victory, the company applied for registration as a crypto asset firm with the UK’s Financial Conduct Authority and for a payment institution license in Ireland. Now, Ripple is definitely planning to expand its footprint in the UK. Over the past 18 months, Ripple has increased its UK and European employees count by about 75%, with over 100 of its approximately 900 global employees based in its offices in London, Dublin, and Reykjavik, Iceland.</p>
<p>Crypto trading company <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/robinhood/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Robinhood Markets Inc</a> (NASDAQ: HOOD) is also moving forward with plans to launch in the United Kingdom. As we have <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/robinhood-uk-branch-us-regulatory/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a>, the company has appointed former Barclays director Jordan Sinclair as its UK arm&#8217;s CEO. Among the jobs posted by Robinhood on LinkedIn are a senior risk and compliance associate, a compliance officer, and an operations lead, all based in London.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-corpay-netting-manager/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-crypto-companies-job-market/">UK Crypto Companies Recruiting despite Sharp Decline in Job Market</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-crypto-companies-job-market/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4149 metric#misses=41 metric#hit-ratio=99.0 metric#bytes=1072254 metric#prefetches=205 metric#store-reads=19 metric#store-writes=2 metric#store-hits=211 metric#store-misses=2 metric#sql-queries=34 metric#ms-total=96.94 metric#ms-cache=4.61 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.2303 metric#ms-cache-ratio=4.8 -->