<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 20:49:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Galaxy Digital CEO: ‘I’m more comfortable being long Bitcoin today’</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/galaxy-digital-ceo-shares-view-on-bitcoin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wajeeh Khan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 20:49:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Interview]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=147030</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Michael Novogratz puts Bitcoin and Gold in the same bucket. Wolfe Research strategist reiterated his bullish view on BTC. Bitcoin is currently up 80% versus the start of the year 2023. Owning Bitcoin today is nowhere as scary as it was about six months ago, says Michael Novogratz &#8211; the Chief Executive of Galaxy Digital. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/galaxy-digital-ceo-shares-view-on-bitcoin/">Galaxy Digital CEO: ‘I’m more comfortable being long Bitcoin today’</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Michael Novogratz puts Bitcoin and Gold in the same bucket.</li>
<li>Wolfe Research strategist reiterated his bullish view on BTC.</li>
<li>Bitcoin is currently up 80% versus the start of the year 2023.</li>
</ul>
<p>Owning <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> today is nowhere as scary as it was about six months ago, says Michael Novogratz &ndash; the Chief Executive of Galaxy Digital.</p>
<h2>Novogratz shares his view on Bitcoin</h2>
<p>Interest rates continued to go up this year; FTX collapsed; the U.S. Securities &amp; Exchange Commission came down hard on <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-sec-strikes-again-first-binance-now-coinbase/">bellwethers</a> of the crypto space.</p>
<p>And yet, Bitcoin has outperformed every other financial asset &ndash; now up 80% year-to-date.</p>
<p>What that establishes beyond doubt, as per Novogratz, is that the world&rsquo;s largest cryptocurrency is here to stay. On CNBC&rsquo;s &ldquo;<a href="https://www.cnbc.com/video/2023/07/20/im-more-comfortable-being-along-bitcoin-today-than-i-was-6-months-ago-galaxy-digital-ceo-novogratz.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Squawk Box</a>&rdquo;, he said:</p>
<blockquote><p>The normalization of 5.0% budget deficit &hellip; is why Bitcoin, gold, silver trade great. I put them all in the same bucket. Bitcoin has got the additional adoption cycle.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Novogratz sees Bitcoin as digital gold</h2>
<p>Novogratz drives his optimism also from <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-07-03/blackrock-s-bitcoin-etf-application-is-refiled-by-nasdaq-to-sec" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BlackRock Inc</a> that has recently filed with the regulator for a Spot Bitcoin ETF which could boost institutional interest in the digital asset.</p>
<blockquote><p>I&rsquo;m more comfortable being long Bitcoin today than I was six months ago. I like to think of BTC as digital gold to store value.</p></blockquote>
<p>Meanwhile, <a href="https://www.ft.com/content/1d1de06a-a904-4db3-9017-4c061bd6854d" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Jacobi Asset Management</a> is all set to debut its Bitcoin-focused exchange-traded fund in Europe by the end of this year.</p>
<p>Also on Thursday, Wolfe Research strategist Rob Ginsberg reiterated his bullish view on BTC. He agreed, though, that the cryptocurrency has to fight an uphill battle to reclaim its former highs.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/galaxy-digital-ceo-shares-view-on-bitcoin/">Galaxy Digital CEO: ‘I’m more comfortable being long Bitcoin today’</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Federal Reserve launches &#8216;FedNow&#8217; instant payment system</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/federal-reserve-launches-fednow-instant-payment-system/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 17:35:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US Federal Reserve]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/federal-reserve-launches-fednow-instant-payment-system/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The newly launched FedNow Service aims to empower banks and credit unions. FedNow will allow for the execution of transactions 24/7 365 days a year. 35 banks and credit unions, including the U Bureau of the Fiscal Service of the US Department of the Treasury, are already equipped to handle payments through the FedNow Service. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/federal-reserve-launches-fednow-instant-payment-system/">Federal Reserve launches &#8216;FedNow&#8217; instant payment system</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>The newly launched FedNow Service aims to empower banks and credit unions.</li>
<li>FedNow will allow for the execution of transactions 24/7 365 days a year.</li>
<li>35 banks and credit unions, including the U Bureau of the Fiscal Service of the US Department of the Treasury, are already equipped to handle payments through the FedNow Service.</li>
</ul>
<p>The FedNow&reg; Service, the Federal Reserve&rsquo;s instant payment platform, <a href="https://www.federalreserve.gov/newsevents/pressreleases/other20230720a.htm?utm_source=dlvr.it&amp;utm_medium=twitter">went live</a> officially on Thursday morning. The service will allow banks and credit unions of all sizes instantly process the transactions of their clients.</p>
<p>The Federal Reserve asserts that FedNow transactions can be carried out every day of the year, around the clock.</p>
<p>To begin with, 35 banks and credit unions and the Bureau of the Fiscal Service of the US Department of the Treasury are among those who are already prepared to handle payments through the FedNow Service. Furthermore, a group of 16 service providers is prepared to support banks and credit unions with payment processing.</p>
<h2>Prudent payments for individuals and companies via FedNow</h2>
<p>Explaining the benefits of the instant payment system, Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell said:</p>
<p><em>&ldquo;The Federal Reserve built the FedNow Service to help make everyday payments over the coming years faster and more convenient. Over time, as more banks choose to use this new tool, the benefits to individuals and businesses will include enabling a person to immediately receive a paycheck, or a company to instantly access funds when an invoice is paid.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p>Jerome Powell, however, clarified that the newly launched system is not attempting to replace fiat money. He said that FedNow is &ldquo;not related to a digital currency.&rdquo; He added that &ldquo;it is like other Federal Reserve payment services, such as Fedwire and FedACH. The FedNow Service is neither a form of currency nor a step toward eliminating any form of payment, including cash.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/federal-reserve-launches-fednow-instant-payment-system/">Federal Reserve launches &#8216;FedNow&#8217; instant payment system</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Labs invests $10 million in DeFi project Radiant</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-labs-announces-10m-in-defi-lender-radiant/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 16:35:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-labs-announces-10m-in-defi-lender-radiant/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Binance Labs&#8217; strategic investment in Radiant Capital will help the DeFi protocol expands its product to more EVM chains. The price of Radiant&#8217;s native token RDNT rose 10% following the news. Binance Labs, the venture capital arm of world&#8217;s leading crypto exchange Binance, has invested $10 million in decentralised crypto lender Radiant Capital (RDNT). Radiant&#8217;s [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-labs-announces-10m-in-defi-lender-radiant/">Binance Labs invests $10 million in DeFi project Radiant</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Binance Labs&rsquo; strategic investment in Radiant Capital will help the DeFi protocol expands its product to more EVM chains.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The price of Radiant&rsquo;s native token RDNT rose 10% following the news.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Binance Labs, the venture capital arm of world&rsquo;s leading crypto exchange <a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/binance/"><u>Binance</u></a>, has invested $10 million in decentralised crypto lender Radiant Capital (RDNT).</p>
<p dir="ltr">Radiant&rsquo;s lending and borrowing protocol is built on top of LayerZero, one of Binance Labs&rsquo; portfolio companies.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Radiant to use funds to expand its DeFi product</h2>
<p dir="ltr">According to an&nbsp;<a href="https://www.binance.com/en/blog/ecosystem/binance-labs-invests-%2410-million-in-radiant-to-support--its-mission-to-lead-the-next-era-of-defi-lending-1438479277678345894" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>announcement</u></a> from Binance, the strategic funding round continues Binance Labs&rsquo; commitment towards crypto innovation, including in supporting next-generation chain-agnostic DeFi projects.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Radiant brings this goal to the market by taking on the fragmented liquidity that beleaguers the DeFi ecosystem. The platform promotes this by allowing users to tap into a bridging innovation to borrow and lend across any chain.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>Binance Labs actively seeks out promising DeFi projects that not only advance the industry but also push the boundaries of innovation. Radiant Capital&rsquo;s commitment to facilitating seamless cross-chain transactions for DeFi, and performance on Arbitrum and BNB Chain demonstrates its potential for driving mass adoption</em>,&rdquo; Binance co-founder and head of Binance Labs Yi He said.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As CoinJournal&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-report-shows-crypto-industry-in-good-health-in-h1-2023/"><u>reported</u></a> today, Binance has released a mid-year report for the crypto industry in which the exchange highlights growth in the past six months. One of the areas to see significant growth is DeFi.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Radiant team says the funding comes at a crucial time as the platform looks to expand its product to more EVM chains. This will add to the traction seen on Arbitrum and BNB Chain, with the protocol looking to become of the&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/compare/best-defi-projects/"><u>best DeFi platforms</u></a> in the world.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Growth is expected to include expansion of oracle support, collateral, cross liquidations and abstract repayments. Also crucial in the product development is deployment on Ethereum mainnet and full integration with LayerZero&rsquo;s messaging support.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Radiant believes the developments will see the next 100 million users come into and benefit from DeFi. Commenting on this milestone, Radiant Capital founder George Macallan said that the partnership with Binance Labs allows his platform to benefit from Binance&rsquo;s &ldquo;extensive expertise, resources, and strategic support.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>Their investment will play a crucial role in propelling Radiant to new heights as the protocol expands to new chains, continues to scale, and drives utility back into the ecosystem</em>,&rdquo; he added.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Radiant&rsquo;s native token RDNT reacted positively to the news, with its value jumping 10% to near $0.32.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-labs-announces-10m-in-defi-lender-radiant/">Binance Labs invests $10 million in DeFi project Radiant</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kuwait bans all crypto activities including mining</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/kuwait-bans-all-crypto-activities-including-mining/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/kuwait-bans-all-crypto-activities-including-mining/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 15:05:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto adoption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto payments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency mining]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/kuwait-bans-all-crypto-activities-including-mining/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>After the July 19 circular, it is illegal to engage in any cryptocurrency activities in Kuwait. Kuwait has joined Thailand, Indonesia, and Turkey to ban crypto activities. Violators are to face penalties as stipulated in Kuwait&#8217;s AML and terrorist financing laws. Kuwait&#8217;s financial watchdog, the Central Markets Authority (CMA), issued a circular on July 19 [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/kuwait-bans-all-crypto-activities-including-mining/">Kuwait bans all crypto activities including mining</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>After the July 19 circular, it is illegal to engage in any cryptocurrency activities in Kuwait.</li>
<li>Kuwait has joined Thailand, Indonesia, and Turkey to ban crypto activities.</li>
<li>Violators are to face penalties as stipulated in Kuwait&rsquo;s AML and terrorist financing laws.</li>
</ul>
<p>Kuwait&rsquo;s financial watchdog, the Central Markets Authority (CMA), issued a circular on July 19 declaring that all cryptocurrency activities including <a href="https://coinjournal.net/cryptocurrencies/invest/">crypto investment</a>, crypto payments, and crypto mining as described <a href="https://coinjournal.net/cryptocurrencies/mine/">here</a> were illegal in the Middle Eastern country.</p>
<p>The CMA also banned local regulators from granting licences to anyone attempting to &ldquo;provide cryptocurrency services as a commercial business.&rdquo;</p>
<h2>Tough penalties for violators</h2>
<p>The nation&rsquo;s anti-money laundering and terrorist financing laws carry harsh punishments, the financial regulator warned. The circular made it clear that &ldquo;securities regulated by the Central Bank of Kuwait and other securities and financial instruments regulated by the Capital Markets Authority&rdquo; are exempt from the prohibitions.</p>
<p>In addition to forbidding cryptocurrency-related activities within the nation, the Kuwaiti regulator informed clients of the dangers posed by cryptocurrencies. &ldquo;They do not carry a legal status and are not issued or supported,&rdquo; it declared.</p>
<p>Kuwait has joined the list of nations like Thailand, Indonesia, and Turkey that forbid accepting cryptocurrency payments.</p>
<p>Kuwait&rsquo;s move to ban cryptocurrencies comes after the National Committee for Combating Money Laundering and the Financing of Terrorism concluded its study that aimed at implementing Recommendation 15 of the International Requirements of the Financial Action Task Force (FATF). However, it is essential to note that the FATF does not mandate that nations outlaw cryptocurrency.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/kuwait-bans-all-crypto-activities-including-mining/">Kuwait bans all crypto activities including mining</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/kuwait-bans-all-crypto-activities-including-mining/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>UK&#8217;s FCA launches a permanent digital sandbox</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/uks-fca-launches-a-permanent-digital-sandbox/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/uks-fca-launches-a-permanent-digital-sandbox/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 14:11:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[UK]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/uks-fca-launches-a-permanent-digital-sandbox/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways FCA&#8217;s digital sandbox is set to launch on August 1st. The sandbox will serve as a testing environment for firms before rolling out their products. UK&#8217;s financial regulator launches a digital sandbox The U.K. Financial Conduct Authority (FCA) announced on Thursday, July 20th, that it will launch a digital sandbox. The regulator said [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/uks-fca-launches-a-permanent-digital-sandbox/">UK&#8217;s FCA launches a permanent digital sandbox</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">FCA&rsquo;s digital sandbox is set to launch on August 1st.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The sandbox will serve as a testing environment for firms before rolling out their products.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr">UK&rsquo;s financial regulator launches a digital sandbox</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The U.K. Financial Conduct Authority (FCA) <a href="https://www.fca.org.uk/news/news-stories/launch-permanent-digital-sandbox" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">announced</a> on Thursday, July 20th, that it will launch a digital sandbox.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The regulator said the permanent digital sandbox will be made available on August 1st, 2023, opening up the platform to an even broader range of innovative businesses, start-ups and data providers.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The platform will serve as a testing environment for firms to see how their products would perform at an early stage of development.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">This&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/"><u>latest cryptocurrency news</u></a> comes nearly three years after the regulator launched the sandbox on a trial basis. The FCA said the sandbox would also be available to data providers and would offer firms access to data sets, application program interfaces (API) and data security protection.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The FCA said;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;Until now, the platform has only been available temporarily to those participating in pilots and TechSprints.</em></p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>The Digital Sandbox works to foster innovation and growth &ndash; more than half of the previous Small to Medium Enterprise participants in the pilots and TechSprints made positive developments, including launching new products, securing funding and partnerships, or receiving industry awards or recognitions.&rdquo;</em></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">The digital sandbox provides data security protection</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The regulatory agency pointed out that its digital sandbox has numerous features that would benefit developers. The sandbox&rsquo;s integrated development environment allows experimentation while safeguarding the data assets on the platform.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Furthermore, developers would have access to over 200 synthetic, public or anonymised data sets and over 1000 APIs to enable testing and validation of technology solutions.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The observation deck feature allows interested parties such as regulators, incumbents and others&#8239;to observe in-flight testing at a technical level.&#8239;Finally, the FCA believes that the sandbox could promote diversity of thought, share learnings and foster an ecosystem between teams, observers and mentors.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Former Economic Secretary John Glen rolled out the plans for the sandbox in 2022 with the aim of making the UK a cryptocurrency innovation hub. Previously, the sandbox was available only during pilots and TechSprints, which brought people from the financial industry together to address industry challenges.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/uks-fca-launches-a-permanent-digital-sandbox/">UK&#8217;s FCA launches a permanent digital sandbox</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/uks-fca-launches-a-permanent-digital-sandbox/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance report shows crypto industry in &#8220;good health&#8221; in H1, 2023</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-report-shows-crypto-industry-in-good-health-in-h1-2023/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 14:04:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto adoption]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-report-shows-crypto-industry-in-good-health-in-h1-2023/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeways The crypto industry experienced growth across Bitcoin and other L1s, L2s, stablecoins, DeFi, and NFTs. Bitcoin network growth included trading volume, transaction count, fees and hashrate. Solana, BNB Chain led L1s, while Liquid staking emerged as a key DeFi component. Binance has released a report covering the first half of 2023, with details [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-report-shows-crypto-industry-in-good-health-in-h1-2023/">Binance report shows crypto industry in &#8220;good health&#8221; in H1, 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">The crypto industry experienced growth across Bitcoin and other L1s, L2s, stablecoins, DeFi, and NFTs.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Bitcoin network growth included trading volume, transaction count, fees and hashrate.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Solana, BNB Chain led L1s, while Liquid staking emerged as a key DeFi component.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/binance/">Binance</a> has released a report covering the first half of 2023, with details suggesting that the overall global crypto industry showed remarkable resilience following the crypto winter.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Crypto growth in H1, 2023</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Published on July 20, the<a href="https://research.binance.com/en/analysis/half-year-2023" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">&nbsp;<u>120-page report</u></a> highlights growth metrics across key industry verticals, including <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a>, stablecoins, DeFi, and NFTs. The H1, 2023 report also details developments within the gaming and metaverse, as well as institutional adoption and funding.</p>
<p dir="ltr">For instance, DeFi has seen a 43% year-to-date increase, while NFT volume &ndash; despite diminishing floor prices, rose compared to the second half of 2022. &nbsp;In fundraising, the report highlights that the top 10 funds raised $3.6 billion.</p>
<p dir="ltr">USDT, the leading stablecoin by market cap increased its market share by 26% even as the global stablecoin market dipped 7%. USDD, crvUSD, GHO and LUSD all saw significant increases. The report also details key pilot cases for CBDCs and tokenization.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Also trending in H1 and today is the liquid staking and LSDfi, with the new subsector of LSDfi experiencing a 460% jump in total value locked between April and end of June.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitcoin&rsquo;s continued network growth</h2>
<p dir="ltr">According to Binance, the state of crypto in terms of adoption, usage, and innovation as observed in the first six months of the year portends an even better half of the year and into 2024.</p>
<p dir="ltr">One of the indicators of a better H1 for crypto in 2023 is Bitcoin&rsquo;s network growth. Binance says this was evident through metrics such as the 185% year-to-date jump in trading volume and 58% spike in transactions count. Also significant during the period was the 143% increase in average transaction fees, 40% YTD hashrate increase and 43% jump in mining difficulty.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As CoinJournal recently reported, Bitcoin&rsquo;s network growth was partially fueled by the surge in Ordinals. [Read more<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-and-ethereum-network-revenues-spiked-in-may-despite-significant-headwinds-etc-group-report/">&nbsp;<u>here</u></a> and<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/why-are-bitcoin-transaction-fees-rising-and-what-are-brc-20-tokens/">&nbsp;<u>here</u></a>].</p>
<p dir="ltr">In terms of market performance, Bitcoin dominance peaked to levels last seen in April 2021. Meanwhile, the flagship cryptocurrency&rsquo;s correlation with TradFi fell to a three-year low.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Solana, BNB and other Layer-1s</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Growth was also witnessed across leading layer-1 chains, with Solana outpacing other L1s in relation to the increase of its market capitalization. Binance&rsquo;s BNB Chain topped others in terms of best network performance YTD overall, with daily transactions increasing 113% compared to 48% for Ethereum. BNB Chain active addresses increased by 118%, compared to Ethereum&rsquo;s 63%.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Also notable during the first six months of 2023 was the growth of subnets on Avalanche and shared security models by Cosmos.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The last few weeks have seen a bullish flip in crypto sentiment, particularly with the filing of a spot Bitcoin ETF by $9 trillion asset manager BlackRock. Ripple&rsquo;s landmark win against the SEC last week is also a key factor driving market confidence today. &nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Binance notes the &ldquo;Bitcoin ETF season&rdquo; could continue to bolster momentum even as the second half of the year sees greater adoption and innovation</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-report-shows-crypto-industry-in-good-health-in-h1-2023/">Binance report shows crypto industry in &#8220;good health&#8221; in H1, 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>3 reasons why Chainlink (LINK) price just surged</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/3-reasons-why-chainlink-link-price-just-surged/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/3-reasons-why-chainlink-link-price-just-surged/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 12:15:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chainlink News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/3-reasons-why-chainlink-link-price-just-surged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Chainlink crypto price surged to the highest level since April. Whales have started accumulating the coin after the CCIP launch. Open interest in the futures market has jumped to 2021 highs. Chainlink price went parabolic on Thursday as investors cheered the recent product news and purchases by whales. LINK token soared to a high of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/3-reasons-why-chainlink-link-price-just-surged/">3 reasons why Chainlink (LINK) price just surged</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Chainlink crypto price surged to the highest level since April.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Whales have started accumulating the coin after the CCIP launch.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Open interest in the futures market has jumped to 2021 highs.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/chainlink"><u>Chainlink</u></a> price went parabolic on Thursday as investors cheered the recent product news and purchases by whales. LINK token soared to a high of $8.20, the highest level since April 20th this year. It has jumped by more than 65% from the lowest level in June.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">LINK whales are buying</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Chainlink price is surging for two main reasons. First, the developers unveiled plans to introduce a new Cross-Chain Interoperable Protocol (CCIP), as I wrote&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chainlink-price-prediction-link-just-formed-a-double-top-pattern/"><u>here</u></a>. This is an important upgrade in the network that seeks to join traditional finance companies to the blockchain.</p>
<p dir="ltr">CCIP will expand Chainlink&rsquo;s use case by making it possible for companies like banks and insurance firms to join the blockchain. The announcement came a &nbsp;month after Chainlink announced that it was running a trial of linking banks to the blockchain through its partnership with Swift.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Second, there are signs that whales have started buying the coin. Data shows that two whales acquired 788,877 LINK tokens this week. They bought these tokens by swapping their stETH and ETH tokens for LINK. Historically, accumulation by whales is usually one of the best buy signals in the market.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Chainlink open interest is rising</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Meanwhile, data by Coinglass shows that open interest in the futures market jumped to the highest level since November. Open interest is an important metric in the futures market that denotes the number of futures contracts held by market participants. A higher figure is usually a bullish sign.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Chainlink&rsquo;s open interest has jumped to more than $267 million, with most of them being from Binance. The other leading exchanges are Bybit, OKX, and Bitget among others.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/20/1689855283220-7690d498-5afc-4ff5-94f5-7701daa06184.jpg" style="width: 578px;height: 175.327px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="578" height="175.327"></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy Chainlink</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>

    <p>eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=MTQ2OTU1&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy LINK with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    Public</h3>

    <p>Public is an investing platform that allows you to invest stocks, ETFs, crypto, and alternative assets like fine art and collectibles&mdash;all in one place.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/public-crypto?guid=MTQ2OTU1&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy LINK with Public today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptocurrency execution and custody services are provided by Apex Crypto LLC (NMLS ID 1828849) through a software licensing agreement between Apex Crypto LLC and Public Crypto LLC. Crypto trading on Public platforms is served by Public Crypto LLC and offered through APEX Crypto. Please ensure that you fully understand the risks involved before trading." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/3-reasons-why-chainlink-link-price-just-surged/">3 reasons why Chainlink (LINK) price just surged</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/3-reasons-why-chainlink-link-price-just-surged/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto price prediction: Arkham (ARKM) and AltSignals (ASI)</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-arkham-arkm-and-altsignals-asi/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 11:35:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AI]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-arkham-arkm-and-altsignals-asi/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Arkham (ARKM) price rose to $0.89 after its Binance Launchpad sale. AltSignals (ASI) token is in presale, currently priced at $0.01875. Both projects have artificial intelligence-powered algorithms, systems that could revolutionise blockchain intelligence and marketplace and trading respectively. Arkham, a blockchain analytics platform and decentralised crypto intelligence marketplace, has a proprietary artificial intelligence (AI) layer [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-arkham-arkm-and-altsignals-asi/">Crypto price prediction: Arkham (ARKM) and AltSignals (ASI)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Arkham (ARKM) price rose to $0.89 after its Binance Launchpad sale.</li>
<li dir="ltr">AltSignals (ASI) token is in presale, currently priced at $0.01875.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Both projects have artificial intelligence-powered algorithms, systems that could revolutionise blockchain intelligence and marketplace and trading respectively.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Arkham, a blockchain analytics platform and decentralised crypto intelligence marketplace, has a proprietary artificial intelligence (AI) layer that&rsquo;s the engine of the platform&rsquo;s capabilities.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The native token ARKM currently trades on the open market and saw significant upside when it debuted after its <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-adds-arkham-arkm-to-launchpad/">Binance Launchpad sale</a>, before paring the gains amid huge profit taking.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Here is the price outlook for Arkham (ARKM) and AltSignals (ASI), another project that could ride the strong <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/ai/">AI</a> narrative.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Arkham: deanonymizing blockchain with AI</h2>
<p dir="ltr">A platform that offers access to on-chain data and analytics, and a marketplace for buying and selling of blockchain intelligence. That&rsquo;s a simple understanding of what Arkham is. The Arkham ecosystem has two components &ndash; an Analytics Platform and the Intel Exchange.</p>
<p dir="ltr">At the heart of it is the native ARKM token and ULTRA, an AI-powered system that was in development for more than three years and had the backing of major AI industry players like OpenAI and Palantir.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Arkham uses an ULTRA enabled algorithm to collect and match data and addresses, linking these to real-world entities and offering users access to key blockchain intelligence.</p>
<p dir="ltr">ARKM is a utility token that is used as the native currency on the Intel Exchange. Arkham uses the token to incentivize users, who get rewarded with ARKM when they submit intel and refer new users. The token also gives holders governance rights.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Can ARKM price reach $1 in 2023?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">While the launch of Intel Exchange drew criticism from some within the crypto space, particularly on so-called &ldquo;snitch-to-earn&rdquo; in place of Arkham&rsquo;s intel-to-earn product, the team and other proponents maintain the goal is to use the intel to expose the bad actors.</p>
<p dir="ltr">A flip in sentiment after the weak hands dumped airdropped tokens could combine with Arkham&rsquo;s unique approach to crypto intelligence and the strong AI narrative to help the price of ARKM. The all-time high for the token is $0.89 and the current price is around $0.62. If bulls were to match to $1 in 2023, Arkham would need to rally more than 61%.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Not impossible, but the unpredictability of the market means it&rsquo;s difficult to say with certainty ARKM will rise to $1. It could be higher or lower depending on market conditions and other factors. That said, Arkham has a great chance of being a successful blockchain platform. Its integration with leading blockchains, including Ethereum, BNB Chain, Arbitrum, Optimism, Avalanche, Polygon and Tron2 is a crucial milestone in its growth trajectory.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is AltSignals?</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://token.altsignals.io/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news"><u>AltSignals</u></a> is a trading platform that has been operating since December 2017, providing signals to a growing number of users.</p>
<p dir="ltr">While it began by providing free crypto signals, the platform&rsquo;s evolution has included expansion to setups for stocks and forex among others. Users get signals on potential buy or sell trades 24/7, factoring in <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/market-analysis/">market analysis</a> and trends &ndash; all with a rising degree of accuracy and profitability powered by the proprietary AltAlgo trading algorithm.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Like Arkham, AltSignals has an AI-powered layer that is set to bring the key benefits of machine learning and natural language processing to the trading industry.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The platform&rsquo;s new AI system is called ActualizeAI and will offer a suite of AI tools for optimised performance. Traders can leverage these tools to bump the potential investment returns across all market conditions.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">ASI token presale</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The ActualizeAI platform will be powered by ASI. This is the native utility token that will not just give holders access to the AI stack, but also power ecosystem transactions, used for rewards and allow holders to earn through staking.</p>
<p dir="ltr">ASI is currently in presale and is seeing huge interest from investors. The token is currently priced at $0.01875 and will rise to $0.02274 in the last stage of the sale offer.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Find more about the AltSignals presale<a href="https://token.altsignals.io/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">&nbsp;here</a>.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">AltSignals price prediction: Can ASI token reach 1 in 2023?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">According to the AltSignals roadmap, its launch on Uniswap is expected in Q3, 2023 and on Binance and Bybit in Q4, 2023. Meanwhile, development of the ActualizeAI Dashboard will continue, with an Alpha launch and live trading expected to go live in Q1, 2024. &nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">I highlight the roadmap milestones because they could be key to ASI token&rsquo;s performance after the presale, especially if an exchange like Binance announces trading support.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The ActualizeAI system debut is also a key milestone to watch out for as demand for the token could build pre-launch. That means a lot of hype could surround ASI in the last quarter of 2023. Will price follow the likely sentiment?</p>
<p dir="ltr">To rise from $0.02274 to $1.00 between October and end of December this year would need buying pressure to push ASI value higher by nearly 4300%. While it is possible, the more likely targets would be much lower given other market forces could be at play. Targets for the immediate term would be around $0.1 by year&rsquo;s end or early 2024.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-arkham-arkm-and-altsignals-asi/">Crypto price prediction: Arkham (ARKM) and AltSignals (ASI)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Memu rides meme coin and AI mania as project raises $994k</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memu-rides-meme-coin-and-ai-mania-as-project-raises-994k/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memu-rides-meme-coin-and-ai-mania-as-project-raises-994k/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Motiur Rahman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 10:23:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technical Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memu-rides-meme-coin-and-ai-mania-as-project-raises-994k/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Shiba Memu has raised $994,000 in a fortnight of presale The presale has generated a frenzy as investors bet big on the AI-led meme token The price of SHMU rises at each presale, with the value expected to explode once listed Shiba Memu (SHMU) is seemingly eyeing the position of one of the best meme [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memu-rides-meme-coin-and-ai-mania-as-project-raises-994k/">Shiba Memu rides meme coin and AI mania as project raises $994k</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu has raised $994,000 in a fortnight of presale</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The presale has generated a frenzy as investors bet big on the AI-led meme token</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The price of SHMU rises at each presale, with the value expected to explode once listed</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu (SHMU) is seemingly eyeing the position of one of the best meme cryptocurrencies of 2023. At a time leading meme coins like Dogecoin and Shiba Inu are reeling from the effects of a prolonged crypto winter, Shiba Memu is attracting huge investor interest. Just two weeks since launching the&nbsp;<a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>presale</u></a>, investors have accumulated almost $994,000 worth of the AI meme cryptocurrency.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>About Shiba Memu</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu is an AI-led meme coin that leverages the technology to market itself and generate hype. The meme can create its own PR and promote itself on social networks and forums. The AI-based software also allows Shiba Memu to learn from successful marketing campaigns to create more intelligent and powerful advertising.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The idea behind using AI is to make Shiba Memu self-sufficient and be a viable investment. Unlike the previous meme projects, where huge budgets are spent on marketing, Shiba Memu leverages AI technology to achieve the objective.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">AI also allows Shiba Memu to work 24/7, with the team anticipating the capability will position it to be the best in creative advertising. Given its self-sufficiency, SHMU can generate huge returns over time.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>What utility does Shiba Memu carry?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu boasts itself as a showoff, capable of doing the work of 100 marketing agencies. Well, that is surely a showoff, but we all know what AI is capable of. With human-like tech capabilities, it means Shiba Memu can do more than what a normal person can. Thus, it is a low-maintenance meme coin that can grow quickly with a low budget.</p>
<p dir="ltr">But again, imagine a meme project that interacts directly with the users. As times have shown, investors are looking for more engagement, which has seen an increased rise in decentralised autonomous organisations.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu features a robotic dashboard. Users can use it to give feedback, ask questions, provide suggestions, and interact with the AI. Indeed, this could be an ideal opportunity for meme lovers to build meaningful relationships with the loved dog-based meme. You can learn from it, including getting to know what&rsquo;s up in the world of creative advertising.</p>
<p dir="ltr">If you are an investor seeking passive income, there are some exciting details. Shiba Memu tokens will be available for staking in a staking pool or smart contract. There is also an opportunity to provide liquidity via the Shiba Memu pool. You simply do it through a decentralised exchange and earn fees for transactions made on the DEX and a portion generated as trading fees by the pool.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>How much can Shiba Memu rise?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">This could be quite a subjective question to answer. But from past experience, Meme cryptocurrencies could be the best to invest for quick gains. These are cryptocurrencies driven by hype and retail mania, with prices rising by thousands of percentages.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Fortunately, Shiba Memu has won the hearts of meme lovers, given the quick presale. Combined with the growing enthusiasm around AI, Shiba Memu could be an ultimate gainer by the time the token is listed on exchanges.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Should you buy Shiba Memu now?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Suppose you have ever missed a promising cryptocurrency that went on to return big to investors. In that case, you probably know what it means to miss an exciting opportunity like Shiba Memu. The meme cryptocurrency is already generating a frenzy, suggesting the potential to explode is huge.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu is also on the move, and procrastinators always pay a higher price tomorrow than today. What does this mean? The price of Shiba Memu rises daily at 6 pm GMT during the presale. This presale is set to occur in 8 stages. After that, the presale will end with whatever amount is raised. Investing now makes sense when the price is low, with a potential for considerable gains in the meme cryptocurrency.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memu-rides-meme-coin-and-ai-mania-as-project-raises-994k/">Shiba Memu rides meme coin and AI mania as project raises $994k</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memu-rides-meme-coin-and-ai-mania-as-project-raises-994k/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
