<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 17:20:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>MarketAcross Forms Alliance with Chainlink Labs to Empower Blockchain Startups</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/marketacross-chainlink-blockchain/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/marketacross-chainlink-blockchain/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 17:20:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ChainLink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketacross]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=262748</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/marketacross-chainlink-blockchain/">MarketAcross Forms Alliance with Chainlink Labs to Empower Blockchain Startups</a></p>
<p>The partnership between MarketAcross and Chainlink Labs highlights a common goal of equipping blockchain companies with the resources and assistance they need to succeed in a competitive market.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/marketacross-chainlink-blockchain/">MarketAcross Forms Alliance with Chainlink Labs to Empower Blockchain Startups</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/marketacross-chainlink-blockchain/">MarketAcross Forms Alliance with Chainlink Labs to Empower Blockchain Startups</a></p>
<p><a href="https://marketacross.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">MarketAcross</a>, the renowned PR and content marketing solution for blockchain startups, has announced its channel partnership with Chainlink Labs. This collaboration marks an exciting step forward for both Web 3.0 outfits and is set to provide immense value to startups participating in the <a href="https://chain.link/economics/build-program" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Chainlink BUILD</a> program.</p>
<p>According to the update, participating startups will have access to various services, such as PR, content marketing, brand reputation management, social promotions, SEO, and community building, utilizing MarketAcross’ expertise in multiple marketing disciplines.</p>
<h2>MarketAcross and Chainlink Partnership Addresses Key Challenges</h2>
<p>As the blockchain industry continues to evolve and gain mainstream recognition, the need for effective marketing and public relations solutions becomes paramount.</p>
<p>One of the key challenges faced by startups in the blockchain industry is gaining visibility and reaching their target audience. Recognizing this challenge, the strategic channel partnership between MarketAcross and Chainlink Labs takes on even greater significance.</p>
<p>Notably, MarketAcross has established itself as a trusted partner in the marketing journeys of some of the largest blockchain projects worldwide. Having contributed to the growth and scaling of prominent names like <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a>, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/polkadot-new/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Polkadot</a>, Solana, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/huobi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Huobi Global Ltd.</a>, and eToro, MarketAcross brings a wealth of experience and a proven track record to the table.</p>
<p>With MarketAcross’ extensive experience in PR and content marketing, entrepreneurs will receive tailored strategies and implementation plans to maximize their brand exposure. This collaboration will empower startups to effectively communicate their unique value proposition, thereby gaining credibility and attracting potential customers and investors.</p>
<p>Chainlink Labs, on the other hand, has garnered a stellar reputation as the developer of the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/chainlink/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Chainlink network</a>, a decentralized oracle solution that connects smart contracts with real-world data. With its comprehensive suite of Web3 services, Chainlink has emerged as the go-to platform for developers and enterprises seeking secure and reliable data connectivity.</p>
<p>The partnership between MarketAcross and Chainlink Labs highlights a common goal of equipping blockchain companies with the resources and assistance they need to succeed in a competitive market. The entities hope to foster innovation, promote acceptance, and open the door for the subsequent wave of blockchain disruptors by combining knowledge and resources.</p>
<h2>A Significant Milestone For Chainlink Build Program</h2>
<p>The Chainlink BUILD program is an initiative launched by Chainlink Labs to support and foster early-stage startups within the Chainlink ecosystem. As one of the leading Web3 services platforms, Chainlink aims to provide these startups with the necessary resources, guidance, and mentorship to accelerate their growth and development.</p>
<p>The program offers a structured framework that assists startups in building their projects and unlocking the full potential of Web3 technology. Participants in the Chainlink BUILD program gain access to a wide range of benefits and support, including technical resources, educational materials, networking opportunities, and business development assistance.</p>
<p>Overall, the collaboration between MarketAcross and Chainlink Labs is expected to bridge the gap between technical innovation and effective marketing strategies. This partnership empowers startups in the Chainlink BUILD program to overcome marketing challenges and position themselves for success.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-stocks-rally-inflation-numbers/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/marketacross-chainlink-blockchain/">MarketAcross Forms Alliance with Chainlink Labs to Empower Blockchain Startups</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/marketacross-chainlink-blockchain/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>US Stocks Rally as Inflation Numbers Come in Below Expectations</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-stocks-rally-inflation-numbers/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-stocks-rally-inflation-numbers/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 16:55:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Indices]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dow jones]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nasdaq composite]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[s&p 500]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stock market]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=262750</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-stocks-rally-inflation-numbers/">US Stocks Rally as Inflation Numbers Come in Below Expectations</a></p>
<p>The Federal Reserve is expected to raise interest rates at its July meeting, according to market estimates. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-stocks-rally-inflation-numbers/">US Stocks Rally as Inflation Numbers Come in Below Expectations</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-stocks-rally-inflation-numbers/">US Stocks Rally as Inflation Numbers Come in Below Expectations</a></p>
<p>The US stock market witnessed a remarkable surge earlier in the day as traders celebrated the release of new data indicating that inflation had risen less than expected compared to the previous month.</p>
<p>According to <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/07/11/stock-market-today-live-updates.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reports</a>, the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-the-dow-jones-industrial-average-index-djia/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Dow Jones Industrial Average</a> (INDEXDJX: .DJI) rose 282 points, or 0.8%, demonstrating strong market momentum. Meanwhile, the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-the-sp-500-index/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">S&amp;P 500 Index</a> (INDEXSP: .INX) is experiencing a notable gain of 0.7%, adding 31 points to 4,470.32, a figure that represents its new high for 2023 and its highest level since April 2022.</p>
<p>The <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-the-nasdaq-composite-index/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Nasdaq Composite</a> (INDEXNASDAQ: .IXIC), known for its technology-heavy composition, outperformed its peers with a remarkable 1.1% increase, contributing to the overall positive market outlook.</p>
<h2>Positive Outlook Fueled by Inflation Data</h2>
<p>The market’s resurgence can largely be attributed to the released inflation data that revealed a milder-than-expected rise in prices. This positive outcome appears to be allaying concerns over inflationary pressures and rejuvenated investor confidence in the US stock market.</p>
<p>As revealed in the report, the latest Consumer Price Index (CPI) for June increased by 3% year-over-year, slightly below economists&#8217; expectations of a 3.1% increase. Furthermore, on a month-on-month basis, the index rose by a modest 0.2%, falling short of the forecast.</p>
<p>Additionally, investors were encouraged by the fact that core inflation, which excludes volatile food and energy prices, also rose less than anticipated. These figures suggest a more moderate inflationary environment than initially predicted, offering some respite to both consumers and investors.</p>
<p>Following the release of the CPI data for June, the focus now turns to the upcoming announcement of the Producer Price Index (PPI). As a well-watched inflation gauge, the PPI provides valuable insights into price movements at the wholesale level.</p>
<p>With mounting concerns over inflationary pressures, market participants eagerly await the release of the June PPI figures, which are scheduled to be announced on Thursday. As the economy progresses, monitoring inflationary trends will remain crucial for assessing the trajectory of economic recovery and financial markets.</p>
<h2>US Stock Market Pricing in Potential Interest Rate Hike</h2>
<p>The Federal Reserve is expected to raise interest rates at its July meeting, according to market estimates.</p>
<p>The US stock market is pricing in a 92% chance of a rate hike, according to CME&#8217;s FedWatch Tool. The anticipation surrounding the Fed&#8217;s decision contributes to increased market volatility, as investors scrutinize economic data for any clues about the Central Bank’s future course of action.</p>
<p>As market participants eagerly await the release of the PPI data, the impact on interest rate expectations and investor sentiment remains uncertain. The interplay between inflationary pressures, the Federal Reserve&#8217;s decision-making process, and market reactions will continue to shape the trajectory of stocks.</p>
<p>However, investors should closely monitor economic indicators, central bank communications, and market sentiment to navigate potential market volatility and adjust their investment strategies accordingly.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bernstein-microstrategy-bitcoin-price/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-stocks-rally-inflation-numbers/">US Stocks Rally as Inflation Numbers Come in Below Expectations</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-stocks-rally-inflation-numbers/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bernstein Report: MicroStrategy Could Sell Its Bitcoin Holdings if Price Drops Drastically</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bernstein-microstrategy-bitcoin-price/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bernstein-microstrategy-bitcoin-price/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Temitope Olatunji]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 14:03:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[microstrategy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=262740</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bernstein-microstrategy-bitcoin-price/">Bernstein Report: MicroStrategy Could Sell Its Bitcoin Holdings if Price Drops Drastically</a></p>
<p>If the price of Bitcoin rises, MicroStrategy will benefit in various ways. Conversely, if the price of Bitcoin falls drastically or even crashes, MicroStrategy may face challenges in recovering from the debt.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bernstein-microstrategy-bitcoin-price/">Bernstein Report: MicroStrategy Could Sell Its Bitcoin Holdings if Price Drops Drastically</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bernstein-microstrategy-bitcoin-price/">Bernstein Report: MicroStrategy Could Sell Its Bitcoin Holdings if Price Drops Drastically</a></p>
<p>According to a recent report by Bernstein, as <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/07/12/microstrategy-only-needs-to-liquidate-bitcoin-in-extreme-price-corrections-bernstein/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reported</a> by Coindesk, MicroStrategy (MSTR) intends to raise long-term debt. However, the company is under pressure as it may need to sell off all its Bitcoin holdings, especially if the price drops drastically. This would be done to protect the company from the adverse effect that a possible Bitcoin price decline could have on its finances between now and 2025 when the debt will be due.</p>
<p>MicroStrategy, founded in 1989, has gained attention for its significant investment in Bitcoin. The company uses Bitcoin as a reserve asset to help protect and enhance its finances in the long run. MicroStrategy owns approximately 152,000 bitcoins bought at an average price of $29,600, totaling $4.49 billion and representing 0.77% of the total <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> supply. With this, the company is one of the largest institutional holders of crypto.</p>
<p>The report highlights that the value of Bitcoin held by <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/microstrategy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">MicroStrategy</a> is  95% of its market capitalization. However, when we consider the debt that the company has taken on to acquire BTC, the value of these assets only amounts to 49% of the company&#8217;s market cap.</p>
<h2>The Potential Effects of Bitcoin&#8217;s Exposure on MicroStrategy&#8217;s Finances</h2>
<p>If the price of Bitcoin rises, MicroStrategy will benefit in various ways. The event will help it to strengthen its financial position, increase share value, and make debt repayment easier. If an increase in stock prices accompanies the rising Bitcoin price, the company will be able to raise more funds for other purposes.</p>
<p>Conversely, if the price of Bitcoin falls drastically or even crashes, MicroStrategy may face challenges in recovering from the debt when it becomes due, as its Bitcoin holdings may not be sufficient to cover the loss. This situation would put additional pressure on the company.</p>
<h2>MicroStrategy and Potential Influence of Its Decisions on the Crypto Market</h2>
<p>If an institutional holder of Bitcoin like <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/microstrategy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">MicroStrategy</a> were to sell off its holdings, it could have various effects on the market. The first impact would be price volatility, as the massive sell-offs and subsequent panic sales due to fear would create downward pressure.</p>
<p>Such sell-offs could also trigger negative sentiment in the market, leading to a lack of confidence among investors. Given Bitcoin&#8217;s dominance, the sell-off could also affect other cryptocurrencies, potentially causing another prolonged period of market price decline, often referred to as a &#8220;crypto winter&#8221;.</p>
<p>However, it&#8217;s important to note that the impact of such an activity would depend on various factors and other events occurring in the crypto world at the time it happens.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-lawsuit-personal-data-ai/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bernstein-microstrategy-bitcoin-price/">Bernstein Report: MicroStrategy Could Sell Its Bitcoin Holdings if Price Drops Drastically</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bernstein-microstrategy-bitcoin-price/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Google Facing Lawsuit Over Misusing Personal Data to Train Its AI Models</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-lawsuit-personal-data-ai/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-lawsuit-personal-data-ai/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Darya Rudz]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 12:01:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[artificial intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[google]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Google AI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[google artificial intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[google lawsuit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[google privacy policy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=262684</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-lawsuit-personal-data-ai/">Google Facing Lawsuit Over Misusing Personal Data to Train Its AI Models</a></p>
<p>As per the lawsuit, the damages brought by Google are equal to over $5 billion. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-lawsuit-personal-data-ai/">Google Facing Lawsuit Over Misusing Personal Data to Train Its AI Models</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-lawsuit-personal-data-ai/">Google Facing Lawsuit Over Misusing Personal Data to Train Its AI Models</a></p>
<p>Tech giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/google/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Google LLC</a> (NASDAQ: GOOGL) has been hit with a lawsuit following its latest privacy policy update. The <a href="https://fingfx.thomsonreuters.com/gfx/legaldocs/myvmodloqvr/GOOGLE%20AI%20LAWSUIT%20complaint.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">lawsuit</a> filed by eight individuals on behalf of &#8220;millions of class members&#8221; in a federal court in California accuses Google of violating users&#8217; privacy. In particular, internet users and copyright holders complained about the company using their data to train its <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/technology/artificial-intelligence-news/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">artificial intelligence</a> (AI) systems.</p>
<p>The text of the lawsuit reads:</p>
<div title="Page 6">
<div>
<div>
<div>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;It has very recently come to light that Google has been secretly stealing everything ever created and shared on the internet by hundreds of millions of Americans. Google has taken all our personal and professional information, our creative and copywritten works, our photographs, and even our emails — virtually the entirety of our digital footprint — and is using it to build commercial Artificial Intelligence (“AI”) Products like “Bard,” the chatbot Google recently released to compete with OpenAI’s “ChatGPT.” For years, Google harvested this data in secret, without notice or consent from anyone.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<p>Lawyers of Clarkson Law Firm – the agency that brought the lawsuit – have named Google, its parent company <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/alphabet-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Alphabet Inc</a> (NASDAQ: GOOGL), and Google’s AI subsidiary DeepMind as defendants. None of them have provided any comments.</p>
<p>Tim Giordano, one of the attorneys at Clarkson, commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Google needs to understand that ‘publicly available’ has never meant free to use for any purpose. Our personal information and our data is our property, and it’s valuable, and nobody has the right to just take it and use it for any purpose.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>As per the lawsuit, the damages brought by Google are equal to over $5 billion. In addition to financial compensation, the lawyers have requested an order to obtain Google users&#8217; explicit permission to use their data first. It includes clear and precise disclosure of the data the company is collecting, as well as the introduction of technological safety measures that &#8220;prevent the technology from surpassing human intelligence and harming others.&#8221;</p>
<h2>Google&#8217;s Updated AI Policy</h2>
<p>Starting in July 2023, Google has introduced significant changes to its privacy policy. Now, the company can use publicly available information to help train its AI models. Besides, instead of using personal data for developing new features, Google can now employ information to create full products.</p>
<p>The company stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Google uses information to improve our services and to develop new products, features, and technologies that benefit our users and the public. For example, we use publicly available information to help train Google’s AI models and build products and features like Google Translate, Bard, and Cloud AI capabilities.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The policy update has received a wave of criticism. The updated policy specifies that publicly available information is used to train Google’s AI products, however, it is not clarified if and how Google will prevent copyrighted materials from being included in that database.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-korea-crypto-rules-transparency/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-lawsuit-personal-data-ai/">Google Facing Lawsuit Over Misusing Personal Data to Train Its AI Models</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-lawsuit-personal-data-ai/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>South Korea Floats New Crypto Rules to Promote Transparency</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-korea-crypto-rules-transparency/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-korea-crypto-rules-transparency/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 11:56:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fsc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[south korea]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=262667</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-korea-crypto-rules-transparency/">South Korea Floats New Crypto Rules to Promote Transparency</a></p>
<p>According to the FSC, the main aim of the proposed new rules is to encourage firms to have accounting transparency.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-korea-crypto-rules-transparency/">South Korea Floats New Crypto Rules to Promote Transparency</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-korea-crypto-rules-transparency/">South Korea Floats New Crypto Rules to Promote Transparency</a></p>
<p>Beginning next year, crypto firms in South Korea will be required to declare their crypto asset holdings in their financial statements. This is according to <a href="https://www.fsc.go.kr/no010101/80379?srchCtgry=&amp;curPage=&amp;srchKey=&amp;srchText=&amp;srchBeginDt=&amp;srchEndDt=" target="_blank" rel="noopener">draft rules</a> released by the country&#8217;s financial regulator, the Financial Services Commission (FSC), on July 11.</p>
<p>The new rules seek to know every little detail about crypto firms. That includes a company&#8217;s business model, its accounting policies, the quantity of crypto it holds, profits made, and the market value of its holdings.</p>
<h2>South Korea Prioritizes Accounting Transparency</h2>
<p>According to the FSC, the main aim of the proposed new rules is to encourage firms to have accounting transparency. The financial regulator believes that the new rules will usher in an era when companies will no longer hold differing opinions from those of their auditors. That is when it comes to admitting whether the company is in profit or not.</p>
<p>For instance, the rule provides that if a company sells virtual assets, profits will only be calculated after the company must have settled its holders.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the new rules also seek to ensure that costs incurred in developing virtual assets and their platforms will not be classified as intangible assets.</p>
<p>Although audit procedure guidelines are currently being prepared, South Korea has been keen on transparency. Its previous efforts include setting up a discussion panel that consists of domestic accounting experts and three agencies &#8211; the Financial Services Commission, the Financial Supervisory Service, and the Accounting Standards Board.</p>
<p>Over the past year, this panel has severally discussed accounting uncertainties, and so the new rules represent a step in the right direction for the country, which has its eyes ultimately set on protecting investors by all means necessary.</p>
<p>Interestingly, the draft rules follow the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-korea-independent-crypto-bill/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Virtual Asset User Protection Act</a> which, also, was just recently passed on June 30.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-offline-payment-digital-yuan/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-korea-crypto-rules-transparency/">South Korea Floats New Crypto Rules to Promote Transparency</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-korea-crypto-rules-transparency/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bank of China Launches Offline Payment Trial for Digital Yuan</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-offline-payment-digital-yuan/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-offline-payment-digital-yuan/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Babafemi Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 11:53:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bank of china]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital yuan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pboc]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=262606</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-offline-payment-digital-yuan/">Bank of China Launches Offline Payment Trial for Digital Yuan</a></p>
<p>For now, the e-CNY app has a limit of 500 yuan ($77) per transaction and 10,000 yuan ($1,540) per day for offline payments.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-offline-payment-digital-yuan/">Bank of China Launches Offline Payment Trial for Digital Yuan</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-offline-payment-digital-yuan/">Bank of China Launches Offline Payment Trial for Digital Yuan</a></p>

<p>The Bank of China <a href="https://mp.weixin.qq.com/s/Il2p2rKE116xMh97Ml0wQg" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">is cooperating</a> with China Telecom and China Unicom, two of the country’s major telecom operators, to enable offline transactions for the digital yuan via SIM cards. The move forms part of China’s broader push to digitalize cash and coins in circulation. It was announced on July 10 with trials commencing immediately the next day.</p>
<h2>How China Is Conducting the Trials</h2>
<p>Per the announcement, the initial phase of the trials will involve only specific Android phones. Again, it will only take place in specific regions, including Beijing, Shanghai, Shenzhen, Chengdu, and Suzhou.</p>
<p>Users will be able to make payments with the digital yuan even without a bank account or an internet connection. To allow this, the trial combines the digital yuan app with specialized “super SIM cards” possessing near-field communication capabilities.</p>
<p>For now, the e-CNY app has a limit of 500 yuan ($77) per transaction and 10,000 yuan ($1,540) per day for offline payments. Users simply need to bring their mobile phones near the point of sale terminals or tap a QR code. Likewise, it will be possible to make payments without needing to turn the phone on.</p>
<p>In the future, the bank plans to expand the scope of the trial and explore additional use cases for the offline payment system.</p>
<h2>China’s Progress with Its Digital Yuan Development</h2>
<p>China’s digital currency project has been in the works since 2014 when the People’s Bank of China (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/peoples-bank-of-china/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">PBoC</a>) established a research team to explore the feasibility and benefits of a <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-central-bank-digital-currency-cbdc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CBDC</a>. The digital yuan was the product of that effort.</p>
<p>The digital yuan is designed to be a legal tender that is backed by the central bank and can be used on various platforms, including online apps and offline devices. The PBoC has also introduced features such as programmability through smart contracts and controllable anonymity to ensure compliance and innovation.</p>
<p>As it stands, China appears to be leading the race for CBDC deployment globally. In 2022, the nation launched a trial of the e-CNY app. More recently, it expanded the usage of the digital yuan through the Belt and Road Initiative and cross-border trades. In Guanzhou, it is now possible to pay for public bus rides with the digital yuan.  The nation also plans to extend digital yuan usage to pay taxes and utility services in the city in the future.</p>
<p>Despite its early successes, the digital yuan will face competition from existing payment platforms such as Alipay and WeChat Pay. However, the PBoC hopes to increase its influence by making the digital yuan a more secure, convenient, and inclusive alternative. The offline payment alternative is an innovative project to achieve this and the success of the trial will determine a lot.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-anchor-investor-arm-ipo/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-offline-payment-digital-yuan/">Bank of China Launches Offline Payment Trial for Digital Yuan</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-offline-payment-digital-yuan/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nvidia Prepares to Be Anchor Investor in Arm IPO</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-anchor-investor-arm-ipo/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-anchor-investor-arm-ipo/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 11:50:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investors News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[IPO News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[arm]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nvidia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NYSE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[softbank]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=262683</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-anchor-investor-arm-ipo/">Nvidia Prepares to Be Anchor Investor in Arm IPO</a></p>
<p>Sources familiar with the matter said that the two players have been negotiating over valuations. They also stated that SoftBank's founder Masayoshi Son is trying to find big investors for Arm, as SoftBank has plans to liquidate its stake. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-anchor-investor-arm-ipo/">Nvidia Prepares to Be Anchor Investor in Arm IPO</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-anchor-investor-arm-ipo/">Nvidia Prepares to Be Anchor Investor in Arm IPO</a></p>
<p>As per the latest report on Wednesday, July 12, chip manufacturing giant Nvidia has been in talks with industry peer Arm to be an anchor investor in Arm&#8217;s <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-initial-public-offering-ipo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">IPO</a> listing on the New York Stock Exchange. As reported by the Financial Times, the listing shall happen as soon as September this year.</p>
<p>Thus, Nvidia joins the bandwagon as different companies are currently in talks with Arm to secure long-term staking in the chip designer ahead of the initial public offering. Over the last few months, Arm has been talking to more than 10 companies, including big names such as Intel.</p>
<p>As per the latest report, both Nvidia and Arm have been negotiating over Arm&#8217;s valuation. <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/nvidia/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Nvidia</a> would prefer a stake that would value Arm anywhere between $35 billion and $40 billion, as per one of the sources familiar with the matter. On the other hand, Arm is seeking a valuation of $80 billion, said the source.</p>
<p>Regulators rejected Nvidia&#8217;s $66 billion acquisition of Arm last year due to concerns about competition. This time, Nvidia and Arm have proposed a much smaller investment in the range of hundreds of millions of dollars. They have also reached out to regulators in advance to address any concerns and alleviate fears, as per sources familiar with the matter.</p>
<h2>Why Anchor Investors Are Important for Arm</h2>
<p>Financial Times <a href="https://www.ft.com/content/4522250e-7f70-4c60-9aad-1c49f42fa47e" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reports</a> that bringing anchor investors aboard is important for Arm to help support the stock as earlier backer SoftBank looks to liquidate its stake. Numerous private tech companies and their advisors are closely monitoring Arm&#8217;s IPO launch in 2023, especially after a decline in new listings over the past year.</p>
<p>In challenging IPO markets, it is common for companies to secure the backing of anchor investors in advance. This strategy helps ensure demand and provides reassurance to other potential investors.</p>
<p>Sources familiar with the matter said that SoftBank&#8217;s founder Masayoshi Son is trying to find big investors for Arm before it goes public. He wants to increase Arm&#8217;s revenue before the IPO. SoftBank declined to comment.</p>
<p>Nvidia is already a customer of Arm, but it wants to invest in the company to expand its business. Nvidia currently makes graphics processing units (GPUs), which are dedicated chips for accelerating specialized tasks like 3D rendering and training artificial intelligence. By investing in Arm, Nvidia could get into the market for central processing units (CPUs), which handle most other computing functions.</p>
<p>Nvidia, the first chipmaker to reach a $1 trillion valuation in May, recently produced its first central processing unit (CPU) using Arm&#8217;s designs. The CPU is part of a &#8220;superchip&#8221; called Grace Hopper, which is designed for artificial intelligence and high-performance computing.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/softbank-us-ipo-paypay/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-anchor-investor-arm-ipo/">Nvidia Prepares to Be Anchor Investor in Arm IPO</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-anchor-investor-arm-ipo/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>SoftBank Group Is Contemplating US IPO for Its PayPay Payments Division</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/softbank-us-ipo-paypay/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/softbank-us-ipo-paypay/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 11:45:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[IPO News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[paypay]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[rishi sunak]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[softbank]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=262651</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/softbank-us-ipo-paypay/">SoftBank Group Is Contemplating US IPO for Its PayPay Payments Division</a></p>
<p>Before the end of 2023, SoftBank may finalize IPO efforts in the US for PayPay and Arm.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/softbank-us-ipo-paypay/">SoftBank Group Is Contemplating US IPO for Its PayPay Payments Division</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/softbank-us-ipo-paypay/">SoftBank Group Is Contemplating US IPO for Its PayPay Payments Division</a></p>
<p>Japanese multinational investment holding company <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/softbank/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SoftBank Group Corp</a> is currently considering a United States initial public offering (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-initial-public-offering-ipo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">IPO</a>) for its PayPay payments subsidiary, according to a Reuters <a href="https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/softbank-considering-us-listing-paypay-payments-business-sources-2023-07-12/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a>.</p>
<p>SoftBank is likely considering a New York listing because tech companies mostly achieve impressive valuations in places other than Tokyo. However, Japanese companies conducting IPOs in New York are not very common.</p>
<p>SoftBank has not decided on whether or not to list or set a timeline for the IPO.</p>
<p>In May, SoftBank had expressed a desire for PayPay to list in the US. Recently appointed CEO Junichi Miyakawa said the idea for a PayPay IPO is independence, adding that the listing could happen soon. Nonetheless, the IPO will likely be delayed until PayPay can properly illustrate a clear path toward profitability. PayPay is owned by SoftBank Group and Z Holdings, the holding company that comprises Yahoo! Japan and the Line instant messaging app.</p>
<p>Both SoftBank Group and Z Holdings shares climbed 2% and 6%, respectively. Z Holdings had its largest one-day rise since February, likely on news of the possible listing. While SoftBank is pursuing a foreign listing for the payments company, Astris Advisory Japan analyst Kirk Boodry believes the tech IPO space in Japan is not yet saturated:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Z Holdings shares reacted on hopes that a US listing might invite a premium valuation but recent domestic listings for Rakuten Bank and SBI Sumishin Net Bank indicate there is room for fintech listings locally.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>SoftBank’s PayPay IPO Joins Possible Arm Listing</h2>
<p>In addition to PayPay, SoftBank’s semiconductor company, Arm, is also considering a US IPO in 2023. Arm <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/softbank-arm-us-only-listing/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">confirmed</a> it would likely pursue a US-only listing this year, abandoning a rumored UK option. Arm CEO Rene Haas described the US option as “the best way forward for the company and its stakeholders” after discussions with the British Government and the UK’s Financial Conduct Authority fell through.</p>
<p>Back in January, Haas <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/arm-london-ipo-listing-plans/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">had a meeting</a> with British Prime Minister <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/rishi-sunak/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Rishi Sunak</a> at the Prime Minister’s residence, with SoftBank founder Masayoshi Son present virtually. According to inside sources, the meeting ended positively as Sunak was enthusiastic about the chance of an Arm listing.</p>
<h2>SoftBank’s Vision Fund Tanked Last Year</h2>
<p>SoftBank may be hoping to improve its books this year with IPO efforts geared at Arm and PayPay. The investment giant’s Vision Fund had an unimpressive 2022, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/softbank-vision-fund-q4-2022/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">recording</a> a 660 billion Japanese Yen ($5 billion) loss, plus a 730.35 loss on investments for the quarter ended December 31st. Because of the result, Son said the fund would begin “defense” mode and be very cautious about further investments.</p>
<p>For the fiscal year ended March 31st, SoftBank <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/softbank-vision-fund-32b-loss/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">said</a> its Vision Fund lost a record 4.3 trillion yen, about $32 billion. The loss for the year was higher than 2.55 trillion yen sustained for the same period in the previous year. The company said a lot of the losses resulted from heavy decreases in several company investments.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/7-eleven-nfts-polygon-slurpee/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/softbank-us-ipo-paypay/">SoftBank Group Is Contemplating US IPO for Its PayPay Payments Division</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/softbank-us-ipo-paypay/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Retail Powerhouse 7-Eleven Launches NFTs on Polygon Network to Celebrate Slurpee Day</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/7-eleven-nfts-polygon-slurpee/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/7-eleven-nfts-polygon-slurpee/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 11:41:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[7-eleven]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[matic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[polygon]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=262694</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/7-eleven-nfts-polygon-slurpee/">Retail Powerhouse 7-Eleven Launches NFTs on Polygon Network to Celebrate Slurpee Day</a></p>
<p>While the Slurpee NFT creation process is exclusive to mobile devices, collectors can provide their name, email address, and telephone number to customize their NFTs.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/7-eleven-nfts-polygon-slurpee/">Retail Powerhouse 7-Eleven Launches NFTs on Polygon Network to Celebrate Slurpee Day</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/7-eleven-nfts-polygon-slurpee/">Retail Powerhouse 7-Eleven Launches NFTs on Polygon Network to Celebrate Slurpee Day</a></p>
<p>The American convenience store chain 7-Eleven has joined the crypto bandwagon with its latest move to embrace non-fungible tokens (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NFTs</a>). The company <a href="https://corp.7-eleven.com/corp-press-releases/happy-slurpee-day-7-eleven-inc-turns-96-today-celebrates-with-free-slurpee-drinks-and-limited-edition-digital-collectibles-" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announced</a> on July 11 that it would launch the first-of-its-kind digital collectible for Slurpee fans nationwide to commemorate its 96th anniversary. The digital artwork will be available on the Polygon network, a layer 2 scaling solution built on the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a> blockchain.</p>
<p>As part of its efforts to keep its customers engaged and excited on Slurpee Day, an event celebrated every July 11; the company has introduced a series of NFTs that customers can mint on <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/matic-network/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Polygon</a>. The retail giant aims to offer its customers a unique and innovative experience worldwide.</p>
<p>The Slurpee NFTs will be part of a sugary collectible game revolving around the company&#8217;s virtual Slurpee cup. The game features four flavors: Blue Raspberry, Cherry, Pina Colada, and Summertime Citrus. NFT collectors can choose their favorite flavor and create their very own Slurpee blend, adding a touch of personalization to the experience.</p>
<p>Marissa Jarratt, Executive Vice President, and Chief Marketing &amp; Sustainability Officer at 7-Eleven, said the move is part of the company&#8217;s plan to celebrate with customers on Slurpee Day.</p>
<p>&#8220;We&#8217;re always looking for new and creative ways to celebrate with our customers on our favorite day of the year, Slurpee Day. This year, we&#8217;re marking another first for the brand with our inaugural digital collectible, &#8216;Find Your Slurpee Vibe,&#8217; maybe you&#8217;ll even give us some inspiration for future flavors,&#8221; said Jarratt.</p>
<h2>7-Eleven Offers Customers Opportunity to Customize Their NFTs</h2>
<p>To claim the &#8220;Slurpee Vibe Digital Collectible,&#8221; customers will need to access the NFT creation process through their mobile devices later today by 7:11 p.m. ET. Once the virtual cup is filled, a screen will appear with two options: claim the collectible or start over. Customers can unleash their creativity and concoct their dream Slurpee by carefully selecting their preferred flavors.</p>
<p>While the Slurpee NFT creation process is exclusive to mobile devices, collectors can provide their name, email address, and telephone number to customize their NFTs. They will then receive a unique six-digit code via email, allowing them to claim their exclusive Slurpee NFT.</p>
<p>The company&#8217;s entry into the world of digital collectibles marks a significant step in mainstream retailers&#8217; adoption of digital artwork. As other major brands, such as Starbucks and Louis Vuitton, and Nike have ventured into the NFT space, this move could open up new avenues for customer engagement and loyalty programs in the future.</p>
<p>With their Slurpee NFTs on the Polygon network, 7-Eleven continues to innovate and offer unique experiences to its customers.</p>
<h2>7-Eleven Unveils Birthday Collection Capsule with Free Shipping</h2>
<p>In addition to the digital collectibles, the American convenience store chain is launching a limited-time 7/11 Birthday Collection  capsule on its online merchandise shop called 7Collection. The new collection will include 7-Eleven-inspired party decor, apparel, balloons, wrapping paper, and more. To celebrate the occasion, the retailer offers free shipping on all orders made on July 11 using the code SLURPEEDAY.</p>
<p>In addition, the company is providing various deals and discounts to its customers to mark the celebration. Some discounts include $1 food deals, savings on fuel for 7Rewards and Speedy Rewards members, and 7NOW Gold Pass subscriptions.</p>
<p>Customers who sign up for the 7NOW Gold Pass via the 7NOW Delivery app on July 11 will receive a free subscription through the end of 2023. Fuel rewards members will enjoy an additional 11¢ off each gallon purchased on July 11 at 7-Eleven and Speedway-branded fuel locations.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ark-invest-sells-12m-coinbase-shares/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/7-eleven-nfts-polygon-slurpee/">Retail Powerhouse 7-Eleven Launches NFTs on Polygon Network to Celebrate Slurpee Day</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/7-eleven-nfts-polygon-slurpee/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cathie Wood’s Ark Invest Sells $12M in Coinbase Shares amid Rally</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ark-invest-sells-12m-coinbase-shares/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ark-invest-sells-12m-coinbase-shares/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mercy Tukiya Mutanya]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 11:37:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investors News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ark invest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ark investment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brian armstrong]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[catie wood]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coin stock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase stock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[etf]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=262673</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ark-invest-sells-12m-coinbase-shares/">Cathie Wood’s Ark Invest Sells $12M in Coinbase Shares amid Rally</a></p>
<p>Meanwhile, some Coinbase executives, including CEO Brian Armstrong, have been taking advantage of the stock’s rally in recent months.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ark-invest-sells-12m-coinbase-shares/">Cathie Wood’s Ark Invest Sells $12M in Coinbase Shares amid Rally</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ark-invest-sells-12m-coinbase-shares/">Cathie Wood’s Ark Invest Sells $12M in Coinbase Shares amid Rally</a></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Cathie Wood’s Ark Investment Management LLC trimmed its sizable holding of Coinbase Global Inc stock on Tuesday, July 11. Wood’s Ark Innovation ETF sold 135,152 COIN shares worth $12 million, its first sale of the stock since July 26 last year. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The 135,152 sold translates to 0.14% of the fund’s total COIN holdings. According to the fund’s </span><a href="https://ark-funds.com/funds/arkk/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">website</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, it currently holds Coinbase shares worth $711.24 million, its second-largest holding after Tesla stock and 8.25% of its total holdings. It was a well-timed sale that comes as COIN shares approach a one-year high following an announcement that the cryptocurrency exchange had reached a surveillance-sharing agreement with Cboe’s BZX Exchange for five of its spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) applications – Wise Origin, WisdomTree, VanEck, Invesco Galaxy and ARK 21Shares. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to </span><a href="https://cdn.cboe.com/resources/regulation/rule_filings/pending/2023/SR-CboeBZX-2023-044-Amendment-No-1.pdf"><span style="font-weight: 400;">amendments</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> made on Tuesday to the </span><a href="https://cdn.cboe.com/resources/regulation/rule_filings/pending/2023/SR-CboeBZX-2023-044.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">original filings</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> with the Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>), the agreement for each of these applications was settled on June 21. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“On June 21, 2023, the Exchange reached an agreement on terms with Coinbase, Inc., an operator of a United States-based spot trading platform for Bitcoin that represents a substantial portion of US-based spot trading platform for Bitcoin that represents a substantial portion of US-based and USD-denominated Bitcoin trading, to enter into a surveillance-sharing agreement (“Spot BTC SSA”) and executed an associated term sheet,” the filing stated. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The price of Coinbase stock surged from $82 to heights of $90.9 on Tuesday, July 11, closing the day at $89. </span><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/NASDAQ-COIN/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">TradingView data</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> shows that COIN stock is up over 60% over a month and more than 140% year-to-date.  </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The sale via the Ark Innovation ETF is the second time Wood has taken profits from COIN stock this year. In March the ARK Fintech Innovation ETF sold 160,887 COIN shares at about $84 shares for a total of $13.5 million. Wood&#8217;s firm is known for making large purchases of Coinbase stock for the various ARK funds. In June, for instance, the investment firm bought COIN shares worth $4 million. They bought a total of $33 million in COIN in April and May and $1117 million in March. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Some Coinbase executives, including CEO Brian Armstrong, have been taking advantage of the stock’s rally in recent months. On July 6, Armstrong and other senior executives sold $6.9 million in COIN stock and before that, on June 29, the exchange’s chief accounting officer Jennifer Jones sold 74,375 shares worth $5.2 million. </span><a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/celsius-lawsuit-stakehound/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ark-invest-sells-12m-coinbase-shares/">Cathie Wood’s Ark Invest Sells $12M in Coinbase Shares amid Rally</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ark-invest-sells-12m-coinbase-shares/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4042 metric#misses=41 metric#hit-ratio=99.0 metric#bytes=1113823 metric#prefetches=158 metric#store-reads=49 metric#store-writes=2 metric#store-hits=211 metric#store-misses=2 metric#sql-queries=34 metric#ms-total=91.66 metric#ms-cache=7.51 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.1503 metric#ms-cache-ratio=8.2 -->