<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 12:24:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Brian Armstrong to meet House Democrats about crypto legislation</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/brian-armstrong-to-meet-house-democrats-about-crypto-legislation/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/brian-armstrong-to-meet-house-democrats-about-crypto-legislation/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 12:24:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Policy and Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/brian-armstrong-to-meet-house-democrats-about-crypto-legislation/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways Coinbase CEO will meet with House Democrats to discuss crypto regulation. Armstrong wants clearer rules on crypto from Washington. Coinbase CEO wants clearer crypto regulation in the US Coinbase Inc. Chief Executive Officer Brian Armstrong is set to meet with House Democrats behind closed doors Wednesday morning. This is according to a&#160;Bloomberg report [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/brian-armstrong-to-meet-house-democrats-about-crypto-legislation/">Brian Armstrong to meet House Democrats about crypto legislation</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Coinbase CEO will meet with House Democrats to discuss crypto regulation.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Armstrong wants clearer rules on crypto from Washington.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr">Coinbase CEO wants clearer crypto regulation in the US</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Coinbase Inc. Chief Executive Officer Brian Armstrong is set to meet with House Democrats behind closed doors Wednesday morning. This is according to a&nbsp;<a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-07-17/coinbase-ceo-brian-armstrong-set-to-meet-with-house-democrats?sref=3REHEaVI" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Bloomberg report</u></a> on Monday, citing sources familiar with the plans.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to the report, Armstrong will speak privately with lawmakers from the New Democrat Coalition about cryptocurrency legislation and related issues, including tax, national security, privacy and climate.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">This&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>latest cryptocurrency news</u></a> comes as Coinbase faces a lawsuit by the Securities and Exchange Commission.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Recently, lawmakers from the House and Senate have introduced bills that would bring clarity to the cryptocurrency industry in the United States. However, the divided nature of Congress makes it unclear whether the bills would be adopted soon.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Coinbase continues to battle SEC in court</h2>
<p dir="ltr">On June 6, the US&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-sec-strikes-again-first-binance-now-coinbase/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>SEC charged Coinbase</u></a> with violating federal securities law, adding that the cryptocurrency exchange was operating as an unlicenced broker, national securities exchange and clearing agency.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The cryptocurrency exchange responded, saying that the SEC&rsquo;s action violates due process and constitutes an abuse of discretion.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">On June 29th,&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-files-to-have-the-lawsuit-by-the-sec-dismissed-for-lack-of-merits/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Coinbase submitted a motion</u></a> to the United States District Court for the Southern District of New York, asking that the SEC complaint charges be dismissed for lack of merit.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Coinbase&rsquo;s stock price has grown by nearly 200% since the start of the year, thanks to Bitcoin&rsquo;s price rallying by nearly 50% during that period. At the start of the year, COIN was trading at $40 per share but currently stands at $105.55.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/brian-armstrong-to-meet-house-democrats-about-crypto-legislation/">Brian Armstrong to meet House Democrats about crypto legislation</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/brian-armstrong-to-meet-house-democrats-about-crypto-legislation/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chainlink price prediction: LINK just formed a double top pattern</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/chainlink-price-prediction-link-just-formed-a-double-top-pattern/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/chainlink-price-prediction-link-just-formed-a-double-top-pattern/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 12:05:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chainlink News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/chainlink-price-prediction-link-just-formed-a-double-top-pattern/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Chainlink announced a new plan to expand in the traditional finance industry. It unveiled the Cross-Chain Interoperability Protocol (CCIP). The coin has formed a double-top pattern on the 4H chart. Chainlink price rose to a high of $7.32, the highest level since April 26th. At its peak on Tuesday, the LINK token was up by [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chainlink-price-prediction-link-just-formed-a-double-top-pattern/">Chainlink price prediction: LINK just formed a double top pattern</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Chainlink announced a new plan to expand in the traditional finance industry.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">It unveiled the Cross-Chain Interoperability Protocol (CCIP).</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The coin has formed a double-top pattern on the 4H chart.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/chainlink"><u>Chainlink</u></a> price rose to a high of $7.32, the highest level since April 26th. At its peak on Tuesday, the LINK token was up by more than 53% from the lowest level in June. It has outperformed other coins like Bitcoin and Ethereum.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Chainlink expands its offerings</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Chainlink is the biggest oracle network in the blockchain industry. An oracle is a network that links off-chain data to the on-chain. It is widely used to provide price feeds in decentralized and centralized exchanges.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Chainlink has been growing its ecosystem in the past few years. In June, the developers announced that they had begun testing connecting banks to the blockchain by partnering with Swift.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In a statement on Tuesday, the company unveiled Chainlink&rsquo;s Cross-chain Interoperability Protocol (CCIP). CCIP is designed to connect traditional financial institutions to the blockchain. The initial blockchains will be&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/avalanche"><u>Avalanche</u></a>, Ethereum, Optimism, and Polygon. Early adopters in this testing were Synthetix and Aave.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, LINK price jumped as investors hope that the network will see more action in the coming months.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Data compiled by DeFi Llama shows that the network has a total value secured (TVS) of over&nbsp;<a href="https://defillama.com/oracles"><u>$21.85 billion</u></a>. This makes it the biggest oracle provider in the world. The other big oracles are Chronicle, WINKLink, Pyth, TWAP, and RedStone.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Chainlink price prediction</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/18/1689681924119-12a04c41-8cdb-4cce-84c6-16d3ffdec0ce.jpg" style="width: 642px;height: 291.503px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="642" height="291.503"></p>
<p dir="ltr">LINK price has been in a strong bullish trend in the past few days. On the 4H chart, the coin has moved above the 25-period and 50-period moving averages. It has also formed an ascending channel shown in black. The price is a few points below the upper side of the channel.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Most importantly, Chainlink has formed a double-top pattern at $7.30. In price action analysis, this pattern is usually a bearish sign. The neckline of this pattern is at $6.50. Therefore, despite the new product launch, there is a likelihood that LINK price will have a bearish breakout.</p>
<p dir="ltr">If this happens, the next level to watch will be at $6.50, which is ~6.50% below the current level. On the flip side, a move above the double-top level of $7.30 will invalidate the bearish view.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy Chainlink</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>

    <p>eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=MTQ2NjE1&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy LINK with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    Public</h3>

    <p>Public is an investing platform that allows you to invest stocks, ETFs, crypto, and alternative assets like fine art and collectibles&mdash;all in one place.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/public-crypto?guid=MTQ2NjE1&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy LINK with Public today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptocurrency execution and custody services are provided by Apex Crypto LLC (NMLS ID 1828849) through a software licensing agreement between Apex Crypto LLC and Public Crypto LLC. Crypto trading on Public platforms is served by Public Crypto LLC and offered through APEX Crypto. Please ensure that you fully understand the risks involved before trading." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chainlink-price-prediction-link-just-formed-a-double-top-pattern/">Chainlink price prediction: LINK just formed a double top pattern</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/chainlink-price-prediction-link-just-formed-a-double-top-pattern/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>CROWN Token Project launches limited-edition NFTs on ADOT marketplace</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/crown-token-project-launches-limited-edition-nfts-on-adot-marketplace/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 12:02:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/crown-token-project-launches-limited-edition-nfts-on-adot-marketplace/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The NFT collection will unlock opportunities for lovers of animated films, starting with Legend of Two Heroes. CROWN Token&#8217;s NFTs will be available on the platform&#8217;s ADOT NFT marketplace. The Legend of the Two Heroes NFT series features 590 NFT mints from 39 NFTs. CROWN Token Project, a Web3 platform that bridges the traditional IPs [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crown-token-project-launches-limited-edition-nfts-on-adot-marketplace/">CROWN Token Project launches limited-edition NFTs on ADOT marketplace</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">The NFT collection will unlock opportunities for lovers of animated films, starting with <em>Legend of Two Heroes</em>.</li>
<li dir="ltr">CROWN Token&rsquo;s NFTs will be available on the platform&rsquo;s ADOT NFT marketplace.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The Legend of the Two Heroes NFT series features 590 NFT mints from 39 NFTs.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://crowntoken.io/" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>CROWN Token Project</u></a>, a Web3 platform that bridges the traditional IPs market with blockchain, has launched its first non-fungible token (NFT) collection.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The <a href="https://coinjournal.net/nfts/">NFTs</a> debut is on<a href="https://www.adotmarketplace.com/" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">&nbsp;<u>ADOT</u></a>, the CROWN Token&rsquo;s own NFT marketplace, and will roll out with a limited-edition of the animated film <em>Legend of the Two Heroes</em>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to a press release shared with CoinJournal on Tuesday, July 18, the NFT series will showcase characters from the $15 million budget film from Hong Kong director Hernan Yau and renowned screenwriter Robert Lence.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Toy Story, Beauty and the Beast and Shrek are some of the feature masterpieces to incorporate Lence&rsquo;s scripts.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">590 mints across 39 NFTs</h2>
<p dir="ltr">While <em>Legend of the Two Heroes</em> is in post-production and is scheduled for global release early next year, CROWN Token says its NFT series on the feature film will be open for minting beginning July 19, 2023. The timing of the mint will see NFT holders included in the film&rsquo;s creation, right from ideation to release on the big screen.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Pan Lorattawut, CEO of VUCA Digital which manages the CROWN Token Project, said:</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>It&rsquo;s exciting to see this project with our ADOT marketplace come to life. We want NFT holders to be involved in the animated action film&rsquo;s creation in every possible way. This is one of the ways we not only reward our ecosystem, but continue to expand the benefits of IPs</em>.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The limited NFT series will allow for 590 mints spread across 39 NFTs, with each NFT having 15 mints. Meanwhile, there will also be 5 rare NFTs each of which will have only 1 mint. Collectors can only buy the rare NFTs with CROWN Token, the platform said.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The top three main characters in the film to feature in the NFTs will later be added to an upcoming MMO role-playing game.</p>
<div class="fr-img-space-wrap"><span class="fr-img-caption fr-fic fr-dib fr-draggable" style="width: 600px"><span class="fr-img-wrap">
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/18/1689679663574-fadd2df1-b4b9-4b7b-879f-6dab0543f5eb.jpg" style="width: 600px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="600" height="598"><span class="fr-inner">A character from Legend of the Two Heroes. Source: CROWN Token Project</span></p>
<p></p></span></span>
<p class="fr-img-space-wrap2">Although the global NFTs market size shrank alongside the broader crypto industry during the crypto winter, projections are that the market size will expand at a CAGR of 27.6% to $342 billion by 2032.&nbsp;</p>
<p class="fr-img-space-wrap2">According to a<a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/en/news-release/2023/05/18/2671911/0/en/NFT-Market-size-to-Cross-USD-342-54-Billion-By-2032-With-an-27-60-CAGR-by-2032-Report-by-Market-Research-Future-MRFR.html" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">&nbsp;<u>report</u></a> by Market Research Future (MRFR), key drivers of this growth will include cryptocurrency use and rising global demand for digital art.</p>
</div>
<p dir="ltr">CROWN Token Project expects its ADOT Marketplace to experience growth in coming years, with the utility of its token expanding as a result. CROWN Token is a crypto project by VUCA Digital, a blockchain consulting firm affiliated to IP management firm T&amp;B Media Global.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crown-token-project-launches-limited-edition-nfts-on-adot-marketplace/">CROWN Token Project launches limited-edition NFTs on ADOT marketplace</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitget added 9,033 new elite traders in Q2</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitget-q2-transparency-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wajeeh Khan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 11:01:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitget]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto exchange]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=146566</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitget says it made a bunch of notable achievements in the second quarter of this year &#8211; a few of which it underscored in a Transparency Report on Tuesday. Bitget continued to increase market share in Q2 According to the quarterly update, its market share climbed further in the three-month period to 8.7%. That translates [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitget-q2-transparency-report/">Bitget added 9,033 new elite traders in Q2</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitget says it made a bunch of notable achievements in the second quarter of this year &ndash; a few of which it underscored in a <a href="https://www.bitget.com/blog/articles/bitget-sees-second-highest-increase-in-market-shares" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Transparency Report</a> on Tuesday.</p>
<h2>Bitget continued to increase market share in Q2</h2>
<p>According to the quarterly update, its market share climbed further in the three-month period to 8.7%.</p>
<p>That translates to a 1.81% increase &ndash; second highest among the top five centralised exchanges. Spot trading exceeded $60 billion in terms of volume while futures trading surpassed $600 billion.</p>
<p>Bitget is the only CEX that saw an increase in futures trading volume this year following the FTX fiasco, as per Nansen &ndash; a blockchain analytics platform.</p>
<p>These disclosures arrive just days after the Seychelles-based company launched &ldquo;Crypto Loans&rdquo; to debut in lending (<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitget-launches-crypto-loans/">find out more</a>).</p>
<h2>Copy trading helped add new elite traders</h2>
<p>Bitget increased its followers by more than 85,000 in the second quarter. Copy trading, it added, helped grow the number of elite traders on the platform by 9,033 as well.</p>
<p>&ldquo;BGB&rdquo; &ndash; its native token outperformed peers unlocking a whopping 23% as trading volume hit $1.3 million &ndash; an 80% increase. The Transparency Report also reads:</p>
<blockquote><p>Demand for BGB has been on the rise, with the number of BGB holders rising by 130% to 305,653 in three months.</p></blockquote>
<p>Bitget remained committed to expansion in the second quarter and successfully registered as a VASP in <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/in/news-releases/bitget-registers-as-virtual-asset-service-provider-in-poland-301831988.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Poland</a> and <a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitget-secures-regulatory-license-in-poland-reserve-funds-up-80m-in-q1" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Lithuania</a>. It also entered <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitget-formally-enters-turkey-bitget-tr/">Turkey</a> in Q2 with a new website.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitget-q2-transparency-report/">Bitget added 9,033 new elite traders in Q2</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>AltSignals’ stage two presale surpasses 50%: should you get in now?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-stage-two-presale-surpasses-50-should-you-get-in-now/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-stage-two-presale-surpasses-50-should-you-get-in-now/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 10:51:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-stage-two-presale-surpasses-50-should-you-get-in-now/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways AltSignals&#8217; stage two presale event is already halfway over, with more investors pouring into the project. Bitcoin continues to struggle to defend its price above the $30k level. The cryptocurrency market has been bearish since the start of the week. Following last week&#8217;s rally, prices of Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies are currently underperforming. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-stage-two-presale-surpasses-50-should-you-get-in-now/">AltSignals’ stage two presale surpasses 50%: should you get in now?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals&rsquo; stage two presale event is already halfway over, with more investors pouring into the project.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin continues to struggle to defend its price above the $30k level.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">The cryptocurrency market has been bearish since the start of the week. Following last week&rsquo;s rally, prices of Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies are currently underperforming.</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, AltSignals&rsquo; presale event continues to surge ahead, with the second presale event already 50% completed.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is AltSignals?</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://token.altsignals.io/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=invezz&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>AltSignals</u></a> is an exciting Web3 project that specially targets traders. The development team seeks to solve some of the pain points of traders and make it easier for people to enter the cryptocurrency market.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to their whitepaper, AltSignals is a trading platform that provides trading signals for stocks, forex, indices, cryptocurrencies, and CFDs.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">One of the biggest concerns for traders is accurately carrying out technical analysis and determining when to enter and exit traders.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals seeks to solve all that thanks to its use of blockchain technology and AI. The team has raised more than $1.1 million in the second presale stage and will use the funds to develop its trading platform.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">ASI will be the native token that powers the AltSignals ecosystem. It is currently going for 0.01875 per token and could increase ahead of the next presale event.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">In their whitepaper, AltSignals explained that they would use the funds generated from the funding rounds to develop ActualizeAI, a solution that could make it easier for more people to enter the cryptocurrency trading scene.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">With ActualizeAI, users would have access to a fully automated solution that makes it easier for people to trade cryptocurrencies.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Visit the official&nbsp;<a href="https://token.altsignals.io/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=invezz&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>AltSignals website</u></a> to learn more about their presale.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">AltSignals continues to generate more buzz</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The cryptocurrency market has been retracing following last week&rsquo;s rally. Bitcoin has lost more than 1% of its value over the past few days and is currently struggling to maintain its price above the $30k threshold. At press time, the&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>price of Bitcoin</u></a> stands at $29,960 per coin.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Other leading cryptocurrencies, including Ether, and BNB, are also underperforming. Despite the recent market retracement, AltSignals&rsquo; presale event continues to attain new milestones.</p>
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals&rsquo; stage two presale event has generated nearly $1.2 million, 52% of the total amount required. The project is still in its early days and could serve as an excellent investment for investors.</p>
<p dir="ltr">With the market currently retracing, more investors could be looking to purchase more cryptocurrencies. Furthermore, other investors could be looking to invest in new projects, and&nbsp;<a href="https://token.altsignals.io/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=invezz&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>AltSignals</u></a> could be one of the projects to consider.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Should you invest in AltSignals now?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Despite the poor performance this week, the cryptocurrency market has outperformed the other financial markets since the start of the year. Bitcoin is up by nearly 50% year-to-date, making it one of the best-performing global assets so far this year.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Market experts predict that Bitcoin&rsquo;s price could surpass the $100,000 mark over the next few months or years. If that happens, other cryptocurrencies could benefit.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals could be one of the biggest beneficiaries due to its niche-specific product. As a product that targets traders,&nbsp;<a href="https://token.altsignals.io/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=invezz&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>AltSignals</u></a> could become an important project in a multi-billion dollar industry.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">ASI is currently in its presale stage, and its price could soar higher once the token gets listed on cryptocurrency exchanges. Furthermore, if the crypto market embarks on a Bull Run, ASI&rsquo;s price could also appreciate in the medium to long term.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-stage-two-presale-surpasses-50-should-you-get-in-now/">AltSignals’ stage two presale surpasses 50%: should you get in now?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-stage-two-presale-surpasses-50-should-you-get-in-now/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Memu nears $1M presale as trailblazing AI integration sparks investor gold rush</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memu-nears-1m-presale-as-trailblazing-ai-integration-sparks-investor-gold-rush/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memu-nears-1m-presale-as-trailblazing-ai-integration-sparks-investor-gold-rush/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 09:58:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOGE]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memu-nears-1m-presale-as-trailblazing-ai-integration-sparks-investor-gold-rush/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Shiba Memu sparks gold rush for crypto investors with trailblazing AI protocol SHMU presale, uniquely tailored to investor interests, is close to hitting $1 million with over $954k raised so far. The Shiba Memu platform targets becoming the superpower of meme coin marketing. Shiba Memu is the latest meme coin craze in the vast cryptocurrency [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memu-nears-1m-presale-as-trailblazing-ai-integration-sparks-investor-gold-rush/">Shiba Memu nears $1M presale as trailblazing AI integration sparks investor gold rush</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Shiba Memu sparks gold rush for crypto investors with trailblazing AI protocol</li>
<li dir="ltr">SHMU presale, uniquely tailored to investor interests, is close to hitting $1 million with over $954k raised so far.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The Shiba Memu platform targets becoming the superpower of meme coin marketing.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news"><u>Shiba Memu</u></a> is the latest meme coin craze in the vast cryptocurrency sphere. But unlike the rival coins that play on the original meme dog theme over and over again, Shiba Memu is looking to ride an innovative strategy powered by artificial intelligence (AI) to change the game.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The token is currently in presale and is more of a gold rush for investors as the raised token sale amount edges closer to a $1 million just days into the 8-week offering. As seen on their <a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">presale page</a>, investors have so far allocated over $954k to the project.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Here we look at what Shiba Memu brings to the meme coin battleground and why investors think it could be a winning bet.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">A first in crypto meme and AI</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The question of what happens to crypto next is no longer a vague one, thanks to a global recognition that the industry is here to stay. While meme coins like Shiba Inu and Pepe have exploded and helped create the next crypto millionaires, none commands as much hype and positivity as does Shiba Memu (SHMU).</p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/ai/">AI</a> is at the center of this outlook for the new token, and as we shall shortly see, could be the differentiator that sends SHMU to the top of the meme list.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Shiba Memu?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu is a meme coin project that integrates the revolutionary technology behind AI. By leveraging the best of machine learning and NLP, the project seeks to evolve into a marketing powerhouse that will focus on bringing value to the SHMU ecosystem.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The project will learn and constantly re-imagine itself with the help of AI capabilities, incorporating all possible marketing strategies that put it ahead of competition and beneficial to SHMU token holders.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to the team, AI will make Shiba Memu a genius marketer, capable of extracting juices from a 24/7 presence across social media and other online platforms.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Compared to <a href="https://coinjournal.net/dogecoin/">Dogecoin</a>, Pepe, and the other so-called Doge killers, Shiba Memu stands out for one thing: the ability to self-market and not rely on human-driven hype to gain traction. It is being designed as the robot meme dog that crypto investors are showing a lot of confidence in.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The SHMU presale is live <a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">here</a>.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What else is unique about Shiba Memu?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The presale offers a unique approach to SHMU pricing. A built-in system allows the price of the token to increase automatically each day at 6 pm GMT. Like an excited Shiba Inu pup, SHMU will spike at this set interval for 8 weeks.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The project will provide access to all the key data on an AI dashboard, with SHMU holders having an opportunity not just to see how AI is growing their visibility but also participate in this growth by sharing feedback and proposals. One earning opportunity will be in getting rewarded with SHMU if the system adopts your proposal.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Is this a good time to buy Shiba Memu?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu is still under development and will have to deliver a working product for its AI dashboard to gain traction. This is the bare minimum if the project has to follow up the success of the presale stage with even more penetration in what could be a crowded AI-powered crypto field. As an investment, it would pay to know that market risks abound.</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, with the industry in upbeat mood amid growth across altcoins and AI a big bet even in mainstream tech companies, there could be no other best opportunity to buy SHMU low.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Currently at $0.01405, the next price jump will see it hit $0.014275 and continue on this trajectory until the token&rsquo;s presale value eventually hits $0.0244. This is when Shiba Memu will look to explode as those who miss out on the presale get to buy it across exchanges.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Adding SHMU to an altcoin portfolio today might therefore be both an exposure to what&rsquo;s shaping up to be a huge prospect.</p>
<p>Do you want to know more about this AI-powered crypto protocol? Visit <a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">ShibaMemu.com</a>.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memu-nears-1m-presale-as-trailblazing-ai-integration-sparks-investor-gold-rush/">Shiba Memu nears $1M presale as trailblazing AI integration sparks investor gold rush</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memu-nears-1m-presale-as-trailblazing-ai-integration-sparks-investor-gold-rush/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Judge orders Ripple, SEC to agree to possible settlement dates</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/judge-orders-ripple-sec-to-agree-to-possible-settlement-dates/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/judge-orders-ripple-sec-to-agree-to-possible-settlement-dates/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 21:35:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Policy and Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple Labs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/judge-orders-ripple-sec-to-agree-to-possible-settlement-dates/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>US Judge Analisa Torres referred Ripple vs. SEC case to Magistrate Judge Sarah Netburn. Last week&#8217;s ruling was that XRP was not a security. The Ripple vs. SEC case continues but Judge Netburn has suggested both Ripple and SEC can agree to possible settlement conference dates if they believe it to be &#8220;productive&#8221; at this [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/judge-orders-ripple-sec-to-agree-to-possible-settlement-dates/">Judge orders Ripple, SEC to agree to possible settlement dates</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">US Judge Analisa Torres referred Ripple vs. SEC case to Magistrate Judge Sarah Netburn.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Last week&rsquo;s ruling was that XRP was not a security.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The Ripple vs. SEC case continues but Judge Netburn has suggested both Ripple and SEC can agree to possible settlement conference dates if they believe it to be &ldquo;productive&rdquo; at this stage.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">The latest <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/ripple/">Ripple news</a> is that US Magistrate Judge Sarah Netburn has ordered both Ripple and the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) to agree on possible dates for a settlement conference.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The order came not long after Judge Analisa Torres of the US District Court for the Southern District of New York referred the next phase of the Ripple vs. SEC court battle to Judge Netburn.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to a court document filed on July 17, Judge Netburn, who will now preside over the General Pretrial, has recommended that the parties come to this agreement 6-8 weeks beforehand, referencing the court&rsquo;s busy schedule. &nbsp;As noted in the judge&rsquo;s order, the parties should agree to three mutually convenient dates.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Will SEC and Ripple want to settle?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The pretrial phase includes aspects of the case around &ldquo;<em>scheduling, discovery and non-dispositive pretrial motions</em>.&rdquo; It is also likely the stage where the parties would want to settle. While the anticipation is that the SEC might want Ripple to settle, the coming days could make it clear whether any of the two sides view this as a route to take.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Fox Business journalist Eleanor Terrett shared the outlook on Twitter:</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">&#128680;To be clear: Judge Netburn is suggesting that both sides agree on some possible dates for a settlement meeting, *IF* "they believe it to be productive at this time." </p>
<p>This doesn't mean we'll see a settlement in 6-8 weeks. It means that if they do decide on a date, it will have&hellip; <a href="https://t.co/3bxqCGLyPr">https://t.co/3bxqCGLyPr</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Eleanor Terrett (@EleanorTerrett) <a href="https://twitter.com/EleanorTerrett/status/1681038538316423168?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 17, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">Last week, Judge Torres effectively declared XRP not a security and sparked a massive rally for the token and the broader crypto market.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Even though the outcome of the rest of the case is anybody&rsquo;s guess, the crypto industry believes Ripple&rsquo;s partial victory provided a watershed moment that could translate into the much needed regulatory clarity.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/judge-orders-ripple-sec-to-agree-to-possible-settlement-dates/">Judge orders Ripple, SEC to agree to possible settlement dates</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/judge-orders-ripple-sec-to-agree-to-possible-settlement-dates/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>MATIC, LINK, AAVE among $59M worth of altcoins moved by Celsius</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/matic-link-aave-among-59m-worth-of-altcoins-moved-by-celsius/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/matic-link-aave-among-59m-worth-of-altcoins-moved-by-celsius/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 17:11:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CEL]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Celsius]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/matic-link-aave-among-59m-worth-of-altcoins-moved-by-celsius/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Celsius has moved over $59 million of altcoins to FalconX ahead of possible liquidation. The crypto lender plans to convert the tokens to BTC or ETH. Celsius&#8217;s largest altcoin holding is its native CEL token, currently worth over $106 million. Celsius Network moved millions of dollars&#8217; worth of&#160;altcoins on Monday, among them&#160;Polygon (MATIC), Chainlink (LINK) [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/matic-link-aave-among-59m-worth-of-altcoins-moved-by-celsius/">MATIC, LINK, AAVE among $59M worth of altcoins moved by Celsius</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Celsius has moved over $59 million of altcoins to FalconX ahead of possible liquidation.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The crypto lender plans to convert the tokens to BTC or ETH.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Celsius&rsquo;s largest altcoin holding is its native CEL token, currently worth over $106 million.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Celsius Network moved millions of dollars&rsquo; worth of&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/altcoins/"><u>altcoins</u></a> on Monday, among them&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/polygon/"><u>Polygon (MATIC)</u></a>, Chainlink (LINK) and Aave (AAVE).</p>
<p dir="ltr">As CoinJournal <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/court-allows-celsius-to-sell-altcoins-for-btc-eth-starting-july-1/">reported</a> in June, the US bankruptcy court recently allowed <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/celsius/"><u>Celsius</u></a> to proceed with plans to liquidate multiple coins and tokens beginning July 1, 2023.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The crypto lender had indicated it would be converting these into Bitcoin (BTC) and Ether (ETH) as part of the preparation towards reimbursing customers impacted by the crypto company&rsquo;s bankruptcy filing in July 2022.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Celsius moves Polygon, Chainlink and Aave tokens to FalconX</h2>
<p dir="ltr">According to on-data from crypto security platform Arkham Intelligence, Celsius deposited $59.4 million worth of various tokens to institutional crypto trading platform FalconX. Per Arkham data, Celsius transferred $13.6 million worth of MATIC, $10.7 million in LINK, and $7.3 million in AAVE to an address controlled by FalconX.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Data Nerd shared details of the transfers:</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">45 minutes ago, <a href="https://twitter.com/CelsiusNetwork?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@CelsiusNetwork</a> began to sell altcoin by depositing to exchange.</p>
<p>So far they have sent:<br>&bull; 1.2M <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24LINK&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$LINK</a> ($8.5M)<br>&bull; 2.8M <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24SNX&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$SNX</a> ($7.8M)<br>&bull; 12.5K <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24BNB&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$BNB</a> ($3M)<br>and more</p>
<p>They still have $65M in alt left (excluding <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24BTC&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$BTC</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24ETH&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$ETH</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24CEL&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$CEL</a> and stablecoin) per <a href="https://twitter.com/ArkhamIntel?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@ArkhamIntel</a>. <a href="https://t.co/cy5lEr123Z">pic.twitter.com/cy5lEr123Z</a></p>
<p>&mdash; The Data Nerd (@OnchainDataNerd) <a href="https://twitter.com/OnchainDataNerd/status/1680801238760443904?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 17, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">The transactions followed earlier transfers involving $8.5 million worth of LINK, $7.8 million of SNX (a Synthetix native token) and $3 million in BNB token. Other tokens sent to the FalconX wallet address include 0x Protocol (ZRX), 1inch (1INCH) FTX Token (FTT) and Tether Gold (XAUT).</p>
<p dir="ltr">Blockchain sleuth Lookonchain also<a href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1680793627034013696" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">&nbsp;<u>highlighted</u></a> that FalconX had started depositing the received tokens onto Binance &ndash; suggesting the sale was on.</p>
<p dir="ltr">After these transfers, Dune Analytics data&nbsp;<a href="https://dune.com/21co/celsius-addresses" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>shows</u></a> the Celsius portfolio still holds over $106 million worth of its native token CEL, $47 million in other altcoins (including $16.5 million in MATIC and $12.7 million in AAVE) and over $29 million in stablecoins ($24 million in USDC and $2 million in USDT).</p>
<p dir="ltr">While Celsius moves ahead with plans to convert the altcoins into BTC or ETH, blockchain firm Kaiko recently&nbsp;<a href="https://research.kaiko.com/insights/celsius-liquidations-could-pressure-altcoin-markets" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>noted</u></a> that the Celsius team might find it difficult to liquidate a number of tokens due to their illiquidity. One of these is CEL, which has next to zero liquidity.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Elsewhere, analysts at Kaiko say the potential sell-off pressure from the liquidations could impact downward pressure on some of the tokens.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/matic-link-aave-among-59m-worth-of-altcoins-moved-by-celsius/">MATIC, LINK, AAVE among $59M worth of altcoins moved by Celsius</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/matic-link-aave-among-59m-worth-of-altcoins-moved-by-celsius/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>FSB publishes recommendations for global crypto framework</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/fsb-publishes-recommendations-for-global-crypto-framework/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/fsb-publishes-recommendations-for-global-crypto-framework/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 15:46:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Policy and Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/fsb-publishes-recommendations-for-global-crypto-framework/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The FSB recommends that authorities ensure adequate disclosures from crypto asset issuers and providers. Segregation of funds to protect clients and measures to ensure no conflict of interest are also highlighted. The watchdog also recommends global rules for stablecoins be adopted. The Financial Stability Board (FSB) said in its latest crypto asset report that the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/fsb-publishes-recommendations-for-global-crypto-framework/">FSB publishes recommendations for global crypto framework</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">The FSB recommends that authorities ensure adequate disclosures from crypto asset issuers and providers.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Segregation of funds to protect clients and measures to ensure no conflict of interest are also highlighted.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The watchdog also recommends global rules for stablecoins be adopted.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">The Financial Stability Board (FSB) said in its latest crypto asset report that the sector needs to see more disclosures on the part of providers and broader cooperation from regulators across the globe.</p>
<p dir="ltr">FSB, tasked by the G20 to come up with a comprehensive framework for <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/crypto-regulation/">crypto regulation</a>, has published two sets of recommendations. The first set relates to the global approach to crypto regulation, including the supervision and oversight of digital asset activities and markets.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Meanwhile, the second set of recommendations focuses on global stablecoin regulation.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>Our global regulatory framework for crypto-asset activities seeks to ensure that crypto assets and global stablecoins are subject to robust regulation and supervision and do not pose risks to financial stability</em>,&rdquo; the organisation <a href="https://twitter.com/FinStbBoard/status/1680894888806690819" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">said</a>.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">FSB recommendations include disclosures, segregation of funds</h2>
<p dir="ltr">A<a href="https://www.fsb.org/2023/07/fsb-finalises-global-regulatory-framework-for-crypto-asset-activities/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">&nbsp;<u>press release</u></a> the organisation published on Monday, July 17, highlighted the two documents, noting that &ldquo;<em>the final recommendations draw on the implementation experiences of jurisdictions and build on the principles &ndash; &lsquo;same activity, same risk, same regulation&rsquo;; high-level and flexible; and technology neutral &ndash; that informed the consultative framework.</em>&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The framework comes after a tumultuous year for crypto going back to summer of 2022, and the FSB says it strengthened the recommendations with the events in mind. Among these are the dramatic collapse of TerraUSD and the implosion of cryptocurrency exchange FTX.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As a result, three of the key areas with greater focus are safeguarding of client assets, addressing concerns around conflicts of interest and strengthening of cross-border cooperation among regulators.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In total, the watchdog has outlined nine key recommendations for the global framework for regulation of crypto asset activities and markets and 10 for the regulation and oversight of stablecoins. One of the recommendations on regulation of crypto asset activities focuses on disclosures and FSB stated:</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>Authorities should require that crypto-asset issuers and service providers disclose to users and relevant stakeholders comprehensive, clear and transparent information regarding their governance framework, operations, risk profiles and financial conditions, as well as the products they provide and activities they conduct</em>.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">In the press release, FSB noted that the final recommendations in the two documents incorporated the lessons picked from events within the crypto market over the past year. They also include feedback collated during the public consultation.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The European Union and the UK are among jurisdictions to pursue comprehensive regulation for crypto asset activities and stablecoins. The EU&rsquo;s Markets in Crypto-Assets (MiCA) regulation is expected to take effect in 2024, while UK&rsquo;s Financial Services and Markets Acts received the royal assent in June following approval by parliament.&nbsp;</p>
<p>As <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/uk-could-roll-out-crypto-regulation-within-a-year-says-senior-minister/"><u>reported</u></a> in April, the UK could deploy its crypto laws by early 2024 as it looks to become a crypto hub.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/fsb-publishes-recommendations-for-global-crypto-framework/">FSB publishes recommendations for global crypto framework</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/fsb-publishes-recommendations-for-global-crypto-framework/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
