<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 20:37:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Helium&#8217;s migration to Solana sends IOT token price through the roof</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/heliums-migration-to-solana-sends-iot-token-price-through-the-roof/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/heliums-migration-to-solana-sends-iot-token-price-through-the-roof/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 20:37:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/heliums-migration-to-solana-sends-iot-token-price-through-the-roof/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Helium successfully migrated to Solana Network last week. More than six billion IOT tokens have been minted since Helium migrated to Solana. IOT Token surged by 370 earlier today to hit a daily high of $0.003927. Helium IOT (IOT) token surprised a majority of crypto investors today after surging by more than 370%. Despite a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/heliums-migration-to-solana-sends-iot-token-price-through-the-roof/">Helium&#8217;s migration to Solana sends IOT token price through the roof</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul class="decimal_type">
<li>Helium successfully migrated to Solana Network last week.</li>
<li>More than six billion IOT tokens have been minted since Helium migrated to Solana.</li>
<li>IOT Token surged by 370 earlier today to hit a daily high of $0.003927.</li>
</ul>
<p>Helium IOT (IOT) token surprised a majority of crypto investors today after surging by more than 370%. Despite a slight retracement, the token was still green trading at $0.00206, up 33.59% at press time.</p>
<p>Today&rsquo;s IOT token price surge is attributed to last week&rsquo;s <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/helium-price-rising-after-confirmation-of-migration-to-solana-in-march/">successful Helium migration to Solana</a> Network which has resulted in more than six billion IOT to be minted.</p>
<h2>Protocol token of Helium&rsquo;s internet-of-things network</h2>
<p>Most are conversant with Helium&rsquo;s native token, <a href="https://coinjournal.net/helium/">HNT</a>, which has also been performing quite well over the past few days after the migration.</p>
<p>Helium has another token, the Helium IOT, which is the protocol token of Helium&rsquo;s internet-of-things network. The Helium IOT is mined from Helium&rsquo;s hotspots, which is the hardware infrastructure behind the IOT network.</p>
<p>Helium IOT is backed by the HNT token and can always be converted to HNT, with the redemption rate being algorithmically set by its treasury swap smart contract.</p>
<p>According to <a href="https://explorer.solana.com/address/iotEVVZLEywoTn1QdwNPddxPWszn3zFhEot3MfL9fns">data from Solana&rsquo;s block explorer</a>, there are about six billion IOT tokens in circulation supply out of the maximum supply of 200 billion tokens.</p>
<p>The IOT token also received another boost after Solana-based decentralized-finance (DeFi) protocol Kamino Finance said it had opened two Helium vaults to allow investors to stake their IOT and HNT tokens for a yield.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/heliums-migration-to-solana-sends-iot-token-price-through-the-roof/">Helium&#8217;s migration to Solana sends IOT token price through the roof</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/heliums-migration-to-solana-sends-iot-token-price-through-the-roof/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>CertiK and zkSync Era plan to compensate Merlin hack victims</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/certik-and-zksync-era-plan-to-compensate-merlin-hack-victims/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 19:49:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/certik-and-zksync-era-plan-to-compensate-merlin-hack-victims/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Merlin is an Ethereum-based decentralized exchange (DEX) which uses zero-knowledge sync (zkSync). The DEX has lost more than $1.8 million in a liquidity pool hack. The hack took place barely hours after smart contract security firm CertiK audited the DEX&#8217;s code. Ethereum-based decentralized exchange (DEX) Merlin woke up to bad news on Wednesday morning after [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/certik-and-zksync-era-plan-to-compensate-merlin-hack-victims/">CertiK and zkSync Era plan to compensate Merlin hack victims</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul class="decimal_type">
<li>Merlin is an Ethereum-based decentralized exchange (DEX) which uses zero-knowledge sync (zkSync).</li>
<li>The DEX has lost more than $1.8 million in a liquidity pool hack.</li>
<li>The hack took place barely hours after smart contract security firm CertiK audited the DEX&rsquo;s code.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/what-is-ethereum/">Ethereum</a>-based decentralized exchange (DEX) Merlin woke up to bad news on Wednesday morning after a hacker(s) drained the DEX $1.8 million in a liquidity pool hack. The hack happened during a public sale of Merlin&rsquo;s native token MAGE.</p>
<p>The hacker(s) stole several cryptocurrency assets including Ethereum (ETH), USD Coin (USDC), and other illiquid tokens.</p>
<h2>CertiK had audited Merlin&rsquo;s code</h2>
<p>A few hours after the hack, security firm CertiK <a href="https://twitter.com/CertiK/status/1651088669187473408?s=20">tweeted</a> saying that it was investigating the incident to understand its impact on the community. It also said that its initial findings suggest that it could have resulted from an issue with a private key management meaning it was hack and not an exploit as widely thought.</p>
<p>CertiK conducted an <a href="https://skynet.certik.com/projects/merlin-dex">audit of Merlin&rsquo;s code</a> on April 24, 2023, and recommended that Merlin improves its &ldquo;centralized roles to the decentralized mechanism like multi-signature wallets to enhance security practices.&rdquo; It also asked Merlin to implement a timelock feature with a latency of at least 48 hours to avoid a single point of key management.</p>
<p>CertiK also promised to collaborate with appropriate authorities in case anything came up.</p>
<h2>CertiK and zkSync Era to compensate lost assets</h2>
<p>While urging the hacker, who CertiK believes is a rogue developer, to return 80% of the stolen funds, the security firm offered a 20% white hat bounty to the hacker.</p>
<p>In a statement to a renowned media outlet on April 26, CertiK reiterated it is investigating the exit scam and has also enlisted the remaining Merlin team to initiate the compensation plan. The firm <a href="https://twitter.com/CertiK/status/1651276441949028373?s=20">said</a>:</p>
<p><em>&ldquo;CertiK is exploring a community compensation plan to cover the ~$2M of user funds lost in the Merlin DEX rug pull. Initial investigations indicate that the rogue developers are based in Europe, and we are working with law enforcement to track them down.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p>CertiK also noted that private key privileges are &ldquo;committed to assisting impacted users&rdquo; notwithstanding that they are outside the scope of a smart contract audit.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/certik-and-zksync-era-plan-to-compensate-merlin-hack-victims/">CertiK and zkSync Era plan to compensate Merlin hack victims</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>SOL price surging after Solana ChatGPT plugin unveiled</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/sol-price-surging-after-solana-chatgpt-plugin-unveiled/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 19:05:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/sol-price-surging-after-solana-chatgpt-plugin-unveiled/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Solana users will soon be able to interact with the network through a ChatGPT plugin. Users can use the plugin to check wallet balances, transfer Solana-native tokens, and buy NFTs. Developers are also encouraged to test using the plugin to retrieve on-chain data. At press time, SOL price was up 7.33% 34 hours after Solana [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sol-price-surging-after-solana-chatgpt-plugin-unveiled/">SOL price surging after Solana ChatGPT plugin unveiled</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul class="decimal_type">
<li>Solana users will soon be able to interact with the network through a ChatGPT plugin.</li>
<li>Users can use the plugin to check wallet balances, transfer Solana-native tokens, and buy NFTs.</li>
<li>Developers are also encouraged to test using the plugin to retrieve on-chain data.</li>
</ul>
<p>At press time, <a href="https://coinjournal.net/solana/">SOL price</a> was up 7.33% 34 hours after Solana announced through a tweet that &ldquo;Solana Labs has created an open-source reference implementation for a ChatGPT plugin that lets users interact with the @solana network directly from ChatGPT.&rdquo;</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">(1/2) Solana Labs has created an open-source reference implementation for a ChatGPT plugin that lets users interact with the <a href="https://twitter.com/solana?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@solana</a> network directly from ChatGPT.</p>
<p>Users will be able to check wallet balances, transfer tokens, and purchase NFTs once ChatGPT plugins are available. <a href="https://t.co/08z1IX76zJ">pic.twitter.com/08z1IX76zJ</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Solana Labs (@solanalabs) <a href="https://twitter.com/solanalabs/status/1650955017585606656?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">April 25, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The news comes two weeks after Solana unveiled yet another achievement, the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/solanas-crypto-first-saga-android-phone-coming-soon/">crypto-first &lsquo;Saga&rsquo; android phone</a>, which will be available for customers to purchase from May 8. Solana Network has seen increased activity over the recent past causing the price of its native token <a href="https://www.coinlore.com/coin/solana">SOL to rise by more than 11% in the last 30 days</a>.</p>
<h2>Solana ChatGPT plugin use</h2>
<p>The open-source reference implementation for a ChatGPT plugin marks Solana&rsquo;s entry into the world of artificial intelligence (AI). Announcing the plugin, Solana Labs noted that it would allow users to interact with the Solana network directly from OpenAI&rsquo;s ChatGPT.</p>
<p>Since its launch in November 2022, ChatGPT has quickly attracted global popularity mainly because of its AI-powered chatbot, which generates sophisticated responses to any request. In the wake of the ChatGPT, several other companies have started leveraging AI technology including players in the crypto sector as they seek to enhance user experience.</p>
<p>Besides allowing users to check wallet balances, transfer Solana-native tokens, and buy non-fungible tokens (NFTs), the ChatGPT plugin will also allow developers to build AI-powered applications on the Solana network.</p>
<h2>Grants to AI developers</h2>
<p>Solana Foundation also announced that it will be allocating grants to its ecosystem teams building AI tools on the Solana blockchain.</p>
<p>According to the foundation, the teams or individuals will be able to seek from $5, 000 to $25,000 grants from a $1 million fund.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sol-price-surging-after-solana-chatgpt-plugin-unveiled/">SOL price surging after Solana ChatGPT plugin unveiled</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase stock outlook: H.C. Wainwright analyst sees upside to $75</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-stock-outlook-analyst-upside-75/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wajeeh Khan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 18:01:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=137823</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>H.C. Wainwright analyst initiates Coinbase with a &#8220;buy&#8221; rating. Mike Colonnese explained his bullish view in a research note. Coinbase stock has lost about 35% in just over a month. A 35% pullback in Coinbase Global Inc over the past month is &#8220;overdone&#8221; and a recovery is coming soon, says Mike Colonnese &#8211; an H.C. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-stock-outlook-analyst-upside-75/">Coinbase stock outlook: H.C. Wainwright analyst sees upside to $75</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>H.C. Wainwright analyst initiates Coinbase with a &ldquo;buy&rdquo; rating.</li>
<li>Mike Colonnese explained his bullish view in a research note.</li>
<li>Coinbase stock has lost about 35% in just over a month.</li>
</ul>
<p>A 35% pullback in <a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/coinbase/">Coinbase Global Inc</a> over the past month is &ldquo;overdone&rdquo; and a recovery is coming soon, says Mike Colonnese &ndash; an H.C. Wainwright analyst.</p>
<h2>Buy Coinbase stock for a 35% return</h2>
<p>On Wednesday, Colonnese recommended that investors buy shares of the world&rsquo;s second-largest and one of the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/compare/best-cryptocurrency-exchanges/">best cryptocurrency exchange</a> as they had upside to $75 &ndash; a 35% premium on its current price.</p>
<p>The analyst is bullish on Coinbase stock for one simple reason that rewards currently outweigh the risks.</p>
<blockquote><p>Coinbase is uniquely positioned to benefit from large and rapidly growing crypto economy given its trusted brand, easy to use products, and focus on compliance and regulation.</p></blockquote>
<p>Coinbase has a footprint in 100 countries and is serving about 8.3 million active users, which, Colonnese wrote, is scale enough for it to expand its market share this year.</p>
<h2>Why else is he bullish on Coinbase stock?</h2>
<p>Coinbase is expected to report its Q1 results next week. <a href="https://www.nasdaq.com/market-activity/stocks/coin/earnings" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Consensus</a> is for it to lose $1.36 a share this quarter versus $1.98 per share a year ago.</p>
<p>The H.C. Wainwright analyst is convinced that the crypto winter is over and the subsequent increase in trading volume will be a catalyst for the company&rsquo;s operating performance. His <a href="https://hcwco.bluematrix.com/sellside/EmailDocViewer?encrypt=2b411f55-2386-4e7f-8f86-4cf9037b824d&amp;mime=pdf&amp;co=Hcwco&amp;id=jayson.derrick@investoogroup.com&amp;source=mail" target="_blank" rel="noopener">research note</a> added:</p>
<blockquote><p>COIN is a scarce asset, as the only publicly listed crypto native company in the U.S. with a market cap &gt;$10B, which means competition for investor capital is extremely limited.</p></blockquote>
<p>Earlier this week, Coinbase sued the <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/04/24/coinbase-sues-sec-after-months-of-silence-from-federal-regulator.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Securities and Exchange Commission</a> after waiting for months to get an answer on its July 2022 petition. Regulatory clarity in the future will also help drive the Coinbase stock up, Colonnese concluded.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-stock-outlook-analyst-upside-75/">Coinbase stock outlook: H.C. Wainwright analyst sees upside to $75</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>BitClout 2.0 Announced as Next Stock Market for People</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitclout-2-0-announced-as-next-stock-market-for-people/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitclout-2-0-announced-as-next-stock-market-for-people/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire &#160;]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 14:50:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=137816</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Los Angeles, USA, April 26th, 2023, Chainwire Today, an exciting announcement was made on decentralized social app Diamond that Bitclout 2.0, the highly-anticipated follow-up to 2021&#8217;s viral sensation that took the crypto world by storm, has been revealed by the infamous @diamondhands. Bitclout 2.0 aims to build upon the success of the original by introducing [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitclout-2-0-announced-as-next-stock-market-for-people/">BitClout 2.0 Announced as Next Stock Market for People</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Los Angeles, USA, April 26th, 2023, Chainwire</strong></p>
<p>Today, <a href="https://diamondapp.com/posts/873df8bb2f8ebf3c79ab3796e420bbd2fe5aeee26cd6f16f6720ad99e9acf5a8" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">an exciting announcement</a> was made on <a href="https://deso.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">decentralized social</a> app <a href="https://diamondapp.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Diamond</a> that Bitclout 2.0, the highly-anticipated follow-up to 2021&rsquo;s viral sensation that took the crypto world by storm, has been revealed by the infamous <a href="https://diamondapp.com/u/diamondhands?feedTab=Hot" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">@diamondhands</a>.</p>
<p>Bitclout 2.0 aims to build upon the success of the original by introducing several new products and features, effectively turning reputation into an asset class on par with what NFTs are today.</p>
<p>BitClout 2.0 is expected to launch with a sophisticated airdrop after the DeSo blockchain&rsquo;s transition to its new <a href="https://revolution.deso.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Revolution Proof of Stake</a> consensus mechanism is complete. The white paper for BitClout 2.0 can be accessed at <a href="https://bitclout2.deso.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">bitclout2.deso.com</a>, and the password can be obtained by sending a DM to <a href="https://diamondapp.com/u/bitclout" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">@bitclout</a> on any DeSo app like <a href="https://diamondapp.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Diamond</a> or <a href="https://chat.deso.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">DeSo Chat Protocol</a>.</p>
<h2>Bootstrapping A Stock Market for People</h2>
<p>One of the most groundbreaking new products BitClout 2.0 introduces is Creator Coins V2, a reimagined version of the original trading product that sparked thousands of celebrities and influencers to join the platform.</p>
<p>Creator Coins are a new type of asset class introduced by <a href="https://docs.bitclout.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">BitClout 1.0</a> that are tied to the reputation of an individual rather than to a company or commodity, and Creator Coins allow creators, celebrities, influencers, and everyday users to monetize their work in ways never before possible in web2.</p>
<p>Since Creator Coins track the reputation of an individual, if Elon Musk successfully lands the first person on Mars or alternatively go bankrupt, it will affect the price of his Creator Coin.</p>
<p>Creator Coins V2 are fully backward compatible with V1, allowing users to transfer over seamlessly, and will be tradeable on DeSo DEX, the world&rsquo;s fastest on-chain order-book exchange (showcased by <a href="https://openfund.com/trade" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Openfund</a>).</p>
<p>Trading activity on BitClout 2.0 will be incentivized with a new $BITCLOUT token, allowing people to accrue fees through Creator Coin V2 trading activity.</p>
<p>Bitclout 2.0 will reward early adopters through a sophisticated and viral airdrop scheme that takes inspiration from both BitClout 1.0 and from NFT marketplace <a href="https://blur.io" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Blur</a>. BitClout 2.0&rsquo;s airdrop mechanics will not only drive trading liquidity but also &ldquo;content liquidity&rdquo; by compensating the most active creators on the platform.</p>
<p>Creators who post regularly and engage the community will also earn $BITCLOUT tokens through airdrops, adding an innovative new incentive structure for creators never seen on other platforms.</p>
<p>People interested in participating in the $BITCLOUT airdrop can start familiarizing themselves with DeSo apps like <a href="https://diamondapp.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Diamond</a>, <a href="https://openfund.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Openfund</a>, <a href="https://desofy.app" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Desofy</a>, or <a href="https://desocialworld.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">DeSocialWorld</a>, and many more <a href="https://wallet.deso.com/explore" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">listed on deso.com</a>, before the launch.</p>
<p>BitClout 2.0 will be built on the <a href="https://deso.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Decentralized Social Blockchain</a>. According to the <a href="https://bitclout2.deso.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">BitClout 2.0 white paper</a>, &ldquo;DeSo is the only blockchain that can support the storage and indexing requirements needed for a decentralized social platform like BitClout 2.0.&rdquo; This is thanks to DeSo&rsquo;s vastly-superior content storage costs, which make it finally feasible for apps to extend beyond DeFi to storage-intensive social applications, and much more.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" src="https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/111_1682512966mnFz73Wfj9.jpg"></p>
<h2>The History of BitClout</h2>
<p>In March of 2021, a mysterious password-protected link began to go viral.</p>
<p>The link allowed users to access a new app called BitClout, created by the pseudonymous founder known as <a href="https://bitclout.com/u/diamondhands" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">@diamondhands</a>. What started as just <a href="https://docs.bitclout.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">a white paper</a> and an associated demo quickly evolved into an addictive worldwide phenomenon, thanks to BitClout&rsquo;s introduction of a novel new concept known as Creator Coins.</p>
<p>BitClout and its concept of Creator Coins were initially so viral and engaging that the early prototype alone attracted organic signups from hundreds of influencers and celebrities.</p>
<p>It also spawned numerous articles about its burgeoning &ldquo;stock market for people,&rdquo; including a long-form piece in <a href="https://www.newyorker.com/tech/annals-of-technology/the-dark-democratizing-power-of-the-social-media-stock-market" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">the New Yorker</a>.</p>
<h2>The Next Great Decentralized Social Application</h2>
<p><iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/kPPb_S5Ry5E?showinfo=0"></iframe></p>
<p>With the launch of Bitclout 2.0, the true power and capabilities of the <a href="https://deso.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">DeSo Blockchain</a> will be on full display for the world to see.</p>
<p>Already one of the fastest and cheapest layer-1 blockchains on the market, DeSo&rsquo;s move to Proof of Stake is likely to cement DeSo&rsquo;s status as the industry leader for developers wanting to build storage-intensive infinite-state applications.</p>
<p>Once completed, DeSo will inch closer to its final form, &ldquo;The Sovereign Internet&rdquo; featuring a &ldquo;Decentralized Web,&rdquo; enabling developers to deploy censorship-resistant storage-intensive applications at scale from anywhere in the world.</p>
<p>Bitclout 2.0 will likely be the first example of what can be built on DeSo post-Proof of Stake, but it won&rsquo;t be the last.</p>
<p>Currently, other proposals are circulating, including Bitfair, the first crypto-native sports betting app, and Pseudo, the first decentralized identity marketplace.</p>
<p>Learn more about the DeSo roadmap and what&rsquo;s next <a href="https://docs.deso.org/deso-roadmap" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">here.</a></p>
<p>About Deso</p>
<p>DeSo is a new layer-1 blockchain built from the ground up to decentralize social media and scale storage-heavy applications to billions of users. It raised $200 million and is backed by Sequoia, Andreessen Horowitz, Coinbase Ventures, Social Capital, Polychain Capital, Winklevoss Capital, Pantera, and other blue chip funds.</p>
<p><strong>Contact</strong></p>
<p>Arash Ghaemi, ash@deso.org</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitclout-2-0-announced-as-next-stock-market-for-people/">BitClout 2.0 Announced as Next Stock Market for People</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitclout-2-0-announced-as-next-stock-market-for-people/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Space and Time announces the beta launch of data warehouse</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/space-and-time-announces-the-beta-launch-of-data-warehouse/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/space-and-time-announces-the-beta-launch-of-data-warehouse/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 14:50:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/space-and-time-announces-the-beta-launch-of-data-warehouse/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways Space and Time&#8217;s beta version of data warehouse is now live. The platform seeks to allow developers to connect verifiable data and computation to applications, smart contracts and large language models. Space and Time come pre-loaded with blockchain data indexed from major blockchains. Data warehouse&#8217;s beta version goes live Space and Time, a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/space-and-time-announces-the-beta-launch-of-data-warehouse/">Space and Time announces the beta launch of data warehouse</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Space and Time&rsquo;s beta version of data warehouse is now live.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The platform seeks to allow developers to connect verifiable data and computation to applications, smart contracts and large language models.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Space and Time come pre-loaded with blockchain data indexed from major blockchains.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr">Data warehouse&rsquo;s beta version goes live</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Space and Time, a decentralised data platform, has announced today, April 26th, that the beta version of its data warehouse and developer suite is now live.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In a press release shared with Coinjournal, Space and Time said it allows developers to leverage provable computation against on-chain and off-chain data to power dapps, smart contracts and verifiable AI models.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">AIs are gaining waves in the business world at the moment and the Space and Time data warehouse aims to ensure that AI models are trained on accurate, verifiable, tamperproof data.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Interested developers can sign up through this link:&nbsp;<a href="https://www.spaceandtime.io/access-beta"><u>https://www.spaceandtime.io/access-beta</u></a> to participate in the Space and Time beta version.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Space and Time is a decentralised hybrid (HTAP) data warehouse that powers low-latency transactional queries and scalable analytics in a single cluster. The platform has developed a novel zero-knowledge proof called Proof of SQL that allows developers to prove that both the query and the data are verifiably tamperproof.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Space and Time is pre-loaded with blockchain data</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The team revealed that its solution is pre-loaded with blockchain data indexed from major chains, decoded and provided for free.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Space and Time data warehouse also comes with pre-built APIs for SQL operations, blockchain data, Kafka streaming and security, as well as a Tamperproof Python service for easily extracting, transforming and loading data or running complex computations.</p>
<p dir="ltr">While commenting on this <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">latest cryptocurrency news</a>, Nate Holiday, CEO and Co-founder of Space and Time, said;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;We are thrilled to open the Space and Time data warehouse and suite of data services to developers everywhere. Space and Time is enabling a new era of data verifiability. As smart contracts and AI is increasingly integrated into business processes, Space and Time aims to ensure that they&rsquo;re connected to and trained on verifiable data and computation.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p dir="ltr">In addition to this, Space and Time has a dApp, which provides a user-friendly interface for interacting with on-chain and off-chain data.</p>
<p dir="ltr">John Kanan, Senior Partner at Bain &amp; Company, said;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;AI is shaping the future of business operations in an unprecedented way. As we move further into the age of AI, enterprises need to develop a focused strategy for leveraging its benefits. The assurance that AI is being trained on verifiable data and computation should instill confidence in enterprises seeking to incorporate it into critical business processes.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p dir="ltr">Space and Time said it would be showcasing its newly launched data warehouse at this year&rsquo;s Consensus conference in a live demo with Shrapnel, the highly anticipated blockchain-enabled AAA first-person shooter game.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Space and Time is a Web3-native decentralized data warehouse that joins tamperproof on-chain and off-chain data to deliver enterprise use cases to smart contracts.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/space-and-time-announces-the-beta-launch-of-data-warehouse/">Space and Time announces the beta launch of data warehouse</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/space-and-time-announces-the-beta-launch-of-data-warehouse/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Investment Property Enthusiasts Discover AltSignals: Diversifying Portfolios with ASI Token Amid Real Estate Market Fluctuations.</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/investment-property-enthusiasts-discover-altsignals-diversifying-portfolios-with-asi-token-amid-real-estate-market-fluctuations/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/investment-property-enthusiasts-discover-altsignals-diversifying-portfolios-with-asi-token-amid-real-estate-market-fluctuations/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[John Butterworth]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 14:07:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/investment-property-enthusiasts-discover-altsignals-diversifying-portfolios-with-asi-token-amid-real-estate-market-fluctuations/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When uncertainty hits the financial sector, the housing market is rarely far behind, causing nervousness among investment property enthusiasts. As the global banking crisis threatens to deepen, investment property experts are beginning to look to diversify their portfolios to protect their money from market fluctuations in real estate. One token that looks like a perfect [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/investment-property-enthusiasts-discover-altsignals-diversifying-portfolios-with-asi-token-amid-real-estate-market-fluctuations/">Investment Property Enthusiasts Discover AltSignals: Diversifying Portfolios with ASI Token Amid Real Estate Market Fluctuations.</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">When uncertainty hits the financial sector, the housing market is rarely far behind, causing nervousness among investment property enthusiasts. As the global banking crisis threatens to deepen, investment property experts are beginning to look to diversify their portfolios to protect their money from market fluctuations in real estate.</p>
<p dir="ltr">One token that looks like a perfect fit for investors seeking to move funds away from the property market is AltSignals&rsquo; new ASI coin which has just launched its presale event. Here&rsquo;s why ASI could record huge gains this year while investment property fans move away from the real estate market.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>AltSignals: New native ASI token has a bright future</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://token.altsignals.io/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal_investmentopportunity&amp;utm_content=as_presale%20_1&amp;utm_id=173" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>AltSignals</u></a> launched its online trading platform in 2017 and has quickly grown into one of the most trusted suppliers of high-quality trading signals. Over the past five years, the AltSignals community has grown to more than 50,000 members, of which 1,400 are VIP members, all of whom rely on the accurate and highly-informed trading signals powered by AltSignals&rsquo; pioneering AltAlgo&trade; trading indicator tool.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The release of the ASI token is designed to support the implementation of a new AI-powered trading stack called ActualizeAI, which will augment the existing AltAlgo&trade; outputs with cutting-edge AI capability. This innovation is designed to turbocharge AltSignals&rsquo; outputs, taking them to unprecedented accuracy and moving the platform to the forefront of the AI/blockchain revolution.</p>
<p dir="ltr">News of the ASI ICO has captured the imagination of AltSignals&rsquo; large existing community alongside interested onlookers in the investment community. Some interested parties could be investment property enthusiasts looking to protect their funds as real estate markets record growing uncertainty.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>What is AltSignals?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals is among the most trusted providers of successful and accurate trading signals. This is illustrated by the platform gaining an average 4.9/5 rating on Trustpilot, courtesy of almost 500 positive reviews, and a success rate on calling Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH) trades of more than 70%.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Alongside daily crypto trades, AltSignals provides valuable signals on various other trades, including Forex, CFD, traditional share trades, and Binance futures. And in 19 out of 32 months, Binance Futures holders made 10x gains on their portfolio.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This success has been driven by AltAlgo&trade; and is set to reach new levels with the development of the ActualizeAI trading stack, which will apply the best AI technologies to outputs, driving improvements in accuracy and helping the community maximize the profitability of their decision-making.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Machine learning will soon enable rules-based logic to be applied to outputs, which benefit from regressive pattern recognition that understands how markets operate. This learning cycle is quickened by natural learning processing (NLP) before predictive modeling applies historical data trends. These trends, which will improve as more data is available over time, will work with reinforcement learning to allow ActualizeAI to provide accurate predictions and balance the risk/reward ratio on all trades.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>How will ASI token work?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">The release of the ASI token is timed to coincide with the development and testing of ActualizeAI while simultaneously underpinning AltSignals&rsquo; entire ecosystem. Coin holders will gain immediate access to ActualizeAI&rsquo;s trading stack once it&rsquo;s released, with access managed on two different levels. Token holders with more than 50,000 coins will be granted lifetime membership, while those with fewer tokens gain access for one year.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In addition, ASI coin holders will unlock several other perks and benefits through membership in the exclusive AI Members Club. For example, club membership unlocks entry into regular online trading tournaments and access to some of the most exciting and potentially lucrative early access private and presale opportunities to support new crypto projects.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Finally, ASI will be the medium of exchange on the platform, unlocking access to educational material to support traders of all abilities and expertise on their trading journeys while enabling all transactions on the platform.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>How high can ASI reach in 2023?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">The level of utility built into the ASI coin is readily apparent to all interested investors. Yet, ASI will also become a valuable governance token, delivering community-led governance to the platform, through which the members are granted full voting rights to determine the platform&rsquo;s future.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This level of control goes beyond what investment property enthusiasts are accustomed to and presents another compelling reason why ASI attracts such interest among those looking to diversify. With this excitement at the early presale stages, analysts expect ASI to record impressive gains after the coin&rsquo;s IDO, rising rapidly from its final presale price of $0.02274 to quite possibly breach the $0.50 barrier before the end of the year.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>ASI is an excellent diversification for investment property experts</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Holding a diverse investment portfolio is a perfect way for investors to minimize the damage of market fluctuations in one or two sectors. With nervousness growing in the real estate market, investment property experts looking for alternative investment opportunities could be wise looking to be involved in the ASI presale.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Tokens are available during stage 1 for only $0.015. With a rich growth potential for early-stage investors thanks to the exciting narrative of AI technologies, anyone reserving their tokens now could stand to record impressive gains in the short, medium, and long terms.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>You can participate in the ASI&nbsp;</strong><strong>presale&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://token.altsignals.io/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal_investmentopportunity&amp;utm_content=as_presale%20_1&amp;utm_id=173" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong><u>here</u></strong></a><strong>.</strong></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/investment-property-enthusiasts-discover-altsignals-diversifying-portfolios-with-asi-token-amid-real-estate-market-fluctuations/">Investment Property Enthusiasts Discover AltSignals: Diversifying Portfolios with ASI Token Amid Real Estate Market Fluctuations.</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/investment-property-enthusiasts-discover-altsignals-diversifying-portfolios-with-asi-token-amid-real-estate-market-fluctuations/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Metacade Token Listing on Top Crypto Exchanges in May. Here’s What Investors Need to Know.</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-token-listing-on-top-crypto-exchanges-in-may-heres-what-investors-need-to-know/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-token-listing-on-top-crypto-exchanges-in-may-heres-what-investors-need-to-know/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice Davies]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 13:50:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-token-listing-on-top-crypto-exchanges-in-may-heres-what-investors-need-to-know/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As the play-to-earn (P2E) space continues to expand, many are looking to invest in crypto projects with a strong chance of capitalizing on the industry&#8217;s growth. One such project is Metacade, an up-and-comer that recently completed its sell-out presale raising $16.4 million. MCADE investors are now looking forward to the project being listed on top [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-token-listing-on-top-crypto-exchanges-in-may-heres-what-investors-need-to-know/">Metacade Token Listing on Top Crypto Exchanges in May. Here’s What Investors Need to Know.</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">As the play-to-earn (P2E) space continues to expand, many are looking to invest in crypto projects with a strong chance of capitalizing on the industry&rsquo;s growth. One such project is Metacade, an up-and-comer that recently completed its sell-out presale raising $16.4 million. MCADE investors are now looking forward to the project being listed on top crypto exchanges.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In this article, you&rsquo;ll learn what Metacade is, why it&rsquo;s attracted so much investment, and where experts think the MCADE token could end by late 2023. </p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Metacade (MCADE)?</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=53" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade</u></a> is a rising star in the GameFi space, providing an all-in-one community hub for P2E gamers. Its goal is to bring gamers, developers, and crypto enthusiasts together in a vibrant ecosystem, with the platform owned and operated by the community. Metacade offers its users a wide range of features designed to enhance the P2E gaming experience, like sub-forums for discussing individual games, real-time chat, and spaces for reading the hottest GameFi alpha.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">At the heart of Metacade is its native token, MCADE, which will serve as a utility and governance token within the platform. This token enables users to experience Metacade&rsquo;s pay-to-play virtual arcade, vote on Metacade&rsquo;s future, and earn rewards for contributing reviews, tips, and other helpful content to the community.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Other features, like a job board, a decentralized funding scheme known as Metagrants, and regularly held gaming tournaments, have caused considerable buzz amongst the crypto community. The project&rsquo;s $16.4 million presale was a sell-out success, with the MCADE token being listed for sale on Uniswap, soon followed by important listings on <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/metacade/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>CoinMarketCap</u></a>, Bitmart, and <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/metacade/usd" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>CoinGecko</u></a>. Those invested in MCADE are excited about its upcoming listing on major crypto exchange MEXC in May, as well.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What You Need to Know About Metacade (MCADE)</h2>
<p dir="ltr">With Metacade gearing up for listings on top crypto exchanges, it&rsquo;s essential to understand what sets this platform apart from the competition and why it&rsquo;s attracted so much attention from the P2E community.</p>
<p dir="ltr">One of the most significant factors is the <a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=53" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metagrant</u></a> program, a potential game-changer for the P2E industry. The scheme offers funding to game developers earning the most votes from the community for their proposals, with the winning game added to Metacade&rsquo;s virtual arcade. This decentralized approach allows the community to shape the future of P2E gaming directly, creating a grassroots fanbase for new titles and likely attracting thousands of players onto the platform.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade&rsquo;s emphasis on community involvement and engagement makes it stand out in the crowded GameFi space. Metacade intends to give MCADE token holders the right to have their say in the platform&rsquo;s direction through its decentralized autonomous organization (DAO), expected in 2024. Through the DAO and Metagrant program, Metacade ensures that its user base remains actively invested in both the platform&rsquo;s success and the longevity of P2E gaming.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">In addition to its community-driven initiatives, Metacade is committed to helping players boost their P2E income. Not only does this mean offering the hottest GameFi alpha being shared by top players, but also includes a job and gig board. Here, users can find work in the Web3 and gaming industries and participate in casual game testing using Metacade&rsquo;s native testing environment in return for MCADE tokens.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Finally, Metacade&rsquo;s upcoming listings on top crypto exchanges will undoubtedly increase its visibility and accessibility, drawing even more interest from those investing in the lucrative GameFi sector. This increased exposure will likely lead to further growth and adoption, which could boost Metacade&rsquo;s price in the coming weeks.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Metacade (MCADE) Price Prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr">After being listed on Uniswap, analysts have observed strong price stability in the MCADE token, overcoming the usual sell-offs to list currently at $0.023. Considering Metacade&rsquo;s staking pool filled in under five hours, it seems investor confidence is exceptionally high. This has led to bullish Metacade price predictions.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Some estimate that MCADE will easily reach $0.25 by the end of the year, while others think $0.45 is a possible reasonable target. Even more ambitious price predictions see MCADE smashing $0.70 in 2023, putting today&rsquo;s investors up 2943%!</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Don&rsquo;t Miss Out on Metacade&rsquo;s (MCADE) Top Crypto Exchange Listings</h2>
<p dir="ltr">In summary, it&rsquo;s easy to see why the hype surrounding <a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=53" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade&rsquo;s</u></a> listings on top crypto exchanges is increasing. Investing in crypto comes with a significant degree of uncertainty, especially for new projects. However, Metacade has demonstrated itself capable of capturing the intense focus of the investment community with its well-thought-out roadmap and unique set of valuable features.</p>
<p dir="ltr">With a recent partnership with metaverse development company <a href="http://metastudio.pt" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>MetaStudio</u></a> stimulating excitement around Metacade, it&rsquo;s safe to say MCADE is likely to see continued price increases in the near future given the impressive 28% rise as the token listed on Bitmart on 20 April, and with MEXC due next in early May.</p>
<p><strong>You can find out how to buy MCADE&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=53" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong><u>here</u></strong></a><strong>.</strong></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-token-listing-on-top-crypto-exchanges-in-may-heres-what-investors-need-to-know/">Metacade Token Listing on Top Crypto Exchanges in May. Here’s What Investors Need to Know.</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-token-listing-on-top-crypto-exchanges-in-may-heres-what-investors-need-to-know/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>iZUMi Finance price: profit deals dump IZI after KuCoin listing</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/izumi-finance-price-profit-deals-dump-izi-after-kucoin-listing/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 13:41:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[KuCoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/izumi-finance-price-profit-deals-dump-izi-after-kucoin-listing/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>iZUMi Finance (IZI) price dropped over 15% amid massive profit taking. The dump followed the token&#8217;s listing on major crypto exchange KuCoin. But while price could fall below $0.030, the cryptocurrency&#8217;s strong ecosystem growth could see increased IZI demand and aid price uptick down the road. iZUMi Finance (IZI) price fell more than 15% early [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/izumi-finance-price-profit-deals-dump-izi-after-kucoin-listing/">iZUMi Finance price: profit deals dump IZI after KuCoin listing</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">iZUMi Finance (IZI) price dropped over 15% amid massive profit taking.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The dump followed the token&rsquo;s listing on major crypto exchange KuCoin.</li>
<li dir="ltr">But while price could fall below $0.030, the cryptocurrency&rsquo;s strong ecosystem growth could see increased IZI demand and aid price uptick down the road.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">iZUMi Finance (IZI) price fell more than 15% early Wednesday as the cryptocurrency&rsquo;s market defied broader <a href="https://coinjournal.net/price/">crypto prices</a> outlook. IZI traded to lows of $0.032 as sell pressure mounted following the coin&rsquo;s<a href="https://twitter.com/izumi_Finance/status/1650812521572630529" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">&nbsp;<u>listing</u></a> on major crypto currency exchange <a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/kucoin/">KuCoin</a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The dump is likely a &ldquo;sell the news&rdquo; scenario as the price of iZUMi Finance rose exponentially over the past few days. This after KuCoin announced it would list the native token of the multi-chain decentralised finance (<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/defi/">DeFi</a>) protocol.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Even with today&rsquo;s dip, IZI/USD was still trading more than 26% up in the past seven days and over 280% up in the past two weeks.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">iZUMi Finance price: sellers in control for IZI/USD</h2>
<p dir="ltr">While current price outlook suggests sellers might push IZI lower, the cryptocurrency is poised at a horizontal demand zone that has helped bulls for much of April. That suggests the profit taking could give way to new upside momentum.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As for immediate price outlook, IZI/USD is likely to trade lower if bulls fail to keep $0.030. The hourly chart shows the token is trending towards the oversold territory though and could thus be due an upward flip should the $0.02 base hold. Otherwise, a dip to $0.011 could happen.</p>
<div class="fr-img-space-wrap"><span class="fr-img-caption fr-fic fr-dib fr-draggable" style="width: 600px"><span class="fr-img-wrap">
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/03/26/1682516448210-6be28185-0091-4350-9c95-32b161dfb3ab.png" style="width: 600px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="600" height="263"><span class="fr-inner"></span></p>
<p dir="ltr">IZI price on the hourly chart. Source:&nbsp;<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/Z3xL2IRx/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">TradingView</a></p>
<p></p></span>
<p></p></span>
<h2 class="fr-img-space-wrap2">iZUMi Finance long term outlook: network strength key</h2>
</div>
<p dir="ltr">A look at Izumi Finance&rsquo;s network performance shows decent growth in total value locked (TVL). According to data on <a href="https://defillama.com/protocol/izumi-finance" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">DeFiLlama</a>, the TVL has risen sharply in the past 10 days &ndash; from under $2 million to over $25 million as of 26 April 2023.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The DeFi protocol&rsquo;s products iZiSwap, LiquidBox and DAO veNFT among others are also seeing greater uptake across the market. Indeed, the platform announced on Wednesday that it had closed a $22 million financing round for the on-chain order book iZiSwap Pro.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The iZiSwap recently launched on zkSync Era, a future-proof zkEVM network helping to scale the Ethereum blockchain.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Other than the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/kucoin/">KuCoin</a>, iZUMi has also struck key partnerships with MEXC Global, Bybit, Woo Network, and BitDAO. iZUMi also has a security partnership with auditing platform secure3io.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Building a strong platform amid the network pillars could inform long term demand for IZI and aid its price.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/izumi-finance-price-profit-deals-dump-izi-after-kucoin-listing/">iZUMi Finance price: profit deals dump IZI after KuCoin listing</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
