<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 16:21:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Leaked Digital Euro Bill Supports Offline Usability, Shuns Interests</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/leaked-digital-euro-bill-usability/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/leaked-digital-euro-bill-usability/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 16:21:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital euro]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ecb]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[EU]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=259113</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/leaked-digital-euro-bill-usability/">Leaked Digital Euro Bill Supports Offline Usability, Shuns Interests</a></p>
<p>The potential issuance of fiat currency in digital form has garnered global attention, with various jurisdictions exploring the concept. The EU, the US, and the UK are among those actively considering the implementation of a CBDC. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/leaked-digital-euro-bill-usability/">Leaked Digital Euro Bill Supports Offline Usability, Shuns Interests</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/leaked-digital-euro-bill-usability/">Leaked Digital Euro Bill Supports Offline Usability, Shuns Interests</a></p>
<p>A leaked draft of the proposed Digital Euro Bill, set to be proposed by the European Commission on June 28, reveals several significant provisions that aim to shape the future of the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-central-bank-digital-currency-cbdc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Central Bank Digital Currency</a> (CBDC).</p>
<p>The draft bill, <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/06/15/eus-leaked-digital-euro-bill-outlaws-interest-large-holdings-programmability/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">seen</a> by CoinDesk, highlights key elements such as the ban on interest and surcharges, offline payment availability from the onset, and limitations on programmability. Notably, the draft bill affirms the digital Euro&#8217;s status as legal tender, placing it on equal footing with traditional fiat currencies. This recognition ensures that shops and businesses must accept the digital euro as a valid means of payment.</p>
<p>According to the text viewed by CoinDesk, the EU intends to make the digital Euro available for both online and offline transactions right from its initial issuance. The regulation aims to ensure a level of privacy equal to taking cash from an ATM during offline, face-to-face interactions.</p>
<p>Notably, privacy has <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-parliament-research-digital-euro/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">emerged</a> as a significant area of public concern surrounding CBDCs, as highlighted by a 2021 survey conducted by the European Central Bank (ECB). The leaked draft of the proposed Digital Euro bill, therefore, acknowledges these concerns and aims to address them proactively.</p>
<p>While privacy is paramount, the leaked draft acknowledges the importance of regulatory monitoring in combating financial crimes such as money laundering. According to the proposed bill, neither the ECB nor the payment service providers will have access to personal transaction data.</p>
<p>Also, in an effort to uphold the essence of fiat currency and maintain its freely usable nature, the draft law emphasizes that the CBDC “shall not be programmable” The inclusion of this provision underscores the commitment to preserving the essential attributes of fiat currency.</p>
<p>Additionally, the draft law incorporates provisions to discourage individuals from utilizing digital euro accounts as a substitute for traditional commercial bank savings accounts. These measures aim to ensure that digital euro holdings do not bear interest and allow for additional controls to be imposed by the ECB.</p>
<p>To encourage the primary use of the digital euro for everyday transactions, ECB Executive Board member Fabio Panetta has suggested a cap of approximately 3,000 euros ($3,250) on individual holdings.</p>
<h2>Digital Euro: Navigating Lawmakers&#8217; Skepticism</h2>
<p>The potential issuance of fiat currency in digital form has garnered global attention, with various jurisdictions exploring the concept. The EU, the US, and the UK are among those actively considering the implementation of a CBDC.</p>
<p>Remarkably, the ECB has <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-parliament-research-digital-euro/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">conducted</a> a detailed assessment of a CBDC, and a decision on its adoption is likely later this year. Fabio Panetta emphasizes that the decision to proceed with a CBDC should be a political one, involving not only central bankers but also political considerations.</p>
<p>Overall, the introduction of a CBDC in the EU necessitates legislation that must be approved by both the European Parliament and the EU Council. However, members of the European Parliament have raised reservations about the CBDC, and the Council appears unlikely to completely reject the initiative.</p>
<p>While speaking anonymously on the issue, a senior EU official has indicated that the Council will not formulate a joint opinion on the digital euro in the near future.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bybit-chatgpt-trading-tools/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/leaked-digital-euro-bill-usability/">Leaked Digital Euro Bill Supports Offline Usability, Shuns Interests</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/leaked-digital-euro-bill-usability/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Exchange Bybit Taps into ChatGPT to Advance Trading Tools</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bybit-chatgpt-trading-tools/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bybit-chatgpt-trading-tools/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 14:02:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Amazon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance academy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bybit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chatgpt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[toolgpt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=259104</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bybit-chatgpt-trading-tools/">Crypto Exchange Bybit Taps into ChatGPT to Advance Trading Tools</a></p>
<p>ByBit is not the only crypto trading platform recognizing the potential of AI in delivering enhanced user experiences. Other leading exchanges have also explored the integration of ChatGPT into their platforms. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bybit-chatgpt-trading-tools/">Crypto Exchange Bybit Taps into ChatGPT to Advance Trading Tools</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bybit-chatgpt-trading-tools/">Crypto Exchange Bybit Taps into ChatGPT to Advance Trading Tools</a></p>
<p>Leading cryptocurrency exchange Bybit is gearing up to enhance its trading services by incorporating an artificial intelligence (AI) tool into its trading platform to enhance market data analysis. In a Twitter post on June 15, Bybit unveiled the latest addition to its Tools Discovery family, dubbed &#8220;ToolsGPT&#8221;, leveraging the capabilities of the famous generative AI technology, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/everything-you-need-to-know-about-chatgpt-ai-chatbot/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ChatGPT,</a> developed by OpenAI.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Welcome the latest addition to our Tools Discovery family, ToolsGPT 🎉</p>
<p>ToolsGPT integrates ChatGPT&#8217;s <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/MachineLearning?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#MachineLearning</a> and <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/AI?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#AI</a> capabilities with Bybit&#8217;s comprehensive market data.</p>
<p>Learn more about it: <a href="https://t.co/8SAQvd9PEK">https://t.co/8SAQvd9PEK</a><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bybit?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Bybit</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/TheCryptoArk?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#TheCryptoArk</a> <a href="https://t.co/CtXKayN3Dq">pic.twitter.com/CtXKayN3Dq</a></p>
<p>— Bybit (@Bybit_Official) <a href="https://twitter.com/Bybit_Official/status/1669283611240017920?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 15, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The newly introduced technology was designed to explore the advanced machine learning of ChatGPT combined with Bybit&#8217;s vast market data. This powerful combination empowers traders with extensive features, enabling them to make informed trading decisions.</p>
<p>The latest development comes after the European Union Parliament <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/eu-parliament-ai-draft-act/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">passed</a> the first AI bill in the world to regulate the use of generative AI technologies in the region.</p>
<h2>ToolsGPT Delivers Unique Responses to User&#8217;s Queries</h2>
<p>One of the standout features of ToolsGPT is its ability to offer valuable insights and predictions for different trading scenarios. By leveraging the vast pool of market data, this AI-powered tool can analyze price trends for numerous crypto assets, including Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a>) and Ether (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ETH</a>), taking into account technical indicators and historical patterns to help investors make informed decisions for successful trading activities.</p>
<p>In addition to providing valuable market insights and predicting bitcoin trajectory using past data, traders can benefit from ToolsGPT&#8217;s other functionalities, such as backtested price data and other essential metrics.</p>
<p>Bybit said the new technology was designed to deliver unique and actionable answers to users&#8217; inquiries. The exchange further disclosed that the tool will be accessible to all users, regardless of their experience, level, or expertise, for free.</p>
<p>Bybit aims to exploit cutting-edge technologies to provide innovative trading solutions to users. The company said the new technology shows its commitment to helping users become successful traders.</p>
<p>&#8220;By integrating ChatGPT into Bybit Tools, we are able to give users more comprehensive information when making their decisions. ToolsGPT is a testament to our commitment to empowering traders with advanced tools and insights,&#8221; <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bybit-integrates-chatgpt-trading-tools-103950875.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a> Ben Zhou, the company&#8217;s CEO.</p>
<h2>Not the First</h2>
<p>ByBit is not the only crypto trading platform recognizing the potential of AI in delivering enhanced user experiences. Other leading exchanges have also explored the integration of ChatGPT into their platforms.</p>
<p>Last month, CryptoCom unveiled its proprietary AI tool, Amy, which harnesses the power of ChatGPT. Amy provides a valuable resource for users with essential insights on token prices, market movements, and updates on various projects.</p>
<p>Similarly, Binance, the world&#8217;s largest crypto exchange, integrated OpenAI&#8217;s chatbot into its Binance Academy platform, offering users access to a vast database of articles and information related to the Web3 ecosystem.</p>
<p>The adoption of AI extends beyond exchanges to various blockchain projects. Notably, Solana Labs, the brains behind the development of the Solana blockchain, recently <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/solana-ai-chatgpt-plug-in/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">launched</a> a ChatGPT-powered plugin into the protocol.</p>
<p>The plugin allows users to perform tasks such as checking wallet balances, transferring Solana-native tokens, and trading non-fungible tokens (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NFTs</a>).</p>
<p>This various integration showcases the versatility of ChatGPT and its potential to streamline user experiences across the blockchain landscape.</p>
<p>Aside from crypto companies, other firms outside the industry are exploring the potential of AI tools. In April, Amazon <a href="http://coinspeaker.com/amazon-ai-service-bedrock/">unveiled</a> its innovative AI product offering called Bedrock. Targeted at Amazon service customers, Bedrock enables users to create personalized generative AI tools tailored to their unique requirements.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/btc-price-25k-fed-interest-rate/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bybit-chatgpt-trading-tools/">Crypto Exchange Bybit Taps into ChatGPT to Advance Trading Tools</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bybit-chatgpt-trading-tools/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>BTC Price Plummets Below $25K as Fed Pauses Interest Rate</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/btc-price-25k-fed-interest-rate/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/btc-price-25k-fed-interest-rate/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Temitope Olatunji]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 12:54:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[federal reserve]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jerome powell]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[us fed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=259069</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/btc-price-25k-fed-interest-rate/">BTC Price Plummets Below $25K as Fed Pauses Interest Rate</a></p>
<p>Following the Fed interest rate pause announcement, the price of BTC broke major price support, raising concerns about a continued decline.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/btc-price-25k-fed-interest-rate/">BTC Price Plummets Below $25K as Fed Pauses Interest Rate</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/btc-price-25k-fed-interest-rate/">BTC Price Plummets Below $25K as Fed Pauses Interest Rate</a></p>
<p>The Federal Reserve announced on Wednesday that it would maintain its interest rate at 5.25%, marking the first time since January 2022 that the rate would remain unchanged. According to the Fed, the inflation rate appears to be decreasing, and it wants to see whether previous rate increases were sufficient to slow price increases. However, it was hinted that the rate could rise if inflation does not appear to be declining and remains a concern.</p>
<p>At a press conference, Fed Chairman, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/jerome-powell/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Jerome Powell</a>, <a href="https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/2023/06/14/fed-interest-rate-hike-live-updates/70313232007/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">stated</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;As we get closer and closer to our destination (the peak rate), it’s reasonable and common sense to go a little slower.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The unemployment rate report also revealed that the final figures were above expectations. The Fed had predicted that the unemployment rate would fall to 4.1% from 4.5%. Nonetheless, the actual result was even lower, dropping to 3.7%, implying that the labor market is performing better than the Fed expected. The lower unemployment rate suggests that the economy’s current state can withstand higher interest rates without causing significant job losses.</p>
<p>Even with the interest rate pause, there are speculations that the rates may be raised twice before the end of the year, depending on how the economy nears its 2% inflation target. Powell also agrees that there may be a case for interest rates to rise later in the year, but only gradually.</p>
<h2>BTC Price Plunges Further Following the Fed Interest Rate Pause</h2>
<p>The interest rate news and many of the announcements that followed were positive for the United States dollar, making it strong against many currencies. Notably, the price of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> broke a major support level, raising concerns about a continued price decline.</p>
<p>Since April 14, the price of BTC has been below $31,000. This price represents the highest point it has reached this year after a long bearish market that persisted through most of 2022. Yesterday’s announcement finally caused it to break the $25,700 support level after more than five weeks of consolidating between $28,000 and $25,700.</p>
<p>The price of Bitcoin is now heading towards major support at $24,300. If this support does not hold, it may continue to decline towards the zone around $22,000, where the next major support level lies.</p>
<p>Given that Bitcoin&#8217;s price greatly influences market sentiment towards cryptocurrencies, the prices of other cryptos may also continue to drop if the bearish trend persists. <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a>, for example, has also broken the $1770 support level and is currently moving towards the $1600 support level. Considering the price direction of major cryptocurrencies, individuals anticipating a major bull run may need to exercise a little more patience.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/celsius-creditor-bankruptcy-exit/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/btc-price-25k-fed-interest-rate/">BTC Price Plummets Below $25K as Fed Pauses Interest Rate</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/btc-price-25k-fed-interest-rate/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Celsius Faces Creditor Pushback Over Bankruptcy Exit Plan</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/celsius-creditor-bankruptcy-exit/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/celsius-creditor-bankruptcy-exit/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Babafemi Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 12:50:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[celsius]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[celsius bankruptcy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fahrenheit]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=258751</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/celsius-creditor-bankruptcy-exit/">Celsius Faces Creditor Pushback Over Bankruptcy Exit Plan</a></p>
<p>Some creditors are unhappy with the revealed plan and have expressed their opposition.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/celsius-creditor-bankruptcy-exit/">Celsius Faces Creditor Pushback Over Bankruptcy Exit Plan</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/celsius-creditor-bankruptcy-exit/">Celsius Faces Creditor Pushback Over Bankruptcy Exit Plan</a></p>

<p>Insolvent crypto lending platform, Celsius, has filed an updated plan to exit bankruptcy with the help of crypto consortium Fahrenheit. However, the plan faces opposition from creditors who are unhappy with the deal and want their money back.</p>
<h2>Celsius’ Journey Out of Bankruptcy</h2>
<p>Celsius filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy protection in April 2022, hoping to restructure its debt and find a buyer for its assets. In October, the company launched an auction for its assets. Following several bids, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fahrenheit-consortium-celsius-network/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Fahrenheit emerged</a> as the winning bidder for Celsius&#8217; assets in May 2023.</p>
<p>Fahrenheit offered to pay $300 million in cash and $700 million in Fahrenheit tokens for Celsius&#8217; assets, which include its user base, technology, brand name, and intellectual property. Fahrenheit also agreed to assume Celsius&#8217; liabilities and honor its obligations to its users and creditors.</p>
<p>However, in a recent development, Celsius submitted an update to its <a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.nysb.312902/gov.uscourts.nysb.312902.2807.0.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener">bankruptcy exit plan</a>. The new plan states that customers who have deposited or borrowed fiat currencies will not receive any recovery from Celsius or Fahrenheit. Instead, they will have to file claims as unsecured creditors. The plan also warns that customers may face tax consequences or regulatory issues as a result of the deal. It advises customers to consult their own tax and legal advisors before accepting the deal.</p>
<h2>Creditors Oppose Updated Bankruptcy Exit Plan</h2>
<p>Some creditors are unhappy with the deal and have expressed their opposition. They argue that Celsius has not returned their collateral or paid them interest as promised. They also claim that Fahrenheit’s bid undervalues Celsius’ assets and does not offer enough recovery for creditors.</p>
<p>One group of creditors, represented by lawyer David Adler, said they would challenge the deal in court. &#8220;This proposed treatment violates every consumer lending law out there,&#8221; Adler <a href="https://twitter.com/DavidJAdler1991/status/1669222668762071040" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">tweeted</a> on Wednesday.</p>
<p>Another group of creditors, represented by an official committee of unsecured creditors, said “The Committee will continue to work diligently with all parties involved in this case to maximize recoveries for all unsecured creditors.”</p>
<p>Whatever the case, the deal still needs to be approved by the bankruptcy court and by a majority of Celsius&#8217; creditors. The court has set a deadline of June 30 for creditors to vote on the deal.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-criminal-charges-ftx-sbf/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/celsius-creditor-bankruptcy-exit/">Celsius Faces Creditor Pushback Over Bankruptcy Exit Plan</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/celsius-creditor-bankruptcy-exit/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>US Prosecutors to Reduce Criminal Charges on FTX Founder SBF in October Trial</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-criminal-charges-ftx-sbf/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-criminal-charges-ftx-sbf/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 12:20:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alameda research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sam bankman-fried]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sbf]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=259066</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-criminal-charges-ftx-sbf/">US Prosecutors to Reduce Criminal Charges on FTX Founder SBF in October Trial</a></p>
<p>The DoJ prosecutors have eliminated five charges relating to fraud, conspiracy, and bribery initially levied against the disgraced FTX founder. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-criminal-charges-ftx-sbf/">US Prosecutors to Reduce Criminal Charges on FTX Founder SBF in October Trial</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-criminal-charges-ftx-sbf/">US Prosecutors to Reduce Criminal Charges on FTX Founder SBF in October Trial</a></p>
<p>In a court filing on Wednesday, June 14, prosecutors with the US Department of Justice (DoJ) <a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/us-prosecutors-say-sbf-will-be-tried-on-original-8-criminal-charges-for-now" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">told</a> the district judge that they would be proceeding with eight charges in the trial levied against <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a> founder <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/sam-bankman-fried/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Sam Bankman-Fried</a> back in December 2022.</p>
<p>The DoJ lawyers also cited a motion filed by SBF in the Bahamas wherein he argued that the 13 charges that he faced were not in the original indictment, which was the premise for his extradition from the country. The US federal prosecutors announced their decision to temporarily withhold five charges of foreign bribery, bank fraud, and conspiracy against Sam Bankman-Fried, the indicted founder of the bankrupt cryptocurrency exchange FTX. Since this could be a lengthy process, the prosecutor wrote that they’re “prepared to proceed to trial as scheduled on the counts contained in the original indictment. It now appears that litigation of that motion will take some time and may not be resolved until near or even after the trial date&#8221;.</p>
<p>On Wednesday, the Supreme Court of the Bahamas noted that the disgraced FTX founder deserves an opportunity to formally challenge all the new charges before the country can agree to them.</p>
<p>In a recent development, prosecutors in Manhattan stated that they would withdraw the five charges against the former billionaire if the Caribbean nation does not cooperate. If found guilty in the trial scheduled for October 2, he could face a lengthy prison sentence.</p>
<h2>The Fall of FTX and SBF</h2>
<p>Following the extradition of Sam Bankman-Fried last year, the DoJ had unsealed an additional of four charges earlier this year in February relating to fraud and conspiracy. Later, in March, they unsealed additional charges related to the bribery to Chinese officials.</p>
<p>FTX owes more than $3 billion to its creditors, according to estimates. Prosecutors claim that Bankman-Fried mixed customer funds together and provided false information to investors about how FTX managed risks, resulting in financial losses for investors and customers.</p>
<p>Caroline Ellison, the former CEO of Alameda Research, and Gary Wang, a co-founder of FTX, have admitted guilt to charges of fraud related to the exchange&#8217;s downfall. However, Bankman-Fried argues that it was not fraud but rather management errors that led to the collapse.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fintech-zepz-expansion/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-criminal-charges-ftx-sbf/">US Prosecutors to Reduce Criminal Charges on FTX Founder SBF in October Trial</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-criminal-charges-ftx-sbf/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fintech Unicorn Zepz Eyes Expansion via Mergers and Acquisitions</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fintech-zepz-expansion/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fintech-zepz-expansion/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 12:09:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Deals News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FinTech News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ma]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[paypal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[zepz]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=259079</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fintech-zepz-expansion/">Fintech Unicorn Zepz Eyes Expansion via Mergers and Acquisitions</a></p>
<p>Zepz CEO revealed that the company is preparing to introduce its first digital wallet, with a focus on meeting the requirements of migrant communities that frequently send money home.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fintech-zepz-expansion/">Fintech Unicorn Zepz Eyes Expansion via Mergers and Acquisitions</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fintech-zepz-expansion/">Fintech Unicorn Zepz Eyes Expansion via Mergers and Acquisitions</a></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In the fast-paced world of financial technology, staying ahead of the competition often necessitates bold and clever initiatives. with Zepz targeting expansion through Mergers and Acquisitions (M&amp;A).</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The CEO of Zepz, Mark Lenhard, recently shared this exciting development in an </span><a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/06/15/fintech-firm-zepz-plans-ma-new-digital-wallet-after-layoffs.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">interview</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> with CNBC. While specific details regarding potential targets were not disclosed, the move signals Zepz&#8217;s determination to strengthen its position in the industry and build upon its existing success. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Zepz, a prominent fintech company based in Europe, has garnered significant attention and support from investors, propelling its valuation to an impressive $5 billion. Backed by renowned investors such as Accel, TCV, and Leapfrog, Zepz has established itself as one of the largest players in the European fintech landscape.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Zepz&#8217;s competitive edge lies in its ability to provide a more cost-effective alternative to traditional banks and established money transfer services. By leveraging technology and streamlining operations, Zepz offers customers a more affordable solution for international money transfers, disrupting the industry and challenging the dominance of traditional players.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In Zepz&#8217;s pursuit of M&amp;A opportunities, the company aims to broaden its range of services and consolidate its market position. By acquiring or partnering with companies that complement its strengths, Zepz can enhance its capabilities, enter new markets, and strengthen its customer base. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lenhard highlights that M&amp;A provides an avenue for Zepz to accelerate its growth trajectory and expand its footprint in the digital payments landscape.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">However, Zepz&#8217;s decision to pursue M&amp;A comes as a surprise to many, given the recent cost reduction efforts undertaken by the company. In May, the fintech firm implemented significant workforce reductions, resulting in the layoff of approximately 420 employees worldwide. At the time, the CEO </span><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/zepz-lays-off-restructure-business/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">stated</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> that the layoff was part of its business restructuring for future growth prospects.</span></p>
<h2><b>Zepz Expansion: Focus on Digital Wallets</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Furthermore, Zepz CEO revealed that the company is preparing to introduce its first digital wallet, with a focus on meeting the requirements of migrant communities that frequently send money home.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Notably, Lenhard&#8217;s emphasis on Zepz&#8217;s digital wallet product reflects the company&#8217;s commitment to enhancing its value proposition and providing a comprehensive suite of services to its customers. Zepz hopes to become a one-stop financial platform that serves its users&#8217; diversified demands by offering a digital wallet, minimizing their reliance on multiple apps and platforms.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">While established players like </span><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">PayPal Holdings Inc</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> (NASDAQ: PYPL) may offer a wider range of products and services, Zepz aims to differentiate itself by providing a focused and tailored experience to its target market.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">However, the success of Zepz&#8217;s digital wallet will depend on its ability to provide a compelling user experience, seamless integration with its existing services, and competitive features that meet the evolving needs of its target market. </span><a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/miami-mayor-us-presidential-bid/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fintech-zepz-expansion/">Fintech Unicorn Zepz Eyes Expansion via Mergers and Acquisitions</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fintech-zepz-expansion/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pro-Bitcoin Miami Mayor Files Paperwork for US Presidential Bid</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/miami-mayor-us-presidential-bid/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/miami-mayor-us-presidential-bid/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 11:39:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[francis suarez]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=259056</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/miami-mayor-us-presidential-bid/">Pro-Bitcoin Miami Mayor Files Paperwork for US Presidential Bid</a></p>
<p>While the Bitcoin community may support the Miami Mayor and cast their vote for him, his acknowledgment about not voting for Trump in the 2016 or 2020 elections could affect their decision.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/miami-mayor-us-presidential-bid/">Pro-Bitcoin Miami Mayor Files Paperwork for US Presidential Bid</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/miami-mayor-us-presidential-bid/">Pro-Bitcoin Miami Mayor Files Paperwork for US Presidential Bid</a></p>
<p>The Mayor of Miami and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> advocate Francis Suarez has signaled his intention to run for the US presidential position. As he joins the Republican race for the seat of president, Suarez has become the first Hispanic in the group. As the son of the city’s first Cuban-born Mayor, Miami voters have elected the Bitcoin bull twice. Currently, he serves as the Mayor of the city, which has around 450,000 residents.</p>
<p>The Miami Mayor is contesting former US president <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/donald-trump/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Donald Trump</a> and fellow Florida Governor Ron DeSantis, who is another Bitcoin advocate, as they all fight to lead the Republican presidency bid.</p>
<h2>Miami Mayor Signals Interest in US Presidential Bid</h2>
<p>The US Federal Election Commission <a href="https://docquery.fec.gov/cgi-bin/forms/C00842971/1707314/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">revealed</a> the Miami Mayor’s move concerning the US presidential seat. According to a document by the Commission, Suarez filed official paperwork on Wednesday, shortly after his opponent Trump had an arraignment in Miami. The former president was charged with hoarding classified documents at his estate in Palm Beach County.</p>
<p>The newly-announced US presidential aspirant will speak at the Ronald Reagan Presidential Library in Simi Valley, California, on the 16th of June. The Miami Mayor is expected to shed more light on his US presidential race at the event.</p>
<p>It is about to be a rejoicing moment for the Bitcoin community if the Mayor wins the election. Suarez, who once stated that BTC could become a global currency, started accepting his salary in Bitcoin in 2021. Last year, he <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/miami-mayor-bitcoin-paychecks/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">confirmed</a> that he still receives his paycheck in Bitcoin but wanted the public to be aware of the risks attached to cryptocurrency. Even as the crypto market was red and many investors lost large percentages of their holdings, Suarez remained positive on the first crypto asset.</p>
<p>Before declaring his intention for the US presidential election, Suarez was also involved in “MiamiCoin” early last year. The MiamiCoin program was designed to help Miami residents buy crypto via a digital wallet and also receive a Bitcoin dividend.</p>
<p>While the Bitcoin community may support the Miami Mayor and cast their vote for him, his acknowledgment about not voting for Trump in the 2016 or 2020 elections could affect him. In addition, the presidential aspirant confirmed that he did not vote for DeSantis in 2018.</p>
<p>Notably, the Miami Mayor had hinted that he could bid for the US presidential post. <a href="https://www.politico.com/news/2023/06/14/francis-suarez-president-mayor-miami-00102030" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Speaking</a> to POLITICO in May, he stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>“because I think I can grow the tent &#8211; not for an election, but for a generation. I think it matters who is the communicator of ideas and how they communicate those ideas. You can look at my history and know that I’m someone who’s a unifier. You can look at my history and see that I’m someone who appreciates the nuances in a variety of different Hispanic cultures.”</p></blockquote>
<p>The 2024 US presidential election is scheduled for the 5th of November, 2024.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-cloud-mining-btc/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/miami-mayor-us-presidential-bid/">Pro-Bitcoin Miami Mayor Files Paperwork for US Presidential Bid</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/miami-mayor-us-presidential-bid/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Cloud Mining: Exchange Floats New Product for Mining BTC</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-cloud-mining-btc/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-cloud-mining-btc/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 10:16:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Binance News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance cloud mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance us]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin cloud mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=259016</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-cloud-mining-btc/">Binance Cloud Mining: Exchange Floats New Product for Mining BTC</a></p>
<p>Binance also disclosed that the BTC mining subscription service will only be active for 180 days or thereabout.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-cloud-mining-btc/">Binance Cloud Mining: Exchange Floats New Product for Mining BTC</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-cloud-mining-btc/">Binance Cloud Mining: Exchange Floats New Product for Mining BTC</a></p>
<p>The weight of regulatory pressure from the US Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) appears to have little or no effect on the activities of crypto exchange <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a>. This follows after the exchange recently announced the Binance cloud mining product and services.</p>
<p>According to the <a href="https://techtelegraph.co.uk/binance-launches-bitcoin-mining-cloud-services-amid-sec-crackdown-in-the-us/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announcement</a>, the service goes live on Thursday, June 15th, and access to it will be subscription-based. That is, from Thursday, Binance users who would love to mine Bitcoin but lack the capacity, may now subscribe to its new service to access the hashrates to do so.</p>
<p>Recall, hashrate describes the computing power used to mine and process transactions on a Proof-of-Work blockchain such as Bitcoin.</p>
<h2>Binance Cloud Mining Not Available to US-Based Users, Says Exchange</h2>
<p>About the cloud mining subscription, Binance confirms that 1 Terahash per second (Th/s) currently goes for $10.7280. The exchange explains the pricing as being the total cost of electricity ($9.558) and that of the hashrate ($1.17).</p>
<p>Furthermore, Binance disclosed that the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a> mining subscription service will only be active for 180 days or thereabout. And for each TH/s that users purchase, they will earn no more than 0.0004338 BTC during the period.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Binance has also confirmed that the service will be made available to all its global users except those living in the United States. However, the reason for this is not far-fetched. A recent crackdown from the SEC has seen the exchange halt all its operations on US soil. Nonetheless, the company insists:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Binance.com is a separate entity and our users will not be impacted by issues at Binance.US.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>On June 6, the SEC <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-sues-binance-securities-rules/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">filed</a> a lawsuit against Binance.US, alleging that the exchange violated US securities laws. But the exchange has since denied the claims and has hired some of the best attorneys in the world to fight against the allegations. Among those that Binance.US hired into its legal team is George Canellos, a former SEC enforcement co-director.</p>
<p>In the meantime, however, Binance.US has <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-us-halts-usd-deposits/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">stopped</a> allowing US dollar deposits and withdrawals with effect from June 13.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hong-kong-hsbc-standard-chartered-crypto/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-cloud-mining-btc/">Binance Cloud Mining: Exchange Floats New Product for Mining BTC</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-cloud-mining-btc/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hong Kong Mounts Pressure on HSBC and Standard Chartered Bank to Service Crypto Customers </title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/hong-kong-hsbc-standard-chartered-crypto/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/hong-kong-hsbc-standard-chartered-crypto/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 09:54:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bank of china]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hkma]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hsbc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sfc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[standard chartered]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=259021</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hong-kong-hsbc-standard-chartered-crypto/">Hong Kong Mounts Pressure on HSBC and Standard Chartered Bank to Service Crypto Customers </a></p>
<p>The new development aligns with the country's ambition to become a prominent global hub for crypto.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hong-kong-hsbc-standard-chartered-crypto/">Hong Kong Mounts Pressure on HSBC and Standard Chartered Bank to Service Crypto Customers </a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hong-kong-hsbc-standard-chartered-crypto/">Hong Kong Mounts Pressure on HSBC and Standard Chartered Bank to Service Crypto Customers </a></p>
<p>In a bold move aimed at embracing the crypto revolution in Hong Kong, the country&#8217;s banking regulator has reportedly exerted significant pressure on major financial services companies, including <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/hsbc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">HSBC</a> and Standard Chartered Bank, to accept crypto exchanges as clients.</p>
<p>According to a Financial Times <a href="https://www.ft.com/content/da31d2d6-e547-43b0-821d-a235097ef9c9" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a> on Thursday citing three people familiar with the matter, the Hong Kong Monetary Authority (HKMA) questioned these banks, including the Bank of China, about their refusal to accept crypto exchanges as clients in May.</p>
<p>Notably, the central bank regulator had already taken a proactive stance on the matter just weeks before last month&#8217;s meeting.</p>
<p>In a letter dated April 27, the HKMA urged financial institutions to pay close attention to new market developments and adopt an ambitious strategy toward emerging sectors like the crypto market. The letter explicitly mandated the banks to facilitate the growth of virtual asset service providers (VASPs) and other crypto companies by ensuring they have access to essential banking services.</p>
<p>The regulator assured the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hsbc-money-laundering-shares/">banks</a> that conducting due diligence on prospective customers should not impose excessive burdens, especially for entities establishing offices in Hong Kong with the intention of exploring opportunities in the region.</p>
<p>&#8220;Due diligence on potential customers should not &#8220;create an undue burden,&#8221; particularly &#8220;for those setting up an office in Hong Kong to look for the opportunities here,&#8221; the letter <a href="https://www.hkma.gov.hk/media/eng/doc/key-information/guidelines-and-circular/2023/20230427e1.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reads</a>.</p>
<h2>Hong Kong Urges Bank Not to Be Afraid</h2>
<p>Hong Kong&#8217;s central bank regulator also encouraged the banks not to be afraid of servicing VASPs.</p>
<p>Sources familiar with the details of the meeting, held in May, revealed that the HKMA advised the banks not to succumb to fear, highlighting strong opposition from senior executives within the traditional banking system who remain skeptical about serving crypto firms.</p>
<p>This skepticism from decision-makers poses a significant challenge to the country&#8217;s vision of fostering a more inclusive environment for crypto clients within the banking sector.</p>
<h2>Hong Kong Moves to Become Global Hub for Crypto</h2>
<p>The new development aligns with the country&#8217;s ambition to become a prominent global hub for crypto. The Securities and Futures Commission (SFC) of Hong Kong initiated a significant move by opening its doors to applications for <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hong-kong-licensed-crypto-exchanges/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">licenses</a> from crypto trading platforms on June 1 in order to service retail customers in the region.</p>
<p>This progressive step indicates the country&#8217;s determination to foster a conducive environment for crypto-related businesses.</p>
<p>Adding to its crypto-friendly reputation, a Hong Kong lawmaker extended an <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/licensing-hong-kong-coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">invitation</a> to Coinbase, the largest crypto exchange in America, urging the company to register its operations in the region.</p>
<p>By attracting prominent players in the crypto space, Hong Kong aims to solidify its position as a key destination for crypto businesses.</p>
<p>While many companies are already <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-firms-hong-kong-licenses/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">seeking applications</a> to register with the appropriate authorities to offer their product offerings to customers across the nation, the Hong Kong government has warned crypto firms not to expect special treatment from authorities.</p>
<p>According to a Coinspeaker <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hong-kong-crypto-businesses-regulation/">report</a> on May 9, the HKMA chief Eddie Yue Wai-man told Bloomberg in an interview that the country will impose stringent regulations on crypto.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-250m-lawsuit-music/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hong-kong-hsbc-standard-chartered-crypto/">Hong Kong Mounts Pressure on HSBC and Standard Chartered Bank to Service Crypto Customers </a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/hong-kong-hsbc-standard-chartered-crypto/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Twitter Faces $250M Copyright Lawsuit from Music Publishers</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-250m-lawsuit-music/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-250m-lawsuit-music/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 09:42:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Amazon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[facebook]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[instagram]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tiktok]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[twitter]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=259037</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-250m-lawsuit-music/">Twitter Faces $250M Copyright Lawsuit from Music Publishers</a></p>
<p>The recent lawsuit against Twitter for alleged copyright infringement involving music publishers has shed light on the platform's struggles with music licensing. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-250m-lawsuit-music/">Twitter Faces $250M Copyright Lawsuit from Music Publishers</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-250m-lawsuit-music/">Twitter Faces $250M Copyright Lawsuit from Music Publishers</a></p>
<p>Social media giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/twitter/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Twitter Inc</a> is no stranger to controversy, but this time it finds itself in hot water as music publishers have filed a lawsuit against the company, seeking a staggering $250 million in damages.</p>
<p>The National Music Publishers&#8217; Association (NMPA) is suing Twitter on behalf of 17 music publishers who represent some of the industry&#8217;s top musicians. The <a href="https://www.documentcloud.org/documents/23848155-music-industry-v-twitter" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">legal action</a> alleges that Twitter has engaged in “massive” copyright infringement by allowing its users to share copyrighted music without proper authorization.</p>
<p>According to the lawsuit, Twitter has been exploiting copyrighted music videos, live performances, and other synchronized videos to augment its platform&#8217;s value and prolong user engagement. The legal battle intensifies as a list of approximately 1,700 songs is presented as evidence in the lawsuit.</p>
<p>The publishers claim that these songs have been repeatedly flagged to Twitter through copyright notices, yet the platform has allegedly failed to take appropriate action. This alleged negligence has resulted in substantial financial losses for music publishers and other rights holders.</p>
<p>The music publishers are requesting that the court impose fines of up to $150,000 per violation on Twitter. If these penalties were applied for each instance of infringement listed, the potential financial repercussions for Twitter amount to about $250 million. The intention behind seeking substantial fines is to hold Twitter accountable for its alleged inaction, hoping that it serves as a deterrent for future copyright infringement on the platform.</p>
<p>Despite the gravity of the lawsuit filed against Twitter by music publishers, the company has not provided any official comment or response.</p>
<p>This silence raises concerns about the platform&#8217;s commitment to addressing copyright infringement and its willingness to engage with the issue transparently. The lack of a clear stance or public acknowledgment leaves stakeholders, including music publishers and the public, in a state of uncertainty.</p>
<h2>Twitter Copyright Lawsuit and Connection to Delayed Licensing Deals</h2>
<p>The recent lawsuit against Twitter for alleged copyright infringement involving music publishers has shed light on the platform&#8217;s struggles with music licensing. It is worth noting that these issues predate Elon Musk&#8217;s $44 billion acquisition of Twitter last year.</p>
<p>Reports suggest that Twitter had been hesitant to enter into music licensing deals due to their potentially substantial costs, estimated at over $100 million annually.  Following <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/elon-musk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Elon Musk</a>&#8216;s acquisition of Twitter, licensing negotiations between the platform and major music labels encountered roadblocks. Reports from March indicated that discussions between Twitter and three major labels had come to a standstill.</p>
<p>However, following Musk&#8217;s announcement of a new Twitter CEO, David Israelite, President of the NMPA, shared a tweet, emphasizing the urgency of addressing the prevalent issue of unlicensed music on the platform.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Platforms such as TikTok, Facebook, Instagram, YouTube, and Snapchat have successfully entered into licensing agreements with music publishers. On the other hand, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/amazon/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Amazon</a>-owned Twitch has recently settled with the NMPA over music copyright issues.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fed-pauses-rate-hike/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-250m-lawsuit-music/">Twitter Faces $250M Copyright Lawsuit from Music Publishers</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-250m-lawsuit-music/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4169 metric#misses=41 metric#hit-ratio=99.0 metric#bytes=1078502 metric#prefetches=208 metric#store-reads=20 metric#store-writes=2 metric#store-hits=215 metric#store-misses=2 metric#sql-queries=34 metric#ms-total=92.64 metric#ms-cache=5.49 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.2616 metric#ms-cache-ratio=5.9 -->