<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 16:25:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>UK’s NFT industry expected to grow to $9,257 million by 2028</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/uks-nft-industry-expected-to-grow-to-9257-million-by-2028/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/uks-nft-industry-expected-to-grow-to-9257-million-by-2028/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 16:25:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto adoption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[UK]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/uks-nft-industry-expected-to-grow-to-9257-million-by-2028/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The United Kingdom&#8217;s NFT industry is expected to grow at a CAGR of 34.5% over the next 5-6 years. NFT spend in the UK will increase from $1,725.2 million in 2022 to $9,257.0 million by 2028. Increased adoption, government support and venture funding are key factors to that growth. The global non-fungible tokens (NFT) market [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/uks-nft-industry-expected-to-grow-to-9257-million-by-2028/">UK’s NFT industry expected to grow to $9,257 million by 2028</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>The United Kingdom&rsquo;s NFT industry is expected to grow at a CAGR of 34.5% over the next 5-6 years.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>NFT spend in the UK will increase from $1,725.2 million in 2022 to $9,257.0 million by 2028.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><strong><em>Increased adoption, government support and venture funding are key factors to that growth.</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">The global non-fungible tokens (NFT) market took a hit alongside the rest of the market in 2022, with sales volumes and creator revenue seeing a significant decline.</p>
<p dir="ltr">But despite the brutal crash that&rsquo;s characterised the crypto sector throughout the year, the latest trends and projections suggest the NFT industry will continue to grow over the next six years.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Key segments in the next few years will be collectibles and art, real estate, sports, gaming, fashion &amp; luxury and utility.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">UK&rsquo;s NFT industry to grow at a CAGR of 34.5% up to 2028</h2>
<p dir="ltr">2021 remains a benchmark year for various sectors, yet according to a recent Research and Markets NFT industry <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/united-kingdom-nft-market-intelligence-report-2022-2028---nft-marketplaces-are-raising-funding-rounds-to-drive-their-growth-301710934.html" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">report</a>, 2022-2028 would see growth at a CAGR of 34.5%.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The United Kingdom will see its NFT industry grow from $1,725.2 million in 2022 to $9,257 million by 2028. The forecast put the NFT Spend Value for the UK on an upwards trajectory of an annual 48% for this year.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Research and Markets report highlighted on Thursday forecasts widespread adoption of digital assets across the country&rsquo;s different user groups will spark even further interest in NFTs.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Among factors to aid the UK NFT industry is the increased participation from innovative startups, sports clubs and even real estate giants. Just recently, Premier League giants Manchester United unveiled their NFT collection, joining an industry that&rsquo;s already boasting of major global brands.As <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tezos-strike-deal-with-manchester-united/">previously reported</a>, the soccer club partnered blockchain platform Tezos in February this year.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The growing recognition and support for the industry from the UK government is another factor, as is the rising number of investors backing NFT startups.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/uks-nft-industry-expected-to-grow-to-9257-million-by-2028/">UK’s NFT industry expected to grow to $9,257 million by 2028</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/uks-nft-industry-expected-to-grow-to-9257-million-by-2028/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Metacade’s Presale Set To Explode in 2023 &#8211; Get In Cheap Before It’s Too Late</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/metacades-presale-set-to-explode-in-2023-get-in-cheap-before-its-too-late/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/metacades-presale-set-to-explode-in-2023-get-in-cheap-before-its-too-late/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice Davies]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 16:03:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/metacades-presale-set-to-explode-in-2023-get-in-cheap-before-its-too-late/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto is famous for producing insane returns, and getting in on crypto presales is the easiest way to ensure the highest potential for gains. This high potential for earning, followed by a decrease, is caused by an economic principle called the law of diminishing returns, which states that an asset&#8217;s value growth will begin to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/metacades-presale-set-to-explode-in-2023-get-in-cheap-before-its-too-late/">Metacade’s Presale Set To Explode in 2023 &#8211; Get In Cheap Before It’s Too Late</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Crypto is famous for producing insane returns, and getting in on crypto presales is the easiest way to ensure the highest potential for gains. This high potential for earning, followed by a decrease, is caused by an economic principle called the <em>law of diminishing returns</em>, which states that an asset&rsquo;s value growth will begin to slow down over time.</p>
<p dir="ltr">One presale that has proven to be a significant success is Metacade (MCADE). Metacade is building a major GameFi platform to rival some of the biggest names in the space, so it&rsquo;s worth investigating before the price rises even further.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">The Metacade presale is a big investment opportunity</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Crypto presales are extremely popular, especially for projects with strong fundamentals like&nbsp;<a href="https://metacade.co/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade</u></a>. Case in point, the beta phase of the MCADE presale attracted over $1.3 million worth of investment in just four weeks, reflecting the project&rsquo;s long-term potential.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade launched its MCADE token at $0.008 at the beginning of its crypto presale, but now the price is rising. The price will continue growing until it reaches $0.02 at the end of the presale. For investors looking to get a good deal, the sooner you pick up tokens the better.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">MCADE price prediction: 2023 and beyond</h2>
<p dir="ltr">After reaching $0.02 at the end of its presale, MCADE will be launched on decentralized exchanges (DEXs), and the team will start to form partnerships to expand the reach of the token. Aside from this, the MCADE token will gain utility once it opens the comprehensive gaming experience planned for the Metacade platform.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The long-term potential of Metacade is very promising as a result. Experts predict explosive price action during 2023, which could see gains of up to 50x. This price explosion would give the MCADE token a value of $1 &ndash; a significant increase from its final crypto presale value of $0.02.</p>
<p dir="ltr">After 2023, analysts expect the crypto market to begin its next bull run once Bitcoin&rsquo;s halving event ends during 2024. Bull markets usually produce major gains across the board, which could push the MCADE token up in value even further. <strong>By this time, MCADE could reach over $5, a massive 250x increase between the crypto presale and 2025.</strong></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Metacade?</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://metacade.co/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade</u></a> is creating the biggest arcade on the blockchain, bringing advanced gaming capabilities to the world of Web3. GameFi enthusiasts can play a wide range of arcade-style games that each offer crypto rewards and participate in paid entry tournaments to win MCADE prizes.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Several additional features truly make Metacade stand out as a prime investment opportunity during its crypto presale. First, the project aims to serve Web3 users directly by providing a central location for gamers to get together and access valuable information about the space.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Over time, Metacade aims to become a decentralized autonomous organization (<a href="https://www.coindesk.com/learn/what-is-a-dao/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>DAO</u></a>). This shift will give complete control over the platform to the Metacade community, as all MCADE token holders will be able to vote in governance proposals and help drive the project&rsquo;s future progress.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How does Metacade work?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Blockchain gamers can access endless challenges across many play-to-earn (<a href="https://www.securitytokenizer.io/what-is-gamefi"><u>P2E</u></a>) games. Whether looking to play casually or competitively, Metacade offers players the chance to enjoy various addictive arcade games while earning MCADE tokens for their efforts.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In the Metacade, gamers also earn crypto tokens for contributing useful information to the community. These contributions can include the latest tips and tricks and anything else to help other gamers make the most out of their blockchain gaming experience.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Another key feature offered by Metacade is the chance to test out brand-new blockchain games before they officially launch. These beta-testing roles allow players to provide feedback to game developers, who can implement any improvements suggested by the Metacade community, including bug fixes and gameplay optimizations.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Metacade is expanding the reach of blockchain-based gaming</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade also aims to provide a critical service that can help the wider GameFi industry to grow. Its Metagrants program will provide funding for the most in-demand blockchain games, as the Metacade community will be able to vote for the titles that they most want to play in the future.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Blockchain is a technological advancement hub, and Metacade supports continuing progress in this area. Early-stage funding is critical in the process, as creating and launching new games requires a high level of support. <strong>Through connecting developers with its community of gamers, Metacade is directly helping to expand the scope and scale of innovation in blockchain.</strong></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Is Metacade worth buying in 2023?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The Metacade presale is a significant buying opportunity for crypto investors. Luckily, $0.008 is a meagre price for a project that offers real promise for the future, and it&rsquo;s no surprise that the beta phase sold out quickly.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The presale will see the MCADE token rise to $0.02, so investors still have time to make some bear market gains. However, Metacade is undoubtedly a great addition to any investment portfolio, and it will be fascinating to see if it will reach the $1 mark during 2023.</p>
<p><strong>You can participate in the MCADE presale&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://metacade.co/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong><u>here</u></strong></a><strong>.</strong></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/metacades-presale-set-to-explode-in-2023-get-in-cheap-before-its-too-late/">Metacade’s Presale Set To Explode in 2023 &#8211; Get In Cheap Before It’s Too Late</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/metacades-presale-set-to-explode-in-2023-get-in-cheap-before-its-too-late/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stark on FTX: If we think this is something we can sell, we’re all in</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/stark-on-ftx-if-we-think-this-is-something-we-can-sell-were-all-in/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/stark-on-ftx-if-we-think-this-is-something-we-can-sell-were-all-in/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Daniela Kirova]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 14:29:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Interview]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/stark-on-ftx-if-we-think-this-is-something-we-can-sell-were-all-in/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SEC stopped ICOs, lending programs, agreements for future tokens Dinner meetings between Bankman-Fried and government officials were &#8220;bad judgment&#8221; John Stark, a former chief of the SEC office of internet enforcement and president of John Reed Stark Consulting, joined CNBC&#8217;s &#8216;Squawk Box&#8217; to discuss the collapse of crypto exchange FTX. Worrying lack of due diligence [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/stark-on-ftx-if-we-think-this-is-something-we-can-sell-were-all-in/">Stark on FTX: If we think this is something we can sell, we’re all in</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>SEC stopped ICOs, lending programs, agreements for future tokens</li>
<li>Dinner meetings between Bankman-Fried and government officials were &ldquo;bad judgment&rdquo;</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p>John Stark, a former chief of the SEC office of internet enforcement and president of John Reed Stark Consulting, joined CNBC&rsquo;s &lsquo;Squawk Box&rsquo; to <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/video/2022/12/29/i-would-be-shocked-if-regulators-did-not-meet-with-ftx-says-john-stark.html">discuss</a> the collapse of crypto exchange FTX.</p>
<h2>Worrying lack of due diligence</h2>
<p>The host raised the issue of due diligence, more specifically the lack thereof where investments in FTX were concerned. He asked Stark what can be done about that. John Stark responded by quoting Sam Bankman-Fried himself:&nbsp;</p>
<p><em>We don&rsquo;t look at the product, service, etc&hellip;we look at whether this is an idea we can pitch to someone. If we think this is something we can sell, then we&rsquo;re all in. Due diligence is absurd. It&rsquo;s just the wrong way to invest. When you invest, you should look for value, you should look for the long-term.&nbsp;</em></p>
<p><strong>The (FTX) business model is something the public isn&rsquo;t used to&hellip;</strong></p>
<p>Stark replied:</p>
<p><em>I agree the model is different, and to me it&rsquo;s absurd, but&hellip;these are investors like everyone else.&nbsp;</em></p>
<p><strong>Which agency&hellip;should be ashamed that we&rsquo;re in this situation, where customers have lost their money and have no claims on anything coming out of bankruptcy?</strong></p>
<p>Stark defended the state agencies in response, pointing out they&rsquo;ve won many cases; they stopped ICOs, lending programs, agreements for future tokens, they stopped <a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/coinbase/">Coinbase</a> from doing the lending program&hellip;They have been very aggressive and are going to be more aggressive when it comes to these crypto intermediaries. &nbsp;</p>
<p>He added that he&nbsp;would be &lsquo;shocked&rsquo; if regulators did not meet with FTX, saying:</p>
<p><em>You try not to meet with con artists.&nbsp;</em></p>
<p>Prompted by the host to discuss the &ldquo;dinner meetings&rdquo; between <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/a-lot-of-people-are-hurt-and-thats-on-me-says-sam-bankman-fried/">Bankman-Fried</a> and government officials, he said those occurrences weren&rsquo;t impeachable offenses, only bad judgment. &nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/stark-on-ftx-if-we-think-this-is-something-we-can-sell-were-all-in/">Stark on FTX: If we think this is something we can sell, we’re all in</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/stark-on-ftx-if-we-think-this-is-something-we-can-sell-were-all-in/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Melinek: Trust in the crypto ecosystem needs to be rebuilt 100%</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/melinek-trust-in-the-crypto-ecosystem-needs-to-be-rebuilt-100/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/melinek-trust-in-the-crypto-ecosystem-needs-to-be-rebuilt-100/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Daniela Kirova]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 14:03:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Interview]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/melinek-trust-in-the-crypto-ecosystem-needs-to-be-rebuilt-100/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Retail investors will sit out of the crypto market in 2023 VC funds aren&#8217;t going to stop investing just because of FTX TechCrunch senior crypto reporter Jacquelyn Melinek talked to CNBC Market Alert about what lies ahead for the crypto market in 2023, after a painful year for digital assets, investors and other stakeholders in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/melinek-trust-in-the-crypto-ecosystem-needs-to-be-rebuilt-100/">Melinek: Trust in the crypto ecosystem needs to be rebuilt 100%</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Retail investors will sit out of the crypto market in 2023</li>
<li>VC funds aren&rsquo;t going to stop investing just because of FTX </li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p>TechCrunch senior crypto reporter Jacquelyn Melinek talked to <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/video/2022/12/29/melinek-theres-a-high-chance-retail-investors-will-sit-out-of-the-crypto-market-in-2023.html">CNBC Market Alert</a> about what lies ahead for the crypto market in 2023, after a painful year for digital assets, investors and other stakeholders in the sector.</p>
<p><strong>Will crypto have any kind of future in 2023?</strong></p>
<p>Jacquelyn Melinek:</p>
<p><em>There&rsquo;s a high chance retail investors will sit out of the crypto market in 2023, especially those who have been interested in the past but have seen many industry changing events like Terra&rsquo;s collapse&hellip;at the same time, the true believers are those who are building the space, so these people <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/best-altcoins-to-buy-during-the-crypto-crash-for-2023/">will continue to be here in 2023</a>.&nbsp;</em></p>
<p><strong>Who will be the main investors in crypto in 2023?</strong></p>
<p><em>VC funds aren&rsquo;t going to stop investing just because of what happened with FTX. We&rsquo;re seeing big brand businesses like Starbucks getting into the space. Beyond that, we&rsquo;re going to keep seeing banks getting into the space.&nbsp;</em></p>
<p><strong>2022 has been a rough year for anyone that needs capital. What needs to happen for the crypto ecosystem to &ldquo;get its mojo&rdquo;?</strong></p>
<p><em>Trust needs to be rebuilt 100%. Regulators <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/us-banking-committee-chairman-suggests-banning-cryptocurrencies/">need to step in</a> and create a framework instead of using old-school techniques that we see with traditional markets.&nbsp;</em></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/melinek-trust-in-the-crypto-ecosystem-needs-to-be-rebuilt-100/">Melinek: Trust in the crypto ecosystem needs to be rebuilt 100%</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/melinek-trust-in-the-crypto-ecosystem-needs-to-be-rebuilt-100/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sandbox, Metacade and Decentraland Price Forecast 2025: Main Players in the Metaverse</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/sandbox-metacade-and-decentraland-price-forecast-2025-main-players-in-the-metaverse/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/sandbox-metacade-and-decentraland-price-forecast-2025-main-players-in-the-metaverse/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice Davies]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 13:53:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/sandbox-metacade-and-decentraland-price-forecast-2025-main-players-in-the-metaverse/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Curious about the future of the metaverse and which projects will dominate? This article will discuss through The Sandbox, Metacade, and Decentraland price forecasts for 2025 and give you an idea of what you might expect in the long-term. What is The Sandbox (SAND)? The Sandbox is a decentralized 3D world that allows users to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sandbox-metacade-and-decentraland-price-forecast-2025-main-players-in-the-metaverse/">Sandbox, Metacade and Decentraland Price Forecast 2025: Main Players in the Metaverse</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Curious about the future of the metaverse and which projects will dominate? This article will discuss through The Sandbox, Metacade, and Decentraland price forecasts for 2025 and give you an idea of what you might expect in the long-term. </p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is The Sandbox (SAND)?</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://www.sandbox.game/en/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>The Sandbox</u></a> is a decentralized 3D world that allows users to create, share, and monetize in-game experiences. The Sandbox lets players build whatever they like using voxels, the blocks that are characteristic of the game&rsquo;s design. This isn&rsquo;t just an aesthetic choice, however; they&rsquo;re designed to be easy to manipulate and allow players to create intricate and detailed objects, like cars, buildings, sculptures, and more.</p>
<p dir="ltr">To build in The Sandbox, players first need to own LAND. LAND tokens are non-fungible, allowing them to be bought and sold with SAND tokens. Once they own LAND, players can choose to buy ASSETs (objects designed by other players) or build items in VoxEdit and use them in the Game Maker to create immersive games and experiences. Companies like Forbes, Gucci, and Warner Music Group have all used these tools to take their first steps in the metaverse, and many more are likely to come.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">The Sandbox (SAND) Price Forecast 2025</h2>
<p dir="ltr">With metaverse adoption growing, it&rsquo;s likely that The Sandbox will live up to its namesake and act as a testing ground for brands looking to join this new digital frontier. Adding more names to its already-growing list of high-profile companies using The Sandbox will likely spur a flood of investment and could push SAND much higher than its current price of $0.42. At the least, $2.50 is definitely achievable, while somewhere between $4.50 and $5 is more likely.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Metacade (MCADE)?</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://metacade.co/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade</u></a> is a community-based platform built for metaverse and play-to-earn (P2E) gaming. It&rsquo;s a hub where gamers go to discover the latest P2E games, explore the rapidly-expanding metaverse space alongside like-minded peers, and make a direct impact on the future of&nbsp;<a href="https://academy.binance.com/en/articles/what-is-gamefi-and-how-does-it-work" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>GameFi</u></a>. At its core, Metacade has everything you&rsquo;ll need to make the most out of metaverse and P2E gaming, like reviews, leaderboards, alpha, forums, and chat rooms, where you can make friends and earn for your contributions to the community.</p>
<p dir="ltr">That&rsquo;s right: every time you post a review, some game-winning tips, or other useful content, you&rsquo;re rewarded with MCADE tokens for your part in growing the platform. You&rsquo;ll also discover regular prize draws and tournaments where you&rsquo;ll go head-to-head against other Metacade users for a chance to win big. There are even plans for a job board in 2024, where you&rsquo;ll find gigs, part-time roles, and salaried positions working with some of the biggest names in Web3.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">By 2025, two of Metacade&rsquo;s most attractive features will be live. The first is its <a href="https://www.investopedia.com/tech/what-dao/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>decentralised autonomous organisation (DAO)</u></a>, where users will be able to participate in shaping the world&rsquo;s first player-owned virtual arcade. The second is the Metagrant. Metagrants are a funding tool that lets Metacade users vote on the development of P2E games. Developers present their ideas to the community, and the one that receives the most votes is awarded funding from the Metacade treasury to help bring their game to life.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Metacade (MCADE) Price Forecast 2025</h2>
<p dir="ltr">With a host of innovative features, a focus on community ownership, and the potential to rapidly attract thousands of players, Metacade is likely to be ahead of the curve by 2025. The MCADE token is currently in presale and is expected to launch to the public at $0.02 per token.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Given that metaverse and GameFi adoption is expected to accelerate by 2025, achieving $0.20 &ndash; a 10x increase &ndash; is a reasonable forecast. If things work out as planned for Metacade, reaching anywhere from $0.50 to $1 is a strong possibility. In other words, a $1,000 investment made at the end of presale could be worth as much as $25,000 to $50,000 by 2025!</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Decentraland (MANA)?</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://decentraland.org/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Decentraland</u></a>, like The Sandbox, is a 3D world where players can own in-game property (also known as LAND), create experiences, and explore others&rsquo; creations. Whereas The Sandbox places a greater emphasis on games, however, Decentraland&rsquo;s purpose is more general, focusing on user-generated content and art. Decentraland also allows users to discover the world around them in VR &ndash; something The Sandbox is yet to offer.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Since its inception in 2017, Decentraland has grown to host art galleries, museums, casinos, nightclubs, hotels, and more. It also regularly hosts events, like concerts, conferences, and social meetups for the community to enjoy. As part of its DAO structure, Decentraland allows users to attend a virtual town hall meeting and vote to determine the future of the platform.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Decentraland (MANA) Price Forecast 2025</h2>
<p dir="ltr">While Decentraland doesn&rsquo;t have partnerships with as many brands as The Sandbox, its status as one of the oldest metaverse projects is likely to give it an edge. As more players join the metaverse revolution, MANA could see a new wave of investment and pick-up traction, sending it much higher than today&rsquo;s price of $0.32.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The most optimistic Decentraland price prediction for 2025 would be for MANA to return back to its November 2021 highs, or somewhere between $5 and $6. The more realistic Decentraland price prediction for 2025 would be around $3.50 to $4.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Metacade (MCADE) is an Immensely Undervalued Metaverse Project</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The Sandbox, Metacade, and Decentraland are all likely to do well over the next few years as more users join the metaverse. But while the ship has probably already sailed for massive gains in SAND or MANA, MCADE has everything to gain. With the token still in stage 1 of presale, there couldn&rsquo;t be a better time to get in. Already, Metacade has sold over $1.55m in MCADE, and this number is expected to reach at least $20 million by the end of presale. Don&rsquo;t wait &ndash; grab your share of MCADE before it&rsquo;s too late!</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>You can buy Sandbox and Decentraland at eToro&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://coinjournal.net/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=OTg5NDQ" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong><u>here</u></strong></a><strong>.</strong></p>
<p><strong>You can participate in the Metacade presale&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://metacade.co/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong><u>here</u></strong></a><strong>.</strong></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sandbox-metacade-and-decentraland-price-forecast-2025-main-players-in-the-metaverse/">Sandbox, Metacade and Decentraland Price Forecast 2025: Main Players in the Metaverse</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/sandbox-metacade-and-decentraland-price-forecast-2025-main-players-in-the-metaverse/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>70% of unregulated exchanges’ volume is wash trading: study</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/70-of-unregulated-exchanges-volume-is-wash-trading-study/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/70-of-unregulated-exchanges-volume-is-wash-trading-study/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 13:38:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Surveys and Reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/70-of-unregulated-exchanges-volume-is-wash-trading-study/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An average of 70% transaction volume on unregulated exchanges are in wash trades. The statistic is part of a report recently released by the National Bureau of Economic Research (NBER). Incentives for exchanges include rankings and short term price movements. A new study on the use of crypto exchanges suggests that nearly three quarters of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/70-of-unregulated-exchanges-volume-is-wash-trading-study/">70% of unregulated exchanges’ volume is wash trading: study</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>An average of 70% transaction volume on unregulated exchanges are in wash trades.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>The statistic is part of a report recently released by the National Bureau of Economic Research (NBER).</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><strong><em>Incentives for exchanges include rankings and short term price movements.</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">A new study on the use of <a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/">crypto exchanges</a> suggests that nearly three quarters of the transactions relate to wash trading activities.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The National Bureau of Economic Research (NBER) says in its <a href="https://www.nber.org/system/files/working_papers/w30783/w30783.pdf" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">research paper</a> &ldquo;<em>Crypto Wash Trading</em>&rdquo; that a bigger percentage of trading volume on unregulated exchanges was down to fake trading &ndash; transactions meant to mislead.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">About 70% of trading volume on unregulated exchanges is fake</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The study focused on both tier 1 and tier 2 exchanges, with the former platforms ranked within the top 700 as indicated on data tracking site SimilarWeb.com.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The researchers also focused on four of the most popular and heavily traded cryptocurrencies &ndash; Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH), Litecoin (LTC), and Ripple (XRP).&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to the findings, crypto exchanges with a longer market presence and global user bases were less likely to engage in wash trading. However, less prominent exchanges seem to attract most of the fake volume behaviour, with statistics showing that an average of 70% of volume on unregulated exchanges was tied to wash trading.</p>
<p dir="ltr">On some tier 1 exchanges, wash trades account for up to 53.4% of reported volume. But the percentage is much higher for unregulated tier 2 platforms, where crypto wash trades can account for more than 81.7% of volume. The average wash trading for all unregulated exchanges is an estimated 77.5%, the study found.</p>
<p dir="ltr">On who&rsquo;s likely to engage in the illegal practice, the researchers wrote:</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>Wash trading is highly likely to be conducted using automated programs or bots, considering the efficiency and quantity of trade orders required. Strong evidence suggests that most wash trading is done by bots, which can be easily added to the trading structure scripted by simple Python programs</em>.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">For exchanges, short-term incentives inform decisions to allow wash trading, including the fact that trading volumes impact exchange rankings by up to 46 positions. Unregulated exchanges (most probably) keen to move up the rankings would opt for this, while the impact of volume on prices is also another factor.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/70-of-unregulated-exchanges-volume-is-wash-trading-study/">70% of unregulated exchanges’ volume is wash trading: study</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/70-of-unregulated-exchanges-volume-is-wash-trading-study/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>SEC vs Ripple verdict will have implications for Ethereum too</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/sec-vs-ripple-verdict-will-have-implications-for-ethereum-too/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/sec-vs-ripple-verdict-will-have-implications-for-ethereum-too/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 11:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple Labs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/sec-vs-ripple-verdict-will-have-implications-for-ethereum-too/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The SEC vs Ripple verdict is expected to come in 2023. The implications will be significant for Ethereum too. The SEC vs&#160;Ripple verdict will likely be the biggest&#160;crypto news&#160;of 2023. While no date has been set for the verdict, analysts expect that it will happen in the coming year. It is still too early to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sec-vs-ripple-verdict-will-have-implications-for-ethereum-too/">SEC vs Ripple verdict will have implications for Ethereum too</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The SEC vs Ripple verdict is expected to come in 2023.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The implications will be significant for Ethereum too.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">The SEC vs&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/ripple/"><u>Ripple</u></a> verdict will likely be the biggest&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/"><u>crypto news</u></a><strong>&nbsp;</strong>of 2023. While no date has been set for the verdict, analysts expect that it will happen in the coming year. It is still too early to predict the outcome of the case, its implication will go beyond Ripple and XRP. It will have an impact on other cryptocurrencies,&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum"><u>Ethereum</u></a> in particular.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">SEC vs Ripple: the basics</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) filed charges against Ripple on December 20th 2020. In the lawsuit, the agency sued the company and its executive of conducting a $1.3 billion unregistered security offering in 2013.</p>
<p dir="ltr">It&nbsp;<a href="https://www.sec.gov/news/press-release/2020-338"><u>alleges</u></a> that Ripple and its execs raised money by selling XRP to investors in the US and around the world. Also, its execs raised $600 million through token sales and failed to register them under the federal securities laws.</p>
<p dir="ltr">By doing that Ripple deprived investors of the required protections that happen when a company raises funds. They also lacked access to information that they were entitled to.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Ripple denies these allegations and argues that the SEC knew that XRP was not a financial security. It points to a speech made by William Hinman, a former SEC director, who stated that ETH was not a security.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Implications bigger than Ripple</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The biggest implication of the SEC vs Ripple verdict will be on Ripple itself. However, analysts believe that other cryptocurrencies like Ethereum will be impacted as well.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As you recall, Ethereum made a transition from a proof-of-work crypto into a proof-of-stake coin in 2022. By so-doing, it made it possible for people to stake the coin and earn returns. Staking is a process where people bond their tokens to a validator and then receive rewards every month.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In a statement after the merge, Gary Gensler, SECs chairman said that he believed that Ethereum was now financial security.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, if the SEC wins, it means that it will train its eyes on other cryptocurrencies, including ETH. It will use the arguments made in court to prove its case.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">A lawsuit against ETH and other platforms in its ecosystem will have a major implication on the coin. For one, many exchanges will delist it in the United States to remain in good books with the SEC. Many exchanges have already delisted XRP in their platforms.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In addition to Ethereum, the SEC will use its argument to go after other platforms that had token sales in the past few years.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy Ripple</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>

    <p>eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=OTg5Mzg&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=VA&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy XRP with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    Bitstamp</h3>

    <p>Bitstamp is a leading cryptocurrency exchange which offers trading in fiat currencies or popular cryptocurrencies.

Bitstamp is a fully regulated company which offers users an intuitive interface, a high degree of security for your digital assets, excellent customer support and multiple withdrawal methods.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/bitstamp-crypto?guid=OTg5Mzg&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=VA&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy XRP with Bitstamp today            </a>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sec-vs-ripple-verdict-will-have-implications-for-ethereum-too/">SEC vs Ripple verdict will have implications for Ethereum too</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/sec-vs-ripple-verdict-will-have-implications-for-ethereum-too/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alameda liquidates millions worth of tokens for Bitcoin</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/alameda-liquidates-millions-worth-of-tokens-for-bitcoin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 10:41:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/alameda-liquidates-millions-worth-of-tokens-for-bitcoin/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Alameda Research addresses sent millions worth of tokens to decentralised exchanges and crypto mixers on Wednesday. According to on-chain data, the tokens were swapped into USDT before being converted into Bitcoin. The Alameda wallets sprung into life a few days after FTX co-founder Sam Bankman-Fried was released on a $250 million bail. Crypto wallets linked [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/alameda-liquidates-millions-worth-of-tokens-for-bitcoin/">Alameda liquidates millions worth of tokens for Bitcoin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>Alameda Research addresses sent millions worth of tokens to decentralised exchanges and crypto mixers on Wednesday.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>According to on-chain data, the tokens were swapped into USDT before being converted into Bitcoin.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><strong><em>The Alameda wallets sprung into life a few days after FTX co-founder Sam Bankman-Fried was released on a $250 million bail.</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/wallets/">Crypto wallets</a> linked to Alameda Research, the quant trading arm of collapsed cryptocurrency exchange FTX, were massively active on Wednesday, on-chain data shows.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Alameda addresses, as data shared online showed, actively sold several small cap cryptocurrencies, swapping these for <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> and in some cases Ethereum.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Alameda sells millions worth of tokens</h2>
<p dir="ltr">According to details <a href="https://mobile.twitter.com/themlpx/status/1607937597783035904" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">shared</a> on Twitter by Martin Lee, a data journalist at blockchain analytics platform Nansen, there were multiple odd transactions that seemed to swap tokens in Alameda wallets for Ethereum and Tether stablecoin USDT.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The funds were then sent to new wallets via decentralised exchanges (DEXs), including ChangeNow and FixedFloat.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Elsewhere, on-chain data shared by blockchain research firm Arkham Intelligence pointed to Alameda wallets offloading over $1.7 million in various tokens.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">In total, Alameda-related wallets have mixed:</p>
<p>270.5Eth through ChangeNOW (~$325k)<br>800k USDT through Fixedfloat<br>200k through Curve SynthSwap (to native BTC)<br>200k through Airswap<br>200k through other crypto-mixing services</p>
<p>reaching a total of $1.7M that has been taken.</p>
<p>&mdash; Arkham | Crypto Intelligence (@ArkhamIntel) <a href="https://twitter.com/ArkhamIntel/status/1608205044930969601?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 28, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">According to the platform, the sales happened on the open market &ndash; a scenario that likely was behind the sharp drop in prices for several tokens. The Ethereum-based cryptocurrencies the wallets sold include Ether (ETH), Curve (CRV), USD Coin (USDC), Dai (DAI), and convex (CVX).</p>
<p dir="ltr">The tokens were sent to two wallets, swapped for USDT and then converted into BTC, blockchain sleuth ZachXBT <a href="https://twitter.com/zachxbt/status/1607915930440302592" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">tweeted</a> on Wednesday.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Alameda wallets came alive after weeks of dormancy, with these transactions intensifying as former FTX CEO Sam Bankman-Fried settled at home following released from jail on a $250 million bail. The sale of multiple tokens also coincided with a sharp price decline for Solana (SOL).</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/alameda-liquidates-millions-worth-of-tokens-for-bitcoin/">Alameda liquidates millions worth of tokens for Bitcoin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin holding $16K amid worst annual performance since 2018</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-holding-16k-amid-worst-annual-performance-since-2018/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-holding-16k-amid-worst-annual-performance-since-2018/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-holding-16k-amid-worst-annual-performance-since-2018/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin was changing hands near $16,600 on Wednesday, about 1% down in the past 24 hours. The cryptocurrency is heading for its worst yearly returns since 2018. Stocks have also hit a brutal patch in 2022, with major US indexes headed for their worst annual returns since 2008. Bitcoin remained uncharacteristically uneventful on Wednesday, trading [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-holding-16k-amid-worst-annual-performance-since-2018/">Bitcoin holding $16K amid worst annual performance since 2018</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>Bitcoin was changing hands near $16,600 on Wednesday, about 1% down in the past 24 hours.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>The cryptocurrency is heading for its worst yearly returns since 2018.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><strong><em>Stocks have also hit a brutal patch in 2022, with major US indexes headed for their worst annual returns since 2008.</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> remained uncharacteristically uneventful on Wednesday, trading around $16,600 as investors weighed an end to a brutal 2022.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The benchmark cryptocurrency was just in the red during early afternoon trading (2:10 pm ET) as Wall Street also turned negative amid fading optimism over China&rsquo;s reopening.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Markets to end 2022 lower</h2>
<p dir="ltr">In crypto, Bitcoin volatility has been at its 2022 low this week, with the surge towards $17,000 cooling off to leave the cryptocurrency 67% down in the past year.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In fact, 2022 is shaping as the year with the second-worst returns for BTC since 2010. The digital gold&rsquo;s performance during this markedly bear year has the asset on track for a worst return since the 73% drawdown in 2018.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In the 2014 bear market, Bitcoin price fell 58%, with other years with lower returns being +35% in 2015 and +66% in 2021 &ndash; indeed Bitcoin is more than 75% down since its all-time high in 2021.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As Bitcoin struggles to hold onto gains above $16k, the picture across the stock market is similar for the major US indexes. The S&amp;P 500 is down 4.1% this month and over 20% year-to-date, while the Dow and the Nasdaq are -2.5% and -7.1% over the past 30 days respectively.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The historically bullish season for equities has been largely negative, with ongoing investor jitters around inflation and rate hikes, and the overall outlook for the global economy, adding to the downward pressure that has persisted for most of the year.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As such, while Bitcoin is set to see its worst yearly performance since 2018, US stocks are poised for their worst annual returns since 2008.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-holding-16k-amid-worst-annual-performance-since-2018/">Bitcoin holding $16K amid worst annual performance since 2018</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-holding-16k-amid-worst-annual-performance-since-2018/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
