<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 20:52:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin could hit $120,000 by the end of 2024: Standard Chartered</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-price-forecast-2024-standard-chartered-analyst/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wajeeh Khan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 20:52:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Standard Chartered]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=145549</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Standard Chartered analyst sees another 60% upside in Bitcoin this year. Geoff Kendrick explained his bullish view on BTC in a research note today. Bitcoin is already up a whopping 85% since the start of the year 2023. The massive rally in Bitcoin since the start of this year is just a drop in the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-price-forecast-2024-standard-chartered-analyst/">Bitcoin could hit $120,000 by the end of 2024: Standard Chartered</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Standard Chartered analyst sees another 60% upside in Bitcoin this year.</li>
<li>Geoff Kendrick explained his bullish view on BTC in a research note today.</li>
<li>Bitcoin is already up a whopping 85% since the start of the year 2023.</li>
</ul>
<p>The massive rally in <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> since the start of this year is just a drop in the bucket compared to where it&rsquo;s headed, as per a Standard Chartered analyst.</p>
<h2>BTC could climb another 60% this year</h2>
<p>On Monday, Geoff Kendrick said the world&rsquo;s largest cryptocurrency could climb further to $50,000 by the end of 2023 which suggests another 60% upside from here.</p>
<p>The analyst is convinced that a continued increase in the price of BTC will make it rewarding for miners to stock huge amounts of it. Reduced net supply, in return, will help the cryptocurrency reach for the skies, he added.</p>
<blockquote><p>If BTC rises [as] we expect by end-2023, share of newly mined being sold should fall to 20%-30%. That&rsquo;s a net annual reduction in selling of BTC 250,000.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Bitcoin supply is set to halve next year</h2>
<p>Note that the total supply of Bitcoin is scheduled to halve in April or May of 2024.</p>
<p>The Standard Chartered analyst sees several other factors helping unlock significant upside in BTC next year. One of them is the recent <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-05-02/bitcoin-climbs-as-us-bank-failure-bolsters-crypto-narrative" target="_blank" rel="noopener">banking crisis</a>. Earlier this year, he had forecast Bitcoin at $100,000 by the end of 2024. In a note today, though, Kendrick said:</p>
<blockquote><p>We now think this estimate is too conservative, and we, therefore, see a 20% upside to our end-2024 target.</p></blockquote>
<p>That essentially means Bitcoin could hit $120,000 next year. The cryptocurrency is expected to benefit if the Securities and Exchange Commission greenlights a Spot Bitcoin ETF that many asset managers, including <a href="https://decrypt.co/147177/blackrock-spot-bitcoin-etf-filing-sec-coinbase-surveillance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BlackRock</a>, have recently filed for.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-price-forecast-2024-standard-chartered-analyst/">Bitcoin could hit $120,000 by the end of 2024: Standard Chartered</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Former SEC Chair says Bitcoin ETF approval &#8216;hard to resist&#8217;</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/former-sec-chair-says-bitcoin-etf-approval-hard-to-resist/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/former-sec-chair-says-bitcoin-etf-approval-hard-to-resist/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 20:25:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Policy and Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US regulation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/former-sec-chair-says-bitcoin-etf-approval-hard-to-resist/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Jay Clayton shared his opinion during an interview with CNBC on Monday. The former SEC chair says if applicants demonstrate efficacy and have surveillance, it would be hard for the SEC to deny a spot Bitcoin ETF. BlackRock, Fidelity and others have market surveillance agreements with Coinbase. The US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/former-sec-chair-says-bitcoin-etf-approval-hard-to-resist/">Former SEC Chair says Bitcoin ETF approval &#8216;hard to resist&#8217;</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Jay Clayton shared his opinion during an interview with CNBC on Monday.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The former SEC chair says if applicants demonstrate efficacy and have surveillance, it would be hard for the SEC to deny a spot Bitcoin ETF.</li>
<li dir="ltr">BlackRock, Fidelity and others have market surveillance agreements with Coinbase.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">The US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has so far denied all the applications for a spot <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/bitcoin-etf/">Bitcoin ETF</a> to come before it.</p>
<p dir="ltr">But now might be the time the regulator gives a seal of approval to the product, former SEC Chair Jay Clayton said on Monday.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>If they&rsquo;re right that the spot market has similar efficacy to the futures market, it would be hard to resist approving a bitcoin ETF</em>,&rdquo; Clayton <a href="https://twitter.com/SquawkCNBC/status/1678381857367289856" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">told</a> CNBC&rsquo;s Squawk Box.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">"I was very skeptical with trading in the <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#bitcoin</a> market when I was SEC Chair," says Jay Clayton. "But if you can demonstrate that the spot market has similar efficacy to the futures market, it would be hard to resist approving a <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#bitcoin</a> ETF." <a href="https://t.co/mig05ZUwIL">pic.twitter.com/mig05ZUwIL</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Squawk Box (@SquawkCNBC) <a href="https://twitter.com/SquawkCNBC/status/1678381857367289856?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 10, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">SEC&rsquo;s approval of futures ETFs</h2>
<p dir="ltr">This is the argument that applicants have put forth, particularly with BlackRock, Fidelity and others taking steps to comply with requirements previously cited as reasons for SEC&rsquo;s disapproval.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Notably, proposals by the Cboe and Nasdaq have included market surveillance agreements &ndash; the so-called surveillance sharing agreement (SSA) with major cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Noting this, and the fact that the SEC has approved futures-based ETFs on this basis, Clayton added:</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>When the SEC approved a futures-based ETF, they said &lsquo;let&rsquo;s look at the futures market, we see the surveillance, we see the protections in that market for the investor, that are sufficient. We don&rsquo;t see them in the spot market, so we&rsquo;re going to make that distinction&rsquo;. I think what the institutions are arguing is that those distinctions have gone away and that the spot product is now less drag, more efficient for the investor</em>.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">With no delta in regulation and efficacy, the SEC will have to approve a first spot Bitcoin ETF for the US market. As highlighted earlier, Clayton believes it would be &ldquo;hard&rdquo; for SEC to &ldquo;resist&rdquo; a spot ETF any further if applicants prove efficacy.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As CoinJournal <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/secs-spot-bitcoin-etf-approval-fairly-high-bernstein/">reported</a> last week, analysts at $650 billion asset manager Bernstein noted that chances of a spot Bitcoin ETF approval are &ldquo;fairly high.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The crypto market has been largely optimistic of an approval ever since BlackRock filed its proposal in mid-June. The optimism was reflected in the price of Bitcoin rallying after the news to reach a new year-to-date high above $31k last month.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/former-sec-chair-says-bitcoin-etf-approval-hard-to-resist/">Former SEC Chair says Bitcoin ETF approval &#8216;hard to resist&#8217;</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/former-sec-chair-says-bitcoin-etf-approval-hard-to-resist/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Raoul Pal shares massive price prediction for Solana</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/raoul-pal-shares-massive-price-prediction-for-solana/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/raoul-pal-shares-massive-price-prediction-for-solana/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 18:54:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/raoul-pal-shares-massive-price-prediction-for-solana/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Raoul Pal, CEO of Real Vision is super bullish on Solana (SOL). According to Pal, SOL could rally 20x from current levels if it mirrors Ethereum&#8217;s 47x move from its 2018 low. He also says Bitcoin price could triple from its all-time high level amid a supply crunch in 2023. Raoul Pal, the founder &#38; [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/raoul-pal-shares-massive-price-prediction-for-solana/">Raoul Pal shares massive price prediction for Solana</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Raoul Pal, CEO of Real Vision is super bullish on Solana (SOL).</li>
<li dir="ltr">According to Pal, SOL could rally 20x from current levels if it mirrors Ethereum&rsquo;s 47x move from its 2018 low.</li>
<li dir="ltr">He also says Bitcoin price could triple from its all-time high level amid a supply crunch in 2023.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Raoul Pal, the founder &amp; CEO of Real Vision suggests&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/solana/"><u>Solana (SOL)</u></a> could embark on a massive price move. If the &ldquo;dream scenario&rdquo; for the world&rsquo;s 10th&nbsp;largest cryptocurrency by market cap occurs, SOL could outperform both&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/"><u>Bitcoin (BTC)</u></a> and Ethereum (ETH).</p>
<p dir="ltr">Pal shared his massively bullish outlook for Solana during a recent&nbsp;<a href="https://youtu.be/fINxauWFYtA" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>interview</u></a> in which he shared &nbsp;views on varied topics. These &nbsp;include AI and its impact on jobs, BlackRock&rsquo;s ETF filing and CEO Larry Fink&rsquo;s remarks about BTC.</p>
<p dir="ltr">He also aired his thoughts on the Ethereum/Bitcoin flippening debate, central bank digital currencies (CBCDs), global economy and government money printing before briefly offering his&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/solana/price-prediction/"><u>price prediction Solana</u></a>. The macro guru also shared predictions for Bitcoin and Ethereum.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Solana price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr">On what he thought of the price performance of BTC, ETH and SOL in the next bull cycle, Pal shared a highly bullish projection for Ethereum&rsquo;s &ldquo;competitor.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Currently, Solana trades around $21, about 1.4% down in the past 24 hours.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, the cryptocurrency is more than 10% in the green over the past seven days and 43% in the past 30 days. While it&rsquo;s also down 43% from its value a year ago, Pal noted that the bottom might have come when prices fell to around $9 in December 2022.</p>
<p dir="ltr">With this outlook, Pal suggests SOL could do what ETH achieved after bottoming in 2018 &ndash; roaring to its all-time high above $4,800 during the last bull market. The macro guru says that if Solana takes on this projection, the potential gains could be staggering.</p>
<p dir="ltr">He compared the 47x that ETH saw after the 2018 low to what Solana could do. He opined:</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>Look&hellip; there&rsquo;s a possibility &ndash; a dream scenario &ndash; that Solana does what ETH did from the 2018 low which was a 47x. The Solana low was nine bucks, so you could do the maths [and] the numbers are potentially very interesting</em>.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">While Solana&rsquo;s price might not do the 47x or so that Ethereum price managed since its bottom in 2018, Pal predicts a &ldquo;20 something x&rdquo; move. According to him, this is a reasonable outlook for a protocol that&rsquo;s battle-tested and is seeing a huge spike in network and ecosystem activity.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Should Pal&rsquo;s bullish outlook for SOL price hold, it would mean an eventual burst to prices above $400 for the cryptocurrency. In the last bull market, Solana rose to the all-time high at $260.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitcoin and Ethereum price predictions</h2>
<p dir="ltr">For BTC and ETH, Pal agreed with projections of a 3x and 5x respectively &ndash; suggesting Bitcoin could more than triple its value during the next bull cycle. However, that is from the all-time highs that was $69,000 in November 2021.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Trippling from that ATH would mean a 6x from current prices, he opined. But that would depend on severa factors that could dictate market direction.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>It&rsquo;s very difficult to predict where it actually goes, but what we can say is [that] it&rsquo;s reasonable that Bitcoin from all-time highs doubles or triples. That&rsquo;s not asking a lot. That will be the worst bull market in Bitcoin&rsquo;s history.</em>&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to him, a potential supply crunch in 2023 is what could squeeze Bitcoin to a new all-time high.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/raoul-pal-shares-massive-price-prediction-for-solana/">Raoul Pal shares massive price prediction for Solana</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/raoul-pal-shares-massive-price-prediction-for-solana/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Presale of the new AI-powered Shiba Menu project attracting huge investor attention</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/presale-of-the-new-ai-powered-shiba-menu-project-attracting-huge-investor-attention/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/presale-of-the-new-ai-powered-shiba-menu-project-attracting-huge-investor-attention/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 16:41:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOGE]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/presale-of-the-new-ai-powered-shiba-menu-project-attracting-huge-investor-attention/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Shiba Menu is a new Shiba-themed AI-powered cryptocurrency project. It is currently conducting a presale for its native token Shiba Menu (SHMU). One SHMU is currently going for $0.012250, however, it is only a matter of hours before that price increases to $0.012475. Shiba Menu, a new cryptocurrency project taking advantage of the meme coin [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/presale-of-the-new-ai-powered-shiba-menu-project-attracting-huge-investor-attention/">Presale of the new AI-powered Shiba Menu project attracting huge investor attention</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul class="decimal_type">
<li>Shiba Menu is a new Shiba-themed AI-powered cryptocurrency project.</li>
<li>It is currently conducting a presale for its native token Shiba Menu (SHMU).</li>
<li>One SHMU is currently going for $0.012250, however, it is only a matter of hours before that price increases to $0.012475.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news">Shiba Menu</a>, a new cryptocurrency project taking advantage of the meme coin and artificial intelligence hype has launched its token presale, which has attracted quite a huge number of investors within the first few days.</p>
<p>The Shiba Menu presale has already raised in excess of $294,961 and the price of SHMU tokens is expected to rise in the next 2 hours.</p>
<h2>What is Shiba Menu?</h2>
<p>Shiba Memu is a ground-breaking cryptocurrency token that combines <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/blockchain/">blockchain</a> and AI to produce an unstoppable, fully independent marketing powerhouse. It is a brand-new and ground-breaking meme token.</p>
<p>Shiba Menu will develop its own marketing strategies, write its own PR, and advertise itself in pertinent forums and social networks, in contrast to other meme tokens that depend heavily on human teams&rsquo; marketing efforts to gain traction.</p>
<p>Shiba Menu&rsquo;s native token SHMU is a distinctive and alluring investment because of its self-sufficient marketing abilities, which are supported by AI technology.</p>
<h2>How Shiba Menu works</h2>
<p>The Shiba Menu platform uses blockchain and AI technologies to generate content including press releases, social content, and marketing materials. The platform&rsquo;s AI continually analyzes data and then self-publishes the generated content across relevant forums and social platforms.</p>
<p>The Shiba Menu interactive AI dashboard responds to user inquiries and channels data from every newly developed insight into conversations it holds with real people across forums and social channels.</p>
<p>Besides blockchain technology, Shiba Menu uses AI-powered Natural Language Processing (NLP), Sentiment Analysis, Image and Video Recognition, Predictive Analytics, and Personalization.</p>
<p>Shiba Menu pegs its success on its self-sufficient marketing and promotion solutions that make it a low-maintenance crypto project. It is powered by a cross-chain token called SHMU token, which operates on both <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/what-is-ethereum/">Ethereum</a> and Binance Smart Chain (BSC).</p>
<p>85% (850 million) of the total SHMU tokens in circulation supply are currently up for grabs in the ongoing token presale that will see 350 million tokens sold on BSC and 500 million tokens sold on Ethereum.</p>
<h2>Why invest in Shiba Menu?</h2>
<p>The meme token has witnessed parabolic growth in recent years just like the artificial intelligence (AI) market that has seen a lot of hype since the launch of ChatGPT. According to Coinmarketcap, the meme token market grew by over $20 billion in two years between 2020 and 2022.</p>
<p>The success of meme tokens like <a href="https://coinjournal.net/shiba-inu/what-is-shiba-inu/">Shiba Inu (SHIB)</a> and <a href="https://coinjournal.net/dogecoin/what-is-dogecoin/">Dogecoin (DOGE)</a> has prompted the development of an array of meme tokens most of which hit the ground running. For instance, the PEPE and KEKE mem coins which were recently launched are now among the most trending cryptocurrencies after witnessing a huge surge in trading volumes.</p>
<p>Going by the recent trends, the demand for meme tokens is only expected to grow even further in the years ahead, offering a great market opportunity for Shiba Menu (SHMU) meme token. The self-sufficient, AI-powered marketing capabilities make SHMU a compelling, highly attractive opportunity for investors.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/presale-of-the-new-ai-powered-shiba-menu-project-attracting-huge-investor-attention/">Presale of the new AI-powered Shiba Menu project attracting huge investor attention</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/presale-of-the-new-ai-powered-shiba-menu-project-attracting-huge-investor-attention/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is the Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC) stock a good buy now?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/is-the-grayscale-bitcoin-trust-gbtc-stock-a-good-buy-now/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/is-the-grayscale-bitcoin-trust-gbtc-stock-a-good-buy-now/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 16:08:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/is-the-grayscale-bitcoin-trust-gbtc-stock-a-good-buy-now/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Grayscale Bitcoin Trust has jumped by over 168% from December lows. The trust is hoping for Bitcoin to have a bullish breakout above the YTD high. The Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC) stock price has moved sideways in the past few days as Bitcoin remained stuck at $30,000. GBTC was trading at $20, the highest [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/is-the-grayscale-bitcoin-trust-gbtc-stock-a-good-buy-now/">Is the Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC) stock a good buy now?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The Grayscale Bitcoin Trust has jumped by over 168% from December lows.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The trust is hoping for Bitcoin to have a bullish breakout above the YTD high.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">The Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC) stock price has moved sideways in the past few days as Bitcoin remained stuck at $30,000. GBTC was trading at $20, the highest level since June last year. It has jumped by more than 168% from the lowest level in December.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitcoin consolidation continues</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The Grayscale Bitcoin Trust is the biggest fund in the cryptocurrency industry. It has over $18.9 billion of assets under management (AUM). Over the years, the fund has jumped by more than 19,200% since its inception.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Grayscale Bitcoin Trust stores its assets in an offline cold wallet with Coinbase Custody Trust. Most companies that have filed for Bitcoin ETFs have also selected&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/coinbase/"><u>Coinbase</u></a> as the custodian of the funds.</p>
<p dir="ltr">GBTC creators have filed to convert the GBTC fund into an exchange-traded fund (ETF). Indeed, the company has sued the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) in a case that could change the industry.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">A ruling in favor of the company will open the possibility for other companies like Blackrock and Invesco to launch their spot ETFs.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">GBTC is widely known for its massive discount to its assets, The market price per share stands at $19.81 compared to its holdings per share of $22. This discount has been narrowing in the past few weeks.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The next key important catalyst for the GBTC stock price will be&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/"><u>Bitcoin</u></a>&rsquo;s price action. Bitcoin has remained stuck slightly above the key support level at $30,000. Therefore, if Bitcoin rebounds, there is a likelihood that the Grayscale Bitcoin Trust will continue rising as well.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">GBTC stock price forecast</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/10/1689005283450-3bc36ee2-b4f5-4838-bec2-08be5178c44d.png" style="width: 579px;height: 281.78px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="579" height="281.78"></p>
<p dir="ltr">The daily chart shows that the GBTC share price has been in a strong bullish trend in the past few days. It has managed to move above the important resistance point at $18.53, the highest level on April 10th.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Grayscale Bitcoin Trust stock price has moved above the 50-day and 100-day exponential moving averages (EMA). Further, the Relative Strength Index (RSI) has moved slightly below the overbought level to 69. GBTC&rsquo;s volume has moved downwards.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, there is a likelihood that the GBTC price will continue rising as buyers target the next key resistance level at $25. A drop below the support at $18.53 will invalidate the bullish view.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/is-the-grayscale-bitcoin-trust-gbtc-stock-a-good-buy-now/">Is the Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC) stock a good buy now?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/is-the-grayscale-bitcoin-trust-gbtc-stock-a-good-buy-now/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto investment products hit 3-week streak of inflows</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-investment-products-hit-3-week-stretch-of-inflows/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 15:03:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Institutional investors]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-investment-products-hit-3-week-stretch-of-inflows/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin inflows over last week was $133 million, compared to Ethereum&#8217;s $2.9 million. Total inflows into crypto asset products was $136 million, with this the third consecutive week of inflows. Altcoins such as XRP, Solana, Polygon, Litecoin and Aave saw minor inflows. Inflows into crypto investment products was $136 million this past week as the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-investment-products-hit-3-week-stretch-of-inflows/">Crypto investment products hit 3-week streak of inflows</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Bitcoin inflows over last week was $133 million, compared to Ethereum&rsquo;s $2.9 million.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Total inflows into crypto asset products was $136 million, with this the third consecutive week of inflows.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Altcoins such as XRP, Solana, Polygon, Litecoin and Aave saw minor inflows.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Inflows into crypto investment products was $136 million this past week as the confidence in the digital assets investment space continued to build momentum.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to data from crypto asset management firm CoinShares, last week marks the third consecutive week of inflows. With investors putting over $470 million into various crypto products, the 3-week period has resulted in a full correction of the outflows recorded over the previous nine weeks.</p>
<p dir="ltr">CoinShares&rsquo; <a href="https://blog.coinshares.com/volume-139-digital-asset-fund-flows-weekly-report-33b877f6baee" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">report</a> highlighting the digital asset investment market puts the year-to-date flows at a net positive of $231 million.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitcoin saw $133 in inflows</h2>
<p dir="ltr">With <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> mostly bullish in the past few weeks, institutional investors&rsquo; focus has largely been predominantly on Bitcoin products. That is explained by the inflows of $133 million for Bitcoin over the week, masively dwarfing Ethereum&rsquo;s $2.9 million. Short-bitcoin products indeed saw outflows of $1.8 million to reinforce this perspective.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Leading altcoins such as XRP, Solana, Polygon, Litecoin and Aave recorded minor inflows. Even then, the signal is investors have a mostly positive outlook for the flagship crypto asset compared to altcoins.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bullish crypto market after BlackRock ETF filing</h2>
<p dir="ltr">This has come at a time when sentiment across the broader crypto market has largely flipped bullish and spot prices ticked up for most cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Numerous spot Bitcoin ETF proposals, led by top asset manager BlackRock, helped bulls push to new YTD levels. [<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-cash-price-hits-1-year-high-as-bch-soars-72-this-week/">Read more</a>]</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, the uptick in inflows has come amid reduced trading turnover. The past week had a total investment products volume of $ 1 billion, compared to an average of $2.5 billion over the two weeks prior. Per CoinShares, low volumes seen over the week are likely due to seasonal effects &ndash; a scenario typically observed between July and August.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-investment-products-hit-3-week-stretch-of-inflows/">Crypto investment products hit 3-week streak of inflows</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chancer mainnet launch after current presale a perfect timing for 2024 Olympics</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-mainnet-launch-after-current-presale-a-perfect-timing-for-2024-olympics/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-mainnet-launch-after-current-presale-a-perfect-timing-for-2024-olympics/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 14:07:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Events]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-mainnet-launch-after-current-presale-a-perfect-timing-for-2024-olympics/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Chancer mainnet will go live in Q1 2024 after the product development testnet in Q4 2023. The mainnet launch will allow users to bet on Olympic Games which will start on Friday, 26 Jul 2024. The ongoing Chancer presale is scheduled to end in Q3 2023 to give way for the launch sequence to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-mainnet-launch-after-current-presale-a-perfect-timing-for-2024-olympics/">Chancer mainnet launch after current presale a perfect timing for 2024 Olympics</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>The Chancer mainnet will go live in Q1 2024 after the product development testnet in Q4 2023.</li>
<li>The mainnet launch will allow users to bet on Olympic Games which will start on Friday, 26 Jul 2024.</li>
<li>The ongoing Chancer presale is scheduled to end in Q3 2023 to give way for the launch sequence to begin.</li>
</ul>
<p>While the decentralized betting platform <a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news">Chancer</a> offers an opportunity for users to bet on anything including on events between friends, the first major gaming event after the platform&rsquo;s mainnet launch will be the 2024 Olympics.</p>
<p>A majority of the currently available betting platforms major on ball games especially football and basketball. However since Chancer is designed to allow users to literally bet on anything, it will be the first major betting platform for those who would want to bet on the many Olympics events.</p>
<h2>Chancer&rsquo;s revolutionary betting approach</h2>
<p>Chancer is the world&rsquo;s first decentralized predictive market-making platform and it will give bettors the opportunity to customize and create peer-to-peer (P2P) markets in real-time on a wide range of interests including award shows, sports, and international politics.</p>
<p>In addition, Chancer lets users create their own betting markets and set their own odds, in contrast to conventional betting platforms where the house determines the odds. This degree of customization and control is unheard of in the gambling industry and demonstrates Chancer&rsquo;s creative thinking.</p>
<p>In essence, Chancer is setting a new standard for online betting in addition to revolutionising it. This platform offers a fun and reliable betting experience by fusing blockchain technology with the thrill of gambling.</p>
<h2>Why invest in Chancer?</h2>
<p>The CHANCER token allows users to create their own markets and place bets on others, enabling participation. One of the main goals of the project is to influence how betting evolves in the Web3 environment, and Chancer&rsquo;s users play a key role in that.</p>
<p>The CHANCER token is expected to appreciate through the presale stages from the current price of $0.010 to $0.021, meaning early investors will be in profit when the token starts listing on cryptocurrency exchanges. According to the project&rsquo;s roadmap, the CHANCER token is scheduled to go live on <a href="https://coinjournal.net/uniswap/what-is-uniswap/">Uniswap</a>, Coingecko, Coinmarketcap, and at least two centralized <a href="https://coinjournal.net/compare/best-cryptocurrency-exchanges/">cryptocurrency exchanges</a> in Q3, 2023.</p>
<p>Chancer is on the path to becoming a decentralized autonomous organization, and it has painstakingly created a roadmap outlining that journey (DAO). Key components of the roadmap include unbiased market moderators for fair outcomes and a Share2Earn program that rewards user engagement. Chancer distinguishes itself as a long-term endeavour committed to developing a user-focused and transparent betting platform by laying out a clear course for growth.</p>
<p>With Chancer offering a chance for anyone to bet on literally anything, the 2024 Olympics is expected to bring quite a huge outpour to the decentralized betting platform that will have just launched its mainnet. The event will most likely also result in a surge in the value of the CHANCER token seeing that it is at the core of the Chancer ecosystem.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-mainnet-launch-after-current-presale-a-perfect-timing-for-2024-olympics/">Chancer mainnet launch after current presale a perfect timing for 2024 Olympics</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-mainnet-launch-after-current-presale-a-perfect-timing-for-2024-olympics/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>AltSignals (ASI) investor uptake increases: stage 2 of the presale 50% sold out</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-asi-investor-uptake-increases-stage-2-of-the-presale-50-sold-out/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-asi-investor-uptake-increases-stage-2-of-the-presale-50-sold-out/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 11:33:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AI]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-asi-investor-uptake-increases-stage-2-of-the-presale-50-sold-out/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>So far, the AltSignals presale has raised $1,124,969.8875. At the current stage, one ASI token is going for $0.01875. Stage 2 of the presale is 50% sold out less than 10 days after it was started. The AltSignals presale is gaining steam amid the increased artificial intelligence (AI) hype. While the first two presale stages [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-asi-investor-uptake-increases-stage-2-of-the-presale-50-sold-out/">AltSignals (ASI) investor uptake increases: stage 2 of the presale 50% sold out</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul class="decimal_type">
<li>So far, the AltSignals presale has raised $1,124,969.8875.</li>
<li>At the current stage, one ASI token is going for $0.01875.</li>
<li>Stage 2 of the presale is 50% sold out less than 10 days after it was started.</li>
</ul>
<p>The <a href="https://token.altsignals.io/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news">AltSignals presale</a> is gaining steam amid the increased artificial intelligence (AI) hype. While the first two presale stages (Beta sale and Stage 1) took slightly longer to sell out, Stage 2 seems it could sell out in a week&rsquo;s time.</p>
<p>The price of the new AltSignals&rsquo; ASI token has been rising across the presale stages and it has so far increased by 56.25%. At the start of the presale, the ASI token was worth $0.01200 and it is now worth $0.01875.</p>
<h2>AltSignals AI initiative</h2>
<p>AltSignals has become a market leader in the trading platform industry and is currently attracting a lot of attention from the cryptocurrency technology industry. Since its launch in 2017, AltSignals has established a reputable name for itself and amassed a sizable user base of more than 50,000 devoted members.</p>
<p>AltSignals&rsquo; initial trading tool AltAlgoTM has been key in assisting traders looking to identify opportunities with the accuracy required for maximum profits. However, it is not resting on its laurels but rather making strides with the introduction of a game-changing AI innovation dubbed ActualizeAI that will be powered by ASI cryptocurrency.</p>
<p>ActualizeAI is designed as a modern trading platform that seamlessly integrates artificial intelligence and <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/blockchain/">blockchain technology</a> to expand the functionality of AltSignals&rsquo; already top-notch trading tools. Machine learning is what makes ActualizeAI unique because it enables the system to quickly analyse a vast amount of market data, including investor sentiment and numerous indicators vital for predicting price movements.</p>
<p>ActualizeAI promises to be a game-changer by offering traders, regardless of their level of experience, precise and timely trading signals to maximise their investment returns.</p>
<h2>Why invest in the new ASI cryptocurrency?</h2>
<p>The ASI tokens will allow holders access to the ActualizeAI toolkit, which will be at the cutting edge of trading technology, once it is released. This is like having an all-access pass to a collection of cutting-edge tools and intriguing possibilities.</p>
<p>Additionally, AltSignals&rsquo;s <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/defi/">DeFi</a> services are accessible through ASI tokens. These consist of staking opportunities, giving users the chance to receive rewards for using the network, and encouraging long-term holding. By participating in governance proposals through voting, ASI token holders can also have a say in the platform&rsquo;s future direction, ensuring a decentralised and community-driven approach to decision-making.</p>
<p>The ASI token also offers exclusive access to the AI Members Club which offers even greater opportunities for the ASI token holders. This elite club is a unique community for astute and discriminating traders and investors, not just a regular neighbourhood. Members have exclusive access to early-stage investment opportunities in crypto technology projects, giving them a head start on potentially game-changing endeavours. Another essential component of this club is access to new tokens during presales and private sales.</p>
<p>The AI Members Club also serves as a hub for social interaction and competitive online trading tournaments where members can test their trading prowess and compete for sizable cryptocurrency prizes. Being able to test and use AltSignals&rsquo; most cutting-edge trading tools before they are made available to the general public is probably one of the most coveted benefits of being a member of the AI Members Club. Members are able to stay on the cutting edge and in the know thanks to this exclusive access.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-asi-investor-uptake-increases-stage-2-of-the-presale-50-sold-out/">AltSignals (ASI) investor uptake increases: stage 2 of the presale 50% sold out</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-asi-investor-uptake-increases-stage-2-of-the-presale-50-sold-out/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance adds Arkham (ARKM) to launchpad</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-adds-arkham-arkm-to-launchpad/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-adds-arkham-arkm-to-launchpad/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 11:15:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNB]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-adds-arkham-arkm-to-launchpad/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Binance has announced Arkham (ARKM) as the 32nd project in the Binance Lanchpad. A snaphot of BNB balances will be taken on July 11 to July 17. BNB, the native Binance coin, surged more than 3% to trade at highs of $243. Binance has added Arkham (ARKM) to the Binance Launchpad, the 32nd project whose [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-adds-arkham-arkm-to-launchpad/">Binance adds Arkham (ARKM) to launchpad</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Binance has announced Arkham (ARKM) as the 32nd project in the Binance Lanchpad.</li>
<li dir="ltr">A snaphot of BNB balances will be taken on July 11 to July 17.</li>
<li dir="ltr">BNB, the native Binance coin, surged more than 3% to trade at highs of $243.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/binance/">Binance</a> has added Arkham (ARKM) to the Binance Launchpad, the 32nd project whose token sale the crypto behemoth has supported.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The price of <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/bnb/">BNB</a>, the native Binance coin, surged more than 3% early Monday to trade at highs of $243.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Binance Launchpad adds Arkham (ARKM)</h2>
<p dir="ltr">In a notice published Monday, Binance said the ARKM sale will be by subscription format. A snapshot for BNB balances starts at 00:00 (UTC) on July 11 to July 17, 2023 at 00:00 (UTC).</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Wen Launchpad? &#128518; <a href="https://t.co/IpDpFuwEdH">https://t.co/IpDpFuwEdH</a></p>
<p>&mdash; CZ &#128310; Binance (@cz_binance) <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1678338410191126529?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 10, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">The ARKM token sale on the Launchpad will have a hard cap of $2.5 million, with each user limited to 300,000 ARKM or $15,000. Binance Launchpad has been allocated 50 million ARKM tokens, which is about 5% of the total Arkham supply of 1 billion.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The public sale price for ARKM is $0.05.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Arkham launches intel markeplace</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Today&rsquo;s news that Arkham is the 32nd Binance Launchpad project coincided with another big<a href="https://www.arkhamintelligence.com/announcements/arkham-intel-exchange" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">&nbsp;<u>announcement</u></a> from the on-chain analytics platform.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This because Arkham also announced its Arkham Intel Exchange, dubbed the &ldquo;world&rsquo;s first on-chain intelligence marketplace.&rdquo; It is expected to go live on July 18. &nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Announcing The World&rsquo;s First On-Chain Intelligence Exchange</p>
<p>Buy and sell information on the owner of any blockchain wallet address&mdash;anonymously, via smart contract. <a href="https://t.co/4xr7dLvOjp">pic.twitter.com/4xr7dLvOjp</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Arkham (@ArkhamIntel) <a href="https://twitter.com/ArkhamIntel/status/1678339355314900992?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 10, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">Intel Exchange will bring to the marketplace an intel-to-earn economy, allowing for anonymous buying and selling of on-chain intelligence on any crypto wallet address. The new platform will be powered by smart contracts and involve buyers placing bounties for intel.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>Anyone can post a bounty seeking some on-chain information, by locking funds to request information on crypto addresses or entities. These bounties can then be fulfilled by &lsquo;bounty hunters&rsquo; &ndash; blockchain researchers or sleuths, who will exchange intelligence in return for the payment</em>,&rdquo; Arkham wrote.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to the Arkham team, demand for on-chain analysis continues to increase, particularly from traders, investors, researchers, journalists, and protocols.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-adds-arkham-arkm-to-launchpad/">Binance adds Arkham (ARKM) to launchpad</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-adds-arkham-arkm-to-launchpad/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
