<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 16:33:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>DWF Labs vote of confidence to the WavesDAO project sends WAVES price up 91%</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/dwf-labs-vote-of-confidence-to-the-wavesdao-project-sends-waves-price-up-91/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/dwf-labs-vote-of-confidence-to-the-wavesdao-project-sends-waves-price-up-91/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 16:33:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/dwf-labs-vote-of-confidence-to-the-wavesdao-project-sends-waves-price-up-91/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>WavesDAO is a For-Profit DAO on the Power Protocol platform aimed to support the development of Waves Blockchain-based projects. Market maker DWF Labs has committed 500K WAVES to the WavesDAO project. The WavesDAO is seeking to channel a third of Waves miners&#8217; rewards into the Waves DAO during the initiation period. WAVES price has hit [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/dwf-labs-vote-of-confidence-to-the-wavesdao-project-sends-waves-price-up-91/">DWF Labs vote of confidence to the WavesDAO project sends WAVES price up 91%</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul class="decimal_type">
<li>WavesDAO is a For-Profit DAO on the Power Protocol platform aimed to support the development of Waves Blockchain-based projects.</li>
<li>Market maker DWF Labs has committed 500K WAVES to the WavesDAO project.</li>
<li>The WavesDAO is seeking to channel a third of Waves miners&rsquo; rewards into the Waves DAO during the initiation period.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://coinjournal.net/waves/">WAVES price</a> has hit a daily high of $2.82 today after a 91.23% price surge in 24 hours. While the surge caught most crypto traders by surprise, the price movement was coming seeing that global digital asset market maker and web3 investment firm DWF labs had shown commitment to the WavesDAO project.</p>
<p>DWF Labs, on June 22, announced its support for the launch of WavesDAO by committing 500K WAVES to Waves staking and voting to support the WavesDAO project. DWF Labs&rsquo; participation in the DAO initiative will go a long way in empowering developers to build on the Waves Blockchain.</p>
<h2>What is WavesDAO?</h2>
<p>WavesDAO is a For-Profit decentralized organization (DAO) on the Power Protocol platform aimed to support the development of Waves <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/blockchain/">Blockchain</a>-based projects and other initiatives.</p>
<p>Essentially, a governor is expected to have a minimum of 1 PWR to participate in the DAO and 100 PWR staked for the initiation of a proposal to succeed.</p>
<p>At the moment, WavesDAO is seeking to channel a third of Waves miners&rsquo; rewards into the Waves DAO. However, this proposal needs to be approved by Waves miners and stakers through on-chain voting.</p>
<p>WavesDAO stands as a pioneering decentralized autonomous organization on the Power Protocol platform. It will be managed by PWR token stakers, which makes it an investment vehicle for the community.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/dwf-labs-vote-of-confidence-to-the-wavesdao-project-sends-waves-price-up-91/">DWF Labs vote of confidence to the WavesDAO project sends WAVES price up 91%</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/dwf-labs-vote-of-confidence-to-the-wavesdao-project-sends-waves-price-up-91/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin hard forks, Bitcoin Cash and Bitcoin SV in the spotlight with double-digit gains</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-hard-forks-bitcoin-cash-and-bitcoin-sv-in-the-spotlight-with-double-digit-gains/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-hard-forks-bitcoin-cash-and-bitcoin-sv-in-the-spotlight-with-double-digit-gains/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 15:55:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin SV News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-hard-forks-bitcoin-cash-and-bitcoin-sv-in-the-spotlight-with-double-digit-gains/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>At press time, BCH price had risen by 52% in the last seven days and 28% in the last 24 hours. BSV, on the other hand, had gained 77% in the last seven days and 30% in the last 24 hours Bitcoin (BTC) has only gained 15% over the last seven days. Recently, attention has [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-hard-forks-bitcoin-cash-and-bitcoin-sv-in-the-spotlight-with-double-digit-gains/">Bitcoin hard forks, Bitcoin Cash and Bitcoin SV in the spotlight with double-digit gains</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>At press time, BCH price had risen by 52% in the last seven days and 28% in the last 24 hours.</li>
<li>BSV, on the other hand, had gained 77% in the last seven days and 30% in the last 24 hours</li>
<li>Bitcoin (BTC) has only gained 15% over the last seven days.</li>
</ul>
<p>Recently, attention has been focused on <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/what-is-bitcoin/">Bitcoin (BTC)</a> and its hard forks, <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin-cash/what-is-bitcoin-cash/">Bitcoin Cash (BCH)</a> and Bitcoin SV (BSV) that split off from the main chain. In the last seven days, the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin-sv/">prices of BSV</a> and <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin-cash/">BCH</a> have skyrocketed, outperforming even BTC.</p>
<p>Despite the markets showing a consolidated trend after the recent price movements, prices of most cryptocurrencies are still skyrocketing with BCH and BSV being among the top three gainers today falling behind <a href="https://coinjournal.net/waves/">Waves (WAVES)</a> which has shot up by 85% today.</p>
<h2>Crypto market breakout after US SEC onslaught</h2>
<p>The SEC lawsuits against <a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/binance/">Binance</a> and <a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/coinbase/">Coinbase</a> for allegedly violating US rules and regulations sent the markets into a sharp decline.</p>
<p>However, the drop did not last long. The prices were up again after industry heavyweights like BlackRock, Invesco, and WisdonTree threw their weight behind the industry. The other force behind the current crypto market boom is the emergence of China back into the cryptocurrency space.</p>
<h2>China&rsquo;s stand on cryptocurrencies</h2>
<p>The historical relationship between China and cryptocurrencies has been quite complicated, with frequent bans that have always had an effect on the entire crypto market.</p>
<p>China has a history of opposing cryptocurrencies despite the fact that it was once the bedrock of most crypto activities including Bitcoin mining. The People&rsquo;s Bank of China (PBC) made its initial attempt in 2013 when it forbade financial institutions from dealing in virtual currencies. Afterwards, authorities tightened their regulations of cryptocurrencies in 2017, especially targeting Initial Coin Offerings (ICOs).</p>
<p>Later in 2021, China took the toughest action and <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chinas-bitcoin-crackdown-widens-as-authorities-shut-down-mining-activities/">outlawed cryptocurrency mining </a>causing a more than 50% decline in the crypto markets.</p>
<p>But recently, China has <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-ceo-says-its-a-big-deal-after-china-broadcast-crypto-on-state-tv/">changed how it views cryptocurrencies</a>. Beijing recently published a whitepaper titled &ldquo;Web3 Innovation and Development White Paper (2023)&rdquo; that promoted Web3 technology as a crucial element of the internet&rsquo;s future development.</p>
<p>If China was to completely lift the crypto ban or ease its stand, the global markets could be deeply impacted, stimulating global demand and boosting prices. However, at the moment, everything is still surrounded by speculations going by what has been happening.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-hard-forks-bitcoin-cash-and-bitcoin-sv-in-the-spotlight-with-double-digit-gains/">Bitcoin hard forks, Bitcoin Cash and Bitcoin SV in the spotlight with double-digit gains</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-hard-forks-bitcoin-cash-and-bitcoin-sv-in-the-spotlight-with-double-digit-gains/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>AltSignals’ first stage presale nearly sold out amid resilient crypto sector</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-first-stage-presale-nearly-sold-out-amid-resilient-crypto-sector/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-first-stage-presale-nearly-sold-out-amid-resilient-crypto-sector/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Motiur Rahman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 11:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technical Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-first-stage-presale-nearly-sold-out-amid-resilient-crypto-sector/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>AltSignals presale nearly sold out with $1.021 million raised An interest in crypto and AI boosting the trading signal service platform $ASI is likely to surge in value as it gets listed on exchanges amid huge investor interest Trading signal service AltSignals ($ASI) has been a&#160;presale sensation this year. The project has raised $1.021 million, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-first-stage-presale-nearly-sold-out-amid-resilient-crypto-sector/">AltSignals’ first stage presale nearly sold out amid resilient crypto sector</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals presale nearly sold out with $1.021 million raised</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">An interest in crypto and AI boosting the trading signal service platform</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">$ASI is likely to surge in value as it gets listed on exchanges amid huge investor interest</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Trading signal service AltSignals ($ASI) has been a&nbsp;<a href="https://token.altsignals.io/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=investment_opportunity" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>presale</u></a> sensation this year. The project has raised $1.021 million, with investors eyeing a share of its upcoming AI-led trading platform ActualizeAI. AltSignals is expected to raise $1.080 million through the presale, meaning that only 5% remains for the first phase to conclude. By all standards, this is a highly successful presale, given that it just opened its doors to investors a few months ago. But why has AltSignals generated so much interest from investors? Let&rsquo;s explain this in some detail.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Crypto is the future, and so is artificial intelligence</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Crypto had a rough year, but investors are still undeterred. Over the past week, recoveries have been widespread, with the crypto king Bitcoin eyeing a breakout past its now-established resistance at $30,000. The gains underline that the search for supernormal profits from the digital sector is far from over.</p>
<p dir="ltr">But we know the investment landscape is changing. As established cryptocurrencies whipsaw within ranges that investors have become accustomed to by now, new crypto projects are a fast gathering storm. They present new and unexploited opportunities that investors are willing to try.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals comes at a time when the application of AI is growing, especially in the trading world. Just imagine the benefit of using AI to generate signals from financial instruments like stocks and forex. Of course, AI has been in use in the trading world as it has been shown to produce more quality signals. The ability to intertwine crypto, AI, and trading makes AltSignals a unique and quality project which is attracting investors.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>What is AltSignals, and how does it work?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals is a trading signal service created in 2017 by a team of professional UK traders. It has grown exponentially over the years, with its trading community increasing to over 52,000 members on Telegram. The signal service boasts approximately 64% signal accuracy, generated using the AltAlgo&trade; algorithm. The top performing markets for the company are shares, forex, the Binance Futures, crypto, and CFDs.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">A strong and growing demand for AltSignals service has prompted the team to expand into AI-led signal service. The team is launching an AI platform dubbed ActualizeAI. The interest in AI has been fueled by a need to increase the quality of signals generated and the number of financial instruments covered.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">To benefit from the AI signals, you need to become an ActualizeAI member. Crypto token $ASI will be the unit of membership. Investors who buy $ASI in the presale will have early access to ActualizeAI and enjoy other benefits.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>What value does $ASI offer?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">If you are a trader or investor interested in trading, $ASI could be an ideal investment. You have access to a trading community benefiting from quality signals generated by professionals. $ASI also gives investors a chance to compete in trading tournaments. This could be an excellent way to improve trading skills while getting rewarded with $ASI for winning the contests. There are exclusive presale opportunities for members of ActualizeAI.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">If you have been searching for a trading community where members have a voice, AltSignals, and ActualizeAI could be the ideal place. You can use $ASI to vote on governance, besides using the tokens to contribute ideas on the platform and get rewarded.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Should you buy $ASI this week?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">$ASI&rsquo;s presale in the first phase is ending with around 5% of tokens left to be sold out. From here, the token&rsquo;s price will increase, and investors may have to spend more. The token could also get boosts from exchange listing after a successful presale. It means buying now offers a perfect chance to join ActualizeAI early and familiarise yourself with the AltSignals platform.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-first-stage-presale-nearly-sold-out-amid-resilient-crypto-sector/">AltSignals’ first stage presale nearly sold out amid resilient crypto sector</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-first-stage-presale-nearly-sold-out-amid-resilient-crypto-sector/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Should you buy Bitcoin as it jumps to a 1-year high?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/should-you-buy-bitcoin-as-it-jumps-to-a-1-year-high/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/should-you-buy-bitcoin-as-it-jumps-to-a-1-year-high/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mircea Vasiu]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 08:27:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/should-you-buy-bitcoin-as-it-jumps-to-a-1-year-high/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin trades above $30k despite the dollar strengthening against other fiat currencies News that BlackRock prepares to launch a spot Bitcoin ETF helped SEC&#8217;s lawsuits create uncertainty Bitcoin trades at a 1-year high after breaking out of a consolidation that looks like a bullish flag pattern. As such, the cryptocurrency has made a new higher [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/should-you-buy-bitcoin-as-it-jumps-to-a-1-year-high/">Should you buy Bitcoin as it jumps to a 1-year high?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitcoin trades above $30k despite the dollar strengthening against other fiat currencies</li>
<li>News that BlackRock prepares to launch a spot Bitcoin ETF helped</li>
<li>SEC&rsquo;s lawsuits create uncertainty</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p>Bitcoin trades at a 1-year high after breaking out of a consolidation that looks like a bullish flag pattern. As such, the cryptocurrency has made a new higher high, keeping the bullish bias intact despite consolidating since April.&nbsp;</p>
<p>While trading above $30k it is hard to make a bearish bet on Bitcoin. That is specifically true if looking at what happened in the traditional currency market, where the US dollar strengthened across the board.&nbsp;</p>
<p>For example, the EUR/USD exchange rate dropped from 1.10 to 1.0850 on news that the European PMIs weakened more than the market expected. Also, the GBP/USD dropped on weak UK data.&nbsp;</p>
<p>All in all, the dollar strengthened last week, but it did not gain against Bitcoin.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Just the opposite.&nbsp;</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/05/24/1687595111908-482a85f6-19a7-489e-969b-da932386dc8d.jpg" style="width: 1800px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="1800" height="487"></p>
<p><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/?exchange=CRYPTO" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Bitcoin chart by TradingView</a></p>
<h2>What drives the Bitcoin price higher?&nbsp;</h2>
<p>By now, it is obvious that the dollar&rsquo;s weakness did not drive the move higher. Therefore, something else must be the cause of this bullish breakout.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Two possible explanations exist.&nbsp;</p>
<p>One is related to BlackRock, the American multinational investment company, one of the largest in the world. News surfaced that the company submitted an application for a spot Bitcoin ETF designed to track the underlying market price of Bitcoin. Therefore, some argue that BlackRock might know something in advance.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Another is that investors&rsquo; trust in the industry builds up with the recent SEC lawsuits. A more transparent industry should be a positive for crypto investors.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Regardless of the reason, Bitcoin trades above $30k on the dollar&rsquo;s strength against other fiat currencies. If the divergence continues, Bitcoin might have more upside.&nbsp;</p>
<p>On the flip side, no one knows how the cryptocurrency market will react to the Binance and Coinbase verdicts.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/should-you-buy-bitcoin-as-it-jumps-to-a-1-year-high/">Should you buy Bitcoin as it jumps to a 1-year high?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/should-you-buy-bitcoin-as-it-jumps-to-a-1-year-high/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Cash price touches 1-year high after BCH soars 72%</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-cash-price-hits-1-year-high-as-bch-soars-72-this-week/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 20:37:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BCH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-cash-price-hits-1-year-high-as-bch-soars-72-this-week/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin Cash price jumped to a 1-year high today when BCH hit $194, up 72% over the week. BCH price broke higher as institutional-driven crypto sentiment pushed Bitcoin (BTC) above $31,000. Bullish sentiment for Bitcoin Cash also followed the listing on BCH on the Citadel-backed crypto exchange EDX Markets. Bitcoin Cash price has soared to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-cash-price-hits-1-year-high-as-bch-soars-72-this-week/">Bitcoin Cash price touches 1-year high after BCH soars 72%</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Bitcoin Cash price jumped to a 1-year high today when BCH hit $194, up 72% over the week.</li>
<li dir="ltr">BCH price broke higher as institutional-driven crypto sentiment pushed Bitcoin (BTC) above $31,000.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Bullish sentiment for Bitcoin Cash also followed the listing on BCH on the Citadel-backed crypto exchange EDX Markets.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin-cash/">Bitcoin Cash</a> price has soared to its highest level in twelve months after spiking more than 40% in 24 hours to hit $194 on Coinbase.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">As CoinJournal highligted <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-cash-surges-as-bch-hits-3-month-high-heres-why/">here</a>, Bitcoin Cash price had jumped to a 3-month high on Wednesday.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Why is Bitcoin Cash price up?</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/bch/">BCH</a> was up by 72% in the past seven days and traded at prices last seen in early June last year. This is when the crypto winter and market contagion pushed it from highs of $210 on June 1 to lows of $103 by the end of the month.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Bitcoin fork cryptocurrency then slumped to lows of $89 in November as the FTX implosion catalysed massive crypto losses.</p>
<p dir="ltr">A bullish start to 2023 however faded with BCH/USD trading around $154 in February. This week&rsquo;s breakout above a technical downtrend line coincided with the broader crypto market rally, buoyed by the news of BlackRock&rsquo;s application for a spot Bitcoin ETF. Today&rsquo;s gains came as <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/btc-hits-31k-as-sec-approves-first-leveraged-futures-bitcoin-etf/">Bitcoin reached $31,450</a>, its highest price since June 2022.</p>
<p dir="ltr">While BTC is up 85% year-to-date, Bitcoin Cash price is slightly higher at 90% YTD.</p>
<div class="fr-img-space-wrap"><span class="fr-img-caption fr-fic fr-dib fr-draggable" style="width: 800px"><span class="fr-img-wrap">
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/05/23/1687551463969-a6e76a5a-5227-4d0e-b526-55fc1b523a06.png" style="width: 800px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="800" height="242"><span class="fr-inner"></span></p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin Cash performance on the daily chart. Source:&nbsp;<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/Mo4JhQt7/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>TradingView</u></a></p>
<p></p></span>
<p></p></span>
<h2 class="fr-img-space-wrap2">BCH open interest up 79%</h2>
</div>
<p dir="ltr">BCH Futures open interest has since jumped, up 79% in the past 24 hours. It follows the bullish breakout above $135 after newly-launched EDX Marketslisted Bitcoin Cash as one of four coins on the exchange alongside Bitcoin, Ethereum and Litecoin.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">EDX Markets, which <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/new-crypto-exchange-edx-markets-goes-live/">went live this week</a>, is backed by some of Wall Street&rsquo;s largest financial investment firms &ndash; Charles Schwab, Fidelity Investments and Citadel.</p>
<p>According to <a href="https://www.coinglass.com/BitcoinOpenInterest"><u>data</u></a> from Coinglass, open interest in BCH was over $200 million as of 3pm ET on Friday, June 23. It&rsquo;s the highest the metric has risen to since March 2022.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-cash-price-hits-1-year-high-as-bch-soars-72-this-week/">Bitcoin Cash price touches 1-year high after BCH soars 72%</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>BTC hits $31k as SEC approves first leveraged Futures Bitcoin ETF</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/btc-hits-31k-as-sec-approves-first-leveraged-futures-bitcoin-etf/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 19:12:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/btc-hits-31k-as-sec-approves-first-leveraged-futures-bitcoin-etf/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin rose to above $31,450 on Friday, its highest level since June 2022. BTC price spiked to the year-high level after the SEC allowed the Volatility Shares 2x Bitcoin Strategy ETF, or BITX. This is the first leveraged Bitcoin Futures ETF in the US and comes after this week&#8217;s BlackRock-fueled bullish sentiment for the crypto [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/btc-hits-31k-as-sec-approves-first-leveraged-futures-bitcoin-etf/">BTC hits $31k as SEC approves first leveraged Futures Bitcoin ETF</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Bitcoin rose to above $31,450 on Friday, its highest level since June 2022.</li>
<li dir="ltr">BTC price spiked to the year-high level after the SEC allowed the Volatility Shares 2x Bitcoin Strategy ETF, or BITX.</li>
<li dir="ltr">This is the first leveraged Bitcoin Futures ETF in the US and comes after this week&rsquo;s BlackRock-fueled bullish sentiment for the crypto market.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> smashed past the $31,000 level on Friday afternoon as the market reacted to the latest news about the US market&rsquo;s first leveraged Futures Bitcoin exchange traded fund (ETF).</p>
<p dir="ltr">The upside pushed BTC price to highs of $31,458 on crypto exchange Bitstamp, with the flagship cryptocurrency&rsquo;s price setting a new year-to-date high and its highest level since June 2022. BTC traded at $31,170 at the time of writing, about 4% higher in the past 24 hours but an impressive 87% up YTD.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">SEC approves first leveraged Futures Bitcoin ETF</h2>
<p dir="ltr">On Friday, June 23, the US market entered a new chapter in crypto investing when the first leveraged Bitcoin Futures ETF became effective. The Volatility Shares 2x Bitcoin Strategy ETF, or<a href="https://www.volatilityshares.com/bitx" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">&nbsp;<u>BITX</u></a>, will begin trading on Tuesday 27 June and will allow its investors an exposure to Bitcoin with daily returns.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">BREAKING: &#127482;&#127480; SEC approves the first  Leveraged <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Bitcoin</a> Futures ETF to start trading on Tuesday.</p>
<p>&mdash; Bitcoin Archive (@BTC_Archive) <a href="https://twitter.com/BTC_Archive/status/1672282287931633678?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 23, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">Instead of investing directly in Bitcoin, BITX will &ldquo;seek to benefit from increases in the price of Bitcoin Futures Contracts,&rdquo; per details of the Fund in the prospectus<a href="https://www.sec.gov/Archives/edgar/data/1884021/000138713123004119/btix-485apos_032323.htm" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">&nbsp;<u>filed</u></a> with the SEC. The 2x Bitcoin Strategy ETF will align with the CME Bitcoin Futures Daily Roll Index.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin has led the market higher over the past week or so, riding on the bullish sentiment triggered by $9 trillion asset manager BlackRock&rsquo;s filing for a spot Bitcoin ETF. BlackRock has a very high rate of success with ETF applications, the reason for the market&rsquo;s optimism.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Analytics platform IntoTheBlock pointed out what a spot ETF would mean for Bitcoin adoption and price.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">&#128161; But why is this important? Unlike the Bitcoin futures ETF approved in 2021, a spot ETF would buy actual Bitcoin instead of derivative contracts. This could draw in traditional investors and fuel Bitcoin's price.</p>
<p>&mdash; IntoTheBlock (@intotheblock) <a href="https://twitter.com/intotheblock/status/1672208680878592000?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 23, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">Indeed, the asset manager&rsquo;s filing paved way for a frenzy of spot ETF applications from several other Wall Street giants and global financial institutions. With BTC price in bullish momentum, its likely the market could see many more mega moves by smart money.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/btc-hits-31k-as-sec-approves-first-leveraged-futures-bitcoin-etf/">BTC hits $31k as SEC approves first leveraged Futures Bitcoin ETF</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto price prediction: Cardano, Polygon MATIC, Stellar Lumens</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-cardano-polygon-matic-stellar-lumens/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-cardano-polygon-matic-stellar-lumens/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 17:49:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stellar]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-cardano-polygon-matic-stellar-lumens/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrencies had a strong performance this week as Bitcoin surged to $30,000. Most altcoins like Cardano, Pepe, and MATIC also jumped. More upside will depend on whether Bitcoin is able to clear $31,000. Cryptocurrencies had a strong performance this week as investors focused on TradFi and the positive comment from Jerome Powell, the Federal Reserve [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-cardano-polygon-matic-stellar-lumens/">Crypto price prediction: Cardano, Polygon MATIC, Stellar Lumens</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Cryptocurrencies had a strong performance this week as Bitcoin surged to $30,000.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Most altcoins like Cardano, Pepe, and MATIC also jumped.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">More upside will depend on whether Bitcoin is able to clear $31,000.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Cryptocurrencies had a strong performance this week as investors focused on TradFi and the positive comment from Jerome Powell, the Federal Reserve chairman.&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/"><u>Bitcoin</u></a> price jumped by more than 20% in the past 7 days while Ethereum soared by 14%. The near-term price action for cryptocurrencies will depend on whether BTC will soar above the year-to-date high of $31,000. So, what next for MATIC, Stellar, and Cardano?</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Cardano price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/cardano/"><u>Cardano</u></a> has been in a strong bearish trend in the past few months. It dropped to a low of $0.4592 on April 16th to a low of $0.2295. The lowest point was a notable one since it was the lowest level in December.</p>
<p dir="ltr">While the recent rebound is welcome, buyers should be cautious considering that the coin has formed an inverted cup and handle pattern. The current rebound is part of the handle section. In price action analysis, the inverted C&amp;H pattern is usually a bearish sign. Therefore, there is a likelihood that the Cardano price will resume the bearish trend in the near term.</p>
<p dir="ltr">If this happens, the next level to watch will be at $0.2414. A break below this level will confirm the bearish thesis and signal that the ADA price could slip to the key support level at $0.20, which is about 30% below the current level.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/05/23/1687542349859-00b227bf-809a-4ea4-8588-acf52c56fec8.png" style="width: 588px;height: 285.801px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="588" height="285.801"></p>
<h3 dir="ltr">How to buy Cardano</h3>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>


<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=MTQzOTkz&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy ADA with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    CEX.IO</h3>


<p>
    <a href="/visit/cex-crypto?guid=MTQzOTkz&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy ADA with CEX.IO today            </a>
    </p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Polygon MATIC price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/polygon/"><u>Polygon</u></a> MATIC price has been in a steep sell-off in the past few months. This decline happened as the layer-2 network faces significant competition from the likes of Optimism and Arbitrum. On the daily chart, the price dropped to $0.5079 in June and then resumed the bullish trend this week. It has now retested the important resistance point at $0.6905, the lowest point on September 20th last year.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">MATIC remains below the 25-day and 50-day moving averages. Therefore, I believe that this recovery will not hold. If this happens, the coin will likely retest the month-to-date low of $0.50, which is about 26% below the current level.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/05/23/1687542349645-c31d5fb8-f08f-4ff3-bbd5-baf6620be9fc.png" style="width: 646px;height: 314.387px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="646" height="314.387"></p>
<h3 dir="ltr">How to buy MATIC</h3>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>


<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=MTQzOTkz&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy MATIC with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    Binance.US</h3>


<p>
    <a href="/visit/binance-us-crypto?guid=MTQzOTkz&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy MATIC with Binance.US today            </a>
    </p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Stellar Lumens price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The daily chart shows that the XLM price crashed to a low of $0.075 on June 15th. This was an important level since it coincided with the lowest level on March 11th of this year. Stellar has now moved slightly above the 25-day and 50-day moving averages. It has also formed what looks like a double-bottom pattern whose neckline is at $0.1145.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, there is a likelihood that the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/stellar-lumens/"><u>Stellar</u></a> coin will likely continue rising as buyers target the key resistance point at $0.10, which is about 11.31% above the current level.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/05/23/1687542349851-aa55772e-21a9-4715-9793-2636fab8de63.png" style="width: 693px;height: 337.26px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="693" height="337.26"></p>
<h3 dir="ltr">How to buy Stellar</h3>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>


<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=MTQzOTkz&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy XLM with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    CEX.IO</h3>


<p>
    <a href="/visit/cex-crypto?guid=MTQzOTkz&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy XLM with CEX.IO today            </a>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-cardano-polygon-matic-stellar-lumens/">Crypto price prediction: Cardano, Polygon MATIC, Stellar Lumens</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-cardano-polygon-matic-stellar-lumens/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>US Supreme Court hands Coinbase key win</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/us-supreme-court-hands-coinbase-key-win/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/us-supreme-court-hands-coinbase-key-win/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 17:22:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Policy and Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Legal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/us-supreme-court-hands-coinbase-key-win/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The US Supreme Court ruled that the district court must stay proceedings in a class action lawsuit when interlocutory appeal is ongoing. Coinbase filed an appeal after its motion to compel arbitration was denied. The ruling comes days after Coinbase was sued by the SEC over allegations of violating securities laws. Coinbase has scored a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/us-supreme-court-hands-coinbase-key-win/">US Supreme Court hands Coinbase key win</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">The US Supreme Court ruled that the district court must stay proceedings in a class action lawsuit when interlocutory appeal is ongoing.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Coinbase filed an appeal after its motion to compel arbitration was denied.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The ruling comes days after Coinbase was sued by the SEC over allegations of violating securities laws.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Coinbase has scored a notable victory after the US Supreme court&rsquo;s ruling on its appeal over arbitration.</p>
<p dir="ltr">On Friday, the apex US court ruled in favour of the crypto exchange&rsquo;s argument, stating that a federal court must stay proceedings in a lawsuit where a defendant&rsquo;s appeal for arbitration is ongoing.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">US Supreme Court sides with Coinbase</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The Supreme Court&rsquo;s verdict comes after the exchange filed an appeal earlier this year after its &ldquo;<em>motion to compel arbitration</em>&rdquo; was denied the US District Court for the Northern District of California.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/coinbase/">Coinbase</a> moved to file an interlocutory appeal and sought to have the District Court stay proceedings of a class action lawsuit pending the resolution of its appeal. That too had been denied at the US Court of Appeals for the Ninth Circuit.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>When a federal district court denies a motion to compel arbitration, the losing party has a statutory right to an interlocutory appeal. The sole question here is whether the district court must stay its pre-trial and trial proceedings while the interlocutory appeal is ongoing. The answer is yes: The district court must stay its proceedings</em>,&rdquo; Justice Brett Kavanaugh noted in the Supreme Court&rsquo;s <a href="https://www.supremecourt.gov/opinions/22pdf/22-105_5536.pdf" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">opinion</a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Coinbase is facing a class action lawsuit filed by Abraham Bielski at the US District Court for the Northern District of California, in which he alleges that the US-based cryptocurrency exchange &ldquo;<em>failed to replace funds fraudulently taken from the users&rsquo; accounts</em>.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Supreme Court notes in its ruling that &ldquo;Coinbase&rsquo;s User Agreement provides for dispute resolution through binding arbitration.&rdquo; This is what informed the exchange&rsquo;s move to file for arbitration &ndash; which the lower courts denied.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>We are grateful to the Supreme Court for its careful review. Another example of why I believe in the American court system. The rule of law is sometime slow, and at times disappointing. But it remains our last, best hope in an imperfect democracy</em>,&rdquo; Coinbase Chief Legal Officer Paul Grewal<a href="https://twitter.com/iampaulgrewal/status/1672252332292157441">&nbsp;<u>tweeted</u></a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">While the majority was in favour of Coinbase, Justice Ketanji Brown Jackson dissented, noting that &ldquo;<em>today&rsquo;s majority invents a new stay rule perpetually favoring one class of litigants&mdash;defendants seeking arbitration</em>.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to Justice Jackson, the move could have &ldquo;<em>significant implications for federal litigation</em>.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Coinbase was recently sued by the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) over allegations of violating securities laws.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/us-supreme-court-hands-coinbase-key-win/">US Supreme Court hands Coinbase key win</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/us-supreme-court-hands-coinbase-key-win/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>MARA stock price tests key resistance: Is Marathon Digital a buy?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/mara-stock-price-tests-key-resistance-is-marathon-digital-a-buy/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/mara-stock-price-tests-key-resistance-is-marathon-digital-a-buy/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 16:31:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/mara-stock-price-tests-key-resistance-is-marathon-digital-a-buy/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin mining stocks made a bullish breakout this week.&#160; Marathon Digital share price soared to the highest level since November. Future price action will depend on the Bitcoin price action. Marathon Digital stock price surged to the highest level since November 2022 as&#160;Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies roared back. MARA shares jumped to a high of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/mara-stock-price-tests-key-resistance-is-marathon-digital-a-buy/">MARA stock price tests key resistance: Is Marathon Digital a buy?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin mining stocks made a bullish breakout this week.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Marathon Digital share price soared to the highest level since November.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Future price action will depend on the Bitcoin price action.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Marathon Digital stock price surged to the highest level since November 2022 as&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/"><u>Bitcoin</u></a> and other cryptocurrencies roared back. MARA shares jumped to a high of $12.75, meaning it has soared by more than 319% from the lowest level in December. Other&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/bitcoin-mining/"><u>bitcoin mining</u></a> companies in the industries like Riot Platform and Hut 8 Mining also surged.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitcoin mining stocks jump</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The main reason why MARA stock price soared is that Bitcoin price neared the highest point this year. This rebound happened as the crypto fear and greed index soared to the greed area.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Most analysts believe that the ongoing trend of TradFi is the main driving factor for Bitcoin prices. TradFi refers to a situation where traditional finance companies move to the crypto industry.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">On Friday, Blackrock, the biggest asset manager in the world, announced that it had applied for the iShares Bitcoin Trust with the SEC. This will be an ETF tracking the spot Bitcoin price and will be similar to the Vanguard Gold Trust.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Other large companies in the industry also unveiled their Bitcoin ETF filings. They included companies like Invesco and WisdomTree. Analysts believe that the SEC will come under pressure and allow these funds this time.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Another TradFi news was that Deutsche Bank applied for a crypto custody license in Germany. Credit Agricole, a large French bank, also received its custody license. These banks hope to take care of wealthy Europeans seeking access to the industry.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, MARA stock price is soaring because its business thrives in a period when Bitcoin price is thriving. Its future price action will depend on whether Bitcoin moves above $31,000. This is an important level since it is the upper side of the double-top pattern. As such, if it rises, it means that the double-top pattern has been invalidated.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">MARA stock price forecast</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/05/23/1687537831412-fc011497-94c1-4e69-9cad-b85a40252eb6.png" style="width: 596px;height: 290.053px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="596" height="290.053"></p>
<p dir="ltr">The daily chart shows that the Marathon Digital stock price has been in a slow bullish trend in the past few months. The shares consolidated at around $10 in the past few weeks. It then moved slightly above the key resistance point at $12.85, the highest level on April 18. The price was along the upper side of the ascending triangle pattern.</p>
<p dir="ltr">MARA share price has jumped above the 25-day and 50-day moving averages. Therefore, while the outlook is neutral, the stock will likely have a bullish breakout as buyers target the next key resistance point at $15. A drop below the support at $10.90 will invalidate the bullish view.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy Bitcoin</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>


<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=MTQzOTg4&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy BTC with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    CEX.IO</h3>


<p>
    <a href="/visit/cex-crypto?guid=MTQzOTg4&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy BTC with CEX.IO today            </a>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/mara-stock-price-tests-key-resistance-is-marathon-digital-a-buy/">MARA stock price tests key resistance: Is Marathon Digital a buy?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/mara-stock-price-tests-key-resistance-is-marathon-digital-a-buy/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
