<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 21:36:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Robinhood reports an 18% sequential decline in its second-quarter crypto trading revenue</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/robinhood-q2-crypto-trading-reveue-down-18/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wajeeh Khan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 21:36:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Interview]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robinhood]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=148397</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Robinhood Markets reported its Q2 financial results on Wednesday. Mizuho analyst Dan Dolev sees upside in &#8220;HOOD&#8221; to $14 per share. Robinhood stock lost roughly 8.0% in after-hours trading today. Robinhood Markets Inc says it swung to a profit in its fiscal second quarter. Shares still lost about 8.0% in after-hours trading. A quick overview [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/robinhood-q2-crypto-trading-reveue-down-18/">Robinhood reports an 18% sequential decline in its second-quarter crypto trading revenue</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Robinhood Markets reported its Q2 financial results on Wednesday.</li>
<li>Mizuho analyst Dan Dolev sees upside in &ldquo;HOOD&rdquo; to $14 per share.</li>
<li>Robinhood stock lost roughly 8.0% in after-hours trading today.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/robinhood/">Robinhood Markets Inc</a> says it swung to a profit in its fiscal second quarter. Shares still lost about 8.0% in after-hours trading.</p>
<h2>A quick overview of Robinhood&rsquo;s second quarter</h2>
<p>The sell-off in extended hours isn&rsquo;t entirely unjustified. There sure were pockets of weakness in its quarterly performance.</p>
<p>For one, the online trading platform brought in $31 million from crypto trading in its recently concluded quarter. That was down 18% sequentially. Crypto trading made up 16% of its total revenue in Q2.</p>
<p>Still, Mizuho analyst Dan Dolev sees upside to $14 a share in Robinhood. Explaining why, he said on CNBC&rsquo;s &ldquo;<a href="https://www.cnbc.com/video/2023/08/02/mizuhos-dan-dolev-on-paypal-for-stock-to-work-branded-checkout-needs-to-grow-in-line-with-e-com.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Closing Bell</a>&rdquo;:</p>
<blockquote><p>They&rsquo;re gaining share from Coinbase. We&rsquo;ve proved it in April and May in crypto. They&rsquo;re crushing it on options. Contract prices are coming down because VIX is coming down.</p></blockquote>
<h2>What else was noteworthy in Robinhood&rsquo;s Q2 results</h2>
<p>Robinhood ended the quarter with $11.5 million worth of crypto under custody &ndash; roughly unchanged versus the prior quarter. Despite the after-hours sell-off, its shares are up more than 40% year-to-date.</p>
<p>Overall, the financial technology company earned 3 cents a share in its second quarter on $486 million in revenue. Analysts, in comparison, had called for a cent of loss and $473 million of revenue.</p>
<p>On the downside, though, Robinhood lost 1 million users in Q2, as per the <a href="https://mondovisione.com/media-and-resources/news/robinhood-reports-second-quarter-2023-results-gaap-net-income-was-25-million/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">earnings press release</a>. Still, Mizuho&rsquo;s Dolev told CNBC today:</p>
<blockquote><p>Retirement is a big initiative. If they do well on retirement, if they give you a few data points on retirement, this is going to make the stock work really well.</p></blockquote>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/robinhood-q2-crypto-trading-reveue-down-18/">Robinhood reports an 18% sequential decline in its second-quarter crypto trading revenue</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Could AltSignals become the hottest token in 2023 as experts laud artificial intelligence?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/could-altsignals-become-the-hottest-token-in-2023-as-experts-laud-artificial-intelligence/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/could-altsignals-become-the-hottest-token-in-2023-as-experts-laud-artificial-intelligence/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Motiur Rahman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 20:54:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technical Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/could-altsignals-become-the-hottest-token-in-2023-as-experts-laud-artificial-intelligence/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>AltSignals has generated more than $1.23 million in a fast-occurring presale TicketMeta co-founder says AI is the biggest news of the century AltSignals has the potential to rise by over 1,000% in the long term Decentralised AI is still in its infancy, although the technology has been used for years. AltSignals, a trading signal platform, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/could-altsignals-become-the-hottest-token-in-2023-as-experts-laud-artificial-intelligence/">Could AltSignals become the hottest token in 2023 as experts laud artificial intelligence?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals has generated more than $1.23 million in a fast-occurring presale</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">TicketMeta co-founder says AI is the biggest news of the century</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals has the potential to rise by over 1,000% in the long term</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Decentralised AI is still in its infancy, although the technology has been used for years. AltSignals, a trading signal platform, has embarked on AI transformation to capitalise on this trend. The platform has been popular with traders and is tapping into AI to supercharge trading. The signal service will launch an AI platform powered by a crypto token, $ASI. Within weeks, the presale has raised $1.23 million. You can participate in the presale through the company&rsquo;s&nbsp;<a href="https://token.altsignals.io/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>website</u></a>.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Experts laud AI as the biggest news of the century</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Although AI has been in use, its application is growing beyond the traditional borders. Irina Jadallah, the co-founder of NFT ticketing service Ticketmeta, says AI is the biggest news of the century. She recognises the latest AI-led innovations like Alexa, Siri, and ChatGPT. Jadallah believes AI has the potential to revolutionise many fields.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Ticketmeta co-founder&rsquo;s sentiments have been echoed across. AI technology is finding applications in crypto. The metaverse and the overall Web 3.0 space have been some of the blockchain application areas.</p>
<p dir="ltr">AI applications in the trading world are also fast expanding. AltSignals wants to tap into AI and blockchain to launch a new and improved signal-generation service.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>About AltSignals and AI trading service</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals is a UK trading service with about 5 years of successfully delivering quality signals. The company covers different financial instruments like forex, stocks, and crypto. The signals average 64% accuracy rates. The company has raised over $2.2 million in revenues from the signals. The service is utilised by over 52,000 traders, with more than 1400 VIP members.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The robust demand for trading signals has fueled the AltSignals team to consider AI. The company will launch a new platform dubbed ActualizeAI. To become a member, one will need to purchase $ASI, the token powering the platform. The aim is to make AltSignals and ActualizeAI member-governed, with $ASI as the medium of voting.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>What is the value proposition of $ASI?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">$ASI has a huge price potential since it powers a successful trading service. Investors could earn from potential price increases. Currently, $ASI goes for $0.01875, but the value is expected to be slightly higher in the next presale stage. With the token price low, a potential increase in demand will raise the value and generate huge returns.</p>
<p dir="ltr">But $ASI is more than an asset for speculation. It means investing for trading profits and learning from the experts. Investors get access to quality trading signals generated by the AltSignals team. There are also learning opportunities where traders can engage in trading contests. Investors are rewarded with $ASI for winning trading tournaments and competitions. This could be an opportunity to improve one&rsquo;s trading skills.</p>
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals also allows investors to join the AI Members Club. The members can earn $ASI by giving feedback and ideas on various projects. There are also exclusive presale opportunities for ActualizeAI members.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Will AltSignals explode in 2023?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals could be an ideal investment opportunity over the long term. Decentralised AI is getting noticed while blockchain is growing. This means $ASI can deliver consistent returns as the AI platform grows in popularity. The prediction doesn&rsquo;t mean $ASI will be muted in 2023.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The token&rsquo;s presale has been happening fast, implying high demand. With $ASI set to list on Uniswap in the third quarter of 2023, the value could finish the year strongly. A conservative double or triple-digit percentage price increase is likely.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">In the long term, $ASI has the potential to rise by more than 1,000% as it witnesses increased use. As such, the token is attractive now when still on presale, and demand is somehow locked.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/could-altsignals-become-the-hottest-token-in-2023-as-experts-laud-artificial-intelligence/">Could AltSignals become the hottest token in 2023 as experts laud artificial intelligence?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/could-altsignals-become-the-hottest-token-in-2023-as-experts-laud-artificial-intelligence/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Litecoin completes third halving, block reward cut to 6.25 LTC</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/litecoin-completes-third-halving-block-reward-cut-to-6-25-ltc/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 16:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/litecoin-completes-third-halving-block-reward-cut-to-6-25-ltc/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Litecoin halving is complete, with block reward reduced to 6.25 LTC. LTC price was $91 at halving, down 4% in the past 24 hours. Litecoin has halved its block reward from 12.5 LTC to 6.25 LTC following the activation of its third halving event at block height 2,520,000. The proof-of-work (PoW) coin&#8217;s latest halving happened [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/litecoin-completes-third-halving-block-reward-cut-to-6-25-ltc/">Litecoin completes third halving, block reward cut to 6.25 LTC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Litecoin halving is complete, with block reward reduced to 6.25 LTC.</li>
<li dir="ltr">LTC price was $91 at halving, down 4% in the past 24 hours.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/litecoin/">Litecoin</a> has halved its block reward from 12.5 LTC to 6.25 LTC following the activation of its third halving event at block height 2,520,000.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The proof-of-work (PoW) coin&rsquo;s latest halving happened as LTC price hovered near price levels also seen during the last event in 2019.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, the network has seen significant growth in terms of total addresses, number of active daily addresses, transaction volume, and hashrate among other metrics, according to market intelligence and on-chain data analytics platform <a href="https://twitter.com/intotheblock/status/1686735190297600000" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">IntoTheBlock</a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Happy halving day <a href="https://twitter.com/litecoin?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@litecoin</a>! Let's compare some key metrics to the last halving in 2019. What do you notice&#128064;?<a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/LITECOINHALVING?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#LITECOINHALVING</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/LTC?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#LTC</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Litecoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Litecoin</a> <a href="https://t.co/V9wneIZkRS">pic.twitter.com/V9wneIZkRS</a></p>
<p>&mdash; IntoTheBlock (@intotheblock) <a href="https://twitter.com/intotheblock/status/1686735190297600000?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 2, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2>LTC price at halving</h2>
<p>Litecoin price is down 4% in the past 24 hours and 17% in the past month.&nbsp;</p>
<p>At current levels of $89.7, LTC/USD is about 78% from its 2021 bull market peak. Notably too is that the coin peaked at just above $115 in its pre-halving rally, a scenario that opens up a potentially short-term negative flip.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Historically though, prices have rebounded higher post-halving and positive market conditions in next few months could aid that outlook.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Crypto analyst Rekt Capital <a href="https://twitter.com/rektcapital/status/1686680324992835584" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">pointed out</a> this forecast earlier today.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Many months later, <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24LTC&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$LTC</a> has registered its Pre-Halving top around the $115 region</p>
<p>Picture-perfect rejection from the orange Macro Downtrend</p>
<p>As per post-Halving tendencies, here's what to expect in the coming months:</p>
<p>&#128201; <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/LTC?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#LTC</a> may experience deep retracement</p>
<p>Historically, LTC&hellip; <a href="https://t.co/XUz1Woukog">https://t.co/XUz1Woukog</a> <a href="https://t.co/RP5oYQSVi9">pic.twitter.com/RP5oYQSVi9</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Rekt Capital (@rektcapital) <a href="https://twitter.com/rektcapital/status/1686680324992835584?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 2, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">As noted above, the price of Litecoin at the time of halving today was largely the same as at the last halving. However, as Rekt mentions above, LTC has rallied more post-halving than pre-halving and the prediction could still materialise in the next several months.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Litecoin&rsquo;s value rose to a new all-time high of $410 in May 2021, before the bear market of 2022 saw the cryptocurrency lose most of that value. Prices dropped to lows of $47 in June as crypto contagion impacted markets after the collapse of Terra and Three Arrows Capital.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/litecoin-completes-third-halving-block-reward-cut-to-6-25-ltc/">Litecoin completes third halving, block reward cut to 6.25 LTC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cautious optimism prevails in crypto, but Chancer presale maintains momentum</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/cautious-optimism-prevails-in-crypto-but-chancer-presale-maintains-momentum/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/cautious-optimism-prevails-in-crypto-but-chancer-presale-maintains-momentum/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Motiur Rahman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 15:56:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technical Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/cautious-optimism-prevails-in-crypto-but-chancer-presale-maintains-momentum/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto markets are mixed this week as the outlook remains unclear Chancer&#8217;s presale has surpassed $1.08 million amid high demand for the token Chancer has strong potential due to a robust betting market and blockchain application Investors might be a little cautious in crypto this week. The market has displayed a mixed outlook, with slight [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/cautious-optimism-prevails-in-crypto-but-chancer-presale-maintains-momentum/">Cautious optimism prevails in crypto, but Chancer presale maintains momentum</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Crypto markets are mixed this week as the outlook remains unclear</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Chancer&rsquo;s presale has surpassed $1.08 million amid high demand for the token</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Chancer has strong potential due to a robust betting market and blockchain application</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Investors might be a little cautious in crypto this week. The market has displayed a mixed outlook, with slight gains and losses across the major cryptos. Meanwhile, investors are undeterred when it comes to newly launching crypto projects. Chancer, a new predictive markets project, continues to attract buyers. The project&rsquo;s&nbsp;<a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>presale</u></a> has surpassed $1.08 million in amounts raised.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>XRP ruling jitters and key market developments this week</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Jitters over last month&rsquo;s ruling that Ripple&rsquo;s XRP is not a security could be rattling crypto markets. The July ruling saw crypto markets, especially XRP, make strong comebacks. Investors believed that the ruling cleared the uncertainty in the crypto sector. But the recovery has now been muted, as SEC is said to consider appealing the court decision.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Meanwhile, investors are also watching the US non-farm payroll data this week for July. The report gives a synopsis of the US labour market and causes huge moves in the market. Investors are looking forward to slower payroll growth amid extreme weather conditions in the US.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Crypto markets have, in the past, reacted to NFP data. Strong payroll data has fueled selling in crypto on expectations of economic tightening. It also has a positive impact on the dollar and a negative relationship with crypto. Thus, the event will be closely watched on August 4.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Chancer presale maintains momentum.</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">As investors exercise caution on crypto this week, the buying of Chancer tokens isn&rsquo;t slowing down. As of August 2, the project had raised more than $1.08 million. Since launching the presale on June 13, Chancer has been selling fast. The demand has been fueled by Chancer&rsquo;s revolutionary betting model.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The project is launched with the promise of taking betting to the blockchain. Chancer will allow a peer-to-peer betting model via a decentralised ecosystem, the first in the world.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Decentralisation is the art of Chancer&rsquo;s predictive markets system. Unlike the current betting system, P2P betting allows users to create their betting markets. They are not constrained by what their bookmakers provide. As such, one can bet on virtually any event through Chancer&rsquo;s P2P markets. The platform also allows users to set their betting rules and bet against whomever they want.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The idea of a decentralised betting ecosystem has attracted interest in the project. In the future, Chancer will focus on adopting a quadratic governance model. This is where participants use their voice credits to vote on governance issues.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Is Chancer a good investment?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Betting is growing fast, allowing Chancer to carve a market niche. But aside from the novel betting model brought by the project, Chancer could be an ideal investment token.</p>
<p dir="ltr">First, the potential for the Chancer token to increase in value is high. The prediction emanates from a strong and growing betting market and the application of blockchain. Allowing investors to create Chancer markets and bet on multiple events will increase the token&rsquo;s use case. This will allow it to increase in value and generate returns to investors.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Secondly, Chancer has an investment model beyond betting. Users get rewarded for creating Chancer P2P markets. Token holders can also participate in building the Chancer platform by staking the tokens. Other income-generating ways are sharing the platform and earning through a Share2Earn feature.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>How much can the Chancer token increase?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Like any other newly launched token with a robust use case, Chancer can rise by up to 10x. The gains can be realised within months after the token debuts on exchanges.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The projection depends on how much the project will unlock value. With the mainnet launching in Q1 2024, the project could start attracting users soon. However, the value of Chancer could start to be unlocked in Q3 2023. This is when the token will be listed on centralised exchanges, starting with Uniswap.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/cautious-optimism-prevails-in-crypto-but-chancer-presale-maintains-momentum/">Cautious optimism prevails in crypto, but Chancer presale maintains momentum</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/cautious-optimism-prevails-in-crypto-but-chancer-presale-maintains-momentum/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hyundai and Kia tap Hedera Network for CO2 emission monitoring system</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/hyundai-and-kia-tap-hedera-network-for-co2-emission-monitoring-system/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/hyundai-and-kia-tap-hedera-network-for-co2-emission-monitoring-system/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 14:58:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/hyundai-and-kia-tap-hedera-network-for-co2-emission-monitoring-system/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Hyundai and Kia have introduced an AI-enabled supply chain carbon emissions tracking solution on the Hedera Network. Hedera (HBAR) briefly surged above $0.053 after the announcement. The adoption of Hedera technology by these two major automakers indicates an increase in blockchain adoption. Two significant automakers, Hyundai and Kia, have adopted the Hedera network, pointing to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/hyundai-and-kia-tap-hedera-network-for-co2-emission-monitoring-system/">Hyundai and Kia tap Hedera Network for CO2 emission monitoring system</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul class="decimal_type">
<li>Hyundai and Kia have introduced an AI-enabled supply chain carbon emissions tracking solution on the Hedera Network.</li>
<li>Hedera (HBAR) briefly surged above $0.053 after the announcement.</li>
<li>The adoption of Hedera technology by these two major automakers indicates an increase in blockchain adoption.</li>
</ul>
<p>Two significant automakers, Hyundai and Kia, have adopted the Hedera network, pointing to an increase in <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/blockchain/">blockchain adoption</a>. Hyundai Motor Company and Kia Corporation have reportedly introduced an AI-powered CO2 Emission Monitoring System with the help of the highly scalable Hedera Network.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">We&rsquo;re excited to announce that <a href="https://twitter.com/HMGnewsroom?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@HMGnewsroom</a>, the largest car manufacturer in South Korea, and <a href="https://twitter.com/Kia?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@Kia</a> have introduced an <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/AI?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#AI</a>-enabled supply chain carbon emissions tracking solution on the highly scalable <a href="https://twitter.com/hedera?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@Hedera</a> network &#127472;&#127479; <a href="https://t.co/PiI7sUfE9G">pic.twitter.com/PiI7sUfE9G</a></p>
<p>&mdash; HBAR Foundation (@HBAR_foundation) <a href="https://twitter.com/HBAR_foundation/status/1686709300629041152?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 2, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>According to a post by the HBAR Foundation, the launch of a blockchain-based Supplier CO2 Emission Monitoring System (SCEMS) on the Hedera mainnet demonstrates that the value of Hedera Network is &ldquo;seen by enterprises beyond the Governing Council&rdquo; and &ldquo;when data accuracy and security are mission critical, Hedera is second to none&rdquo;</p>
<p>The SCEMS is made to calculate carbon emissions at every step of the supply chain, giving Hyundai Motor and Kia access to accurate information about the operations of their suppliers, including the sourcing of raw materials, the manufacturing process, and the transportation of finished goods.</p>
<p>This is a huge step towards successfully mitigating the effects of climate change, which requires a reduction of carbon emissions.</p>
<p>SCEMS also incorporates AI technology, allowing for the precise prediction of future carbon emissions and the setting of carbon reduction goals.</p>
<h2>Hedera (HBAR) price reaction</h2>
<p>The <a href="https://coinjournal.net/hedera/">price of HBAR</a>, the native token of Hedera Network, saw a significant price surge that briefly pushed the price above $0.053, although the price has since slightly pullback to around $0.052 at the time of writing.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/07/02/1690988037411-63f54aa9-c03f-4fe3-a73d-76a1fbb110ef.jpg" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="615" height="372"></p>
<p>While there was a slight price surge, the pullback could good sign that Hedera is under quite some strong bear forces that have been pulling down the HBAR price over the past month.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/hyundai-and-kia-tap-hedera-network-for-co2-emission-monitoring-system/">Hyundai and Kia tap Hedera Network for CO2 emission monitoring system</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/hyundai-and-kia-tap-hedera-network-for-co2-emission-monitoring-system/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple CEO slams SEC for weaponizing XRP reports in lawsuit</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/ripple-ceo-slams-sec-for-weaponizing-xrp-reports-in-lawsuit/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/ripple-ceo-slams-sec-for-weaponizing-xrp-reports-in-lawsuit/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 14:23:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/ripple-ceo-slams-sec-for-weaponizing-xrp-reports-in-lawsuit/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse says the SEC took Ripple&#8217;s transparency reports and used them against the company. The SEC sued Ripple over its XRP sales in December 2020, alleging the sales amounted to securities contracts. A court decision recently declared XRP not a security. In Ripple news today, CEO Brad Garlinghouse has slammed the US [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ripple-ceo-slams-sec-for-weaponizing-xrp-reports-in-lawsuit/">Ripple CEO slams SEC for weaponizing XRP reports in lawsuit</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse says the SEC took Ripple&rsquo;s transparency reports and used them against the company.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The SEC sued Ripple over its XRP sales in December 2020, alleging the sales amounted to securities contracts.</li>
<li dir="ltr">A court decision recently declared XRP not a security.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">In <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/ripple/">Ripple news</a> today, CEO Brad Garlinghouse has slammed the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) over its apparent weaponization of what&rsquo;s been &ldquo;good-faith&rdquo; transparency reports on <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/xrp/">XRP</a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Acccoridng to him, the SEC took the regular reports and used their details in its lawsuit against the company and its top executives. Garlinghouse, who was also sued by the SEC in December 2020, however, reiterated Ripple&rsquo;s commitment to transparency.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>We began these reports to voluntarily provide updates given our XRP holdings. Sadly, they were used against us in the SEC lawsuit &ndash; however, we remain steadfast in our commitment to transparency but I suspect they&rsquo;re going to look a bit different moving forward</em>,&rdquo; he <a href="https://twitter.com/bgarlinghouse/status/1686618130674774016" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">said</a>.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Ripple&rsquo;s XRP markets reports</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Garlinghouse&rsquo;s remarks followed Ripple&rsquo;s release of its <a href="https://ripple.com/insights/q2-2023-xrp-markets-report/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Q2, 2023 XRP Markets Report</a>, with the company noting the different approach taken. With previous editions, Ripple has focused on multiple XRP ecosystem developments, including market insights and quarterly sales.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">We began these reports to voluntarily provide updates given our XRP holdings. Sadly, they were used against us in the SEC lawsuit &ndash; however, we remain steadfast in our commitment to transparency but I suspect they&rsquo;re going to look a bit different moving forward <a href="https://t.co/oANR6WCG09">https://t.co/oANR6WCG09</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Brad Garlinghouse (@bgarlinghouse) <a href="https://twitter.com/bgarlinghouse/status/1686618130674774016?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 2, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>While published in a good faith effort at transparency, these quarterly reports have been weaponized against the Company by the SEC. Ironic for an agency that touts transparency and disclosure. Accordingly, Ripple is re-evaluating the role and contents of this report going forward and will have updates on that front in Q3 2023</em>,&rdquo; Team Ripple wrote in its report published July 31.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The change in approach already saw the Q2 report focus on the July 13, 2023 court ruling on XRP, including details &ldquo;debunking misconceptions&rdquo; about the ruling being a split decision and that the court deemed some sales of XRP as securities and others not.</p>
<p dir="ltr"></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ripple-ceo-slams-sec-for-weaponizing-xrp-reports-in-lawsuit/">Ripple CEO slams SEC for weaponizing XRP reports in lawsuit</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/ripple-ceo-slams-sec-for-weaponizing-xrp-reports-in-lawsuit/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Worldcoin to allow governments and businesses to use its ID-verifying technology</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/worldcoin-to-allow-governments-and-businesses-to-use-its-id-verifying-technology/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/worldcoin-to-allow-governments-and-businesses-to-use-its-id-verifying-technology/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 14:14:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/worldcoin-to-allow-governments-and-businesses-to-use-its-id-verifying-technology/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Worldcoin launched its native token WLD on its mainnet on July 24, 2023. The crypto project has faced serious criticism from several quarters for fears of data privacy. The latest development is the Worldcoin suspension in Kenya because of what the government says are security concerns. According to a Reuters report, Worldcoin intends to broaden [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/worldcoin-to-allow-governments-and-businesses-to-use-its-id-verifying-technology/">Worldcoin to allow governments and businesses to use its ID-verifying technology</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Worldcoin launched its native token WLD on its mainnet on July 24, 2023.</li>
<li>The crypto project has faced serious criticism from several quarters for fears of data privacy.</li>
<li>The latest development is the Worldcoin suspension in Kenya because of what the government says are security concerns.</li>
</ul>
<p>According to a Reuters report, Worldcoin intends to broaden its operations so that businesses and governments can make use of its iris-scanning and identity-verification technology to attract more users.</p>
<p>In the report, Ricardo Macieira, the general manager for Europe at Tools For Humanity, which is the company that created Worldcoin, said that the company is on a mission of &ldquo;building the biggest financial and identity community&rdquo; possible.</p>
<p>Macieira said, &ldquo;The idea is that as we build this infrastructure and that we allow other third parties to use the technology.&rdquo; He went ahead to add &ldquo;The idea is that anyone can in the future build their own orb and use it to benefit the community that it&rsquo;s aiming for.&rdquo;</p>
<h2>Plans to open-source the Orbs technology</h2>
<p>To enable broader use of Worldcoin&rsquo;s products, Macieria added that the company intends to open source the technology that powers the iris-scanning orbs. This will be a huge step towards countering difficulties in attracting users.</p>
<p>However, although reports about Worldcoin&rsquo;s difficulties attracting users after its launch have recently gone around, Sam Altman, a co-founder of the project, has refuted those allegations in posts on X that include videos of people waiting in line for iris scans.</p>
<p>In the report, Macieira has also gone ahead to explain Worldcoin intends for companies and governments to pay to use its digital identity system. This will allow the institutions to implement some sort of localized system without having to gather personal data.</p>
<p>However, it is not clear how Worldcoin intends to circumvent the regulatory framework around the world, especially seeing that its data collection methods have already come under scrutiny from regulators around the world.</p>
<p>France&rsquo;s privacy watchdog said that it <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/frances-privacy-watchdog-questions-worldcoins-data-collection/">finds the project &ldquo;questionable,&rdquo;</a> while German regulators launched investigations into Worldcoin&rsquo;s operations back in 2022. Regulators in the UK are also considering opening an inquiry into Worldcoin. And in Kenya where the project had received such a huge reception, the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/kenya-suspends-worldcoin-activities-after-nearly-half-a-million-sign-ups/">government has slumped the door</a> citing security concerns.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/worldcoin-to-allow-governments-and-businesses-to-use-its-id-verifying-technology/">Worldcoin to allow governments and businesses to use its ID-verifying technology</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/worldcoin-to-allow-governments-and-businesses-to-use-its-id-verifying-technology/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kaspa (KAS) price pops amid Tier-1 Exchange listing campaign</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/kaspa-kas-price-pops-amid-tier-1-exchange-listing-campaign/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 13:35:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/kaspa-kas-price-pop-amid-tier-1-exchange-listing-campaign/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Kaspa (KAS) token has gained 76% over the past month. Most of the gains were recorded in the past three days. Kaspa has embarked on a vigorous campaign to have the token listed on a Tier-1 crypto exchange. Kaspa (KAS) cryptocurrency has been making headlines in the recent past. It has shown quite a remarkable [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/kaspa-kas-price-pops-amid-tier-1-exchange-listing-campaign/">Kaspa (KAS) price pops amid Tier-1 Exchange listing campaign</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Kaspa (KAS) token has gained 76% over the past month.</li>
<li>Most of the gains were recorded in the past three days.</li>
<li>Kaspa has embarked on a vigorous campaign to have the token listed on a Tier-1 crypto exchange.</li>
</ul>
<p>Kaspa (KAS) cryptocurrency has been making headlines in the recent past. It has shown quite a remarkable performance even in the bear market. There are actually reports that traders are disposing of their <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/what-is-bitcoin/">bitcoins</a> for KAS tokens.</p>
<p>At press time, the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/kaspa/">price of KAS</a> had risen by 6% to add to its 76% rise in the past month compared to <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">Bitcoin (BTC)</a> which has only risen by 2% in the past 24 hours and lost 3% in the past month. But why has Kaspa become such a sensation? Well, here is what is happening around Kaspa.</p>
<h2>Kaspa campaign to list KAS on Tier-1 Exchange</h2>
<p>Three days ago, Kaspa initiated a new crowdfund aimed at securing a Tier-1 Exchange listing for the KAS token.</p>
<p>The target of the crowdfund, which was scheduled to close today August 2 2023, is to raise $30,000 in the form of USDT and KAS.</p>
<p>The money raised through this campaign is intended to pay the listing fee obligations that may be established by the centralised exchange (CEX) listing the KAS token. This money will be used by the CEX, at its discretion, to run a thorough advertising campaign.</p>
<p>This marketing initiative will be essential after Kaspa is listed on the exchange since it intends to raise awareness of Kaspa, attract new users (who will benefit both Kaspa and the CEX), increase trading volume, and enhance liquidity. When taken as a whole, these results support Kaspa&rsquo;s overarching goals of facilitating universal adoption and inclusivity.</p>
<p>Kaspa (KAS) has recently broken into the top 52 market cap coins, a significant accomplishment that has been met with improved buying power. The cryptocurrency&rsquo;s performance has been so strong that there is speculation it could break its all-time high anytime if it continues on the same trajectory.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/kaspa-kas-price-pops-amid-tier-1-exchange-listing-campaign/">Kaspa (KAS) price pops amid Tier-1 Exchange listing campaign</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu gains while investors grab 50M Shiba Memu tokens on meme craze</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-gains-while-investors-grab-50m-shiba-memu-tokens-on-meme-craze/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-gains-while-investors-grab-50m-shiba-memu-tokens-on-meme-craze/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Motiur Rahman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 12:57:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technical Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-gains-while-investors-grab-50m-shiba-memu-tokens-on-meme-craze/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Shina Inu has risen by over 6% amid positive Shibarium news. Shiba Memu benefits from the meme craze as it raises $1.5 million. Shiba Memu has huge potential from its AI application. Meme cryptocurrencies continue to attract interest despite crypto markets remaining mixed. A few weeks after launching a&#160;presale, investors bought over 50,000,000 tokens of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-gains-while-investors-grab-50m-shiba-memu-tokens-on-meme-craze/">Shiba Inu gains while investors grab 50M Shiba Memu tokens on meme craze</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Shina Inu has risen by over 6% amid positive Shibarium news.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu benefits from the meme craze as it raises $1.5 million.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu has huge potential from its AI application.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Meme cryptocurrencies continue to attract interest despite crypto markets remaining mixed. A few weeks after launching a&nbsp;<a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>presale</u></a>, investors bought over 50,000,000 tokens of Shiba Memu (SHMU). The AI and blockchain-led project has generated nearly $1.5 million. Is this an indication of the growing popularity of meme cryptocurrencies?</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Shiba Inu is the top gainer among the top 20 cryptos</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Perhaps underlining the interest in meme cryptocurrencies is Shiba Inu. Unlike Shiba Memu, Shiba Inu has been in the meme space for a while. The cryptocurrency has attracted praise and criticism in equal measure. For critics, Shiba Inu carries little or no value.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The delayed launch of Shibarium has been a particular source of criticism. Shibarium is expected to give Shiba Inu more utility. This includes powering the project&rsquo;s metaverse dream. For enthusiasts, Shiba Inu can take on established blockchains and cryptocurrencies.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">As such, Shiba Inu has witnessed wild price swings on changing investor sentiment. However, Shiba Inu is the top-gaining cryptocurrency this week among the top 20 peers. In the past week, the cryptocurrency has added over 6%. The gains are about half its closest top gainer, BNB, with 3.30%.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The gains in Shiba Inu came when the Shibarium Beta Bridge went live for public testing. Enthusiasts have reacted to the developments, which suggest Shibarium is well on course. But meanwhile, Shiba gains underline that investors are still banking on tokens that drive overnight hype. The fast-selling Shiba Memu presale partly underlines this sentiment.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Why is the Shiba Memu presale in high demand?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">&nbsp;Like any other meme cryptocurrency, Shiba Memu is benefiting from investor demand. These tokens rise at the slightest of news, returning big to its early movers. But Shiba Memu is crafting a niche that investors are banking on.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu is a self-marketing cryptocurrency. It leverages artificial intelligence to market itself and generate hype. By leveraging AI, Shiba Memu aims to become self-sufficient. This creates a unique investment opportunity as it can deliver consistent results.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu enters the meme space when the application of AI is rising. There is no limit on what AI can do, meaning that Shiba Memu can become more intelligent and powerful. The project also learns every time, and being robotic-led, it can do more than humans. This gives the token a huge potential to explode as AI and blockchain become more pronounced.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>What is the investment potential of Shiba Memu?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Meme cryptocurrencies are always an exciting asset class. They always surprise the market, pulling double and triple-digit returns in hours or a few days. In fact, meme tokens have grown so popular that their market cap crossed $20 billion in 2022. The market value was $0 in early 2020.</p>
<p dir="ltr">With the market growth, a huge potential lies in meme tokens like Shiba Memu. That also reflects a changing investment landscape where meme stocks and tokens are growing popular. Shiba Memu could ride the meme frenzy to become a strong and valuable cryptocurrency.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Apart from the market size and dynamics, Shiba Memu is the only meme cryptocurrency that is AI-led. Users can use the project&rsquo;s AI dashboard to monitor hot and trending topics in creative advertising. This could also be a chance for users to engage the AI itself. They can ask questions, provide feedback, and give suggestions. The engagement could make Shiba Memu user-centric and drive value for the native token.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Shiba Memu price dynamics are unique</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">The desire to own Shiba Memu at presale is high as this will only be an 8-week affair. Within this period, the price of SHMU will have doubled from $0.011125 to $0.0244. This is because the price of SHMU increases every day at 6 pm GMT. It means investors that buy now are better off than 24 hours later. That potentially explains the fast happening presale.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-gains-while-investors-grab-50m-shiba-memu-tokens-on-meme-craze/">Shiba Inu gains while investors grab 50M Shiba Memu tokens on meme craze</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-gains-while-investors-grab-50m-shiba-memu-tokens-on-meme-craze/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
