<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 20:18:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Perpetual DEX Palmswap Joins Forces with Gotbit Ahead of Liquidity Event </title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/palmswap-gotbit-liquidity-event/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 20:18:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gotbit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[palm]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[palmswap]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[plp]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=260202</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/palmswap-gotbit-liquidity-event/">Perpetual DEX Palmswap Joins Forces with Gotbit Ahead of Liquidity Event </a></p>
<p>The upcoming Palmswap V2 is an enhanced iteration of the decentralized leveraged trading platform and is set to debut on July 5.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/palmswap-gotbit-liquidity-event/">Perpetual DEX Palmswap Joins Forces with Gotbit Ahead of Liquidity Event </a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/palmswap-gotbit-liquidity-event/">Perpetual DEX Palmswap Joins Forces with Gotbit Ahead of Liquidity Event </a></p>
<p>Palmswap, a decentralized exchange (DEX) focused on perpetual futures trading, has partnered with crypto market maker Gotbit Hedge Fund in preparation for its upcoming liquidity program scheduled for next week.</p>
<p>As part of the collaboration, Gotbit has allocated a certain amount of funds, the exact figure undisclosed, to provide liquidity through the minting and auto-staking of the Palmswap Liquidity Provider (PLP) token. The event is slated to commence on June 27 for early adopters and June 29 for all participants.</p>
<p>Bernd Stöckl, an executive at Palmswap, expressed enthusiasm about the upcoming liquidity event, noting that Gotbit is well-equipped to handle the expected transaction volumes, speeds, and order management during the program.</p>
<p>&#8220;Our upcoming liquidity event will usher in a new era of fast, efficient, and user-friendly decentralized trading. We are excited about our partnership with Gotbit for our liquidity event and are confident in the platform&#8217;s ability to handle the expected transaction volumes, speeds, and order management of the event,&#8221; said Stöckl.</p>
<p>While the amount of liquidity Gotbit provided to Palmswap was not disclosed, the market maker and infrastructure provider has been offering liquidity to early-stage blockchain projects through its liquidity-providing program, which opened in November 2022. The liquidity can be locked or frozen for up to 12 months, depending on the agreement with the project developers.</p>
<h2>Palmswap to Distribute 60% Transaction Fees to Users</h2>
<p>According to a recent <a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2023/06/21/2692466/0/en/Palmswap-Secures-Partnership-with-Gotbit-for-the-Palmswap-Liquidity-Event.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">press release,</a> users who stake their PLP tokens during the event will earn up to 500% APR (Annual Percentage Rate) and receive additional incentives based on trades and market activity on Palmswap V2. The upcoming Palmswap V2 is an enhanced iteration of the decentralized leveraged trading platform and is set to debut on July 5.</p>
<p>Palmswap has been making strides in advancing its offerings, including introducing the alpha mainnet earlier this year, which utilizes a robust Automated Market Maker (AMM) algorithm. However, with the new V2 underway, the protocol aims to provide a seamless experience to users as the network is designed with a synthetic framework to reduce transaction costs and enhance scalability.</p>
<p>Based on the Binance Smart Chain (BSC), the DEX protocol plans to distribute 60% of all transaction fees generated on the platform to PLP holders and stakers. These rewards will be paid out in USDT stablecoin during the liquidity event.</p>
<h2>PALM to Start Trading from $1</h2>
<p>Palmswap also established a reward program for early minters on July 27. A total of 25 million PALM, the native <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/crypto/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">crypto</a> of the Palmswap V2 network, valued at over $500,000, will be released on a first-come, first-served basis and will start trading at $1.</p>
<p>The minting process for PLP tokens and Palmswap V2 tokens (PALM) will involve multiple tiers, with each level accessible once the preceding one is completed.</p>
<p>Palmswap is confident that its partnership with Gotbit, along with the liquidity provision and the active involvement and expansion of the Palmswap user community, will position Palmswap V2 for sustainable growth and engagement among the new wave of Web3 participants.</p>
<p>Commenting on the alliance with the protocol, Alex Andryunin, founder and CEO of Gotbit Hedge Fund, praised Palmswap for its unique approach among decentralized trading platforms and commended the company&#8217;s commitment to user-friendly, cost-effective, fast, and reliable digital asset trading.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-leveraged-bitcoin-futures-etf/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/palmswap-gotbit-liquidity-event/">Perpetual DEX Palmswap Joins Forces with Gotbit Ahead of Liquidity Event </a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>SEC Approves First Leveraged Bitcoin Futures ETF</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-leveraged-bitcoin-futures-etf/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Temitope Olatunji]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 14:57:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funds & ETFs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cboe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=260208</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-leveraged-bitcoin-futures-etf/">SEC Approves First Leveraged Bitcoin Futures ETF</a></p>
<p>The BITX being a 2x leveraged ETF can help investors to increase their profit two times faster than they would do without the leverage.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-leveraged-bitcoin-futures-etf/">SEC Approves First Leveraged Bitcoin Futures ETF</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-leveraged-bitcoin-futures-etf/">SEC Approves First Leveraged Bitcoin Futures ETF</a></p>
<p>The first leveraged Bitcoin futures exchange-traded fund (ETF) has received approval from the US Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>). The ETF, the Volatility Shares 2x Bitcoin Strategy (BITX), will be launched on the Chicago Board Options Exchange (CBOE) BZX Exchange on Tuesday, June 27th.</p>
<p>ETFs can be traded on exchanges like stocks, and their prices change often within the same day as they are bought and sold. Bitcoin ETFs are of two main types: the Bitcoin futures and the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> spot price. The approval of futures ETFs will expose investors to Bitcoin without having to invest in the actual asset.</p>
<p>Although many in the crypto industry are pleased with the introduction, some are concerned about the order in which they are being granted. They wonder why a leveraged futures product like BITX is being introduced before a traditional spot ETF.</p>
<p>Nate Geraci, the President of ETF Store, is one of the people who believe the spot ETF should have been prioritized. In expressing his views about the announcement, he made the following comment in a tweet.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">When we look back on the bitcoin ETF saga in 5 or 10yrs, this will be one of the most ridiculous aspects&#8230;</p>
<p>A 2x leveraged futures product launching before a straightforward spot ETF.</p>
<p>Wild.</p>
<p>— Nate Geraci (@NateGeraci) <a href="https://twitter.com/NateGeraci/status/1672276942039445514?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 23, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The BITX being a 2x leveraged ETF can easily mean investors will increase their profit two times faster than they would have without the leverage. On the other hand, the chances of losing their money in the case of a less favorable market condition are also doubled. Thus, as it offers more profit, it also increases the chances of losses.</p>
<p>In expressing their thoughts about the risks involved in trading leveraged products, the SEC <a href="https://www.sec.gov/ix?doc=/Archives/edgar/data/1884021/000138713123007744/bitx-485bpos_052323.htm" target="_blank" rel="noopener">stated</a> that:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The Fund presents different risks than other types of funds. The Fund is not suitable for all investors and should be used only by knowledgeable investors who understand the consequences of seeking daily leveraged (2x) investment results, including the impact of compounding on Fund performance.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2><span id="output-sentence-box~0"><span id="output-sentence~0"><span id="output-phrase~0~0">The Approval </span><span id="output-phrase~0~1">of </span><span id="output-phrase~0~2">BITX </span><span id="output-phrase~0~3">is G</span><span id="output-phrase~0~4">ood News </span><span id="output-phrase~0~5">for </span><span id="output-phrase~0~6">the Cryptocurrency I</span><span id="output-phrase~0~7">ndustry</span></span></span></h2>
<p><span id="output-sentence-box~0"><span id="output-sentence~0"> </span></span><span id="output-sentence-box~1"><span id="output-sentence~1"><span id="output-phrase~1~0">With </span><span id="output-phrase~1~1">the SEC&#8217;s </span><span id="output-phrase~1~2">various lawsuits </span><span id="output-phrase~1~3">against </span><span id="output-phrase~1~4">crypto </span><span id="output-phrase~1~5">companies, </span><span id="output-phrase~1~6">including </span><span id="output-phrase~1~7">the recent </span><span id="output-phrase~1~8"><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-sues-binance-securities-rules/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">suing</a> </span><span id="output-phrase~1~9">of </span><span id="output-phrase~1~10">Binance </span><span id="output-phrase~1~11">and </span><span id="output-phrase~1~12">Coinbase, </span><span id="output-phrase~1~13">one </span><span id="output-phrase~1~14">may conclude </span><span id="output-phrase~1~15">that the </span><span id="output-phrase~1~16">SEC&#8217;s </span><span id="output-phrase~1~17">chairman, </span><span id="output-phrase~1~18">Gary Gensler, </span><span id="output-phrase~1~19">is critical of </span><span id="output-phrase~1~20">cryptocurrencies.</span> However, the recent updates may provide other perspectives on how the regulatory body sees cryptocurrencies.</span></span></p>
<p>Eric Balchunas, a senior ETF analyst at Bloomberg, expressed his thoughts in <a href="https://twitter.com/EricBalchunas/status/1672274997187051521" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">a tweet</a>, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>“The 2x bitcoin ETF $BITX has become effective, scheduled to launch Tuesday. I was doubtful it would happen but looks like it’s official. Could this be early sign of SEC lightening up? After $BITO launch I believe they made earlier 2x filers withdraw.”</p></blockquote>
<p>The approval can affect how investors perceive the industry, attracting more of them and making the market more volatile. While it may be too early to conclude how the SEC sees cryptocurrencies, this news is a move in the right direction for the crypto industry.</p>
<h3>BTC Price Spiked after BITX News Release</h3>
<p>The news affected the price of Bitcoin, which spiked to $31,450 shortly after its release on Friday, June 23rd. The figure represents the highest price it has reached in a year. It is also a 5% increase from its closing price of $29,890 the day before. The sudden rise in price signals investors’ confidence in crypto and that the market received the news well.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/maye-musk-fight-tesla-meta/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-leveraged-bitcoin-futures-etf/">SEC Approves First Leveraged Bitcoin Futures ETF</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Maye Musk Cancels Jiu Jitsu Fight between Her Son Tesla CEO and Meta Platforms Co-Founder Mark Zuckerberg</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/maye-musk-fight-tesla-meta/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 14:56:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[facebook]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mark zuckerberg]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[maye musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Meta]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tesl]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tesla]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=260178</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/maye-musk-fight-tesla-meta/">Maye Musk Cancels Jiu Jitsu Fight between Her Son Tesla CEO and Meta Platforms Co-Founder Mark Zuckerberg</a></p>
<p>Earlier, Meta co-founder Mark Zuckerberg had agreed to a Jiu-Jitsu fight in a cage with Tesla CEO Elon Musk following social media pressure.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/maye-musk-fight-tesla-meta/">Maye Musk Cancels Jiu Jitsu Fight between Her Son Tesla CEO and Meta Platforms Co-Founder Mark Zuckerberg</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/maye-musk-fight-tesla-meta/">Maye Musk Cancels Jiu Jitsu Fight between Her Son Tesla CEO and Meta Platforms Co-Founder Mark Zuckerberg</a></p>
<p>In what was described to be the biggest Jiu-Jitsu fight of the century, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/meta/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Meta Platforms Inc</a> (NASDAQ: META) co-founder <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/mark-zuckerberg/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Mark Zuckerberg</a> and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/tesla/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tesla Inc</a> (NASDAQ: TSLA) CEO <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/elon-musk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Elon Musk</a> had agreed to lock each other in a physical contest. The fight was ostensibly triggered by Mario Nawfal, CEO of Web3 incubator platform IBC Group, after highlighting the competitive nature between Twitter and Meta in the social media industry. However, Musk’s mother Maye Musk &#8211; popularly known for her model and dietitian career &#8211; canceled the fight before it even materialized.</p>
<p>Notably, Maye emphasized the fight was canceled through Twitter as more people cheered on either side. In a video podcast, Musk joked about how his body mass could help him win the fight even though Zuckerberg could have the skills in Jiu Jitsu.</p>
<p>“Actually, I canceled the fight. I haven’t told them yet. But I will continue to say the fight is canceled, just in case..,” she <a href="https://twitter.com/mayemusk/status/1672002803139506179" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">emphasized</a>.</p>
<p>Interestingly, Musk replied with an emoji of face and tears of joy, which prompted mixed reactions from the followers. Reportedly, the cage fight that was to be undertaken through a UFC style between Musk and Zuckerberg would use Joe Rogan as a potential referee. Already, UFC President Dana White had confirmed that he had spoken to both Elon and Zuckerberg and indicated that they are serious. However, Maye insisted that the two should fight in words only or through an armchair.</p>
<p>“No joking. Fight with words only. In armchairs. 4 feet apart.  The funniest person wins,” she noted in a tweet.</p>
<h2>Twitter vs Meta</h2>
<p>While Twitter is a private company that was acquired by Musk late last year with approximately $44 billion, Meta Platforms is a  Family of Apps (FoA) and Reality Labs (RL) segments including Facebook, Instagram, Messenger, and WhatsApp, among others. Notably, Meta is currently valued at approximately $730.19 billion with its stock market up approximately 133 percent YTD to trade around $280 on Friday.</p>
<p>The two social media entities have been competing on obtaining the highest number of online advertisers, but Musk through the latest Twitter CEO, Linda Yaccarino, a former global advertising and partnerships chairperson at NBCUniversal Media, has taken a different stance via free speech.</p>
<p>As of March, Meta Platforms noted that its family of apps recorded monthly active people of about 3.81 billion. Facebook alone reported monthly active users (MAUs) of about 2.99 billion as of March 31, 2023. During the Q1 <a href="https://s21.q4cdn.com/399680738/files/doc_financials/2023/q1/Meta-03-31-2023-Exhibit-99-1-FINAL-v2.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a>, Zuckerberg insisted that the company is focused on artificial intelligence (AI) to ensure future growth prospects.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/siemens-energy-issues-turbine-problems/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/maye-musk-fight-tesla-meta/">Maye Musk Cancels Jiu Jitsu Fight between Her Son Tesla CEO and Meta Platforms Co-Founder Mark Zuckerberg</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Siemens Energy Stock Loses 35% as Review of Issues at Subsidiary Shows Wind Turbine Problems Could Last for Years</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/siemens-energy-issues-turbine-problems/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 14:05:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[siemens]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[siemens energy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=260113</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/siemens-energy-issues-turbine-problems/">Siemens Energy Stock Loses 35% as Review of Issues at Subsidiary Shows Wind Turbine Problems Could Last for Years</a></p>
<p>Siemens Energy CEO Christian Bruch said that "too much had been swept under the carpet" concerning Siemens Gamesa.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/siemens-energy-issues-turbine-problems/">Siemens Energy Stock Loses 35% as Review of Issues at Subsidiary Shows Wind Turbine Problems Could Last for Years</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/siemens-energy-issues-turbine-problems/">Siemens Energy Stock Loses 35% as Review of Issues at Subsidiary Shows Wind Turbine Problems Could Last for Years</a></p>
<p>Shares of Siemens Energy declined 35% earlier today as the company discarded its profit prediction and mentioned lasting wind turbine issues. Following a review of concerns at its subsidiary Siemens Gamesa, the company announced its findings of a “substantial increase in failure rates of wind turbine components”. However, its shares plunged as the market reacts to the unpleasant update.</p>
<h2>Siemens Energy Wind Turbine Issues Linger</h2>
<p>The Thursday report shows that the Siemens Gamesa board has started an “extended technical review” to upscale product quality. Meanwhile, the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/siemens/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">parent company</a> noted that the review cost is now “significantly higher” than earlier predicted. The current estimation is over 1 billion euros, also $1.09 billion. As for Siemens Energy, it is currently impossible to have a precise estimate of the incoming financial impacts of the quality subjects considering the issues. It is also too early to calculate the result of the review of its assumption on its business plans. Speaking on the wind turbine issues, Siemens Energy <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/06/23/siemens-energy-scraps-profit-outlook-as-wind-turbine-troubles-deepen.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">noted</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“However, based on our initial assessment as of today, the potential magnitude of the impact leads us to withdraw the profit assumptions for Siemens Gamesa and consequently the profit guidance for Siemens Energy Group for fiscal year 2023.”</p></blockquote>
<p>According to Reuters, Siemens Energy CEO Christian Bruch said that &#8220;too much had been swept under the carpet&#8221; concerning Siemens Gamesa. The chief executive added that the quality issues at the company were more than he envisaged. As for the senior research analyst at Alliance Bernstein, although Siemens Energy can recover from its fall, the market is utterly shocked by the recent developments. He explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>“There’s a 17 billion euros service order book and that is delivering service on installed wind farms and in wind turbines for quite a number of years ahead &#8211; five years ahead, sometimes 10-year contracts &#8211; and to discover that a handful of your components aren’t working as you planned, that maybe you’ll need to go in and replace those components, that is a very large liability that you’re taking on.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Additionally, Green questioned Siemens Energy’s estimate of its component failures. The company said the component failures may occur in between 15% and 30% of its installed fleet of turbines. On the other hand, the research analyst said there is still a “slight question mark about where that liability ends”.</p>
<p>Fingers are crossed in expectation of another update come August. Green stated that the company may have precise estimates by then. He noted that Siemens Energy may have handled the issues at its subsidiary &#8211; Siemens Gamesa. He concluded that &#8220;certainly it is an alarmingly large hit and it’s taken the market by surprise.”</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-justice-department-prosecutor-sec/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/siemens-energy-issues-turbine-problems/">Siemens Energy Stock Loses 35% as Review of Issues at Subsidiary Shows Wind Turbine Problems Could Last for Years</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Hires Former Justice Department Prosecutor in Fight with SEC</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-justice-department-prosecutor-sec/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 14:01:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Binance News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance cz]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance us]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chnagpeng zhao]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cz]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=260185</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-justice-department-prosecutor-sec/">Binance Hires Former Justice Department Prosecutor in Fight with SEC</a></p>
<p>Kendall Day led the department's efforts to combat money laundering, including dealing with charges related to money laundering, deferred prosecution agreement, etc. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-justice-department-prosecutor-sec/">Binance Hires Former Justice Department Prosecutor in Fight with SEC</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-justice-department-prosecutor-sec/">Binance Hires Former Justice Department Prosecutor in Fight with SEC</a></p>
<p>Amid its ongoing legal fight with the US Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>), crypto exchange <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a> has <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-06-22/binance-hires-former-justice-department-prosecutor-in-sec-fight" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">hired</a> a former white-collar prosecutor of the Department of Justice (DoJ), as per the court filing on Thursday, June 22.</p>
<p>M. Kendall Day, a partner at Gibson Dunn &amp; Crutcher&#8217;s Washington DC office, will serve as counsel for Binance in the SEC case. Previously, Day worked for 15 years as the former acting deputy assistant attorney general at the Department of Justice&#8217;s Criminal Division, as mentioned in his biography on the Gibson Dunn website.</p>
<p>While at the Department of Justice, Day served as the chief of the Money Laundering and Asset Recovery Section, responsible for overseeing anti-money laundering efforts across the country. This role involved dealing with cases related to money laundering, deferred prosecution agreements, and non-prosecution agreements involving financial institutions, as detailed on the Gibson Dunn website.</p>
<p>Earlier this month, the SEC accused Binance, its CEO <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/changpeng-zhao/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Changpeng Zhao</a>, and another exchange owned by Zhao, Binance.US, of mishandling customer funds, misleading investors and regulators, and violating securities rules. The SEC also requested the return of cryptocurrency owned by US customers.</p>
<p>During his time at the Justice Department, Day held the position of chief of the Money Laundering and Asset Recovery Section. In this role, Day had authority across the country to supervise the department&#8217;s efforts to combat money laundering, including dealing with charges related to money laundering, deferred prosecution agreements, and non-prosecution agreements involving financial institutions. This information can be found on the Gibson Dunn website.</p>
<h2>BinanceUS and the Recent SEC Lawsuit</h2>
<p>Earlier this month, the US Securities and Exchange Commission slapped a lawsuit against Binance.US for allegedly violating the securities laws.</p>
<p>Binance, its CEO Changpeng Zhao (CZ), and affiliated exchange Binance.US are facing charges from the SEC for mishandling customer funds, misleading investors and regulators, and breaking securities rules. The SEC is also requesting the return of cryptocurrency owned by customers in the US.</p>
<p>The exchange has been under investigation by several US agencies, including the Department of Justice. Recently, Binance.US reached an agreement with the SEC that prevents Binance Global officials from accessing customer funds. CZ expressed his relief about the agreement in a tweet on June 17.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tiktok-retail-shop-e-commerce/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-justice-department-prosecutor-sec/">Binance Hires Former Justice Department Prosecutor in Fight with SEC</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>TikTok Moves to Expand Online Retail Shop with New E-Commerce Initiative</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tiktok-retail-shop-e-commerce/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 13:56:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bytedance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tiktok]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=260110</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tiktok-retail-shop-e-commerce/">TikTok Moves to Expand Online Retail Shop with New E-Commerce Initiative</a></p>
<p>The new shopping feature introduced by TikTok is limited to UK users for now.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tiktok-retail-shop-e-commerce/">TikTok Moves to Expand Online Retail Shop with New E-Commerce Initiative</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tiktok-retail-shop-e-commerce/">TikTok Moves to Expand Online Retail Shop with New E-Commerce Initiative</a></p>
<p>TikTok, the popular video-sharing social media platform, is taking a big step into the world of e-commerce with its latest shopping venture. The company has recently introduced a new in-app feature called &#8220;Trendy Beat&#8221;, which serves as a gateway to a world of trending and popular items.</p>
<h2>TikTok Unlocking a New E-Commerce Experience</h2>
<p>The new shopping feature allows users to explore and purchase a wide selection of products featured in viral videos, such as ear wax extraction tools and fashionable apparel. The company has chosen the United Kingdom as the testing ground for its &#8220;Trendy Beat&#8221; shopping feature. The move allows TikTok to gather valuable insights and fine-tune the user experience before a potential global expansion.</p>
<p>While the new e-commerce feature is limited to UK users for now, the company said it is designed to leverage the TikTok influence on consumer behavior to provide users with a seamless and immersive shopping experience within the app.</p>
<p>The company has also recently filed a trademark application for its Trendy Beat in the United States, indicating a potential expansion to the country and promising a broader audience the opportunity to be part of the Trendy Beat shopping experience.</p>
<p>The trademark application covers many apparels, including dresses, scarves, hats, footwear, bathing suits, sleep masks, sweaters, skirts, and shirts.</p>
<h2>TikTok to Ship Items from China</h2>
<p>According to an earlier Financial Times report, all advertised items on Trendy Beat will be shipped and sold by an undisclosed subsidiary of ByteDance, TikTok&#8217;s parent firm. The company <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2023/06/22/tiktok-challenge-amazon-shein-with-new-e-commerce-initiative/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">confirmed</a> the news with TechCrunch on Thursday.</p>
<p>With TikTok&#8217;s deep understanding of product trends and user behavior, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/bytedance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ByteDance</a> aims to leverage its massive user base to sell its products through the platform. The Beijing-based firm plans to acquire or manufacture the items based on trends and user preferences. This ambitious move is internally referred to as &#8220;Project S&#8221;.</p>
<p>The new business initiative challenges traditional retail models and positions TikTok to compete with industry giants like Amazon and Shein. The social media platform aims to establish itself as a dominant player in the e-commerce sector by capitalizing on its user base&#8217;s influence and engagement.</p>
<p>TikTok&#8217;s influence on consumer behavior is unparalleled, and its impact on shopping habits is undeniable. The phrase &#8220;TikTok made me buy it&#8221; has become a cultural phenomenon, showcasing the platform&#8217;s ability to drive impulse purchases and shape consumer preferences.</p>
<p>However, introducing the new shopping feature is set to change the dynamic of its current e-commerce strategy as it plans to sell its own products. The current TikTok Shop marketplace allows other brands to leverage its popularity to sell their products to users within the app.</p>
<p>With billions of views and a massive audience, TikTok&#8217;s integration of the Trendy Beat shopping section aims to amplify its influence further and strengthen its position in the online retailing business.</p>
<h2>TikTok Chief Operating Officer Steps Down</h2>
<p>Meanwhile, TikTok&#8217;s chief operating officer V Pappas has resigned after five years of service. According to the <a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/tiktok-coo-pappas-has-quit-information-2023-06-22/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announcement</a>, the Australian-born COO stepped down to refocus on her entrepreneurial passion.</p>
<p>&#8220;Given all the successes reached at TikTok, I finally feel the time is right to move on and refocus on my entrepreneurial passions,&#8221; said Pappas.</p>
<p>Before her departure, the company&#8217;s CEO, Shou Chew, announced in a letter to employees that Zenia Mucha would join the TikTok team as chief brand and communications officer.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/business-activity-europe-economy/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tiktok-retail-shop-e-commerce/">TikTok Moves to Expand Online Retail Shop with New E-Commerce Initiative</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Business Activity Growth Slows in Europe as Economy Suffers from High Interest Rates</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/business-activity-europe-economy/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 13:48:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mpc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pmi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[s&p global]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sp global market intelligenc]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=260122</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/business-activity-europe-economy/">Business Activity Growth Slows in Europe as Economy Suffers from High Interest Rates</a></p>
<p>There is a recorded plunge in business activity as Europe reels from rising inflation and a consistent increase in interest rates.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/business-activity-europe-economy/">Business Activity Growth Slows in Europe as Economy Suffers from High Interest Rates</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/business-activity-europe-economy/">Business Activity Growth Slows in Europe as Economy Suffers from High Interest Rates</a></p>
<p>Business activity in Europe is waning as the region suffers slow economic growth. Recent data shows that the euro zone’s flash composite Purchasing Managers’ Index (PMI) fell from 52.8 in May, to 50.3 in June. Although analysts had predicted 52.5, any score above 50 represents growth, while scores less than 50 points to shrinkage.</p>
<p>In a conversation with CNBC’s Street Signs Europe, S&amp;P Global Market Intelligence’s chief business economist, Chris Williamson, blamed several “worrying” factors. Williamson says a continuous increase in the cost of living, along with rising interest rates, are all causing the slowdown in growth.</p>
<p>The S&amp;P Global said in a recent release that the current situation points to economic weakness despite a short period of growth recently recorded. The release also highlights the same factors Williamson blames for the slowdown in Europe’s economic and business activity.</p>
<p>“Although energy and supply chain worries have eased since late last year, June has seen a further escalation of concerns over demand growth, and in particular the impact of higher interest rates, and the resulting possibilities of recessions both in domestic markets and further afield,” wrote he.</p>
<p>The flash composite PMI in Germany reflected the general region’s slowdown in growth. The PMI fell from 53.9 in May to 50.8, lower than expected by economists and analysts. In a note to clients, Pantheon Macroeconomics chief eurozone economist Claus Vistesen said Germany’s GDP (gross domestic product) will be “subdued” in Q2 and Q3.</p>
<p>GDP is a metric that measures the total output of a country’s finished products and services in a specific timeframe.</p>
<p>In Q4 2022, Germany’s economy fell by 0.5%, preceding a technical recession in Q1 of 2023 when it plunged by another 0.3%.</p>
<h2>Business Activity May Plunge Further as BoE Raises Interest Rates Again</h2>
<p>The Bank of England (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/bank-of-england/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BoE</a>) has been consistently hiking interest rates to fight inflation. While rising interest rates may tackle inflation, it forces higher expenditure for most companies and households. Recently, the BoE has increased interest rates for the 13th consecutive time, with a 50-basis-point hike. The Monetary Policy Committee voted 7-2 to support the increase, pushing base rates to 5%.</p>
<p>Already, the PMI in France fell from the 51.2 recorded in May, to 47.3 in June.</p>
<p>Consumer prices in May climbed by an annual 8.7% in the UK. This is higher than the 8.4% expected by economists polled by Reuters. According to the Office for National Statistics (ONS), core inflation &#8211; excluding food, energy, alcohol, and tobacco &#8211; climbed an annual 7.1%. The figure is an increase from the 6.8% recorded in April. Interestingly, April’s figure was the highest recorded since March 1992.</p>
<p>In April, UK’s inflation <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-inflation-first-time-august-2022/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">dropped below 10%</a> for the first time since August 2022. Regardless, finance minister Jeremy Hunt said although the drop was welcome, “this battle is far from over”. However, in a Wednesday statement, Hunt <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/06/21/uk-inflation-exceeds-expectations-in-may-piling-pressure-on-the-government-and-bank-of-england.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a> his ministry understands the effects of inflation on businesses and families. The minister added that it will provide support for struggling families, while it also supports the BoE&#8217;s efforts to fight inflation.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-euro-settlement/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/business-activity-europe-economy/">Business Activity Growth Slows in Europe as Economy Suffers from High Interest Rates</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>JPMorgan Introduces Euro-Dominated Transaction Settlement for Corporate Clients</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-euro-settlement/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 13:40:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Currencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jpm coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jpmorgan]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=260127</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-euro-settlement/">JPMorgan Introduces Euro-Dominated Transaction Settlement for Corporate Clients</a></p>
<p>Now, wholesale payment clients including renowned multinationals can choose to transfer either dollar or euro to/from their JPMorgan accounts anywhere in the world. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-euro-settlement/">JPMorgan Introduces Euro-Dominated Transaction Settlement for Corporate Clients</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-euro-settlement/">JPMorgan Introduces Euro-Dominated Transaction Settlement for Corporate Clients</a></p>
<p>American multinational investment bank <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/jpmorgan-chase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">JPMorgan Chase &amp; Co</a> (NYSE: JPM) has introduced euro-dominated payments for its corporate clients as <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-06-23/jpmorgan-jpm-switches-on-jpm-coin-payments-system-in-euros?srnd=all" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">unveiled</a> by Basak Toprak, JPMorgan’s head of Coin Systems for Europe, the Middle East and Africa. This was delivered as part of the investment giant&#8217;s plan to expand one of the most high-profile projects to bring blockchain technology to <a href="https://www.jpmorgan.com/payments/payments-and-cross-currency-solutions" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">traditional banking</a> through JPM Coin.</p>
<p>Four years ago, JPMorgan <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpm-coin-jp-morgan-worlds-first-cryptocurrency-by-bank/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">launched</a> the world’s first bank-backed cryptocurrency dubbed JPM Coin which runs on top of Quorum. It was used as an instant settlement for transactions between the clients of the JPMorgan wholesale payments business. At the time, the token had three major use cases amongst which were cutting down on settlement times while replacing the wire transfers for global payments, and securities issuance.</p>
<p>Umar Farooq, head of JPMorgan’s blockchain projects said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Money sloshes back and forth all over the world in a large enterprise. Is there a way to ensure that a subsidiary can represent cash on the balance sheet without having to actually wire it to the unit? That way, they can consolidate their money and probably get better rates for it.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>JPMorgan on Track with JPM Coin Roadmap with Its Euro Settlements</h2>
<p>A few months after the introduction of the JPM Coin, the investment manager began to <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-trials-jpm-coin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">initiate</a> trials of the token with its corporate clients. The coin was only linked to the United States dollar at that initial stage but Farooq hinted at plans to expand its offering in the near future to accommodate other fiat currencies. With the introduction of euro transactions, JPMorgan is on the road to actualizing that vision.</p>
<p>Now, wholesale payment clients including renowned multinationals can choose to transfer either dollar or euro to/from their JPMorgan accounts anywhere in the world.</p>
<p>Payments could also be made to other customers of the bank by utilizing blockchain instead of conventional traditional banking methods. Markedly, JPM Coin transactions are not limited to certain working hours like traditional banking processes, rather it is constantly in operation and are faster.</p>
<p>Toprak, who announced the development, also mentioned that Siemens AG in Germany conducted the first euro payment on the platform. This is a major milestone for JPMorgan as many large banking firms have constantly explored blockchain, seeking answers to how the technology will make their processes easier but so far, only a few applications have been put to <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-tests-jpm-onyx/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">commercial use</a> and large-scale benefits have proved elusive.</p>
<p>This outcome has caused many to wonder if blockchain technology is a solution that is seeking a problem. Since the launch of JPM Coin, the investment bank has used it to process transactions worth over $300 billion. Generally, as a banking giant, JPMorgan processes about $10 trillion worth of transactions on a daily basis.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sap-payments-circle-usdc/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-euro-settlement/">JPMorgan Introduces Euro-Dominated Transaction Settlement for Corporate Clients</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>SAP Clients Testing Cross-Border Payments with Circle’s USDC</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sap-payments-circle-usdc/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 12:28:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[circle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sap]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[usd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[usdc]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=260090</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sap-payments-circle-usdc/">SAP Clients Testing Cross-Border Payments with Circle&#8217;s USDC</a></p>
<p>Customers will receive a designated amount of USDC along with an invoice, enabling them to experience the benefits of fast, affordable, and reliable cross-border payments.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sap-payments-circle-usdc/">SAP Clients Testing Cross-Border Payments with Circle&#8217;s USDC</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sap-payments-circle-usdc/">SAP Clients Testing Cross-Border Payments with Circle&#8217;s USDC</a></p>
<p>In a significant move towards revolutionizing cross-border payments, German software giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sap/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SAP SE</a> (ETR: SAP) has made an exciting announcement in this sphere. In a <a href="https://blogs.sap.com/2023/06/15/cross-border-payments-made-easy-with-digital-money-experience-the-future-today/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">blog post</a>, the company revealed its collaboration with <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/circle/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Circle</a>, a leading digital currency firm, to test the use of its stablecoin, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/usd-coin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">USD Coin</a> (USDC) as a means of facilitating international transactions.</p>
<p>For businesses engaged in international trade, cross-border payments have long been plagued by a range of issues. Cumbersome procedures, high fees, delays, and currency conversion complexities have created significant challenges that hinder smooth financial transactions. SAP, being a leader in enterprise software solutions, recognizes the importance of addressing these issues and is actively working towards finding innovative solutions.</p>
<p>In a bid to empower its clients and facilitate seamless cross-border payments, SAP has introduced a unique approach. The company is leveraging a “play money” version of Circle&#8217;s USDC, allowing clients to test the efficacy of sending money overseas.</p>
<p>As revealed by the company, customers can now receive USDC, which runs on Ethereum, as “play money” to test out the payment option. The test will take place on a different blockchain, not Ethereum, and will not use genuine ERC-20 USDC tokens.</p>
<p>By offering this test phase, SAP aims to gauge customer interest and gather valuable feedback on the usability and functionality of receiving USDC as a payment method. This experimental approach provides clients with a risk-free environment to explore the potential benefits and challenges associated with Ethereum-based cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>If SAP clients show interest in adopting USDC, it could potentially result in a significant surge in crypto adoption within the Ethereum ecosystem. Notably, SAP&#8217;s broad customer base, which includes many major corporations, holds the potential to drive substantial traction for digital currencies on the Ethereum platform.</p>
<p>It is important to note that the experiment will not allow customers to use USDC for making actual payments. Instead, customers will receive a designated amount of USDC along with an invoice, enabling them to experience the benefits of fast, affordable, and reliable cross-border payments.</p>
<h2>Why Is USDC a Suitable Option for SAP?</h2>
<p>USDC&#8217;s impressive market position as the fifth largest digital asset, with a substantial market capitalization of $28.4 billion, underscores its significance and widespread adoption within the cryptocurrency market. The high trading volume of over $4 billion in USDC within 24 hours, as per by <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/usd-coin" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">CoinGecko</a>, further exemplifies its liquidity and active market participation.</p>
<p>Notably, USDC&#8217;s popularity can be ascribed to several characteristics, including trust and stability, widespread acceptance, and use case variety. As a stablecoin pegged to the US dollar, USDC provides users with a reliable digital currency option.</p>
<p>This stability reduces the volatility associated with other cryptocurrencies and enhances trust among investors and market participants. Also, its widespread availability makes it easily accessible to users looking for a stable and reliable digital asset.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/k5-global-ftx-700m/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sap-payments-circle-usdc/">SAP Clients Testing Cross-Border Payments with Circle&#8217;s USDC</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>K5 Global Sued to Court by FTX, May Pay $700 Million</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/k5-global-ftx-700m/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 12:14:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alameda research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bryan baum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx sam bankman-fried]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[k5]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[k5 global]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[michael kives]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sam bankman-fried]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sbf]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=260070</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/k5-global-ftx-700m/">K5 Global Sued to Court by FTX, May Pay $700 Million</a></p>
<p>The suit was filed at the United States Bankruptcy Court for the District of Delaware.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/k5-global-ftx-700m/">K5 Global Sued to Court by FTX, May Pay $700 Million</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/k5-global-ftx-700m/">K5 Global Sued to Court by FTX, May Pay $700 Million</a></p>
<p>Bankrupt FTX exchange has filed a lawsuit against K5 Global – an investment firm owned by a former aide to Hillary Clinton. According to a Reuters <a href="https://www.reuters.com/legal/ftx-sues-ex-clinton-aides-investment-firm-700-million-2023-06-22/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a>, the suit was filed at the United States Bankruptcy Court for the District of Delaware. It contains 16 counts against the defendants and seeks to recover about $700 million from them.</p>
<p>According to the filing, the defendants include K5 Global, Mount Olympus Capital, SGN Albany Capital, their affiliates, and K5 Global co-founders Michael Kives and Bryan Baum. The filing also revealed how the then-CEO of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a> Sam Bankman-Fried (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/sam-bankman-fried/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SBF</a>) misappropriated company funds for personal gains.</p>
<h2>FTX Says Deal with K5 Global Was &#8216;Avoidable&#8217;</h2>
<p>FTX alleges that its investment arm Alameda Research transferred no less than $700 million to Kives, Baum, and K5 Global. The complaint also added that the transfers were done as though they had any business with shell companies SGN Albany and Mount Olympus Capital.</p>
<p>However, the suit points out that the transfers were carried out &#8220;without receiving equivalent value&#8221; thus, making them avoidable. And as it is, the US bankruptcy law allows an avoidable transaction to be reversed under the Bankruptcy Code.</p>
<p>Nine out of the 16 counts in the suit were about fund transfers. But Kives and Buam got personal charges for aiding and abetting breach of fiduciary duty and dishonest assistance. SGN Albany Capital, on the other hand, was charged with unjust enrichment.</p>
<h2>Lawsuit Lacks Merit, K5 Responds</h2>
<p>K5 Global has dispelled the allegations and has responded to the lawsuit. According to a company spokesperson, the entire suit lacks merit and should not even be made to look important.</p>
<p>The spokesperson cites how K5 is a Venture Capital firm with over $1 billion in assets under management (AUM). That is excluding any funds linked to SBF or affiliates. K5 also has investments in 148 companies, he said.</p>
<p>However, he also acknowledged that FTX&#8217;s Alameda truly bought a third of K5’s general partnership for cash and stock in mid-2022. That, and that SBF and his company eventually made a $400 million investment in certain funds managed by K5. Nonetheless, the spokesperson said that &#8220;K5 was under the impression – like many others – that SBF was completely legitimate and they were entering into a fair, long-term, and mutually beneficial business relationship&#8221;.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/100000-chatgpt-credentials-leaked/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/k5-global-ftx-700m/">K5 Global Sued to Court by FTX, May Pay $700 Million</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4002 metric#misses=41 metric#hit-ratio=99.0 metric#bytes=1088454 metric#prefetches=208 metric#store-reads=19 metric#store-writes=2 metric#store-hits=214 metric#store-misses=2 metric#sql-queries=34 metric#ms-total=100.15 metric#ms-cache=4.80 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.2399 metric#ms-cache-ratio=4.8 -->