<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 04:12:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Fed rate hikes to peak as inflation cools: Implications for Chancer</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/fed-rate-hikes-to-peak-as-inflation-cools-implications-for-chancer/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/fed-rate-hikes-to-peak-as-inflation-cools-implications-for-chancer/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 04:12:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/fed-rate-hikes-to-peak-as-inflation-cools-implications-for-chancer/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The US published weak jobs and inflation data this month. The Fed could now hike rates less times than expected. A dovish tone could be a good thing for Chancer and other cryptocurrencies. American stocks jumped to a multi-month high while the US dollar index slipped to the lowest level since April 2022 on Thursday. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/fed-rate-hikes-to-peak-as-inflation-cools-implications-for-chancer/">Fed rate hikes to peak as inflation cools: Implications for Chancer</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The US published weak jobs and inflation data this month.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The Fed could now hike rates less times than expected.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">A dovish tone could be a good thing for Chancer and other cryptocurrencies.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">American stocks jumped to a multi-month high while the US dollar index slipped to the lowest level since April 2022 on Thursday. Similarly, US bond yields and the CBOE VIX index turned red after the US published encouraging inflation data. These numbers, coupled with last week&rsquo;s soft jobs data, could have an impact on cryptocurrencies, including&nbsp;<a href="https://chancer.com/"><u>Chancer</u></a><strong>.</strong></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">US inflation and jobs data</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The US published mixed jobs numbers last week. A report by ADP showed that the American economy added over 400k jobs in June, the highest figure in years. A separate report by the statistics bureau revealed that the country&rsquo;s economy added over 209k jobs during the month. &nbsp;The official report was relatively soft than expected.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The US then published soft consumer inflation data on Wednesday. According to the Bureau of Labor Statistics, the headline consumer price index (CPI) dropped from 4% in May to 3.0% in June. Core inflation also continued falling during the month.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, inflation is moving near the 2%<a href="https://www.ft.com/content/c86136db-17be-487d-aa8f-642b4b81aa1f"><u>&nbsp;target&nbsp;</u></a>rate and this trend could happen faster than expected. For one, global shopping costs have plummeted while China has moved close to deflation. China is a big exporter to the United States.</p>
<p dir="ltr">These numbers will have an impact on all financial assets because of their impact to the Federal Reserve. Most economists now believe that the Fed will deliver another 0.25% rate hike this month and then pause indefinitely. In a note, an analyst at Point72&nbsp;<a href="https://www.ft.com/content/c86136db-17be-487d-aa8f-642b4b81aa1f"><u>said</u></a>:</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;What we&rsquo;re seeing is consistent with the market scaling back tightening expectations for after the July meeting, but it doesn&rsquo;t seem that it should be pricing in scope for rate cuts this year.</p>
<p dir="ltr">A change of tune by the Fed will be a good thing for assets like stocks and cryptocurrencies.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Chancer token sale continues</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Another big&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/"><u>crypto news</u></a><strong>&nbsp;</strong>of the week is that Chancer developers introduced more ways to buy the token. In addition to BUSD, the developers added Ethereum, Tether (USDT), and Binance Coin as options to buy the token. This is an important move because it gives users diverse ways to invest in the token.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">&#128640;&#128142; The moment you've been waiting for is here! &#127775;&#128184; </p>
<p>You can now purchase $CHANCER using <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24ETH&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$ETH</a>, opening up a whole new world of possibilities! &#128165;&#128293;</p>
<p>Get in on the action, secure your tokens, and ride the wave to incredible profits! &#127760;&#128176;</p>
<p>&#129297;BUY HERE: <a href="https://t.co/iHffMmdhCk">https://t.co/iHffMmdhCk</a> <a href="https://t.co/ppSxsDQfrQ">pic.twitter.com/ppSxsDQfrQ</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Chancer.com (@ChancerProject) <a href="https://twitter.com/ChancerProject/status/1679175154474139659?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 12, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer&rsquo;s token presale is going on well. For one, thousands of people have already bought the token, bringing the total amount raised to over $748k. The total amount of Chancer token sold stands at over 74 million.</p>
<p dir="ltr">For starters, Chancer is a platform that seeks to disrupt the sports betting and prediction market using the blockchain technology. It is a global platform that will make it possible for people to bet on international sports using cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p dir="ltr">At the same time, Chancer will enable any member to create their own markets and livestream them using the platform&rsquo;s tools. For example, a user can create a market of a local game and then let a global audience bet on it. The user will take a cut of all the amounts placed in that market.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer is now selling tokens as the developers prepare to launch the testnet in the coming months. You can buy the $CHANCER token&nbsp;<a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news"><u>here</u></a>. Also, you should read the Chancer&nbsp;<a href="https://chancer.com/whitepaper.pdf"><u>white paper</u></a> to know more about the project, Most importantly, we recommend that you excise caution when investing in Chancer and other token presales.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/fed-rate-hikes-to-peak-as-inflation-cools-implications-for-chancer/">Fed rate hikes to peak as inflation cools: Implications for Chancer</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/fed-rate-hikes-to-peak-as-inflation-cools-implications-for-chancer/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kava 14 Accelerates Cosmos Ecosystem Expansion</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/kava-14-accelerates-cosmos-ecosystem-expansion/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/kava-14-accelerates-cosmos-ecosystem-expansion/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire &#160;]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 19:45:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=145878</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Georgetown, Cayman Islands, July 12th, 2023, Chainwire Kava, a Layer-1 blockchain that combines the developer power of Ethereum with the speed and interoperability of Cosmos has launched the Kava 14 upgrade. This upgrade deploys &#8216;internal bridge&#8217; technology to seamlessly convert native Cosmos assets to and from Ethereum&#8217;s ERC20 token standard. Kava 14 is one of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/kava-14-accelerates-cosmos-ecosystem-expansion/">Kava 14 Accelerates Cosmos Ecosystem Expansion</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Georgetown, Cayman Islands, July 12th, 2023, Chainwire</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://www.kava.io/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Kava</a>, a Layer-1 blockchain that combines the developer power of Ethereum with the speed and interoperability of Cosmos has launched the Kava 14 upgrade. This upgrade deploys &lsquo;internal bridge&rsquo; technology to seamlessly convert native Cosmos assets to and from Ethereum&rsquo;s ERC20 token standard.</p>
<p>Kava 14 is one of a cluster of milestones in the making. In early July, Tether announced it&rsquo;s decision to make Kava the gateway for issuing native USDt on Cosmos. With the launch of Kava 14, USDt can now be minted and easily converted on Cosmos, to &mdash; and from &mdash; USDt on every other L1 with native USDt including the: Bitcoin (Omni &amp; Liquid protocol), Ethereum, TRON networks, and more.</p>
<blockquote><p>&ldquo;Within the first few days of Kava launching the official Tether integration, more USDt has been issued on Cosmos than on Polkadot and Near combined,&rdquo; said Scott Stuart, Kava Co-Founder. &ldquo;It&rsquo;s clear that people want USDt on the interchain. I&rsquo;m optimistic that having a native stablecoin and a safe, reliable way to convert it across chains via the Kava 14 upgrade will finally unlock the incredible tech the Cosmos ecosystem has built.&rdquo;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Kava Gains Momentum</h2>
<p>Following Tether&rsquo;s July announcement, Kucoin now supports Kava&rsquo;s Cosmos and EVM networks, providing a reliable CEX for user transactions within the Cosmos ecosystem. Meanwhile, Curve Finance&rsquo;s launch of a USDt liquidity pool offers a decentralized alternative for experienced users. In parallel, Stargate, a top omnichain liquidity layer, is set to launch on Kava, anticipating increased usage and liquidity. This expansion comes after a governance proposal that plans to widen the scope of the Kava Rise incentive fund.</p>
<p>The Kava 14 upgrade is a leap forward for Cosmos&nbsp;DeFi builders and users providing a safer, more secure, and more reliable method for converting assets to and from the Cosmos ecosystem.</p>
<p>Follow <a href="https://twitter.com/KAVA_CHAIN" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">@KAVA_CHAIN</a> on Twitter for more information and updates on Kava 14&rsquo;s mainnet launch.</p>
<h3>About Kava</h3>
<p><a href="https://www.kava.io/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Kava</a> is a secure, lightning-fast Layer-1 blockchain that combines the developer power of Ethereum with the speed and interoperability of Cosmos in a single, scalable network. Committed to fostering innovation and growth, Kava is a trusted choice for developers and users worldwide.</p>
<p>For more updates, follow Kava on <a href="https://twitter.com/KAVA_CHAIN" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Twitter</a>.</p>
<p><strong>Disclaimer</strong></p>
<p><em>This press release is not an offer to sell or the solicitation of an offer to buy USDt or KAVA tokens.</em></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Contact</strong></p>
<p>Media Manager<br>
Guillermo Carandini<br>
Kava<br>
guillermo.carandini@kava.io</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/kava-14-accelerates-cosmos-ecosystem-expansion/">Kava 14 Accelerates Cosmos Ecosystem Expansion</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/kava-14-accelerates-cosmos-ecosystem-expansion/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Conflux (CFX) soaring after Bank of China announced SIM Card NFC payments</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/conflux-cfx-soaring-after-bank-of-china-announced-sim-card-nfc-payments/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/conflux-cfx-soaring-after-bank-of-china-announced-sim-card-nfc-payments/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 18:07:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[China]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/conflux-cfx-soaring-after-bank-of-china-announced-sim-card-nfc-payments/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>At press time, Conflux (CFX) token was trading at $0.1981, up 10% in the last 24 hours. Conflux Network partnered with China Telecom to develop a Blockchain-powered SIM card (BSIM) in May 2023. The Bank of China will start testing of SIM card-linked payments using the digital yuan. The Bank of China declared on July [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/conflux-cfx-soaring-after-bank-of-china-announced-sim-card-nfc-payments/">Conflux (CFX) soaring after Bank of China announced SIM Card NFC payments</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>At press time, Conflux (CFX) token was trading at $0.1981, up 10% in the last 24 hours.</li>
<li>Conflux Network partnered with China Telecom to develop a Blockchain-powered SIM card (BSIM) in May 2023.</li>
<li>The Bank of China will start testing of SIM card-linked payments using the digital yuan.</li>
</ul>
<p>The Bank of China declared on July 10 that it would begin testing SIM card-linked payments using the digital Yuan on July 11. The announcement has boosted <a href="https://coinjournal.net/conflux/">Conflux (CFX) price</a> seeing that <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/china-telecom-and-conflux-network-to-pilot-blockchain-enabled-sim-card-in-hong-kong/">Conflux Network partnered with China Telecom</a> to develop a Blockchain-powered SIM card (BSIM). In May 2023, the two <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/conflux-and-china-telecom-debut-first-on-chain-interaction-with-blockchain-sim-card/">unveiled their jointly developed BSIM card</a> at the Xuhui District West Bank Artificial Intelligence Center in Shanghai.</p>
<p>The state-owned bank asserted in its statement that it is implementing this programme in conjunction with telecom behemoths China Telecom and China Unicom. With the help of the near-field communication protocol (NFC) and &ldquo;super SIM cards&rdquo; technology, the project aims to make payments possible.</p>
<p>Users will essentially be able to process digital Yuan payments by making contact with designated payment terminals with their mobile phones.</p>
<h2>Excitement among the Conflux community</h2>
<p>The CFX community now believe the Conflux Network will have a big impact on the new SIM Card e-CNY payment system. This enthusiasm resulted in a rise in price, which increased by 10% this morning to reach a high of $0.2046.</p>
<p>Prior to the announcement, the CFX token was experiencing a seven-day price decline that saw it slip from $0.197 to $0.175.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/conflux-cfx-soaring-after-bank-of-china-announced-sim-card-nfc-payments/">Conflux (CFX) soaring after Bank of China announced SIM Card NFC payments</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/conflux-cfx-soaring-after-bank-of-china-announced-sim-card-nfc-payments/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase stock could see a near-term pullback – analyst says</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-stock-downgraded-at-atlantic-equities/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wajeeh Khan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 17:49:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=145866</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Atlantic Equities downgraded Coinbase stock to &#8220;neutral&#8221; on Wednesday. Cathie Wood also trimmed her stake in the crypto exchange today. Coinbase stock is currently up more than 150% versus the start of 2023. Investors should pull out of Coinbase Global Inc now that it&#8217;s rallied more than 150% since the start of this year, says [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-stock-downgraded-at-atlantic-equities/">Coinbase stock could see a near-term pullback – analyst says</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Atlantic Equities downgraded Coinbase stock to &ldquo;neutral&rdquo; on Wednesday.</li>
<li>Cathie Wood also trimmed her stake in the crypto exchange today.</li>
<li>Coinbase stock is currently up more than 150% versus the start of 2023.</li>
</ul>
<p>Investors should pull out of <a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/coinbase/">Coinbase Global Inc</a> now that it&rsquo;s rallied more than 150% since the start of this year, says Simon Clinch &ndash; an Atlantic Equities analyst.</p>
<h2>Coinbase stock has downside to $80</h2>
<p>On Wednesday, Clinch downgraded the crypto exchange to &ldquo;neutral&rdquo;. His $80 price target warns of a 10% downside from its previous close.</p>
<p>In his research note, the analyst cited valuation and ongoing regulatory scrutiny as reasons for turning dovish on Coinbase stock.</p>
<blockquote><p>The risk/reward looks less attractive at this level given continued regulatory challenges ahead and the surprisingly weak volume backdrop.</p></blockquote>
<p>The Securities and Exchange Commission sued Coinbase Global Inc last month for violating the U.S. securities laws. The Nasdaq-listed firm also added an <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-adds-instant-messaging-feature-to-wallet/">instant messaging</a> feature to its wallet on Wednesday.</p>
<h2>Cathie Wood trims her stake in Coinbase</h2>
<p>Clinch recommends moving to the sidelines in Coinbase stock also because the USDC market cap has declined which will affect the company&rsquo;s interest income.</p>
<blockquote><p>With these factors in mind, we&rsquo;re concerned the outlook for rest of FY23 may have deteriorated incrementally despite strength in crypto asset prices over the past month.</p></blockquote>
<p>Coinbase Global Inc is expected to lose 84 cents a share in its current financial quarter versus $4.95 per share a year ago.</p>
<p>Also on Wednesday, famed investor <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cryptocurrency/23/07/33193286/cathie-woods-ark-offloads-12m-worth-of-bitcoin-linked-stock-amid-10-rally-on-cboe-tie-up" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Cathie Wood</a> trimmed her stake in the crypto exchange. Her flagship Ark Innovation ETF sold 135,152 shares of Coinbase for roughly $12 million.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-stock-downgraded-at-atlantic-equities/">Coinbase stock could see a near-term pullback – analyst says</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase adds instant messaging feature to wallet</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-adds-instant-messaging-feature-to-wallet/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-adds-instant-messaging-feature-to-wallet/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 17:42:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wallets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-adds-instant-messaging-feature-to-wallet/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Coinbase Wallet now supports instant messaging across any two Ethereum addresses. The feature will leverage the XMTP protocol and offer encrypted and private wallet-to-wallet communication and crypto payments. Coinbase is rolling out the feature to a small subset of users first before expanding it. Coinbase has introduced a new feature that allows for instant messaging [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-adds-instant-messaging-feature-to-wallet/">Coinbase adds instant messaging feature to wallet</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Coinbase Wallet now supports instant messaging across any two Ethereum addresses.</li>
<li>The feature will leverage the XMTP protocol and offer encrypted and private wallet-to-wallet communication and crypto payments.</li>
<li>Coinbase is rolling out the feature to a small subset of users first before expanding it.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/coinbase/">Coinbase</a> has introduced a new feature that allows for instant messaging between two wallet addresses for users of Coinbase Wallet.</p>
<p dir="ltr">A <a href="https://www.coinbase.com/blog" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">blog post</a> the company published on July 12 stated that the messaging capability will utilise a built-in system powered by Extensible Message Transport Protocol (XMTP). With this feature users can now tap into all-in-one messaging and payments, which includes gas-free USDC transfers on Polygon.</p>
<p dir="ltr">To send any of the crypto assets that Coinbase Wallet supports, users will simply need to start a chat.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Encrypted and private messaging</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The wallet-to-wallet messaging will be fully encrypted, private and portable, Sid Coelho-Prabhu, Director of Product Management at Coinbase, wrote.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Wallet-to-wallet messaging is here. <a href="https://t.co/vfM8RCdy65">pic.twitter.com/vfM8RCdy65</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Coinbase Wallet &#128737;&#65039; (@CoinbaseWallet) <a href="https://twitter.com/CoinbaseWallet/status/1679178581224873985?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 12, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">Users can connect directly through their <a href="https://coinjournal.net/wallets/">wallets</a>, and will be able to take conversations and chat histories across other XMTP compatible apps. Coinbase Wallet is rolling out the messaging feature to a small group of users first, including those of Web3 social platform Lens protocol.</p>
<p dir="ltr">One needs access to the Coinbase Wallet mobile app to get started. They also need a .lens account, or should have an invitation sent via QR code. If one has used other XMTP apps, including Orb and Lenster, they will find all their chats in their Coinbase Wallet inbox.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-adds-instant-messaging-feature-to-wallet/">Coinbase adds instant messaging feature to wallet</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-adds-instant-messaging-feature-to-wallet/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chancer prediction as stage one presale tops $700k</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-prediction-as-stage-one-presale-tops-700k/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-prediction-as-stage-one-presale-tops-700k/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 17:06:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Events]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-prediction-as-stage-one-presale-tops-700k/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways Bitcoin has been trading around the $30k region for the last two weeks. Chancer&#8217;s first presale stage is more than 70% completed as more investors enter the project.&#160; The cryptocurrency market has been stable over the past few days, with the prices of most coins and tokens within a particular range. Will Bitcoin [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-prediction-as-stage-one-presale-tops-700k/">Chancer prediction as stage one presale tops $700k</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin has been trading around the $30k region for the last two weeks.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Chancer&rsquo;s first presale stage is more than 70% completed as more investors enter the project.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">The cryptocurrency market has been stable over the past few days, with the prices of most coins and tokens within a particular range. Will Bitcoin and the broader market rally higher in the near term, or would the market face a retrace?</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitcoin maintains its price above $30k</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin, the world&rsquo;s leading cryptocurrency by market cap, continues to trade just above the $30k mark. BTC has been trading around that range for the past three weeks.</p>
<p dir="ltr">At press time, the&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>price of Bitcoin</u></a> stands at $30,468, down by less than 1% in the last 24 hours.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The performance comes after the consumer price index rose 0.2% in June and was up 3% from a year ago. The data indicated that inflation in the United States rose 0.2% last month, less than expected as consumers get a break from price increases.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Chancer?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Despite the price pullback earlier today, the cryptocurrency market has performed excellently so far this year. Bitcoin is up by nearly 50% year-to-date, outperforming the other major asset classes in the world.</p>
<p dir="ltr">With the market in a positive mood, investors could be looking to get in on new projects. One of the projects to consider could be Chancer.&nbsp;<a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Chancer</u></a> is a unique Web3 peer-to-peer (P2P) custom betting platform designed to enable users to live stream betting events.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer seeks to differentiate itself from other betting platforms by adopting a decentralised method of operations. On Chancer, users can bet on a wide range of events, beyond traditional sports and casino bets.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">At the moment, the project is still in its stage one presale, with an aim of raising $1 million. Chancer developers will use the funds to build a P2P betting platform.</p>
<p dir="ltr">On Chancer, players would enjoy excellent features such as betting markets in real-time and based on user interests, social media connections, and expertise.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">With Chancer, users might no longer face the challenges associated with using bookmakers. The platform would allow users to set up their custom P2P betting markets.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Perhaps the biggest selling point of Chancer is that users can bet on a wide range of things, beyond the sporting and casino bets found on traditional betting platforms.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">While the sport and casino bets would be available, Chancer users can et on any event they desire, whether mainstream or made-up. It doesn&rsquo;t matter the event, users can bet on them on the platform</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Chancer&rsquo;s presale is over 70% completed</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer&rsquo;s stage one presale could be completed soon as the team has raised more than 70% of the required funds. At the moment,&nbsp;<a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Chancer</u></a> has raised more than $700k, accounting for more than 70% of the required funds in stage one.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The development team has earmarked the funds to develop its suite of products. The team intends to carry out 12 presale events, with a target of $15 million.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Chancer ecosystem would be powered by CHANCER, its native token. CHANCER is going for $0.01 BUSD per token, but its price could increase once the token launches on cryptocurrency exchanges.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">CHANCER would power the various activities on the betting platforms. Token holders would be allowed to create markets and invest in markets created by other users.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Furthermore, by holding CHANCER, users can create, participate in, and profit from their very own predictive markets.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The presale is open to everyone, and Chancer supports a wide range of wallets, including, Trust Wallet, MetaMask, Coinbase Wallet, and Rainbow.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Visit the Chancer website</u></a> to get more information about the presale.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Should you invest in Chancer today?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The cryptocurrency market has been stagnant over the past week, with prices of Bitcoin and other major coins and tokens ranging within specific prices. However, Bitcoin is up by nearly 50% year-to-date.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">As more retail and institutional investors enter the market, Bitcoin&rsquo;s value could increase in the medium to long term.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Investors would be looking at new projects with strong fundamentals, and&nbsp;<a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Chancer</u></a> could be one of the tokens to consider.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">As a decentralised betting platform, Chancer could gain huge adoption in the Web3 ecosystem and beyond. Chancer is still in its presale stage and could provide huge value for investors in the long term.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-prediction-as-stage-one-presale-tops-700k/">Chancer prediction as stage one presale tops $700k</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-prediction-as-stage-one-presale-tops-700k/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>LBRY Credits Token plummets after federal court ruled against LBRY Inc.</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/lbry-credits-token-plummets-after-federal-court-ruled-against-lbry-inc/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 16:42:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Security Tokens]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/lbry-credits-token-plummets-after-federal-court-ruled-against-lbry-inc/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>At press time, LBRY Token had plunged to $0.009298 from a high of $0.01235 on July 11. The plunge followed a ruling that LBRY Inc. violated US securities laws. LBRY Inc. has stated that it is shutting down its business. The LBRY Credits (LBC) fell by 24% early today as a result of a Federal [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/lbry-credits-token-plummets-after-federal-court-ruled-against-lbry-inc/">LBRY Credits Token plummets after federal court ruled against LBRY Inc.</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>At press time, LBRY Token had plunged to $0.009298 from a high of $0.01235 on July 11.</li>
<li>The plunge followed a ruling that LBRY Inc. violated US securities laws.</li>
<li>LBRY Inc. has stated that it is shutting down its business.</li>
</ul>
<p>The LBRY Credits (LBC) fell by 24% early today as a result of a Federal Judge&rsquo;s ruling that LBRY, Inc, the company that created the LBRY protocol, is responsible for breaking US securities laws. . LBRY was <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sec-sues-crypto-startup-lbry-over-unregistered-securities/">sued by the SEC in March 2021</a> for offering unregistered securities.</p>
<p>Following the final judgment, the company is permanently prohibited from selling unregistered securities unless it first registers with the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). LBRY, Inc also has thirty days to pay a fine of $111,614.</p>
<h2>Winding LBRY Inc. down</h2>
<p>After the ruling, the decentralized content-sharing project LBRY Inc. was quick to announce its next steps stating that it working on winding down completely.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">The final judgement in SEC vs LBRY is out.</p>
<p>In accordance with the court's order and our promises, we expect to spend the next several months winding LBRY Inc. down entirely.</p>
<p>As to what happens to LBRY from here, well, that's up to you. <a href="https://t.co/cU8O3nATT6">pic.twitter.com/cU8O3nATT6</a></p>
<p>&mdash; LBRY &#128640; (@LBRYcom) <a href="https://twitter.com/LBRYcom/status/1678866789407551489?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 11, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>It&rsquo;s crucial to note that the SEC never requested a total shutdown of the project, at least not in their initial complaint, despite the project&rsquo;s announcement that it is closing. On the contrary, the regulator sought to prevent unregistered securities offerings of any kind and the return of &ldquo;ill-gotten&rdquo; profits from those activities, and civil penalties.</p>
<p>The SEC cited explicit statements on LBRY&rsquo;s website that it was selling LBRY Credits (LBC) tokens to &ldquo;financially support its operations&rdquo; both through their protocol and on secondary markets, which refer to the buying and selling of tokens on platforms that aren&rsquo;t the cryptocurrency&rsquo;s original issuers. These statements were made during the litigation process.</p>
<h2>Last year&rsquo;s ruling against LBRY</h2>
<p>In November last year, Judge Paul J. Barbadoro of the U.S. District Court of New Hampshire ruled against LBRY Inc. ruling that the project could not provide &ldquo;any reasonable trier of fact that could reject the SEC&rsquo;s claims.&rdquo; As a result, LBRY Inc. declared they lost.</p>
<p>However, <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/lbry-credits-lbc-shoots-up-by-90-after-being-declared-not-a-security/">LBRY Inc. filed and won an appea</a>l focusing on whether the secondary market sales of the LBC tokens should be included in an injunction the US SEC is seeking the court to approve.&nbsp;</p>
<p>After yesterday&rsquo;s ruling, the company&rsquo;s CEO, Jeremy Kauffman, tweeted that &ldquo;neither the SEC nor the federal judge himself can tell me what the law allows and doesn&rsquo;t allow,&rdquo; adding that &ldquo;all I&rsquo;ve ever wanted to do is follow the law.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/lbry-credits-token-plummets-after-federal-court-ruled-against-lbry-inc/">LBRY Credits Token plummets after federal court ruled against LBRY Inc.</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Struct Finance Transforms DeFi Landscape on Avalanche With the Launch of Tranche-based BTC.B-USDC Vaults</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/struct-finance-transforms-defi-landscape-on-avalanche-with-the-launch-of-tranche-based-btc-b-usdc-vaults/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/struct-finance-transforms-defi-landscape-on-avalanche-with-the-launch-of-tranche-based-btc-b-usdc-vaults/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire &#160;]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 15:47:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=145848</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Tortola, British Virgin Islands, July 12th, 2023, Chainwire In its ongoing journey to reshape the crypto investing landscape, Struct Finance, a DeFi platform that enables investors to engage with tailored interest rate products linked to digital assets, is thrilled to announce the launch of the BTC.B-USDC Vaults. The tranche-based BTC.B-USDC Interest Rate Product was made [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/struct-finance-transforms-defi-landscape-on-avalanche-with-the-launch-of-tranche-based-btc-b-usdc-vaults/">Struct Finance Transforms DeFi Landscape on Avalanche With the Launch of Tranche-based BTC.B-USDC Vaults</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Tortola, British Virgin Islands, July 12th, 2023, Chainwire</strong></p>
<p>In its ongoing journey to reshape the crypto investing landscape, Struct Finance, a DeFi platform that enables investors to engage with tailored interest rate products linked to digital assets, is thrilled to announce the launch of the BTC.B-USDC Vaults.</p>
<p>The tranche-based BTC.B-USDC Interest Rate Product was made possible by effectively leveraging Avalanche&rsquo;s BTC.B (Bridged Bitcoin) for DeFi applications. The new vault beautifully complements Struct Finance&rsquo;s Genesis USDC Vaults, heralding an exciting era in DeFi yield opportunities. Struct Finance built the new vault on top of GMX&rsquo;s Liquidity Provider Token (GLP) to generate predictable yields for BTC in the form of fixed returns, and USDC in the form of variable returns, while still leveraging a secure asset and minimizing volatility and exposure to other risks.</p>
<blockquote><p>&ldquo;Our BTC.B-USDC Vaults represent an innovative application of Bitcoin in DeFi. We&rsquo;re taking full advantage of Avalanche&rsquo;s Bridged Bitcoin (BTC.B) to bring about a fresh wave of opportunities in the digital asset space,&rdquo; said Ersin Dalkali, the Co-founder of Struct Finance.</p></blockquote>
<p>While Bitcoin continues to dominate the market, its inherent lack of a DeFi layer has traditionally made native yield generation quite challenging. Avalanche has unlocked new possibilities for Bitcoin in DeFi with BTC.B (Bridged Bitcoin). Unlike WBTC that relied on centralized bridges, BTC.B is minted via Avalanche Core &mdash; a decentralized bridge &mdash; and can be trustlessly bridged across networks using the Layer Zero bridge.</p>
<p>At present, Bitcoin investments in prominent lending pools yield between 0.2&ndash;0.5%. Even the stable swap pools offering wBTC-BTC.B products only manage to deliver returns of about 2%. Struct&rsquo;s BTC.B-USDC product shatters these limitations, offering significantly higher yields.</p>
<p>The purpose of BTC.B is to empower BTC holders to explore DeFi opportunities on the Avalanche blockchain, without the need to acquire secondary tokens or rely on centralized bridges. BTC.B represents BTC coins transferred to the Avalanche blockchain in the form of ERC-20 tokens. With over 6000 BTC bridged and a fully diluted value of $180 million, BTC.B is carving a niche for itself in the crypto arena.</p>
<p>The Bitcoin ETF applications by BlackRock, WisdomTree, and Invesco &ndash; three of the world&rsquo;s leading asset managers &ndash; are not just a mere submission. It is a signal that the traditional financial realm is ready to embrace Bitcoin on a new level. Recently, the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) gave the green light to a 2X leveraged Bitcoin ETF, sparking an enthusiastic wave of speculation and anticipation for approval of a spot Bitcoin ETF.</p>
<h2>Delta hedging</h2>
<p>Amid the highly volatile crypto industry, Struct Finance&rsquo;s Interest Rate Products allow anyone to split and repackage the risk of any yield-bearing DeFi assets in different parts to fit their risk profile through an innovative process called &ldquo;tranching.&rdquo; Every Interest Rate Product is a single vault split into two portions, or tranches that have different return configurations:</p>
<ol>
<li>A Fixed-return Tranche for conservative investors looking for consistent returns</li>
<li>A Variable-return Tranche for investors with a higher risk appetite seeking superior returns</li>
</ol>
<p>The yield from the underlying asset flows into the fixed tranche first to ensure predictable returns. The remainder is then allocated to the variable tranche, which gets enhanced exposure to the underlying yield-bearing asset. Compared to the fixed tranche, the variable tranche might accrue more yield, less yield, or no yield.</p>
<p>As part of its BTC.B-USDC Vaults, Struct Finance has implemented a unique approach to managing investment risk: delta hedging. While the fixed tranche takes center stage with its high yield, the variable side of the product offers an additional layer of intriguing complexity and potential.</p>
<p>Upon deployment of funds into the vault, the BTC.B in the fixed tranche gets converted into GMX&rsquo;s GLP token, setting up a position that&rsquo;s short Bitcoin against GLP and contributing a negative delta. In contrast, the USDC on the variable side is converted into GLP, which inherently carries a positive delta.</p>
<p>This innovative delta-hedged product design achieves a fine balance between the positive and negative delta forces. It results in a robust strategy that allows investors to confidently navigate the crypto market&rsquo;s inherent volatility.</p>
<p>This artful interplay of the fixed and variable sides within the vaults opens the doors for investors to tap into the potential of Bitcoin investments like never before. By catering to a diverse range of risk appetites, Struct Finance ensures that both retail and institutional investors can tailor their strategies to maximize their returns, regardless of market conditions.</p>
<h3>About Struct Finance</h3>
<p>Struct Finance is at the forefront of the DeFi revolution, with a vision to transform the design and utility of financial products. It empowers users to design their own financial instruments, harnessing the power of tokenized, yield-bearing positions to unlock a world of diverse investment opportunities. Moreover, its cutting-edge financial products adopt a tranche-based system, smartly distributing yield between different investor classes. This balanced approach guarantees a steady yield for risk-averse investors while also offering the prospect of heightened returns to the more adventurous. Initially available on Avalanche, Struct Finance plans to go multichain in the near future.</p>
<p><strong>For more information, visit</strong>:</p>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://www.struct.fi/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Website</a></li>
<li><a href="https://twitter.com/structfinance" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Twitter</a></li>
<li><a href="https://discord.gg/kngan3PD" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Discord</a></li>
<li><a href="https://t.me/struct_finance_announcements" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Telegram</a></li>
</ul>
<p class="ql-align-center"><strong>Disclaimer: This release is for informational purposes only and should not be construed as financial promotion.</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Contact</strong></p>
<p>Miguel Depaz<br>
media@struct.fi</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/struct-finance-transforms-defi-landscape-on-avalanche-with-the-launch-of-tranche-based-btc-b-usdc-vaults/">Struct Finance Transforms DeFi Landscape on Avalanche With the Launch of Tranche-based BTC.B-USDC Vaults</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/struct-finance-transforms-defi-landscape-on-avalanche-with-the-launch-of-tranche-based-btc-b-usdc-vaults/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Helium price spikes as Bitcoin and Ethereum hover at key levels</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/helium-price-spikes-as-bitcoin-and-ethereum-hover-at-key-levels/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/helium-price-spikes-as-bitcoin-and-ethereum-hover-at-key-levels/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 15:44:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/helium-price-spikes-as-bitcoin-and-ethereum-hover-at-key-levels/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Helium rose double digits as did 1inch and NEM after US inflation data&#160; Bitcoin price on the other hand touched $31k on Coinbase and Ethereum hovered near $1.9k. Consumer prices rose 0.2% month-over-month and 3% year-over-year in June. Bitcoin moved slightly higher on Wednesday after stock markets reacted positively to the latest US inflation data. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/helium-price-spikes-as-bitcoin-and-ethereum-hover-at-key-levels/">Helium price spikes as Bitcoin and Ethereum hover at key levels</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Helium rose double digits as did 1inch and NEM after US inflation data&nbsp;</li>
<li dir="ltr">Bitcoin price on the other hand touched $31k on Coinbase and Ethereum hovered near $1.9k.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Consumer prices rose 0.2% month-over-month and 3% year-over-year in June.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> moved slightly higher on Wednesday after stock markets reacted positively to the latest US inflation data. However, the flagship cryptocurrency continued to hover near a crucial level as bulls looked to retest year-to-date highs.</p>
<p dir="ltr">BTC was changing hands near $30,800 at 11 am ET, having touched intraday highs of $31k on Coinbase</p>
<p dir="ltr">Elsewhere in the crypto market, the second largest cryptocurrency by market cap Ethereum was trading towards $1,900 as the total market cap rose 1.5% to above $1.24 trillion. The rest of the top 10 coins were also green at the time of writing.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Litecoin, which had plunged 10% in the past week by early morning, had recouped some of the losses and was 5% down in that timeframe.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The biggest gainers in the past 24 hours among the top 200 by market cap were 1inch, NEM and <a href="https://coinjournal.net/helium/">Helium</a>. All three had seen double digit upsides with HNT trading to highs of $1.48.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitcoin, altcoins move higher on CPI data release</h2>
<p dir="ltr">US <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/stocks/">stocks</a> opened higher on Wednesday too as the US consumer price index (CPI) data for June showed inflation had cooled year-over-year during the past month. Prices rose 0.2% month-over-month and 3% YoY in June, the latter a deceleration from the 4% recorded in May.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to data released by the US Bureau of Labor Statistics, CPI was at its slowest in June, with the last time it was at this pace being March 2021.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Commenting on the CPI release, Charlie Bilello, Chief Market Strategist at Creative Planning Investor<a href="https://twitter.com/charliebilello/status/1679113174484746247">&nbsp;<u>tweeted</u></a>:</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>US CPI has moved down from a peak of 9.1% last June to 3.0% today. What&rsquo;s driving that decline? Lower rates of inflation in fuel oil, gasoline, gas utilities, used cars, medical care, apparel, new cars, food at home, electricity and transportation. Shelter is the only major component that has a higher inflation rate than a year ago and it is a wildly lagging indicator (actual housing inflation is much lower w/ home prices/rents down YoY)</em>.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Federal Reserve paused its interest rate hike cycle last month, although it noted it was likely to go for a 0.25% hike on another two occasions before the end of 2023. How markets react to upcoming central bank moves will be key to both equities and crypto.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Jim Bianco of Bianco Research LLC notes markets still expects a 25 bps rate hike on July 26.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">1/6</p>
<p>Despite the better-than-expected CPI report today, the probability of a July 26 rate of 25 basis points to 5.25% to 5.50% barely moved. </p>
<p>The market is strongly expecting a hike in two weeks. <a href="https://t.co/Kl2N5CEdPN">pic.twitter.com/Kl2N5CEdPN</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Jim Bianco (@biancoresearch) <a href="https://twitter.com/biancoresearch/status/1679150658656804870?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 12, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/helium-price-spikes-as-bitcoin-and-ethereum-hover-at-key-levels/">Helium price spikes as Bitcoin and Ethereum hover at key levels</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/helium-price-spikes-as-bitcoin-and-ethereum-hover-at-key-levels/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
