<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 14:08:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>UK Fintech Powerhouse Wise Accused by Smaller Rival of Questionable Competition Practices</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-fintech-wise-competition-practices/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-fintech-wise-competition-practices/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 14:08:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FinTech News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[atlantic money]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wise]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=234239</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-fintech-wise-competition-practices/">UK Fintech Powerhouse Wise Accused by Smaller Rival of Questionable Competition Practices</a></p>
<p>Atlantic Money recently accused its more illustrious British rival Wise of undermining competition in the money transfer space.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-fintech-wise-competition-practices/">UK Fintech Powerhouse Wise Accused by Smaller Rival of Questionable Competition Practices</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-fintech-wise-competition-practices/">UK Fintech Powerhouse Wise Accused by Smaller Rival of Questionable Competition Practices</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/transferwise/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Wise Plc</a> (LON: WISE) has <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/01/27/6point6-billion-worth-fintech-wise-accused-by-rival-of-harming-competition.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">come under fire </a>for allegedly stifling competition by delisting a rival startup in the money transfer market. On Friday, Atlantic Money, a smaller foreign exchange service, accused Wise of undermining its status in the international money transfer business. According to Atlantic Money, the $6.6 billion UK fintech firm unfairly delisted it from the price comparison section of Wise’s website. Atlantic Money also alleged that Wise refused to include the company on the Exiap foreign exchange fee comparison site it also owns.</p>
<p>Atlantic Money currently offers a flat £3 charge on all currency conversions amounting to £1 million. Furthermore, the London-headquartered firm’s costs are lower than Wise’s for transfers of £1,000 or more.</p>
<h2>Atlantic Money Dispute with Wise iver Unfair Competition Practices</h2>
<p>In a letter to the UK Competition and Markets Authority (CMA), Atlantic Money aired its grievances against Wise, saying:</p>
<p>“Wise is effectively acting as a gatekeeper to the market and creating a substantial barrier to entry for cheaper and more innovative providers to establish themselves. This conduct is harmful to competition across the UK and EU and, we would submit, ultimately results in higher fees for end consumers.”</p>
<p>Atlantic Money further explained that it was initially listed by Wise on its website on October 14th, 2022. However, the fintech giant later delisted it on January 20th this year, claiming that it was no longer deemed it a “legitimate competitor.”</p>
<h2>Wise Retorts</h2>
<p>A Wise spokesperson responded to Atlantic Money’s claims, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>“We decided to remove Atlantic Money for the time being for a number of operational reasons, including queries received from customers about their business. We take any complaints very seriously. We’re really proud to have the comparison tool as part of our website, and we’re not afraid to list cheaper competitors. We’ve done that for years and still do.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Wise also said that Atlantic Money was not the first provider  ousted from its price comparison lists. According to the leading fintech and money transfer facilitator, the removal process is part of regular reviews. Wise further suggested that it keeps the list “useful for our customers” by pruning it. The company, formerly known as TransferWise, has long promoted itself as a pioneer of consumer rights. This agenda also includes agitating for more transparent bank charges to move money across borders.</p>
<p>Wise said it has not received any official correspondence from the CMA regarding Atlantic Money’s complaints. A spokesperson for the UK competition watchdog suggested that it is conducting a formal investigation. However, the CMA spokesperson did not offer any specifics about the exact probe or investigation.</p>
<h2>Wise</h2>
<p>Wise’s shares were trading at £5.14 during the early morning London session. The company’s stock, which debuted on the London Stock Exchange in 2021, was 2% below the Thursday market close.</p>
<p>Wise currently has a market capitalization of £5.3 billion, or $6.6 billion.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/arizona-bill-bitcoin-legal-tender/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-fintech-wise-competition-practices/">UK Fintech Powerhouse Wise Accused by Smaller Rival of Questionable Competition Practices</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-fintech-wise-competition-practices/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Arizona Senator Introduces Bill to Make Bitcoin Legal Tender</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/arizona-bill-bitcoin-legal-tender/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/arizona-bill-bitcoin-legal-tender/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 13:52:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Senator Wendy Rogers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=234218</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/arizona-bill-bitcoin-legal-tender/">Arizona Senator Introduces Bill to Make Bitcoin Legal Tender</a></p>
<p>There is already a number of states that have officially recognized Bitcoin as a legal means of paying for certain goods and services.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/arizona-bill-bitcoin-legal-tender/">Arizona Senator Introduces Bill to Make Bitcoin Legal Tender</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/arizona-bill-bitcoin-legal-tender/">Arizona Senator Introduces Bill to Make Bitcoin Legal Tender</a></p>
<p>In her frantic bid to see <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> (BTC), the world’s largest digital currency become legal tender in the state of Arizona, Senator Wendy Rogers has introduced some crypto bills to the state parliament.</p>
<p>Taking to Twitter, Senator Wendy <a href="https://twitter.com/WendyRogersAZ/status/1618037820471537664" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">shared</a> the news in line with the earlier report from American multinational investment bank <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/goldman-sachs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Goldman Sachs Group Inc</a> (NYSE: GS) which states that Bitcoin ranked as the best-performing asset in 2022.</p>
<p>The lawmaker said she introduced the crypto bills as well as another bill for Photo Radar Prohibition in the state of Arizona. According to her, the bill has almost all of her Republican colleagues as co-sponsors, implying that she will only have to contend with the other members of the parliament from other parties to get the bill to scale through.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="474" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">“Breaking: <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Bitcoin</a> is the best performing asset in the world this year according to data from Goldman Sachs.”</p>
<p>Launched my <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Crypto?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Crypto</a> bills today, as well as Photo Radar Prohibition, which included nearly all my Republican senator colleagues as cosponsors <a href="https://twitter.com/JeffWeninger?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@JeffWeninger</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/JDMesnard?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@JDMesnard</a> <a href="https://t.co/ueUeFSEybo">pic.twitter.com/ueUeFSEybo</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Wendy Rogers (@WendyRogersAZ) <a href="https://twitter.com/WendyRogersAZ/status/1618037820471537664?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 25, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>There is nowhere in the United States where Bitcoin is recognized as a legal tender as many are still torn about the status of digital currencies. This discrepancy in laws has kept a lot of institutional investors away from investing directly in digital currency.</p>
<p>While there are a few companies with vested investment in Bitcoin like <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/microstrategy-incorporated/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">MicroStrategy Incorporated</a> (NASDAQ: MSTR), the majority of those who embraced the asset are doing so through Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC) or the few approved Bitcoin Futures Exchange Traded Funds (ETF) trading today.</p>
<p>Senator Wendy is looking at changing this narrative in Arizona as a passage of the Bill will set a positive and clear path for Bitcoin to be accepted as payment for debt securities, charges, and other core state requirements. Known as a long-term advocate for digital currency, the introduction of this Bill is the second attempt by Senator Wendy.</p>
<p>She made a push to make BTC a legal tender in April last year but her efforts were not successful at the time.</p>
<h2>Arizona to Trail El Salvador in Making Bitcoin Legal Tender</h2>
<p>At present, there is a number of states that have officially recognized Bitcoin as a legal means of paying for certain goods and services and these include Colorado and California. Miami Mayor, Francis Suarez is also a big proponent of Bitcoin, however, his influence is just limited to the city.</p>
<p>Should Arizona succeed in making Bitcoin a legal tender, it will be following in the footsteps of El Salvador, a country in Central America that <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/el-salvador-bitcoin-legal-tender-51k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">made Bitcoin a legal tender</a> back in September 2021. El Salvador was criticized for its adoption of Bitcoin at the time, and though the country seems to be meeting up with its debt obligations, many, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-senate-bill-bitcoin-el-salvador/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">including</a> US authorities still believe the country made a mistake with the move.</p>
<p>The chances that Arizona will also face backlash for attempting to give Bitcoin a similar legal tender status as the United States Dollar may fuel a lot of kickback even beyond the state. This second bill presentation may also face as much of an intense push as the first.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/proof-of-reserves-on-chain-off-chain/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/arizona-bill-bitcoin-legal-tender/">Arizona Senator Introduces Bill to Make Bitcoin Legal Tender</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/arizona-bill-bitcoin-legal-tender/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Does Proof of Reserves for On-Chain and Off-Chain Assets Work?</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/proof-of-reserves-on-chain-off-chain/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/proof-of-reserves-on-chain-off-chain/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 13:39:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Work It]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=234215</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/proof-of-reserves-on-chain-off-chain/">How Does Proof of Reserves for On-Chain and Off-Chain Assets Work?</a></p>
<p>Proof of Reserves is a good way for crypto exchanges to show their clients and regulatory authorities that they have enough funds to cover all their liabilities and operate transparently and honestly.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/proof-of-reserves-on-chain-off-chain/">How Does Proof of Reserves for On-Chain and Off-Chain Assets Work?</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/proof-of-reserves-on-chain-off-chain/">How Does Proof of Reserves for On-Chain and Off-Chain Assets Work?</a></p>
<p>Proof of Reserves is a mechanism to ensure that a cryptocurrency exchange or other financial institution has the assets it claims to have. It helps build trust between the exchange and its customers while providing greater transparency and accountability. <a href="http://okx.com/proof-of-reserves" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Proof of reserves</a> allows outside parties to view the exchange&#8217;s <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/crypto/blockchain-news/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">blockchain</a> addresses or other records and confirm whether the exchange holds the assets it claims to have.</p>
<p>This is made possible through a Proof of Reserves audit conducted by an independent auditor who reviews the exchange&#8217;s records, such as blockchain addresses for on-chain assets or third-party documentation for off-chain assets, to confirm that the exchange holds the correct amount of assets. The auditor then issues a report, proofing that the exchange has the assets it claims to hold.</p>
<p>Proof of Reserves audits are a growing practice among cryptocurrency exchanges and other financial institutions, as it helps to build trust with customers and increase transparency. It can take different forms depending on the type of assets held by the exchange. For example, on-chain and off-chain assets.</p>
<h2>What Is the Difference between On-chain and Off-chain Assets?</h2>
<p>The on-chain and off-chain assets differ in how they are recorded, stored, and transferred. On-chain assets are recorded on a blockchain, a public, decentralized ledger. They are transparent and easily verifiable by anyone. On-chain assets can be transferred directly between individuals without the need for an intermediary, and the transactions are permanently recorded on the blockchain. Cryptocurrencies like <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a> are great examples of on-chain assets.</p>
<p>On the other hand, off-chain assets don&#8217;t have a trail on the blockchain. Instead, they are recorded and stored in centralized systems, such as bank accounts, databases, or physical assets. Off-chain assets are typically transferred through intermediaries such as banks or other financial institutions. These assets need to be more transparent; therefore, proving that an institution holds the assets it claims to have could be challenging. Examples of off-chain assets are cash, gold, real estate, stocks, etc.</p>
<p>Overall, the main difference between on-chain and off-chain assets is that on-chain assets are recorded on a public, decentralized ledger, and off-chain assets are recorded and stored in centralized systems.</p>
<h2>Types of Proof of Reserves</h2>
<p>PoR covers two types: on-chain and off-chain.</p>
<p>On-chain PoR involves publishing a public record of the assets held by the exchange or institution on a blockchain. This can be done by publishing a list of the addresses of the assets held in cold storage or creating a special transaction on the blockchain that proves the assets exist. For example, a Bitcoin exchange can create a transaction on the blockchain that sends a small amount of BTC to an address that the exchange controls, thus proving that the exchange holds that specific amount of BTC.</p>
<p>Off-chain PoR, on the other hand, is a method that uses a third-party auditor to verify the assets held by an exchange or institution. The auditor will typically perform a physical inspection of the assets and perform various tests to ensure that they are authentic and that the exchange or institution can access them.</p>
<h2>How Often Are Proof of Reserves Updated?</h2>
<p>The frequency of Proof of Reserves updates can vary depending on the project or organization. Some projects may update their Proof of Reserves daily, while others may update them weekly or <a href="https://www.okx.com/learn/january-proof-of-reserves-report?channelid=ACEAP6502255" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">monthly</a>. It&#8217;s recommended to check the project&#8217;s website or whitepaper for more information on the specific frequency of their reserve updates.</p>
<h2>Conclusion</h2>
<p>Both methods have advantages and disadvantages, and the choice of which method depends on the specific requirements of the exchange or institution.</p>
<p>On-chain PoR increases transparency by bringing independent auditors and reduces the risk of fraud through public records. At the same time, off-chain PoR builds trust by providing documentation from a reputable third-party auditor.</p>
<p>However, some disadvantages of on-chain PoR include the required time to perform the audit and the costs of hiring independent auditors. The same applies to off-chain PoR, except that there is more room for lack of transparency. This is because off-chain assets are not recorded on a public, decentralized ledger, making it difficult for customers to verify the assets by relying on auditors&#8217; reports or other documentation.</p>
<p>Overall, Proof of Reserves is a good way for crypto exchanges to show their clients and regulatory authorities that they have enough funds to cover all their liabilities and operate transparently and honestly.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fidelity-ant-group-valuation/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/proof-of-reserves-on-chain-off-chain/">How Does Proof of Reserves for On-Chain and Off-Chain Assets Work?</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/proof-of-reserves-on-chain-off-chain/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fidelity Investments Trims Ant Group’s Valuation by Another 9%</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fidelity-ant-group-valuation/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fidelity-ant-group-valuation/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 13:35:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ant]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ant group]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fidelity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fidelity investments]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=234221</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fidelity-ant-group-valuation/">Fidelity Investments Trims Ant Group’s Valuation by Another 9%</a></p>
<p>Apart from Fidelity, another investment management company Blackrock also lowered its estimates for Ant in 2022.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fidelity-ant-group-valuation/">Fidelity Investments Trims Ant Group’s Valuation by Another 9%</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fidelity-ant-group-valuation/">Fidelity Investments Trims Ant Group’s Valuation by Another 9%</a></p>
<p>Financial services corporation Fidelity Investments has again cut Ant Group Co.’s valuation. According to <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-01-27/fidelity-cuts-ant-group-valuation-by-another-9-to-64-billion" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Bloomberg</a> calculations based on filings, Fidelity trimmed Ant Group’s valuation by 9% from the end of May to approximately $63.8 billion as of the end of November. This is down from $235 billion just before regulators halted Ant’s $37 billion initial public offering (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-initial-public-offering-ipo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">IPO</a>) in November 2020. Before now, Fidelity Investments reduced its estimate for Ant from $78 billion in June 2021 to $70 billion in May 2022. We are now in 2023, and filings show that the financial services provider had dropped its estimates once more to about $63.8 billion in November 2022.</p>
<p>Apart from Fidelity, another investment management company Blackrock (NYSE: BLK) also lowered its estimates for Ant in 2022. The asset manager dropped its estimate from $174 billion as of March to $151 billion. T.Rowe Price Group Inc also cut the value from $189 billion to $112 billion. Following the new valuation estimates last year, Bloomberg revealed Ant’s valuation range to be between $70 billion and $151 billion.</p>
<p>Over time, the Ant Group has been managing its operations to comply with the government’s demands. At the same time, the company is looking forward to receiving regulatory approval to apply for a license as a financial holdings company. This license is bound to support its continuity as a fintech service provider. Amid the approval wait, the government has permitted the company’s consumer lending unit to increase capital. This allows the consumer-finance arm to generate the equivalent of $1.5 billion in new capital. Ant Group owner Jack Ma also spoke about conceding the company’s control.</p>
<p>On the other hand, Ant has been facing setbacks in its operations. The company is struggling with regulatory crackdowns and managing to stay afloat in the deteriorating Chinese economy. Its affiliate company, Alibaba Group Holding Ltd, emphasized Ma’s vision of economic interest. Alibaba revealed that the Ant Group owner plans to reduce and limit his direct and indirect economic interest in Ant Group “over time.” The businessman intends to lower the economic interest to not more than 8.8%. Part of his plans is to own about 6.2% of voting rights after conceding control.</p>
<p>Currently, Ant Group has <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ant-group-ipo-jack-ma-control/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">no plans for a public offering</a>. The company’s spokesperson noted:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Ant Group has been focusing on its business rectification and optimization, and does not have a plan for an IPO.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Read other <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/business/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">business news</a> on Coinspeaker.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bids-celsius-binance-galaxy-digital/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fidelity-ant-group-valuation/">Fidelity Investments Trims Ant Group’s Valuation by Another 9%</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fidelity-ant-group-valuation/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Leaked Bids on Celsius Network’s Assets by Binance, Galaxy Digital</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bids-celsius-binance-galaxy-digital/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bids-celsius-binance-galaxy-digital/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sanaa Sharma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 13:30:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bank to the future]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[celcius network]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[galaxy digital]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sam bankman-fried]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sbf]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=234180</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bids-celsius-binance-galaxy-digital/">Leaked Bids on Celsius Network&#8217;s Assets by Binance, Galaxy Digital</a></p>
<p>The blog explained that Binance offered a bid of $15 million for the assets, noting that $12 million would be deposited to Celsius estate and $3 million to be disbursed to relocated customers on a pro-rata basis.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bids-celsius-binance-galaxy-digital/">Leaked Bids on Celsius Network&#8217;s Assets by Binance, Galaxy Digital</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bids-celsius-binance-galaxy-digital/">Leaked Bids on Celsius Network&#8217;s Assets by Binance, Galaxy Digital</a></p>
<p>According to leaked information about bids on Celsius Network&#8217;s crypto assets, at least five companies including <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a>, Bank To The Future and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/galaxy-digital/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Galaxy Digital</a> have shown interest and placed offers.</p>
<p>Tiffany Fong is a crypto blogger who is responsible for making Celsius&#8217;s crypto bidding process public. She is an avert follower of Celsius news and rose in popularity because of several interviews with <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/sam-bankman-fried/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Sam Bankman-Fried</a> after <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a>&#8216;s downfall. According to Fong, she has documents dated December 20 that illustrate the bids on Celsius Network&#8217;s crypto assets.</p>
<p>In a post on Substack, Fong described that she originally withheld from disclosing the information of bids to prevent demolishing the bidding procedure but was suggested to do so following the latest comment from an advocate representing Celsius.</p>
<p>Bidders exposed by Fong comprise crypto exchange Binance, online investment company Bank To The Future, virtual asset investment manager Galaxy Digital, crypto trading firm Cumberland DRW and digital asset investment company NovaWulf.</p>
<p>According to Fong, the offers, which were submitted on November 2022 have been deserted majorly.</p>
<p>The blog <a href="https://tiffanyfong.substack.com/p/bids-on-celsius-networks-crypto-assets-09a" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">explained</a> that Binance offered a bid of $15 million for the assets, noting that $12 million would be deposited to Celsius estate and $3 million to be disbursed to relocated customers on a pro-rata basis. In the claimed Summary Term Sheet from Binance, it was explained that the company plans to obtain and shift all liquid and a few illiquid cryptos at the right market value to Binance&#8217;s exchange.</p>
<p>In a recent tweet on January 26, Chief Executive Officer of Bank To The Future Simon Dixon affirmed that the contents of the leaked bids about his company were very precise.</p>
<p>Fong also acknowledged in the blog post that she possesses knowledge of only five of these bids on Celsius&#8217;s crypto assets. She also said that Novawulf&#8217;s bid was especially intriguing since it had an uncanny similarity to Celsius&#8217;s Network&#8217;s recently-suggested revamping plans. Fong also claimed to have had several interactions with Celsius Network employees, and to her amazement, they were not even made aware of the bids.</p>
<p>Fong claimed that the creditors and most of the employees were unaware of the bids on crypto assets that investors submitted to the platform. The influencer claims to be uncertain about the future of the firm now that it is receiving bids but thinks that the creditors deserve more transparency.</p>
<p>Binance has refused to give a statement on the same.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/british-finance-minister-tax-hikes/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bids-celsius-binance-galaxy-digital/">Leaked Bids on Celsius Network&#8217;s Assets by Binance, Galaxy Digital</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bids-celsius-binance-galaxy-digital/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>British Finance Minister Calls on Tech Giants to Stoke Growth in Nation amid Reformative Tax Hikes</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/british-finance-minister-tax-hikes/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/british-finance-minister-tax-hikes/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 13:26:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Currencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Amazon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[google]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Meta]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=234202</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/british-finance-minister-tax-hikes/">British Finance Minister Calls on Tech Giants to Stoke Growth in Nation amid Reformative Tax Hikes</a></p>
<p>Finance Minister Jeremy Hunt has implored companies to play a crucial role in British economic growth as the country angles for tax hikes.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/british-finance-minister-tax-hikes/">British Finance Minister Calls on Tech Giants to Stoke Growth in Nation amid Reformative Tax Hikes</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/british-finance-minister-tax-hikes/">British Finance Minister Calls on Tech Giants to Stoke Growth in Nation amid Reformative Tax Hikes</a></p>
<p>British Finance Minister Jeremy Hunt recently indicated that he would push ahead with the country&#8217;s tax hikes. The Chancellor of the Exchequer also pledged post-Brexit reforms for growth in the United Kingdom.</p>
<p>On Friday, Hunt said in a speech to tech giants, &#8220;The best tax cut right now is a cut in inflation.&#8221; The British Finance Minister also intimated companies like <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/amazon/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Amazon</a> (NASDAQ: AMZN), <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/alphabet-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Google</a> (NASDAQ: GOOGL), and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/meta/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Meta</a> (NASDAQ: META) on dispelling UK economic gloom. According to Hunt, there is a need to develop Brexit in such a way that it spurs economic growth in the country.</p>
<p>Amid his stated agenda regarding British tax hikes, Hunt <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/01/27/british-finance-minister-sticks-to-tax-hiking-plans-pledges-post-brexit-reforms.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">mentioned</a> that optimism in the European nation has been low recently. As a result of this optimistic &#8220;short supply,&#8221; the UK politician implored companies to help make the nation &#8220;the world&#8217;s next Silicon Valley.&#8221; According to Hunt, these companies were essential for Britain&#8217;s economic outlook and instrumental to its growth plans. However, the high-ranking British Cabinet member also suggested a mutually beneficial relationship between Britain and the corporations. In his Friday address, Hunt played up the market potential of the UK, saying, &#8220;Britain is vital for your future too.&#8221;</p>
<h2>Finance Minister Explains Tax Hikes Necessary to Pull British Economy Out of Inertia</h2>
<p>While stressing the importance of making the UK an appealing business hotspot, Hunt underscored the need for a favorable tax structure. According to the Chancellor of the Exchequer, the country needs to attain &#8220;nothing less than the most competitive tax regime of any major country.&#8221; However, the British senior government official intends to angle for said tax regime amid the restoration of the planned rise in corporation tax from 19% to 25%. Hunt&#8217;s short-tenured predecessor Kwasi Kwarteng previously scrapped the corporation tax increment plans while in office.</p>
<p>Kwarteng was a Cabinet member of the short-lived Liz Truss government between September and October last year. While serving as Finance Minister between September 6th and October 14th, 2022, many of his policies proved unpopular with the British parliament and populace. These policies, including Kwarteng&#8217;s &#8220;mini-budget&#8217;s&#8221; economic policies and tax cuts, ultimately resulted in his dismissal from office. Following Kwarteng&#8217;s ousting, Truss appointed Hunt, who retained his role as Chancellor under Rishi Sunak following her resignation.</p>
<h2>Pound Downturn</h2>
<p>After Hunt&#8217;s&#8217; reform&#8217; speech, the British pound sank 0.25% to $1.237 against the US dollar. The sterling had initially recouped some of its losses from when Hunt&#8217;s speech began but ultimately regressed from Thursday&#8217;s six-week high.</p>
<p>In September, the pound sank to its <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/british-pound-lowest-us-dollar-1985/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">lowest level against the dollar in 37 years</a> amid several macroeconomic headwinds. These constraints included surging inflation, the highest among all G-7 nations, looming recession, and tax cuts.</p>
<p>At the time, the British currency slumped to a low of $1.135 against the US greenback before rebounding slightly to $1.1378. A few days later, the pound would <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/british-pound-dollar-tax/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">further slide</a> to $1.1029 per dollar and an <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/pound-all-time-low-dollar-mini-budget/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">all-time low</a> of $1.03 to a dollar.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fbi-hive-ransomware-130m/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/british-finance-minister-tax-hikes/">British Finance Minister Calls on Tech Giants to Stoke Growth in Nation amid Reformative Tax Hikes</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/british-finance-minister-tax-hikes/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>FBI Infiltrates Hive Network Thwarting $130M in Crypto Ransomware</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fbi-hive-ransomware-130m/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fbi-hive-ransomware-130m/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 13:22:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cybersecurity News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fbi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hive network]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=234195</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fbi-hive-ransomware-130m/">FBI Infiltrates Hive Network Thwarting $130M in Crypto Ransomware</a></p>
<p>The FBI in their report stated that they have helped victims by offering them decryption keys and thwarted ransom demands of $130 million in crypto. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fbi-hive-ransomware-130m/">FBI Infiltrates Hive Network Thwarting $130M in Crypto Ransomware</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fbi-hive-ransomware-130m/">FBI Infiltrates Hive Network Thwarting $130M in Crypto Ransomware</a></p>
<p>On Thursday, January 26, the US Justice Department disclosed the results of its months-long joint operation with the Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI) that entirely disrupted the activities of the Hive ransomware group.</p>
<h2>Hive Ransomware Group</h2>
<p>The investigation noted that the Hive ransomware group had targeted more than 1500 victims across 80 countries including hospitals, financial firms, school districts, and critical infrastructure.</p>
<p>Over the last eight months, the FBI has been infiltrating Hive&#8217;s computer networks, capturing the descriptions keys, and offering them to victims worldwide. Besides, they also help in preventing victims from paying a sum of $130 million in ransom demand.</p>
<p>The report notes that since July 2022, the FBI has provided a total of 300 decryption keys to previous Hive victims. Furthermore, the FBI has been coordinating with German law enforcement and the Netherlands National High Tech Crime Unit, thereby distorting Hive&#8217;s ability to attack and extort victims. Speaking on the development, US Attorney General Merrick B. Garland <a href="https://www.justice.gov/opa/pr/us-department-justice-disrupts-hive-ransomware-variant" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Last night, the Justice Department dismantled an international ransomware network responsible for extorting and attempting to extort hundreds of millions of dollars from victims in the United States and around the world. We will continue to work both to prevent these attacks and to provide support to victims who have been targeted. And together with our international partners, we will continue to disrupt the criminal networks that deploy these attacks.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>The Rise of Crypto Ransomware</h2>
<p>Amid the strong growth of the crypto market, the total number of ransomware attacks in the crypto space has also been on the rise. Ransomware basically involves malicious software that can lock a computer while demanding ransom in order to restore access.</p>
<p>Much recently, attackers have been demanding ransom largely in crypto. Any devices connected to the internet could be potentially a victim of ransom. However, phishing attacks are usually the prime attack vector.</p>
<p>As per the FBI, Hive targets victims by stealing their sensitive data such as documents, emails, pictures, and videos. Later, they encrypt these files and demand ransom in <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> from the victims in return for the decryption key required to restore the files. Besides, Hive would also extort additional in the promise of not publishing the stolen data on the dark web. If the victim doesn&#8217;t pay, Hive publishes the data on the dark web.</p>
<p>“Cybercrime is a constantly evolving threat,” Garland said. “But as I have said before, the Justice Department will spare no resource to identify and bring to justice, anyone, anywhere, who targets the United States with a ransomware attack.”</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/web3-spatial-labs-10m-funding/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fbi-hive-ransomware-130m/">FBI Infiltrates Hive Network Thwarting $130M in Crypto Ransomware</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fbi-hive-ransomware-130m/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Web3 Hardware Startup Spatial Labs Raises $10M in Funding Backed by Jay-Z</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/web3-spatial-labs-10m-funding/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/web3-spatial-labs-10m-funding/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 13:17:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investors News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jay Z]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[matic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[polygon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[spatial labs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=234170</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/web3-spatial-labs-10m-funding/">Web3 Hardware Startup Spatial Labs Raises $10M in Funding Backed by Jay-Z</a></p>
<p>Spatial Labs recently secured substantial funding to provide cutting-edge hardware services for the Web3 space. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/web3-spatial-labs-10m-funding/">Web3 Hardware Startup Spatial Labs Raises $10M in Funding Backed by Jay-Z</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/web3-spatial-labs-10m-funding/">Web3 Hardware Startup Spatial Labs Raises $10M in Funding Backed by Jay-Z</a></p>
<p>Web3 hardware startup Spatial Labs has <a href="https://decrypt.co/120006/backed-by-jay-z-web3-hardware-startup-spatial-labs-raises-10-million" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">raised $10 million</a> in funding led by Blockchain Capital. In addition, Spatial Labs also secured the backing of Jay-Z-owned venture capital firm Marcy Venture Partners. Adding the crypto hardware startup’s initial pre-seed fundraising of $4 million brings Spatial Labs’ total funding to $14 million.</p>
<p>Amid the Spatial Labs funding development, the platform’s founder, Iddris Sandu, provided insight into the company’s core agenda. In addition to sharing his vision, Sandu also opened up on his collaborative relationship with his renowned celebrity investor Jay-Z.</p>
<p>Sandu launched Spatial Labs back in 2019 in a bid to leverage the emerging metaverse. However, unlike most rising software and application-driven metaverse-centric companies, Spatial Labs focuses on the hardware that facilitates the concept. For instance, the company developed a 13-millimeter microchip, dubbed the LNQ One Chip, which is sewn or embedded into physical fashion items. Furthermore, each LNQ One Chip is also scannable with a smartphone using near-field communication (NFC) technology. Scans reveal the item’s details and create a digital replica for metaverse interaction.</p>
<p>Each physical chip also ties to a non-fungible token (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NFT</a>) on <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/matic-network/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Polygon</a>, at which point brands have unlimited, customizable options.</p>
<p>Speaking on the chip functionality and offerings, Sandu explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>“We think our approach is going to create much more of an equitable metaverse. If you look at economies of scale, people don’t have the luxury of buying things twice over and over again.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>Spatial Labs Funding Would Facilitate Company’s Chip Technology</h2>
<p>In addition to harboring many ideas for his LNQ chip technology, Sandu also spoke of the technology’s potential. According to the 25-year-old Ghanaian-American entrepreneur, LNQ can provide authentication services for luxury brands that already have metaverse plans. These luxury brands include Balmain, Gucci, and Prada.</p>
<p>Sandu explained these brands could embed loyalty programs directly into their products without needing customer sign-up services. According to the Spatial Labs founder, “…you can now think about your products unlocking tickets, specific interviews, podcasts, stuff like that. And so it’s for a lot of brands that want to find potential use cases for Web3 and the metaverse.”</p>
<p>Sandu cited higher gas fees as the main reason he chose the Polygon blockchain for his hardware over <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a>. According to him, the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a> mainnet is not “really built for economies of scale.” Furthermore, the Spatial Labs founder also added that Polygon offers fees much closer to <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/visa-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Visa</a> or <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/mastercard/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Mastercard</a> sales.</p>
<p>Sandu’s hardware allows Spatial Labs to build without any bottlenecks that typically accompany app stores. For example, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/apple-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Apple’s</a> (NASDAQ: APPL) app store enforces strict developer rules regarding NFTs and Web3 elements. In Sandu’s own words, the chip technology is independent of any app store approval and “works out of the box.” He also explained that the technology does not require any app installation to access its customizable metadata.</p>
<h2>Jay-Z</h2>
<p>Sandu described his working relationship with billionaire rapper mogul Jay-Z as perfectly harmonious. As one of the few founders of color of a hardware-focused company, the Spatial Labs pioneer cited Jay-Z among his inspirations. Referring to the Brooklyn native as a “big brother,” Sandu also calls Jay-Z a good friend and investor. According to Sandu, he and Jay bounce ideas off each other and share the same impactful vision.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/stripe-public-offering-goldman-jpmorgan/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/web3-spatial-labs-10m-funding/">Web3 Hardware Startup Spatial Labs Raises $10M in Funding Backed by Jay-Z</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/web3-spatial-labs-10m-funding/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stripe Considers Public Offering, Taps Goldman Sachs &amp; JPMorgan for Advice</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/stripe-public-offering-goldman-jpmorgan/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/stripe-public-offering-goldman-jpmorgan/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 13:08:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[IPO News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[goldman]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[goldman sachs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jpmorgan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jpmorgan chase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[shopify]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stripe]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=234181</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/stripe-public-offering-goldman-jpmorgan/">Stripe Considers Public Offering, Taps Goldman Sachs &#038; JPMorgan for Advice</a></p>
<p>Leading fintech Stripe is considering a public offering within the next year amid the broader tech selloff. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/stripe-public-offering-goldman-jpmorgan/">Stripe Considers Public Offering, Taps Goldman Sachs &#038; JPMorgan for Advice</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/stripe-public-offering-goldman-jpmorgan/">Stripe Considers Public Offering, Taps Goldman Sachs &#038; JPMorgan for Advice</a></p>
<p>Financial services and software as a service company <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/stripe/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Stripe Inc</a> is <a href="https://www.wsj.com/amp/articles/stripe-sets-one-year-timetable-to-decide-on-going-public-11674749304?mod=Searchresults_pos1&amp;page=1" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reportedly</a> mulling a public offering in the next 12 months. Reportedly, the popular internet payment processor has enlisted the services of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/goldman-sachs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Goldman Sachs</a> (NYSE: GS) and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/jpmorgan-chase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">JPMorgan Chase</a> (NYSE: JPM) for advice. Stripe wants the banking giants to advise on the direct listing or private-market transactions involving employees’ shares within the next year. This development also implies that the company’s executives look to take the company public or allow employees to sell shares in private transactions.</p>
<p>A potential Stripe public offering could be one of the most significant public-market debuts in recent memory. This prospect is because Stripe already ranks among Silicon Valley’s most valuable startups. Furthermore, the company’s management is unlikely to opt for a traditional initial public offering (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-initial-public-offering-ipo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">IPO</a>) because it does not need to raise extra capital. Instead, Stripe will likely pursue a direct listing where it places existing shares on a public bourse for the market to decide the price. This strategy also lends credence to the company’s belief in itself as an established internet payment facilitator throughout Silicon Valley.</p>
<h2>Potential Stripe Public Offering Comes 14 Years After Company’s Inception</h2>
<p>Established in 2009 by Irish entrepreneurs Patrick and John Collison, Stripe offers payment processing solutions to several major internet companies. These include <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/shopify/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Shopify Inc</a> (NYSE: SHOP) and Instacart Inc.</p>
<p>In 2021, Stripe <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/fintech-stripe-scores-blockbuster-95-billion-valuation-11615763209?mod=article_inline" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">raised</a> $600 million at a $95 billion valuation, which made it one of the world’s most valuable startups. At the time of the fundraiser, the company’s investors included Ireland’s National Treasury Management Agency and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/fidelity-investments/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Fidelity Investments</a>. In addition, Stripe also saw investment from leading insurers Allianz and AXA.</p>
<p>Although at the forefront of 2010s-era startups that grew into colossal tech platforms, Stripe long preferred to remain private. Furthermore, the Irish-American dual-headquartered company also disclosed few exterior details about its performance. Over the years, this trend created high desirability among investors who angled to buy into Stripe but did not have a chance.</p>
<p>Soaring inflation, rising interest rates, and recession fears have sparked a broader selloff of tech stocks in the past year. The stocks of newly public companies in the tech space are affected mainly by this unsavory trend. Furthermore, several startups that previously harbored plans to go public have been forced to shelve such an agenda.</p>
<h2>Stripe Relationship with Digital Currencies</h2>
<p>Despite its reputation as an internet payment processor, Stripe has displayed ambivalence toward digital assets for at least eight years. In 2015, the Dublin and South San Francisco-based company announced it would accept Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a>). At the time, this development meant that Stripe users could send and receive the leading token as they would fiat currencies. However, the company halted its BTC services three years later in 2018, with its founders giving a perceived practical reason. According to the Collison brothers, Bitcoin is better applicable as an asset or store of value rather than a medium of exchange.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/intel-weak-2022-q4-performance/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/stripe-public-offering-goldman-jpmorgan/">Stripe Considers Public Offering, Taps Goldman Sachs &#038; JPMorgan for Advice</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/stripe-public-offering-goldman-jpmorgan/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>INTC Stock Falls as Intel Reveals Weak 2022 Q4 Performance and More Losses for Current Quarter</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/intel-weak-2022-q4-performance/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/intel-weak-2022-q4-performance/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 13:01:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wall Street]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[intc stock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[intel]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[intel stock]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=234189</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/intel-weak-2022-q4-performance/">INTC Stock Falls as Intel Reveals Weak 2022 Q4 Performance and More Losses for Current Quarter</a></p>
<p>Intel CEO said the company will deal with "persistent economic headwinds" for at least the first half of the year.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/intel-weak-2022-q4-performance/">INTC Stock Falls as Intel Reveals Weak 2022 Q4 Performance and More Losses for Current Quarter</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/intel-weak-2022-q4-performance/">INTC Stock Falls as Intel Reveals Weak 2022 Q4 Performance and More Losses for Current Quarter</a></p>
<p>Semiconductor Corporation <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/intel/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Intel</a> (NASDAQ: INTC) saw its shares drop 9% during after-hours trading on Thursday due to weak <a href="https://d1io3yog0oux5.cloudfront.net/_8020e84ca449012613cb7a51a8b3788c/intel/db/887/8894/earnings_presentation/Q4%272022+Earnings+Deck_Final.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">2022 Q4 results</a>. In addition to falling short of analysts&#8217; expectations last quarter, the company also predicted a poorer performance for the current quarter. While analysts expected earnings to come in at 20 cents per share, the semiconductor company reported 10 cents per share. In addition, the quarterly revenue was $14.04 billion, lower than the projected $14.45 billion. This represents a 32% fall compared to the same quarter in 2021.</p>
<h2>Intel in 2022 Q4</h2>
<p>Notably, 2022 Q4 is the fourth consecutive quarter Intel will see sales decline. The company still struggles with the sales drop fueled by the global health pandemic. In addition to the losses, the technology company recorded a $664 million net loss. Meanwhile, it had a profit of $4.62 billion in the year-ago quarter.</p>
<p>During the fourth quarter, $6.63 billion of the revenue came from Intel&#8217;s Client Computing Group, which includes PC chips. The revenue contribution was down 36% and lower than the $7.68 billion analysts&#8217; estimation.</p>
<p>The declines are not ending for Intel in 2022 Q4 as the company now calls for an adjusted net loss of 15 cents per share in the current quarter. Also, it expects between $10.5 billion to $11.5 billion in revenue. On the other hand, analysts polled by Refinitiv&#8217;s projections were 24 cents in earnings per share and $13.93 billion in revenue.</p>
<p>Like many other companies, Intel refused to give full-year guidance. CEO Pat Gelsinger cited &#8220;the uncertainty in the current environment&#8221; for not providing the entire year forecast. This is similar to a statement by Tesla CEO Elon Musk on projections for new vehicle productions. Musk <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-earnings-revenue-q4-2022/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">said</a> the company plans to produce just 1.8 million vehicles in 2023 due to uncontrollable situations. He mentioned situations like earthquakes, tsunamis, wars, pandemics, etc. Companies are treading carefully on full-year projections as they do not know what the year holds for the economy.</p>
<p>Intel CEO said the company will deal with &#8220;persistent economic headwinds&#8221; for at least the first half of the year. IT research and consultancy company Gartner confirmed that there was a sharp drop in the PC market in Q4. According to the IT company, the decline was more significant than any other quarter since it started compiling the industry&#8217;s results in the 1990s. While Intel initially saw an addressable market of between 270 million to 295 million PCs in 2023, the company now expects the market to be at the lower end of the range.</p>
<p>Following its share loss in reaction to the 2022 Q4 results, Intel stock was down 9.64% to $27.19 at pre-market trading.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/argo-blockchain-class-action-lawsuit/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/intel-weak-2022-q4-performance/">INTC Stock Falls as Intel Reveals Weak 2022 Q4 Performance and More Losses for Current Quarter</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/intel-weak-2022-q4-performance/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>